<Game>
	<Name>Accele Brid (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Accele Brid is a mech shoot 'em up of the "tube shooter" variant released for the Super Famicom on November 26, 1993 by Tomy, exclusively in Japan. Players can choose one of three large robots, and then control it as it flies down a large pipe, shooting, kicking, and punching enemies and maneuvering around the pipe's twists and turns as the stage progresses.An unofficial English translation patch was released by Aeon Genesis on May 28th, 2002.Playable CharactersCharacterStatsNitikaHeight - 2.62 mWeight - 0.99 tMax Speed - 192.6 kmBeliwsHeight - 2.20 mWeight - 2.05 tMax Speed - 166.6 kmSilver MareHeight - 2.51 mWeight - 1.08 tMax Speed - 171.1 kmCheat: Misc. CheatsAt the TOMY logo, hold A, B, X, Y on Controller 2 until the title screen appears. If done right, the title will be red instead of blue. Now, wait until the Silver Mare's attack demo starts and when it reaches the "Attacker" animation, hold any of the following buttons on Controller 2 until the gameplay demo starts with the words "Press Start". You can then release the buttons and start the game normally.Cheat: Misc. CheatsAt the TOMY logo, hold A, B, X, Y on Controller 2 until the title screen appears. If done right, the title will be red instead of blue. Now, on Controller 1, hold L + R + Start. If done right, you'll be taken to the sound test menu.Cheat: Misc. CheatsAt the TOMY logo, hold A, B, X, Y on Controller 2 until the title screen appears. If done right, the title will be red instead of blue. Now, start the game, select your weapon and at the "Attacker or Defender" screen, pick one and right before the screen completely fades to black, hold one of the following buttons on Controller 1:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Tomy</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>-cAOX6kRaXo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>23247</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570996-accelebrid</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/accele-brid</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/accele-brid/3030-2607/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Accele_Brid</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/UUnIM8b.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/JYzmPHw.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/XC2O31r.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/4nLQ75o.png</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/U12REjX.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/KEv6Yr5.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/h7tpoex.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/fNatsvW.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/IuHSySj.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/dqoRjhe.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/JssLlfZ.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/qiWJz1M.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/KVBbMGI.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/9br7YSY.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vWJwVQX.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/CzcT4qd.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Players progress through the game as a robot racing through a pipe, shooting everything that moves. The robot can shoot from both arms, jump, kick and punch. There are also power-ups and bonuses that can be collected to upgrade the robot's weapons and armor. There are three different types of robots to choose from: Silver Mare, Beliws, and Nitika. Weapons are chosen before each stage and every level has Mode 7 graphics. Three difficulty levels can be chosen; ranging from easy, medium, and hard.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>-cAOX6kRaXo</VideoURL1>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0e41076c-9c01-44aa-a70d-8738b896861c.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f541b9e3-8e59-4b41-9c62-ecae34cc2193.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98da8ef9-88d9-4106-9c31-5f0e335869ee.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8e588e1c-e2a1-40cf-99d9-1ac3faae407e.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82014c07-8729-43d6-96c8-3b569ffb83ce.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/22df7297-59b2-406c-a885-4badd2e3c95b.jpg</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Tomy</Publisher>
</game>