<Game>
	<Name>ACME Animation Factory (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:ACME Animation Factory is an art creation program on which players can use the SNES Mouse peripheral in order to paint, music, color, and animate pictures. The game is licensed by and features characters from the Looney Tunes franchise. It was released exclusively for the Super Nintendo in 1994.There is also a video game mode where the player can play Concentration (a.k.a. Memory) with animated Looney Toons characters; this mode has an added wrinkle where the player must avoid "broken" cards that will end the game prematurely if the player uncovers three of them (out of four). The player has a minute to find all seven pairs, and can reset the game with different configurations.Cheat: Hidden Sound EffectsIn the title screen, click on letter L, O, O, N, E, and Y (located above the picture of Looney Tunes characters), and T, U, N, and E (located below the picture of Looney Tunes characters) to play various sound effects. Note that for the letter O, you must click near the center of the letter.Cheat: Hidden Sound EffectsAt the main screen, click the letter S (in TUNES)</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sandbox</genre>
	<Developer>Sun Corporation of America</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>0.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>uyk_RNCgOPQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1528</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588182-acme-animation-factory</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/acme-animation-factory</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/acme-animation-factory/3030-30605/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/9isX6da.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/2b8lLm6.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/0hiRBbn.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/cvXvP1u.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/oaqPO27.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/5mwADXE.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/lj2suCm.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/yWcneYZ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Iik0bre.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/QRGoIfr.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/a1PUXkb.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/OEcHT2M.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DmbWsV3.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/r4895D8.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Get set to"draw, pard'ner"-- and design, paint and animate, too! Acme Animation Factory is more than a video game. It actually lets you create your own cartoon adventures starring your favorite Looney Tunes friends!  - Create and save cartoons to watch any time! - Choose from a full menu of Looney Tunes scenes and characters, or draw your own! - Color your creation any way you want, then add titles and create music! - Use your control pad or the Nintendo mouse to make it even easier! Step into the Acme Animation Factory. You'll come out cartoon crazy!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>uyk_RNCgOPQ</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1a9e0851-8d54-4846-9ee2-f2c17392c0ab.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/681c2a1a-cf16-4df1-8958-9bf58119787b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/244fcdf8-34e4-4a34-9cea-6d7fe05c4f6e.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5aaf8581-92ca-4114-8d28-a8442ef7e95b.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a98bf666-f879-4599-8933-b8671cef8cff.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ba717e2f-81a3-4802-a327-9850ff838767.jpg</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sunsoft</Publisher>
</game>