<Game>
	<Name>Addams Family, The (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The Addams Family is a multi-platform platformer game based on the movie of the same name. It was developed and published by Ocean on almost every system available in the early 90s.Gameplay:This game is a traditional platformer. Familiar mechanics such as precisely timed jumping, avoiding spikes, pouncing atop the heads of enemies are all featured.Gomez in The Addams Family.The Addams Family game follows Gomez Addams, as he searches the Addams' residence (which has been taken over by Gomez's evil lawyer, Tully Alford), for his missing family members. There are several stages in the game accessible through different doors in the main hall (there are also hidden doors that can lead to rooms with a good amount of pickups, or even some that can serve as short cuts), each housing an imprisoned member of Gomez's family. To free his family, Gomez must traverse each stage and defeat a boss.Pickups include: hearts which increase health; a sword that is lost after taking damage; a rapid firing marble like item, a power up that is also lost after taking damage; and yellow dollar signs, one hundred of which will award the player with an extra life.Once Gomez frees Uncle Fester, Wednesday, Pugsley, and Grandmama, he can then enter the final area of the game to save his wife, Morticia.Cheat: Snap Things FingersDuring the opening sequence, press L + R to snap Thing's fingers.Cheat: Get an Extra ItemWatch the demo then when Fester recieves and item, press Start and you will get that item when you start the game.Cheat: Get an Extra ItemWhen you lose your last life, head over to the door that says continue. Don't go through, just keep walking left and you'll enter a bonus room with four extra lives.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/3/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ocean of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>HL4WfcpZT6M</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3668</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563504-the-addams-family</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/addams-family</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-addams-family/3030-2865/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/8wGkfWG.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9RM8Fgu.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ieGu2AP.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/TRgDxh7.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/3yHIAS5.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/5BiZpaA.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/OfK7p6i.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/mwGy0vE.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/sFQ8UeC.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VtHBI3c.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/1WOuswn.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/D4hR8He.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/9utPbvV.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/1mLxXMY.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Uv0ZZ5t.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/NRrzakM.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4Hd9gvm.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/9VCHeSu.png</clearlogo1>
</game>