<Game>
	<Name>Addams Family, The - Pugsley's Scavenger Hunt (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The Addams Family: Pugsley's Scavenger Hunt is an action/platformer published by Ocean Software and released on multiple platforms. It is based on the 1992 animated series incarnation of The Addams Family, rather than the movies, live-action TV show or the original comics.The Addams Family: Pugsley's Scavenger Hunt has a somewhat unusual release history; originally released on the SNES, versions for the Game Boy and Nintendo's previous console the NES were published a few months later. It was also made available in Europe several months before the US, as Ocean was a UK-based publisher.Gameplay:Pugsley's Scavenger Hunt is a 2D platformer in which the player controls Pugsley Addams, who must venture forth into his house in search of items hidden by his sister Wednesday.Certain rooms, such as the bathroom level, are explored with Pugsley haven been shrunk in size. Different characters are also encountered in each of the rooms. For example, the Addams' butler Lurch is found in the Attic stage.The game is known for its colorful graphics but high difficulty and total lack of a password feature.Critical ReceptionWhen the NES version was released Electronic Gaming Monthly's Mike Weigand gave the review score of 7 out of 10. He wrote, "...another version of the multi-platform game... if you played the SNES version, there is nothing here that is terribly different, except, of course, diminished graphics and sound. This is one of the better games for the NES system".</plot>
	<releasedate>20/2/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ocean of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>mHkg6QRaJtQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3669</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563505-the-addams-family-pugsleys-scavenger-hunt</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/addams-family-pugsleys-scavenger-hunt_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-addams-family-pugsleys-scavenger-hunt/3030-14644/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Absfo7T.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/cHC35WM.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/rMTOPpI.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/mig2g8d.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ntO13QK.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/LJViscx.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/m1h6QKk.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/oTwdXmr.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ORDH4JQ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/okgO13i.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/tbup5hR.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/BWMbfH2.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/0GQKHnb.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/TkN2YwM.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/wTiA1z7.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/la0hhjM.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ui0lrob.png</clearlogo1>
</game>