<Game>
	<Name>Aerobiz Supersonic (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview::Aerobiz Supersonic is a turn-based business strategy game, in which the player takes the reigns of a start-up airline and grows it into the largest airline in the world. The game is a simulation, but it does not aim for the same level of detail as its PC contemporaries. It is part of Koei's "Executive Series", which are mostly business simulations.The game features licensed aircraft from most major manufacturers, which become available (or go out of production) as time passes. Scripted world events (wars, the Olympics, the cold war) and random events (storms, plane crashes) sometimes alter the business climate, and are the game's only real plot points. The game is played on a simplified map of the real world, with cities whose locations and statistics bear some similarity to their real-life counterparts. An average playthrough on "Turbo" difficulty (medium) takes about two hours.Cheat: Hidden Flag Gameyou can play the flag game with an existing game or a new one.  start a game and wait for the menu bar to appear.  pick the icon that looks like a super nes controller. press A, select to begin a game where you need to identify the flag.Cheat: Quicker GameHold L or R and press Y to move over the map quickly.  Hold Down to scroll through the text faster.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/8/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Construction and Management Simulation; Life Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>KOEI Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>mUyFxlVCkic</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3159</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588190-aerobiz-supersonic</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/aerobiz-supersonic</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/aerobiz-supersonic/3030-19317/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/oCOMXh8.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/8j8mCsn.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/J8EBCBC.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/V9ywwd3.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Xnx0pQl.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/pqEi66D.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Mw0xnv4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/5K9mXmZ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/xVjeGKb.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DTXQZ4y.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Lqs2jhp.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/aZKhCNX.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QsQzWxY.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/DUwpkVf.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/pFfcO4j.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/JF5FKu2.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>It's the beginning of the 21st century and competition in the airline industry is heating up. As a young, ambitious CEO, it's up to you to make sure your airline is a survivor and not just another casualty. To succeed, you will have to make some tough decisions including where to fly, which planes to purchase and how to attract visitors to the cities you service. Your goal: to differentiate your airline from the rest while still turning a profit. In Aerobiz Supersonic, fashion a powerful fleet of aircraft from more than 50 possible choices, organize routes to 89 global destinations and invest your profits in a variety of new services including amusement parks, ski resorts and airport shuttle services. And don't forget, as CEO you're still responsible for things like plane maintenance, advertising and handling those periodic emergencies such as a plane crash or employee strike. Get ready to make some tough decisions! If you make the right ones, your planes will dominate the skies of the 21st century.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a56daddc-f6de-4ede-85ad-fadc635ec44d.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/209da85d-ff8d-43d8-87d9-36d0999a9aba.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/679352a9-d822-441c-9ace-bd58bc503d85.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/84592321-babf-4302-8a46-9d7f55c4810a.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9ca77a6e-0b07-4317-acba-87ac8adf6fcb.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/47ccdd3a-c42e-4194-b66d-cf11df69d339.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
</game>