<Game>
	<Name>Aero the Acro-Bat 2 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Aero the Acro-Bat 2 is a SNES-exclusive mascot platformer from Iguana Entertainment and SunSoft, and the sequel to the original Aero the Acro-Bat. The story involves Ektor narrowly surviving his climactic battle with Aero in the previous game, getting saved by his henchman Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel, while Aero accidentally falls into a magician's box and is teleported to an unknown location.As with the previous game, the platforming is built around Aero's ability to "drill" through the air. This works as both a means to attack enemies and as a double jump to get around obstacles, though the distance and direction is fixed: Aero can only fly at a 60 degree angle up or down (dependent on whether or not the player is holding down on the D-pad). Levels also have a number of secret areas and power-ups to find, often behind fake walls. Aero the Acro-Bat 2 also includes snowboarding levels.The credits of Aero the Acro-Bat 2 features a dedication to Ayrton Senna, the Formula One racer who passed away in the May of 1994.Cheat: Level SelectEnter the options menu, and play music tracks in the following order: 10, 15, 06, 08Start the game, pause, and press Down + A + L + R together.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SunSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>CFTRGb7am_s</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1530</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563507-aero-the-acro-bat-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/aero-the-acro-bat-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/aero-the-acro-bat-2/3030-11514/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/zOJfUJd.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/i1F8YCg.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/1mcQGGl.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/RwpVhvR.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Ohg2LIU.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/S2Lipkb.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/fY4iVjx.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/i6xOmP6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/GSUStYg.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/V9TQsf0.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/MG2sTi6.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/hODw6hL.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Ia3SC2g.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/VtXjYEg.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/AvRbD19.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/jsDlc8e.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The aerialist extreme, Aero the Acro-Bat bounds back into the spotlight once again to stop the wicked industrialist, Edgar Ektor! Aero has entered a new realm of enchantment and must now use all his acrobatic prowess to foil a criminal plot known only as "Plan B!" Join Aero as he discovers new friends (and enemies) in a world custom built for his high-flying adventures.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b73f4eb4-10b3-43fb-9b51-5d452ab16a22.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6883b083-7d5c-4aa1-abd7-6fc84d55ec29.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/28462dd6-1800-4f82-8aad-c07f37b561f7.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb2dc90c-eef3-4e55-b777-396d2ac5d6b8.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/21ef045c-d868-45d7-a37c-cf6909cc9d77.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a279807b-a458-4b15-b1c8-e72a5f3c7a9f.png</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Sunsoft</Publisher>
</game>