<Game>
	<Name>Aero Fighters (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Aero Fighters (Sonic Wings in Japan) is a vertical shoot 'em up from Video System and the first game in the Aero Fighters/Sonic Wings series. Its core special feature is the ability to choose different characters from around the world. Each one has their own fighter plane with a distinctive type of firepower. Each character also has a different ending after beating the game.Aero Fighters was originally released in the Arcades in 1992 by Tecmo. It was ported to SNES/Super Famicom the following year (McO'River handled the US release), and would eventually appear in a Japan-only PS2 compilation of emulated Arcade games named Oretachi Geasen Zoku Sono.CharactersThe are two characters per region (Player One and Player Two):USA: Blaster Keaton and Keith BishopUK: William Pride and Lord River N. WhiteJapan: Hien and Mao MaoSweden: Kohful the Viking and Tee-Bee 10Unknown Origin: Rabio and Lepus (two hidden characters added to the SNES version, who are rabbit characters from the Arcade game Rabbit Punch)Cheat: Player Select Screen CodesAt the player select screen, hold the R button then enter the code on Controller 2Cheat: Player Select Screen CodesAt the title screen, hold the R button on Controller 1 and then press the following buttons on Controller 2. If done right, a sound will be heard and the "Super" mode will be available in the options.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Video System Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<rating>4.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>kYdtFt-iWzU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>203</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588188-aero-fighters</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/aero-fighters</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/aero-fighters/3030-2032/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/lbuHUZA.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/QZHm7DL.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/jaMEyqk.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/W2Gjx9a.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Bfmqdo5.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/PvezjU6.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ydiUFKU.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/BJArT7v.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ttBbPrp.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/cWws6NF.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/JctBk6M.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/lHZEIKe.gif</snapshot9>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/5iRrNJJ.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/KXP7pby.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/LJUUYfF.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/5gU7d2O.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The world's hope hinges on your combat skills and sheer determination as an "Aero Fighter". Defend the world from unknown alien forces that are attempting to take over the world. You must extract these unknown forces before they can execute their plot for dominance. After conquering the unknown forces, the battle continues into space where the "controlling intellect" dictated the take-over attempt. You must seek and destroy this evil force to prevent it from seizing other worlds.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>7GLM3Ui7Q6w</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/97b367c6-af73-4f67-ae54-9394fef6c9f1.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/803a35c2-0c5c-4831-9984-214ac258acf5.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9100f285-d3db-4de2-bed3-c96ebf5a150e.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/27deff32-909c-435c-963b-a4e0ec5b474f.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1776e807-5a8a-49be-9bc0-196e3f377301.png</snapshot10>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b81f190-e4a5-4399-9ec2-4775dbd3446f.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>MC O'River</Publisher>
</game>