<Game>
	<Name>Aerobiz (USA)</Name>
	<plot>You are the CEO of an airline company. Your goal is to become the most successful airline in the world by connecting all 22 cities with air routes, maintain a profit, and meet the required quota of passengers. If you cannot turn a profit for a year or meet the victory conditions in 32 years you lose. Some strategic decisions you must make include negotiating for open air routes, purchasing or selling aircraft, invest in branch offices and hotels, advertise your airline and set budgets. You must also pay attention to statistics like quarterly and annual sales reports, as well as city data. World events also affect your airline, from natural disasters to war and even the Olympic games, all of which will affect how many passengers you get. All the planes in the game are based on real-life aircraft, such as the Boeing 747 and the Concorde.Cheat: Sound TestAt the New Game / Continue screen, press Select. Then you should go to the sound test mode. Press Up or down to scroll, A to play the song and B to return to the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/2/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>KOEI Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>AjtiTHjz1u4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1534</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563508-aerobiz</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/aerobiz</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/aerobiz/3030-18626/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/VuQ2VKv.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/C2ce4sI.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/7Eq7f5S.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/HPluzEn.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qg2x6SU.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/VDjt2qO.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/MR0x2qP.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Tlppwag.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/OSvgcM9.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/JBT33OQ.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5pZ47MH.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/rCrbKE2.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/XVZEnLM.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/j9ysiQ2.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ZjngF75.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/rZykuQj.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You're ambitious and you strive for excellence. Your goal is to create a global airline network. You know travelers depend on your airline to get them where they want to go. Now convince them your airline is the best way to fly! A clean safety record, ad campaigns and special services will distinguish you from the rest. As your network expands, establish hub offices and invest in a hotel chain. Tourism will boost income and win passengers away from your competitors. Be aggressive and maintain superiority in the skies.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5f631494-d6af-4c49-b754-666ac869d5c6.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/72057297-d954-42cf-bdc7-df331aa5dcf2.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d5776cbc-64ee-4cb0-b108-0e20f2f3b78d.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a109886c-24a6-41d5-8c70-32efe2356bd5.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d2956b66-2ab5-43c7-8866-78d1b1af533b.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2d47a896-d11d-43a8-bd99-950ad4a8c97e.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
</game>