<Game>
	<Name>Air Cavalry (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Air Cavalry is a one or two-player, dual mode-7 game in which each player controls a high-tech helicopter gunship. Flying above the desert, ocean or jungle, the players will accomplish a series of missions from recon to full assault. Recon missions will use the OH-6 Defender. Transport and rescue missions will use the UH-60 Black Hawk. Attack missions will use either the AH-64H Apache or the futuristic AH-94. Air Cavalry. Choose from three theatres ofof operations with six to eight missions of increasing danger and complexity. Practice in the training mission, climb into your automated cockpit and prepare for air war.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/6/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Cybersoft, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>273</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588191-air-cavalry</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/air-cavalry</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/air-cavalry/3030-7643/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/bUkIZk5.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/SzkoiR5.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/gXIwxPK.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/1IzcOGf.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/gImUfOA.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Rrf6mKL.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ofIkQpj.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/tNJnyDs.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BU0ICbC.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/gXnc29S.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/sl5ZBhQ.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/A9jlfqQ.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/7NGdSQu.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4pzwUHp.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/OpPSFd2.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Air Cavalry is a one or two-player, dual mode-7 game in which each player controls a high-tech helicopter gunship. Flying above the desert, ocean or jungle, the players will accomplish a series of missions from recon to full assault. Recon missions will use the OH-6 Defender. Transport and rescue missions will use the UH-60 Black Hawk. Attack missions will use either the AH-64H Apache or the futuristic AH-94. Air Cavalry. Choose from three theaters of of operations with six to eight missions of increasing danger and complexity. Practice in the training mission, climb into your automated cockpit and prepare for air war.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0ad7a8d4-ba19-4b1c-b1af-718e4985284b.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/da681c1c-6d91-4ff8-9042-245cf604f890.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6a6a3f34-dc18-479e-9470-074807682643.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2bb68f7a-04db-4521-beff-f25974231d84.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a3e2559-483a-459f-afcd-f30aa16e178d.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Cybersoft</Publisher>
</game>