<Game>
	<Name>Akumajou Dracula (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>A century of Transylvanian tranquility is about to come to a shocking end. Once again the mortifying screams of helpless villagers shake the ground as they huddle against new nightmarish horrors unleashed by the Duke of Darkness, Count Dracula. And this time he has a tombstone with your name on it, Simon Belmont.You must descend into Castle of the Undead and its gruesome ground, accompanied by the most chilling sound effects to ever tingle your spine. Inside, a freshly dug 11 levels maze features the treacherous Terrace of Terror, the dangerous Rotating Dungeon, the Sunken Ruins of Lost Spirits, torture chambers and creature filled caves. Use your whip like a grappling hook and swing past hundreds of traps and a host of ghost freaks, living corpses and hidden goblins. All while dodging or destroying the unpredictable spitting lizards, carnivorous coffins, and more.Find the concealed weapons needed to defeat everything from eerie phantoms to haunted furniture. Then prepare to find yourself face-to-thing with hideous torments like the Tongue Lasher, the Darkest Knight, the Bone-Afide Horseman and the Granite Crusher. When your nerves get shot, use your password and take a breather. But forge on, Simon Belmont, because if you though Dracula was down for the count, he's only just begun to fright!Cheat: CodesNote:  When you reach the screen that says ''Enter Your Name'' leave the space blank, do not enter a name or the password will not work. Cheat: Stage passwordsNote: When you come to ''Enter your name'' Leave the space blank or these passwords won't work.       Cheat: Full ArsenalIn the last stage, before you climb the stairs to Dracula, jump down to the left.   You will land on an invisible platform.   Move all the way to the left of the screen and you will get full health, 99 hearts, a cross, a full upgraded whip, and a III stone.Cheat: Full Arsenal There are three hidden branches from the main path in this game.   The first one is in stage 3-1. There will be a point where you must descend a short vertical shaft. Halfway down here is a wall of pillars to the left. These can easily be demolished, where you will find a small side room containing hearts, cash bags, and some Roast.   The second secret, which is an actual hidden Block, is in stage 6-2. At the very beginning you'll need to pass a hallway with Axe Knights and falling chandeliers. The third archway has a chandelier but no guard. Hit the floor a couple of times and it'll crumble, revealing a stairwell into a secret area.   The last one is in Block 9-2. The third section has you jump across a bed of spikes at the beginning. After this you'll see several whirlwind tunnels and some coffins. The last upper platform on the right has a coffin and a tunnel. Let the tunnel suck you in and you'll find a hidden area full of bonuses.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.1</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>8iak17nQT1Y</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1308</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588726-super-castlevania-iv</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-castlevania-iv/3030-11443/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Castlevania_IV</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/zYxgvsY.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/v7CKMPv.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/dmHgI0Z.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/sccFd31.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/w6XD44m.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/kCTLlDv.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/bADUrWk.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/pQUdHt4.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/cAgLNXD.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/O3dvFYB.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/nqbmBmB.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/cMGmJ76.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/bt7Cxb1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/jYaTiXD.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/Uzpm3nh.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/T4HYFXH.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Bsck7d7.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/ZlVcEQ2.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://i.imgur.com/9CuUvie.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://i.imgur.com/dAvS6tL.png</clearlogo4>
</game>