<Game>
	<Name>Al Unser Jr.'s Road to the Top (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>This racing game features both a practice and a Road to the Top mode. In the Road to the Top mode, four different racing events are held with three courses for each event. Each event features a different vehicle to use. The player can choose from one of three vehicles which feature different attributes for handling, top speed, braking, and acceleration. The player begins by racing go-karts, then moves up to snow mobiles, then IROC racing cars, and then finally Indy racing cars. If the player places high enough in all the races, then the final challenge is to take on Al Unser, Jr. in the finals in Vancouver. In the practice mode, the player can practice every course in the game except for the final race.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Software Toolworks, Inc., The</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>V56VRCI0dQ4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1605</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588193-al-unser-jrs-road-to-the-top</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/al-unser-jrs-road-to-the-top-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/al-unser-jrs-road-to-the-top/3030-31005/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/B69n6m2.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/uMFviPB.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ptFxHXl.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/nEP6xyQ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/A6dcnYN.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/eg0Djq7.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/A0xUNK6.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/lYiylHY.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/SDnGkZZ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/DwHagDB.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/DYEX2sK.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/sdEJZOC.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jxgwDJT.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/MrLp434.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Have You Got The Drive To Make It To The Top? Start as a novice, learn the courses, and race your way to the professional Indy Circuit the same way Al Unser Jr. did! Four different styles of racing and four entirely different vehicles with one- or two-player simultaneous action: - Go-karts on twisting dirt tracks. - Souped-up snowmobiles on slippery snow courses. - Hot, high-horsepower IROC racers. - Indy cars on the fastest tracks of all! Race hard and place high to take on the ultimate challenge of Pike's Peak! It won't be easy to race to the top - this is a challenge you'll want to come back to again and again! If you're the best, you'll make it to the final showdown against Al Unser Jr. himself! The thrill come from hanging in there until you reach the top!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2b07f7ea-b492-48d6-9cbf-da48eb415a23.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40901f2a-16f9-49cf-801f-4340d94e6173.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2be7db92-adb0-4601-bb06-2ccdb7eb785e.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/190f0413-d3c8-47cb-a8f7-40d1f2ad1580.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Software Toolworks</Publisher>
</game>