<Game>
	<Name>Albert Odyssey (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The town of Gouto hosted a miraculous artifact, the Key of Resurrection. The evil wizard Oswald invaded the town with his army of goblins and dragons. Three brave knights went out to defend the homeland, and one of them was killed in battle. His wife and his daughter Sophia left the house crying, but Oswald was already in the town, and with one strike he killed Sophia's mother...Fast-forward ten years. In a nearby town lives a young brave warrior named Albert. He just turned sixteen, and he undergoes an initiation as a descendant of brave heroes of the past. Meanwhile, Sophia became the court wizard of the kingdom. She hasn't forgot the murder of her parents, but she needs the help of a brave warrior like Albert to avenge their death and to stop Oswald..."Albert-Odyssey" is a console-style strategy RPG. The story is told in cut-scenes between battles and traveling within towns. World map and dungeons are handled as huge battlefields, where your party moves in turn-based style, waiting for the enemy turn until you can perform your next action. Enemies often come in large groups, and strategic positioning of your party members on the battle field plays an important role.</plot>
	<releasedate>5/3/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>SunSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>m4v1g8iR4hg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>23757</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588194-albert-odyssey</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/albert-odyssey</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/albert-odyssey/3030-33881/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Le85ChO.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/1Ug8jhG.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/mwW8dRv.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/APcm1j5.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/2FGzGqo.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/52qupMK.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/868IFuN.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/8BvKYFc.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/kiVknzi.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/GIGIFhn.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/LVPsZ2J.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/0fSr32c.gif</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Ca070mH.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Albert Odyssey (アルバートオデッセイ Arubaato Odessei?) is a tactical role-playing video game developed and published by Sunsoft and released for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System in Japan in March 1993. The game features strategy-based combat in addition to traditional role-playing game elements in two-dimensional environments. It is the first game in the Albert Odyssey series, and was followed by two sequels, Albert Odyssey 2: Jashin no Taidou in 1994, and Albert Odyssey: Legend of Eldean in 1996. On June 12, 1996, Albert Odyssey was made available as a full game download on the Satellaview add-on as BS Albert Odyssey (BSアルバートオデッセイ BS Arubaato Odessei?),[citation needed] and the original Albert Odyssey was re-released for Satellaview in March 1998.[1] Players assume the role of Albert, the young heroic swordsman who lives in a fantasy world filled with monsters and mythical creatures. While much of the world remains in relative peace following a great war many years before, a military faction led by the dark magician Globus has emerged to conquer the newly pacified nations and expand their empire. With the help of Albert's friends as well as hired mercenaries, the player must travel the world and eventually confront Golbus and his forces to prevent another large-scale conflict.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/85d91961-663a-47a9-bf9e-620576acfe44.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fe8ccb6d-d4fe-4230-9a03-642c2d03b00c.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a7df5ae-3d3a-4351-8f51-a3098c84ba0a.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d9f65271-d116-4df5-bc44-245108814570.png</snapshot12>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<Publisher>Taito</Publisher>
</game>