<Game>
	<Name>Albert Odyssey 2 - Jashin no Taidou (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Albert Odyssey 2: Jashin no Taidou ("Albert Odyssey 2: Sign of the Devil") is a Super Famicom SRPG and the sequel to the 1993 Super Famicom game Albert Odyssey. It is set ten years later and follows a new protagonist, Dean, who trains to become a warrior after being inspired by the exploits of Albert: the hero from the first game. Dean's quest to stop an evil god, Okutoba, leads him to many of the same locations and NPCs from the original Albert Odyssey.The game uses a tactical map screen for its combat. The player moves their units around this map and positions them to fight other units - either up close or at a distance depending on the character's skills and weapons. The game uses Mode 7 to depict this grid map as a concave landscape. Similar to Intelligent Systems' Fire Emblem, each time two units meet the game switches to a 2D animated cutaway that displays the exchange of damage.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SunSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>v4XjagJWKiQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>23758</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575561-albert-odyssey-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/albert-odyssey-2-jashin-no-taidou/3030-46806/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/RRnmBKt.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ovNuryC.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Qqfb51c.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/pzH28Lx.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/GCHhf0q.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/SrjL40z.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/cW4qj5k.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/79MsE2W.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/8W3bJ0i.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/OWLwHH6.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/oFbx3M7.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/7Nqt92y.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/aEeB4di.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Albert Odyssey 2: Jashin no Taidou  is a tactical role-playing video game developed and published by Sunsoft for the Super Famicom and released in December 1994. It is the sequel to the original Albert Odyssey and retains many of the same gameplay and story elements while featuring enhanced graphics and battle features. The game is set ten years after the previous title and follows the story of Dean, a young warrior who is enthralled by the exploits of the hero Albert who saved the world a decade earlier from an evil magician. Setting off on his own journey to investigate the conflict, Dean becomes entangled in an adventure of his own while meeting characters from the previous game. He soon learns that the world is once again in danger from an ancient evil god known as Okutoba, and must become a hero himself to stop him from throwing the world into darkness.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98943ec7-2a0f-4707-a685-67bb2ca72f05.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3bcbfbcf-3546-43dc-9448-3261c6ec7595.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9e5b827c-ddb4-4118-b2ad-9f463c95623d.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e2d592b1-7c52-43ec-9195-6b8e5fc64e42.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>