<Game>
	<Name>Alfred Chicken (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Alfred Chicken is a 1993 platformer developed by Twilight Games, and published by Mindscape for multiple platforms. The eponymous main character is able to jump and glide, but not directly attack enemies unless he is diving down fast while gliding. In order to complete each level, the player has to have Alfred peck all of the balloons that are tied down in various parts of the levels. Once all of the balloons have been pecked, a boss is fought to complete the level.For a publicity stunt to promote the game Karl Fitzhugh, an employee of Mindscape, ran for a political office as the Alfred Chicken party candidate in Christchurch, Dorset, England. Unsurprisingly, he did not win.Cheat: Scene SelectIn the title screen, press Select, then Start to bring up the configuration screen. On the second controller keep pressed A, X, L, R while pressing Start on the first controller. Now the scene selection screen should appear.Cheat: Level PasswordsFrom the title screen, go to "Start", then "Use Password".Cheat: Warp up to level 6Locate the giant sunflower balloon in level 1. Get to the right side of the screen without releasing the balooon. Once toushing the right wall, jump stright up to find a hidden block. Use the block to jump left off the screen, then walk left to find the warp.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/2/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Mindscape International Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>ZiWYEMogYW0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3754</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588195-super-alfred-chicken</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/alfred-chicken</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/alfred-chicken/3030-8966/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/fN74uHH.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/XKiiFfE.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ygfV0MZ.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/iBkpgQj.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wbLgtgI.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/bpjAurg.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/nSv75G7.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/y8y1U6M.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/QReZHcI.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Hqrxzir.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/gGJD5Wb.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/34fZT9s.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/F0XFChj.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/JDK43bG.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/I1i5A5g.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/b1iMdGa.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/lrNKfkF.png</clearlogo2>
</game>