<Game>
	<Name>Alien vs Predator (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Based on the Alien VS Predator comic book series. During the 25th century, mankind has colonized many planets. On one of these, New Shanghai, strange creatures have been discovered. These Aliens cause much havoc. New Shanghai initiates a distress call to other planets in the galaxy. A cloaked ship belonging to hunting creatures known as Predators intercepts the message. The Predators on board decide that these strange Alien creatures might make worthy trophies for the collection. The player takes the role of one of the Predators. The Predator will fight through several levels of alien creatures in aside scrolling manner. The Predator's ability includes attacking,jumping, sliding and firing bolts from it's shoulder cannon. Additionally, the shoulder cannon can be charged up to unleash adevastating attack that also harms the Predator. Most aliens willdrop power-ups which include health, trophy skulls, a double edgedthrowing weapon, throwing spears and active camouflage. Boss aliens wait at the end of most levels.Cheat: A few codesEnter code at the start menuCheat: Stage SelectAt the title screen, press Select to access the configuration menu, then press Start. At the Options Menu, hold the following on Controller 2: X + A + L + R Then on Controller 1 press Start</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Activision, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<rating>1.2</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>NSHZMRRl15o</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3310</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563511-alien-vs-predator</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/alien-vs-predator_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/alien-vs-predator/3030-1297/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/VdpY0II.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/MtERorz.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/2BJBgVD.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/2lVXejN.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/2JMAwjp.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/zfYTCLG.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/IMQJAjS.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/WKXFFA3.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/jEn8jL5.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/scZ2F6x.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Cvtpkip.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/reKoryb.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/e3fPhGY.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/GlFf8L7.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/hAPeHFY.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/y34cYAt.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/YizkrPb.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/HOcenpQ.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/OXKNMYD.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/IZdLN7N.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/4XTsgiC.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://i.imgur.com/uZutG06.png</clearlogo3>
	<Notes>You're a Predator warrior in the 25th century--an awesome monster with an ugly face, brute strength and very cool weapons. Trained to fight with all that Predator technology has to offer--destroy or be destroyed! You've come to New Shanghai, a city on the planet Vega 4, to hunt humans, but instead, you find Aliens--powerful, double-jawed beasts bent on annihilating life. You're outnumbered, but not outsmarted--the hunt is on. Alien drones, warriors, chest-bursters and face-huggers stand in your way. Use your lasers, blades and special weapons of destruction to win honor for your deeds. Destroy the Guardian Aliens to advance to the next level, then follow your primal instinct to reach the ultimate prey... the Alien Queen!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/909963f0-d51b-4278-bc8c-64dcf2dd0e43.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea2e699a-86dc-4198-a2b4-166bc9194df8.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63a95c7a-2a79-4a97-9258-f6648132d830.png</clearlogo4>
	<clearlogo5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7957fabc-cc92-4006-a96e-035d567afb7f.png</clearlogo5>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/10034d4b-7d2c-47d4-944e-a791e189401d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/047c6499-da9c-4dca-a038-845ac3fde326.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>