<Game>
	<Name>American Gladiators (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:American Gladiators is a video game adaptation of the TV show, in which regular people compete with professional athletes and gymnasts in numerous events. The game contains five events with four difficulty levels. If the player can successfully complete all four difficulty levels, they get to compete in The Eliminator Challenge. The player can compete against another human companion, or an AI.The game received multiple console and computer versions, most of which shared the same events and only had graphical differences. EventsThe Human CannonballAssaultPowerballThe WallJoustAtlasphere (not in NES version)The EliminatorGladiatorsGeminiGoldLaceNitroLaserBlazeCheat: Easy WinAt the beginning of the Joust game, step forward two spaces, hold B and press back.  You should see your character start spinning their jousting stick over their head.  Do not let go of the B button while doing this.  If done correctly, the gladiator will not block and you'll be able to hit him repeatedly and easily win.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/4/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>GameTek, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>1.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>2761</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588196-american-gladiators</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/american-gladiators</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/american-gladiators/3030-346/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/CAJtZL1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nY1EpCp.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/U9ux4EJ.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ql2RR6Y.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/La4Ax6j.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Y2lzdHr.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/mz0LYNu.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/xZKSC8x.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7syim2u.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/yRov28i.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/KKfCKqg.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/oAtJtHY.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/eq4X45m.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/0msMDru.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8mWTRNc.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/JxKimhE.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Television's most innovative sports event, AMERICAN GLADIATORS, is now the most innovative sports game available for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. Seven events including: The WaII, The Joust, The Assault, Human Cannonball, Atlasphere, Powerball and the Eliminator are all captured with digitized photography, and life-size combat. We've included all of the action, drama, and competitiveness, right down to the personalities and profiles of all the real-life Gladiators. Nitro, Ice, Laser, Thunder, Gold, Turbo, Zap, Lace, Blaze, and Gemini are all here, and just like their television counterparts, they'll never give in without a fight to the finish. With tournament play, scoring, game rules and arena design taken right from the show, this game is as real as it gets. GameTek's AMERICAN GLADIATORS for your Super Nintendo Entertainment System, is survival of the fittest.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3c9851b4-93e4-4ba2-8938-5f3e1976930d.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/37921cad-3f25-4015-b0a3-6ee6f03347fd.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/262d4a2e-b0ea-4507-98b3-43f3dcfd0da0.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb2cab45-ef55-4760-ab32-8921749cb6aa.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>GameTek</Publisher>
</game>