<Game>
	<Name>America Oudan Ultra Quiz (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:America Oudan Ultra Quiz is a quiz game developed by Genki and published by Tomy. It is the fourth game in the America Oudan Ultra Quiz video game franchise and the first to be released on the Super Famicom. The game was never released outside of Japan and requires fluency in Japanese to answer any of its questions.It follows the formula of the TV game show Ultra Quiz, which originated in the UK and was adapted by broadcasters across the globe. A large number of contestants are whittled down to a small number through a series of elimination challenges, most of which require answering general knowledge questions, in a manner similar to 1 vs. 100. In America Oudan Ultra Quiz, the player can select the name and gender of their character and take part in the quiz with many NPCs.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Trivia</genre>
	<Developer>Genki</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570871-america-oudan-ultra-quiz</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/america-oudan-ultra-quiz/3030-38013/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/America_%C5%8Cdan_Ultra_Quiz</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/5xnxHl1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Y6Bhj8n.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/yVZdYVm.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/XN6CUL6.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6NWmrmT.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/9DtUUIM.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/zLuI3H3.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/3TBoT1B.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/LeNLPGP.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/7ZdrkyX.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/9wc0JmM.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Y3TEJ2k.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/I92h3gO.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/eDiUdzJ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>America Oudan Ultra Quiz is a quiz game that follows the formula of the TV game show Ultra Quiz, which originated in the UK and was adapted by broadcasters across the globe. A large number of contestants are whittled down to a small number through a series of elimination challenges, most of which require answering general knowledge questions, in a manner similar to 1 vs. 100. In America Oudan Ultra Quiz, the player can select the name and gender of their character and take part in the quiz with many NPCs.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/03500d67-1663-4147-bb9c-2b182c77cd40.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/707ae3af-8586-46bf-a4fd-0f63669851ec.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/934aaae9-4875-4949-b6c9-0ea7e948a30d.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Tomy</Publisher>
</game>