<Game>
	<Name>Appleseed - Prometheus no Shintaku (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Appleseed: Prometheus no Shintaku ("Oracle of Prometheus") is a side-scrolling shooter from Kan's and Visit. It is based on the cyberpunk sci-fi manga and anime Appleseed by Masamune Shirow, who worked on it before creating Ghost in the Shell. Two ESWAT members, Deunan Knute (a blonde female human with impeccable marksmanship) and Briareos Hecatonchires (a towering male cyborg with an enormous amount of strength), must protect the fledgling utopian nation of Olympus: one of the last bastions of humanity in a planet ravaged by the apocalyptic World War 3.The game is a standard side-scrolling shooter. The characters have their standard handgun side-arm and a special sub-weapon with finite ammo that is different for the two. They also have a number of grenades which they can throw at any time. The player must make their way through various missions, getting briefed each time.The game uses the Greek mythological figure Prometheus in its title, a naming convention with the four editions of the manga.</plot>
	<releasedate>26/8/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Kan's</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1</rating>
	<VideoURL>https://AkhGEQ36z-I</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>17195</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/appleseed-prometheus-no-shintaku/3030-46704/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ymF9lzf.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/UFMcQSl.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/gLgTMzK.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/HL7415V.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/5ssGroT.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6BDxIFx.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/CeHvNkk.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/NO0opdu.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/SbRChXy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/MyWUXCI.jpg</snapshot7>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/VOSRhIk.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/YoyZAgk.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/nOklqP4.jpg</fanart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/U6gQCmv.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>World War III is over, and nomad soldier Duenan Knute and her cyborg partner Briareos struggle to survive in the abandoned cities and demilitarized zones of the post-war wasteland, the "Badside." Matters appear on the upswing, however, when they are found and brought to Olympus, an urban utopia and centerpiece for the reconstruction of civilization. Duenan and Bri join the Olympus' police, a force that seems hardly necessary in such a paradise. But, like in most pretty pictures, perfection is an illusion, and Olympus' peaceful facade hides a dark secret, a violent struggle between human and cyborg that could once again plunge the world into war... and genocide.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>https://AkhGEQ36z-I</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/19ff020f-41fd-4143-a6d2-1125a49ef3eb.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d851611-795d-471b-ad50-0a28238fc89c.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0b9dd660-61a8-42fa-b524-4b044f6b1f6a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9f5c12ce-807b-4dff-afce-3d8b46e503dc.jpg</snapshot8>
	<Publisher>Visit</Publisher>
</game>