<Game>
	<Name>Arcana (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Arcana, or Card Master: Seal of Rimsalia in Japan, is a SNES RPG and one of very few that is a first-person dungeon crawler like Might and Magic or Shining in the Darkness, rather than a top-down game in the vein of Final Fantasy or Dragon Quest. The player is able to summon spirit helpers to assist him in the game's turn-based encounters, as well as various recruitable characters, and can return to a hub town to replenish their supplies and rest.Everyone featured in the game, including NPCs and monsters, are depicted as cards that feature their stats and appearance. The card presentation is entirely superficial, as the game doesn't really employ any card-based systems.	Cheat: Stage SelectAt the title screen, press Down, Select, Select, X, Y, Select, Select, L, R, Select, Select, Left, Right, Up and then: A for Stage 2 B for Stage 3 X for Stage 4 Y for Stage 5Cheat: Sound TestAt the title screen, hold L + R + B</plot>
	<releasedate>20/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>HAL America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>XQQXS5phDK4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1707</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563513-arcana</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/arcana</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/arcana/3030-8765/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XrEoc3A.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/pKaWZ9x.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/rfNIxqJ.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/e4umIvf.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ulguhGM.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ScHcjnh.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/k3gqLmf.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/4tYkLjj.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/uSKxPVL.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/umijD2d.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/J9Slt0W.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/9z6dSyr.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/5WrTUcR.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/8f66YrM.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/BoboFsH.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Rz6RJal.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Arcana - 1. Mysterious knowledge known only to initiates. 2. Ancient rites and spiritual powers understood by only a few. 3. The secrets held by the Card Masters now fast disappearing. The art of the Card Masters has gradually died out. None of the young people want to learn the ancient system of casting spells and calling up spirits using the cards. But an evil conspiracy has taken hold of the kingdom. Rooks, descended from the last of the true Card Masters, is recruited to overthrow the sinister regime. Relying on what little he knows of the ancient art, learning along the way, trusting no one. Rooks sets out on a journey to restore order and save his homeland. Only a Card Master can do it.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7c374259-8e01-4afb-baec-2068c3d60682.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2c742442-707f-4834-bcbe-faf855488e26.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/84b04cd1-a782-4769-b284-9f8fe041f084.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a627a89c-5a8c-4b14-b826-b56f69fa340a.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8785ceac-9cba-46d4-afdd-e258fb00a361.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>HAL Laboratory</Publisher>
</game>