<Game>
	<Name>Aretha II - Ariel no Fushigi na Tabi (Japan) (Beta 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Aretha II: Ariel no Fushigi na Tabi ("Aretha II: Ariel's Mysterious Journey") is a role-playing game developed by Japan Art Media and published by Yanoman Corporation for Game Boy and Super Nintendo platforms. It is the sequel to the first Super Famicom Aretha. Ariel is once again called into action to save her friends Kyle and Doll (Dole) from peril.The game has a novel equipment creation system that uses the colored souls of enemies to craft new gear depending on the configuration of colors the player uses. The player's party is dictated by the player's place in the story with characters joining and leaving at various points, similar to Final Fantasy IV. The eponymous heroine is the only constant.The game should not be confused with Aretha II for the Game Boy. The original three Game Boy Aretha games were released several years earlier and have a separate arching storyline.							</plot>
	<releasedate>2/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Japan Art Media (JAM)</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>26437</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581804-aretha-ii-ariel-no-fushigi-na-tabi</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/aretha-ii-ariel-fushigi-no-tabi</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/aretha-ii-ariel-no-fushigi-na-tabi/3030-18252/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aretha_II:_Ariel_no_Fushigi_na_Tabi</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/lzxkKG7.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/yFCrTU1.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/sBMwyRN.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/WCg12SE.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ZOY1nfb.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Js7uV7w.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SVz85kB.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/LG1506O.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/xJ6Pt9f.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/XQmA45Y.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/G9DBK0T.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Nxw5vph.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/bIfdZCt.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/55kvsUT.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The game continues the story of the young princess Ariel. After she rightfully regained her throne, people enjoyed a peaceful life under her benevolent reign. But this peaceful existence did not last long... Two adventurers who were wandering through mountains met a mysterious evil being, who threatened to ruin Ariel's kingdom. After that, the two men disappeared without a trace. Ariel's servants reported to her about the matter. After consulting her wise grandmother, Ariel decided to go out herself, to meet up with her old trusty companions and to find out the origin of the new threat. The game is a console-style RPG - you fight random enemies in turn-based combat viewed from first-person perspective. Enemies may attack you from the sides, and you should pay attention which enemy you face. A unique feature the game uses is the ability to get special items called "souls" after battles, and then to use them to forge your own armor.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0c4b7db-9f8c-447c-ab14-f05ed978d3bd.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/316bb399-f8f4-4f14-89e2-1a8fe07be50c.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/448306f7-8914-41b6-a9ba-4a8db02b4011.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49983798-af57-4773-8350-97a34d966937.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/51141803-7216-417d-b8dc-85f12ca1208a.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f17e9b5f-848a-4f3d-bd64-b1bfe3443889.png</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Yanoman</Publisher>
</game>