<Game>
	<Name>Asameshimae Nyanko (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Asameshimae Nyanko ("Piece of Cake Kitty") is a 1994 puzzle game that plays similarly to Reversi. Players must place two tiles of their color on either side of one of more pieces of the opponent's color, which flips the opponent pieces and makes them the player's. In Asameshimae Nyanko, these pieces are cats, and occasionally the player will be forced to "fight" enemy cats to take them over. These fights are simple button mashers, where the player that mashes hardest will win.The game was released exclusively for the Super Famicom and never saw an English localization.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>J-Force</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581908-asameshimae-nyanko</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/asameshimae-nyanko/3030-40110/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/GCTc2aq.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/OdrF4LG.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/g01KkkI.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/250iTb8.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/rFrZqqJ.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/kATgAJ0.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/wkHQlRF.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/HFWrUpQ.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/o98efZm.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Q4OiF8x.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/6e01TYE.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/aGGpcGq.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/jDPJlQz.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Asameshimae Nyanko has similarities with Reversi (or Othello) and with fights that are similar to rock-paper-scissors to intercept additional moves with kittens that have different proficiency with vertical/horizontal and diagonal moves. In the game, players partake in a Reversi-esque game and get to choose a number of stages to play on and the type of kitten they want to use. They can also change the rules and settings to an extent. It's red versus blue, with a random player going first. As players would in Reversi or Othello, sandwich kittens vertically, horizontally or diagonally (though since the game is isometric, it's hard to say vertically or horizontally). They will change all the kittens in between to a certain color, but can additionally select cats in the area to do battle with. Winning allows players to further convert cats to their cause. There are special items which have certain effects such as making players lose a turn, but, there isn't much interruption from them.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0b0ca6b3-d513-4d88-95ab-79d7b874e41d.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d0a89e02-dcb2-4cdd-b572-bbf782f494ea.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f40a43b7-0298-4a80-be7b-e76b4bcddc74.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/449428cf-7ea6-4fc9-b7e7-27696128410f.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1ad22ac8-46ec-43aa-8fba-3e771319dd09.jpg</snapshot13>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<Publisher>Zamuse</Publisher>
</game>