<Game>
	<Name>Asterix (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Asterix &amp; Obelix is a game released by Infogrames in 1996, for the PC, SNES, Game Boy and Game Boy Color, the player can choose to play with both Asterix or Obelix. The game also supports two players at the same time (both in the keyboard).Cheat: Level select menu and level skipEnter the code at the Infogrames logo.  As you press each button, it must be held down until the rest of the code is entered.  A sound effect will play when the level select menu is enabled, and again for the full version of the code with level skip.  During gameplay, press L + R + Select to open the stage menu.  During gameplay, hold Select and press down for the level skip.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Side-Scrolling, Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Infogrames</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>SFJKpafD1u4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3160</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/926384-asterix</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/astrix</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/asterix/3030-36064/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/HcvNnvm.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/GuPogJr.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/WAwH26e.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/DKU7Bhh.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/EbXAmMA.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/NHiTJ6P.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/BkUbqea.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/XipOnmS.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/0XAmDKy.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/JV8NZXm.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/QHeqOOY.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/IkdqlB3.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Sa0GoYa.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/IvaIHJN.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/9XtLef3.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/JnFsp3I.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/FGE1k0u.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The year is 50 BC. Gaul is entirely occupied by the Romans. Well, almost entirely... One small Gaulish village continues to defy the occupying forces, the villagers protected by a magic potion which makes them invincible. But now Obelix has vanished! The Romans have confirmed his capture and taken him to an unknown destination.  Astérix is a platform game based on the eponymous comic books, where the short and mustached Gaul has to progress through levels located all across Europe, fighting Romans and various aggressive animals along the way, to rescue his friend Obelix before Caesar throws him to the lions....</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7cf57e7-9aa2-40a2-be8d-799ed74d83ad.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/004dfa0f-11f8-41d3-84bd-27b9039eae57.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/00db0b00-2782-48d1-952b-b56177016a41.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Infogrames</Publisher>
</game>