<Game>
	<Name>Axelay (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Axelay is a side- and vertically-scrolling shoot 'em up from Konami created specifically for the Super Nintendo to take advantage of its Mode 7 capabilities. Many of the stages employ this tech, displaying a wraparound affect in some stages as the player flies over the horizon of planets. The game was released in 1992 (1993 for Europe) and was later released on the Wii's Virtual Console in 2007.Plot:Axelay takes place in the fictional Illis Solar System, which is under attack by alien invaders known as the Armada of Annihilation, which seeks to take over the planets of Illis. The game begins on the planet Corliss, which is similar to Earth. The player must take their ship, the D117B Axelay Fighter and free the planets of Illis, eventually making their way to the Fortress of the Armada of Annihilation and stop the invasion.Trivia:If the game is completed twice on the hardest difficulty, a message appears and promises a sequel to Axelay. However, an Axelay 2 was never released and no plans for a sequel have yet to materialize. Cheat: Play Normal and Hard Modes with Extra CreditsBeat Easy mode without continuing.  You will have 2 extra credits on Normal mode.Beat Normal mode without continuing.  If you began in Easy mode, you will have 4 extra credits in Hard mode.  If not, you will have 2 extra credits.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>mBJ6IcdKk8M</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1573</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563514-axelay</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/axelay</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/axelay/3030-12192/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Axelay</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Gv3sV6H.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/yM2F1xL.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/YdBPM1p.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/eNZB547.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/Q8hEaUH.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/MjWBi84.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/cG9OMaf.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/1LwAA30.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/8oBa2Nv.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/77rTISZ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/OxVB81d.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/SEQHbNl.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/TAEzT5o.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/XcDSVf7.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/0fZP0HS.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/xZn5qNC.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/88c7e76.png</banner1>
	<banner2>http://i.imgur.com/tQgSeN6.png</banner2>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/W0xUo46.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>KISS YOUR AXELAY GOOD-BYE. You're stewed. Even though you've got the Axelay prototype combat stratafighter with the most sophisticated weaponry in the Illis solar system, the 3-D graphics and perspectives are so realistically shocking that you'll probably freak out and bury the ship in an asteroid. Nevertheless, you're the only remaining hope for a cluster of worlds bonded by one common goal - to suppress the ruthless onslaught brought forth by the Armada of Annihilation in a six level galactic blitzkrieg. The planets of the Illis solar system combined their technology to create a defense force like no other by engineering the D-117B, code name: Axelay. A fighter so advanced and costly; only one could be built.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>ks_FfxFFjYc</VideoURL1>
	<banner3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c6c6d7b3-ad83-498e-b8f7-fcd7dbf69411.jpg</banner3>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7bac440e-e023-432c-a1fb-8b16327b4dd3.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b1d835e0-0264-44f1-8204-4f949a2aa43f.png</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea41846f-443d-497b-9e79-b05aa7a6a77a.png</boxart8>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3c88f992-61d4-4705-9a4d-ce60bb3a0c07.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a39edec-9de2-47f3-af91-ee456a0b801c.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b3a410e-7051-4f96-90a1-a0efebf48d73.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/05695e07-6e5b-40c7-9b20-fa9596a4d6aa.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0d10f85d-181a-44bd-8677-10e7a7247aa1.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/518f1002-f847-459c-bccb-32ecc2673a73.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c16276f8-521f-40cf-b6c5-8a516da78c7e.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2485375e-52c2-4ae1-9f55-0ce84b87ad5f.jpg</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/da90ab3e-2b07-4091-b280-1bb7c805e073.jpg</snapshot18>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>