<Game>
	<Name>Barbarossa (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Barbarossa is a turn-based strategy game set during World War II. The player controls a senior Wehrmacht officer in charge of several troops as Nazi Germany begins their 1941 invasion of the Soviet Union, which was codenamed Operation Barbarossa. The player has four years with which to cross the map from Berlin to Moscow and conquer the Russian capital before Hitler dies and Nazi Germany surrenders in 1945.The game plays similarly to other strategy war-sims of the era, such as Famicom/Nintendo Wars or Military Madness (for instance, it uses a hexagonal spaces on the map). Each unit on the map - comprised of several instances of the same unit type - has their own stats concerning attack power, fuel consumption, maintenance costs and mobility. Whenever two units meet in combat, the view changes to present a dramatic enactment of the battle.The game was never released outside of Japan, possibly because Nazi Germany is the only playable side.Cheat: Debug modeAt the title screen press in order the following buttons. After succeeding, the "Push Start Button" will turn red.Cheat: Debug modeAt the title screen press in order the following buttons:Cheat: Debug modeIf you push X while pushing LR when there's no unit on the map, the map will be cleared. In the same way, if you push A while pushing LR, you'll lose. And if you push LR while the cursor is on the unit, that unit will disappear.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/11/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>SystemSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570875-barbarossa</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/barbarossa/3030-39830/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/IFWRt1B.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/oQnsIo7.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/skq2pzK.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/h6sYCNq.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/fP5KuCH.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/m1rPjxA.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/0j0msE4.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/dJIx6im.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/RmFvxbr.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6BXBKlZ.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Am0Ad8C.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/aGSAHuZ.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/PPlYgQq.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/ISL7fRa.jpg</fanart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/S3prsTs.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Strategy game based on WWII barbarossa campaign. Operation Barbarossa (German: Unternehmen Barbarossa) was the code name for Nazi Germany's invasion of the Soviet Union during World War II, which began on 22 June 1941. The operation was driven by Adolf Hitler's ideological desire to conquer the Soviet territories as outlined in his 1925 manifesto Mein Kampf ("My Struggle"). In the two years leading up to the invasion, the two countries signed political and economic pacts for strategic purposes. Still, on 18 December 1940, Hitler authorized an invasion of the Soviet Union for a start date of 15 May 1941, but this was not met; instead, the invasion began on 22 June 1941. Over the course of the operation, about four million soldiers of the Axis powers invaded the Soviet Union along a 2,900-kilometer (1,800 mi) front, the largest invasion force in the history of warfare. In addition to troops, the Germans employed some 600,000 motor vehicles and between 600–700,000 horses. It marked the beginning of the rapid escalation of the war, both geographically and in the formation of the Allied coalition.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7c8b2357-ba8a-4e03-aef9-785aa04a5b99.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40f30926-1296-48d4-b229-4b8138f563e8.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fd64a6a1-7a62-45ba-9900-737c17495768.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/629b25a3-ce75-45a5-8663-979e803cea16.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/748d0186-e77a-4e75-9f6a-fc5a4568dbc1.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Sammy Studios</Publisher>
</game>