<Game>
	<Name>Bastard!! - Ankoku no Hakaishin (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bastard!! Ankoku no Hakaishin ("Bastard!! The Destructive God of Darkness") is a multiplayer fighting game for the Super Famicom that is based on the Bastard!! manga from Kazushi Hagiwara. The player, as the legendary (and megalomaniacal) wizard Dark Schneider, must fight his former associates the Lords of Havoc and conquer the world in the single-player story mode.The game is similar to the Dragon Ball Z: Super Butouden series (developer Cobra Team also developed Dragon Ball Z Arcade games). The player can move from the ground to the sky and fire projectiles at their opponent. They can also rush towards them for melee damage.Cheat: In put one of the following codes to get that effectPause game play during a battle and input the code</plot>
	<releasedate>28/1/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Cobra Team</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3479</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/564397-bastard</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bastard-ankoku-no-hakaishin/3030-37461/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/1zrUOjs.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/PdvlS6N.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/0QzVfNA.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/nliTrbH.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ZI5H2l8.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/JQpX4rd.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/W8YLUrv.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/zDiulEH.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/3a14VHo.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/uZy5DoW.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ntTVMCw.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/FQ31P1R.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/dUgUk8q.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/tQ0GkBx.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/97mQZog.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In this game, you're either in the foreground or the background, and your opponent is always on the opposite end of the screen. To fight whoever flies thar yonder in the distance, you send out projectiles, in our case fireballs. These behave differently depending on which of the four main buttons you press: if you press the A button, they fly in a curve towards the upper right part of the screen, if you push the Y button, they go left and down and so on and so forth. Sadly, they move so slowly your opponent has a good three seconds to get out of the way, and in so weird curves that aiming is impossible. Also, the screen constantly twists in all directions.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d0fb248e-5f22-4df1-83d1-056d24a631d6.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/46b55e2f-c2bb-4257-b5e8-8b2e73e606de.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0bf7061a-dfa5-4b05-b13a-25ab7263fe5d.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/175db48c-322d-44e2-b900-7f2a9fdc122a.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a2d3026f-21bf-402f-add9-f3df0268fe3b.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e00f5ba5-b9f1-445c-b746-9561fe37c84c.jpg</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Cobra Team</Publisher>
</game>