<Game>
	<Name>Battletoads in Battlemaniacs (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Battletoads in Battlemaniacs is the first  SNES release of the popular  Battletoads series, continuing the trend of ludicrous humor and storylines, coupled with brutal difficulty established by its predecessor,  Battletoads. The traditional  side-scrolling beat 'em up gameplay mechanics are retained, as are occasional off-beat action sequences like the speeder bike chase.Continuing the ludicrous story from the original game, Battlemaniacs sees Rash and Pimple sucked into an virtual world of Professor T. Bird's virtual reality machine T.R.I.P.S. (Total Reality Integrated Playing System) and setting out to rescue the kidnapped daughter of the CEO that sponsored Professor T. Bird's project as well as their fearless leader Zitz.Battlemaniacs was to receive a Master System port in Europe on July 1994, but it was cancelled last second. This port was eventually released in Brazil by Tec Toy, though the quality of the build was far from finished.			</plot>
	<releasedate>20/6/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Tradewest, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>WjzP6u6ayjc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1606</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563520-battletoads-in-battlemaniacs</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/battletoads-in-battlemaniacs</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/battletoads-in-battlemaniacs/3030-19860/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/xQ8qFwx.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Ruxg86B.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/YfXLzRY.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/S5ObsJv.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/3gISWjP.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/GHiz1jy.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/31FQVJi.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/DzgY8Yg.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6JBlOrq.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/9MO6Bne.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/fZF2lgm.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/oO3SmIO.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/GQ9dgPP.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/TtRLEX5.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/xQybAQy.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/fK457cO.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/WYtpl3N.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/pNE1Iwe.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/4xP7jWa.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>When Machiko Tashoku, the daughter of the Pscane Corporation's head honcho, is abducted by the Pigs of the Apocalypse and forced indignantly into the Gamescape, Zitz leaps into the action fists-a flain! But Even for a Battletoad there's too much pork to pummel - and after a beastly bashing, he jains Machiko as the Parkers' prisoner! Rash and Pimple are soon to soar on the scene - an' with Rash lookin' lean an' green and Pimple actin' mean, it's obvious that a rescue's about to begin! Only it ain't gonna be seay, 'cuz the pigs have taken them to the dingy Dark Tower, home of the sinister Silas Volkmire and his equally evil partner, the deadly Dark Queen! Their malevolent minds have found a way to leak their computerized world into ours, with the fiendish intention of creating a worldwide Gamescape over which they would rule!</Notes>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/786ed1e6-19c8-4a9e-ac7e-a7ea00202458.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a0cfe284-cf69-4d71-a5d6-68922ec2642e.png</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e7a4c885-9baa-4530-981a-eb6362992587.png</boxart9>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c74064bb-c31e-41f5-86bd-f85172e59146.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e2f746c6-b280-451b-9f1f-f73a8c7daade.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Tradewest</Publisher>
</game>