<Game>
	<Name>Battle Cars (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Battle Cars takes place in the 22nd century.  In the century beforehand, the Greenhouse Effect has taken a toll on the world, the polar ice caps have melted, causing countries to begin to go underwater, as a result, battles for territory become more fierce, causing confrontations to become nuclear, forever altering the landscape.You are a rookie driver, in the new blood sport known as Battle Cars, held by the IBCA (International Battle Cars Association) and your goal is to qualify for each race then take out your rivals and eventually face the top driver of that circuit in a final fight for supremacy.There are nine levels in all, each with their own unique boss and the ability to upgrade your car and weapons.  The game resembles F-Zero in a way of gameplay, but the cars are more modeled after Formula One cars.Cheat: Code - Alternate Car ColorHighlight a car at the selection screen then press A + Select + Start. You will now be able to choose a color for your car.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>1709</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588210-battle-cars</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/battle-cars</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/battle-cars/3030-12364/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XTnB3jl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/7QKjszb.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/s0WBuzl.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/CHxwtup.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/RYoKHGw.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/1GrfxVV.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/zrwm3Ng.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/jwXC5Zp.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/5d63tHz.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/q4nBaM1.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/qyV7BG5.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/iNMpy7S.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/VyKImUp.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/vlkiSfw.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KUdb4qA.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/O1JeZ6h.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The start of the 22nd century saw a true new world order. Survivors of the devastation lived in city states. Technology sophisticated and jaded by years of war the people demanded a new sport for their new age....Battle Cars...technology...aggression...Battle Cars. Afforded the same popularity earlier cultures had given artists or pop musicians, Battle Car drivers are heroes. Their only rule is to win.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/46347341-5d3d-4da9-8efc-4385cadacad9.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b1e61510-0fb8-4e45-acb3-4b48c35e4d4d.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>