<Game>
	<Name>Battle Pinball (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Battle Pinball is a Pinball game, published by Banpresto, which was released in Japan in 1995.Tips:Configuration MenuAt the title screen, enter the following code: Down, Down, Down, A, Y, Select, Select. This will open a configuration screen where you can adjust the 'extend' and 'ball' settings.http://www.gamefaqs.com/console/snes/home/571233.htmlCheat: Configuration MenuAt the title screen, enter the following code: Down, Down, Down, A, Y, Select, Select. This will open a configuration screen where you can adjust the "extend" and "ball" settings.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Pinball</genre>
	<Developer>Banpresto</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>10.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>5HFcPMuGPVM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>25943</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571233-battle-pinball</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/battle-pinball/3030-37946/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/f1d2pZ1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/6ip1YkR.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/sFf02e2.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/UUVJBHD.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/OnARJWq.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/S9k7yCC.jpg</snapshot4>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/n0RAWgp.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/VUi9O9H.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Battle Pinball is a multi-table pinball game exclusive for the Super Famicom and part of Banpresto's "Compati Hero Series" that brings together the licenses for Ultraman, Kamen Rider and Gundam. As with other games in the series, all the characters have been super-deformed to normalize the heights of the differently-sized heroes. The game contains four tables, each themed to a different hero: Kamen Rider, who fights in dusty wastelands with a number of his recurring enemies; Ultraman, who fights in a city against various kaiju; Knight Gundam, who fights in space; and Banpresto's own original character Fighter Roar, whose stage is set under the ocean. Each table also has three screens, each with their own set of paddles, and the player attempts to earn highscores from the various features on each table.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c8d55d56-a5e5-4f3b-b78e-7256528f271c.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98ee3208-07d4-46a8-a31a-5392aa1bea7d.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Banpresto</Publisher>
</game>