<Game>
	<Name>Bebe's Kids (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This side-scrolling beat em' up game is based on a 1992 Paramount Pictures animated movie which was the first ever to feature an all-Black main cast. The characters were originally from comedian Robin Harris' "Bb's Kids" (pronounced Bay-Bay) stand-up comedy act. They're described as little hellions and bad-ass troublemaker kids.  In this game, someone has taken control of the Fun World amusement park, and you've got to help Kahlil, LaShawn, and PeeWee make things right. You can play as either Kahlil or LaShawn and can use each character's different special attacks. Kahlil uses a spin-tuck to take out almost any enemy you meet and LaShawn uses powerful cartwheels. Enemies such as animatronic robots and security guards must be taken out in the first time-limited level.  Some items can also be picked up and thrown at enemies.   The second level has the baby PeeWee in a china shop knocking glasses off shelves and you must break 10 before they hit you or the ground or are grabbed by your caretaker Robin.  There is also a haunted house maze level where you must keep trying different doors until you find the exitwhile avoiding mummies along the way. Then there's a pirate ship beat em' up level and eventually you make your way to the underground control center and the Big Boss.Cheat: Developers Debug CodeAt the Paramount Pictures logo, press Up, Down, X, R, A, Y, B, A, B, Y.The game will immediately start as well as place photos of the development team through various spots in the game. This also unlocks some in-game cheats. Hold Select and press Left to clear all enemies.  Hold Select and press Down to go back a room. Holding Select and pressing Up goes up a room.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Motown Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>G-ROMm8tHYU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1713</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588216-bebes-kids</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/bebes-kids</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bebes-kids/3030-5173/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/2YtiJzf.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/WvY8zXg.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/PD5ZLw6.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Z256a8l.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wo5mE2R.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/0Tajq5L.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ex6LdwH.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SMCt3qA.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/tjsuNPj.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Z9pjiGz.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/haPSIAg.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/dfQNXrI.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/WaGXZ5O.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/7av7riA.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ke6rVtP.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/KOryrB8.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>They're rough, they're tough, they're Bebe's Kids! Enter the comical world of Robin Harris' Bebe's Kids! Join Kahlil, LaShawn, and Pee Wee on an adventure like no other. Someone has taken over Fun World, and it's up to Bebe's Kid's to make things right. Strange happenings at the amusement park require investigating by a couple of tough kids. Kahlil, with his amazing spin-tuck, and LaShawn with her devastating cartwheels are ready for anything! They better be! Animatronic robots and security guards are looking for the feisty kids. Kahlil and LaShawn have to make their way past these android threats to the Underground headquarters of the master robot in the final battle for the freedom of Fun World! Play as either Kahlil or LaShawn for an entire adventure! Do cartwheels, spin-kicks, and super punches to stop the enemies! Collect items to launch multiple long-range attacks! All the humor from the hit movie is now a video game sensation!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a978edc2-a1bc-4645-8ba2-8bb74e477524.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c16f6fa2-1621-4616-81b4-05335e7742dd.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Motown Games</Publisher>
</game>