<Game>
	<Name>Beethoven - The Ultimate Canine Caper! (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Beethoven: The Ultimate Canine Caper is a side-scrolling platformer, based on the 1993 movie sequel Beethoven's 2nd (the game's title screen refers to the game as such as well). Each level challenges the player to rescue one of Beethoven and Missy's puppies, and is divided into 2 stages each. In the first stage the objective is to get to the puppy while in the second, Beethoven must carry the puppy back to Missy.Beethoven was released for the Super Nintendo and PC by Hi-Tech Expressions. Rozner Labs Software Group developed the DOS version, while the SNES version was handled by Riedel Software Productions (or RSP) Inc. A Game Boy port released the following year was developed by Unexpected Development.Gameplay:Beethoven's main attack is his loud barking, which releases supersonic waves that can devastate man or beast. Barks can be "charged" by growling, resulting in even greater destructive power. Beethoven can also shake water off of his body, once soaked by a sprinkler or other water fixture, in order to hurt enemies.						</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>RSP</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>Thp-xh68VvE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1575</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588217-beethoven-the-ultimate-canine-caper</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/beethovens-2nd</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/beethoven-the-ultimate-canine-caper/3030-9801/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/5f1JRzK.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/G7xNFv4.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/pZ2vRpY.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wc4T2sK.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/pIanKHQ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/6LDqSDd.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/4aku8Rd.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/5101Lq9.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/scloDfp.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/vSg9U2M.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/R0WBR5s.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/1EHKBa4.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/KJmJNHC.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vSDMDNM.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/roqONJa.png</clearlogo1>
</game>