<Game>
	<Name>Biker Mice from Mars (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Biker Mice From Mars is an isometric racing game based on the 1990s cartoon of the same name. Three anthropomorphic mice from Mars (who happen to be bikers) escape to Earth after their home planet is conquered by the fish-like Plutarkians and help the citizens of Earth to avoid the same fate.This Super Nintendo game from Konami is a racing game with vehicular combat that pits the trio of Biker Mice - Throttle, Modo and Vinnie - against several of their recurring enemies: Greasepit, Dr. Karbunkle and Lawrence Limburger. Each character has their own distribution of three core stats: Max speed, grip (handling) and acceleration. It uses an isometric perspective and plays similarly to Rare's RC Pro-Am or Blizzard's Rock N' Roll Racing.When the animated TV show was rebooted in 2006 it saw equivalent video game adaptations for the Nintendo DS and PlayStation 2. Those games should not be mistaken for this one.Cheat: Max Upgrade PasswordsStart in round 1 with all upgrades maxed, on hard or super hard, with specific characters.Cheat: Extra boost of speedWhile running in any type of race, you can rapidly press the B button to gain a boost of energy that is similar to a nitro.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Konami (America), Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>JGXN8t5T0Nk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1520</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588219-biker-mice-from-mars</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/biker-mice-from-mars</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/biker-mice-from-mars/3030-9842/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/FomWRar.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mOdLuIy.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/DnClmsx.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/8miJdpO.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/q6ivMLW.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/TvYP0yx.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lVsIKB3.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/02CJFK8.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/YlikSwC.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/9DA8CqJ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IA4wi3w.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/0S7Mn7C.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/bidyrsz.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/azqZc0k.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/BnGXPzI.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/QjnvPAD.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/7ToRK1K.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/xdVKi9o.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/gbg7I55.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The fish-faced Plutarkians have devastated Mars--the home planet of Throttle, Vinnie and Modo. These three rebel rodents escaped the mayhem and landed in Chicago, only to find that Limburger, the Plutarkian Leader, set Earth as his next target! No "rescue the kidnapped victim" No phony plots and no unbelievable story lines -- just hard core racing that'll get your blood pumpin' and make the sweat gush out of your pits! You can play in PRACTICE mode, try the MAIN RACE, or tackle the brutal BATTLE RACE. No "mission to save the Earth" Rev up your bike and get ready for some real heavy metal, "no holds barred" racing thrills. The cool 3-D perspective adds tension to every turn in the track. You never know what lies ahead of you -- or who is coming up from behind! Use turbo jumps, thundering wheelies and other powerful moves to win prize money. Take your cash to Charley's Race Shop to upgrade your bike and dominate all! And definitely no wimps! Take the role of one of the heroic Biker Mice -- or go the nasty route and pick the big cheese Limburger, the overlubed Greasepit or the diabolical Dr. Karbunkle. They all have different abilities, speeds, and oh yeah... WEAPONS! The streets aren't safe for long...</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/76fe2438-59b8-4966-9eba-acf8bedbc723.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a6a32aff-96e5-4f18-b8c4-c4c4b45cc361.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c6e79867-7818-40ec-bfe3-4fffc0bfec67.png</boxart7>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d3c76783-4a37-4109-a763-1d488cebfd94.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>