<Game>
	<Name>Bing Bing! Bingo (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bing Bing! Bingo is a bingo- and gambling-focused mini-game collection that allows the player to play four different variations on the conventional game of bingo, as well as three additional mini-games.The Bingo games include a slot machine, which randomly spits out a random number; a pirate ship cannon, which also spits out a random number but players can narrow it down to a band of numbers (each row is color-coded); Mode-7 skydiving where players can land on the numbers they want with a little skill; and the game's Amidar-themed (the game namedrops the Konami Arcade classic) bingo game features Santa Claus as the game was released a few days before Christmas, and players select a route for him to follow to the bottom of the screen.The three other mini-games are arm wrestling which requires mashing the button, whack-a-creature with a harisen that uses all four face buttons, and the equestrian sport of horseracing where players can bet money on the outcome of races.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>Copya Systems</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581956-bing-bing-bingo</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bing-bing-bingo/3030-37831/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/cQshbJc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/gKxc5mG.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/QFGNqVp.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/jwwc8di.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/4Si8vDS.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/7Qn9VGL.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/0oQAcxO.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/HLhyAtU.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/clKM4Uk.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/gefnXFx.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/yCjtNu7.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/esdKykO.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/p6oHlek.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The basic concept of Bing Bing! Bingo is that the player is on a vacation to a private island somewhere in the world that is known for their Bingo-oriented lifestyle. He can either play Bingo through a slot machine, while skydiving, aplay a game of Bingo with Santa Claus, and an option to play Bingo on a pirate ship. There is also arm wrestling and a mode where players get to make imaginary wagers on the horses in case the player does not like Bingo. However, the numbers are announced in Japanese rather than English, so knowledge of Japanese numbers is vital for multiplayer action. Full card Bingo is mandatory for single player games but party games can use any variation of Bingo that the players consent to. A party mode is present for two players.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5272d09b-91a1-46d5-b4d8-ad759a246a74.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a5637bc1-d6b7-47df-8ea3-d023e2c799ee.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f44e8a76-3a2e-4ee9-b8ac-7d2b2385a06c.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>KSS</Publisher>
</game>