<Game>
	<Name>Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon S - Kondo wa Puzzle de Oshioki yo! (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon S: Kondo wa Puzzle de Oshioki yo!! ("Pretty Soldier Sailor Moon S: Now It's Puzzle Punishment Time!!") is a puzzle game from Tom Create and published by Bandai. It uses the Sailor Moon anime/manga license and allows the player to play as any of the Sailor Moon soldiers (besides Saturn) or as Tuxedo Mask.The goal of the game is to remove all the bricks from the playing field. Clicking on a block removes it and every block of the same color that is sitting adjacent (the player cannot remove a block if it is by itself). There are also special icons that, once moved to the bottom of the grid, can be used to clear blocks or otherwise make it easier to clear them. In multiplayer, removing a lot of bricks in one click will drop junk on the other player. Junk blocks cannot be removed directly, but will be removed along with colored bricks if adjacent.The game has single-player, single-player versus computer and two-player competitive modes. It was never released outside of Japan.		</plot>
	<releasedate>15/7/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Tom Create</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>28786</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/580009-bishoujo-senshi-sailor-moon-s-kondo-wa-puzzle-de</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/bishjo-senshi-sailor-moon-s-kondo-wa-puzzle-de-oshioki-yo</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bishoujo-senshi-sailor-moon-s-kondo-wa-puzzle-de-o/3030-13917/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/hkjnwoc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9zSsUuZ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/LCCXW3O.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6ThO3xa.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/py4n52B.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/CSffvsO.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/W1p99vP.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/6pmy6ZU.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/sxJz2Xq.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/wZd8HA9.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/SWXWQFg.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/kPrHrcE.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/bkFKeRd.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The Sailors try to find Princess Serenity, who was lost a long time ago fighting the forces of evil in the Moon Kingdom. The Negaverse are trying to go back in time to rule the Moon Kingdom as well, so time is not on your side.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9a98e9bd-ac8f-438e-b836-00d5c6b794ef.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23d64746-68a8-4220-9f6e-9160c1e25299.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>