<Game>
	<Name>Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon S - Jougai Rantou! Shuyaku Soudatsusen (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon S: Jougai Rantou!? Shuyaku Soudatsusen ("Pretty Soldier Sailor Moon S: Out-of-Bounds Brawl!? Protagonist Competition") is a fighting game published by Angel for the Super Famicom platform. The developer is unknown, though Arc System Works has been linked to the game due to various ASW staff members in the game's credits.The plot of the game concerns a contest to determine the leader (or "protagonist") of the Sailor Senshi team. Every Sailor Senshi, besides Sailor Saturn, is available as a playable character in the versus mode. Sailor Uranus, Sailor Pluto and Sailor Neptune are not available in the single-player story mode, though they do show up as opponents. The player, as their chosen character, simply has to defeat the other eight characters to win.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Angel</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>22761</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/580007-bishoujo-senshi-sailor-moon-s</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/bishjo-senshi-sailor-moon-s-jgai-rant-shuyaku-sdatsusen</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bishoujo-senshi-sailor-moon-s-jougai-rantou-shuyak/3030-14008/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/JzdZZFp.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/pWUuMqm.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/gXNm00I.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/a7xl2RD.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/rsxCKxH.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/F8Hy7s5.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/3qZ30hP.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/NUSCVMq.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/71ETyVI.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/EDvlUv8.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/cBlEUHL.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Ua0xKIO.gif</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/vIdW0v5.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The Sailor Senshi are fighting to choose a new leader. After defeating an enemy, Sailor Moon was teased by Sailor Chibi Moon and Sailor Mars, who called her undependable. The rest of the Sailor Senshi then decided to have a contest to choose a new leader.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0e9da492-061d-4e3f-a3f1-68fc2d6f6a3d.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/06b0f525-d6d0-42a7-a4f5-1a0d38aef34c.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>