<Game>
	<Name>Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon SuperS - Zenin Sanka!! Shuyaku Soudatsusen (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The game is based on the manga/anim series Sailor Moon. It tells the story of Pretty Sailor Fighters, teenage girls who were summoned to protect the futuristic Moon Kingdom and to fight the forces of darkness, led by the evil Queen Beryl and Prince Diamond. The main heroine is a girl named Tsukino Usagi, who was contacted by the magical talking cat Luna to become Sailor Moon, the leader of the group.This fighting game is an enhanced version of  Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon S: Jougai Ranto!? Shuyaku Soudatsusen. Girls compete against each other in tournament mode, story mode, player-vs.-computer mode, and two players mode. They can use physical attacks and magical spells. In story mode you can also upgrade your fighter's attributes (strength, defense power, etc.) New in this expanded version: additional playable characters (hence the title Zen'in Sanka - "Everyone Participates"), different scenes in story mode, additional backgrounds for battles.Cheat: Customized GameFinish Story Mode as any Senshi and you'll have the game customized for her. For instance, if you finish the game as Sailor Chibimoon, you'll have her saying something in the Intro screen, and her transformation pen as the cursor in the Menu.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/3/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Angel</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>mh2CirS-L7s</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>28683</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575571-bishoujo-senshi-sailor-moon-super-s-shuyaku</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/bishjo-senshi-sailor-moon-super-s-zenin-sanka-shuyaku-sdatsusen</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bishoujo-senshi-sailor-moon-super-s-zenin-sanka-sh/3030-5774/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/PTkgqiw.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/REpMmpn.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/jVehhwy.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/si0FC8u.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/pjpGH9F.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/PSorumd.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/saodSdD.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Y3BMlre.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/r4WKvUu.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/d97yA4g.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/QAINbfA.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/VGBzWgr.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Vdm2V4M.gif</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ZsYek4c.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>This game is the sequel and an update to Sailor Moon S: Jougai Rantou!? Shuyaku Soudatsusen. The Sailor Senshi are fighting to choose a new leader. After defeating an enemy, Sailor Moon was teased by Sailor Chibi Moon and Sailor Mars, who called her undependable. The rest of the Sailor Senshi then decided to have a contest to choose a new leader. This game is based on the popular Anime series "Sailor Moon" and was released only for the japanese Super Famicom.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c66fb551-024a-4fc7-b794-97a52a488417.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/57cc3d5f-e71a-4fbd-b6a9-9461f3d9e095.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Angel (BANDAI)</Publisher>
</game>