<Game>
	<Name>Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon - Another Story (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Sailor Moon: Another Story is a Japanese RPG released in 1995 for the Super Famicom. One of many games developed for the franchise on the SNES platform, it is the only one out those not directly based on any particular season of the anime television show. As the name suggests, the game presents itself as a side story. Though it does feature cameos and references involving characters from seasons 1 and 2, the events in this game aren't tied to Sailor Moon cannon. Like many games in the series, it was never localized or ported to any other platform. This led to a community effort to create a successful fan translation of the game for the use in software emulation.Gameplay:Another Story fits the build as a Japanese rpg. Random encounters and turn based battles give it that playing field of SNES era games such as    Final Fantasy. An interesting twist on combat was the ability to combine the abilities of any two Sailor Scouts to pull of devastating attacks using each characters signature moves taken directly from the show, similar to the combo system of  Chrono Trigger.When you aren't in battle, Another Story features a nicely designed 2D world to explore with Non-playable characters abound to talk to. The game also features numerous cut-scenes and written dialogue moments for character and plot developments which also play out in similar fashion to    Final Fantasy.			</plot>
	<releasedate>22/9/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Angel (Bandai)</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>UPB6uoAjWxM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18726</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588640-bishoujo-senshi-sailor-moon-another-story</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/bishjo-senshi-sailor-moon-another-story</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bishoujo-senshi-sailor-moon-another-story/3030-3526/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Sailor_Moon_video_games#Bishoujo_Senshi_Sailor_Moon:_Another_Story_.28Angel.29_1995</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/CLdb2nf.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/17ZIInQ.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/MjyuLlp.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/kYoJydh.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/vL3pokn.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/e7D1Zrw.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/E2dKW6V.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/UHCheii.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ptWsE3S.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4NXbK22.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BJW3Ovz.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/cGRltnt.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/YFhEJ3y.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/AV8uyZR.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/BysFJ7I.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/RyqjL9C.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In the future Crystal Tokyo, a small band of discontent citizens have come together to form an rebel team of Senshi called the Oppositio Senshi, who feel that the Sailor Senshi and the Silver Crystal are the source of all of Earth's past battles. Together with a mysterious woman named Apsu, they desire to twist time and change the destiny of the Earth. In the present day, the Sailor Senshi are enjoying peace now that the Death Busters have been defeated. However, strange things begin happening in the city. Previously defeated Daimons, Droids and Youma appear throughout the city. A visit by Ryo Urawa reveals a cryptic statement that the past and future are being replaced. Rei sees strange apparitions in the fire, and then the four Inner Senshi, along with Chibiusa go missing. Sailor Moon meets up with Uranus, Neptune, and Saturn to go look for the missing Senshi.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aec50514-6ae0-47bd-8475-f6cf261fdd5a.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f8d8891f-3c78-455f-a745-e20fc6d4935d.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7b643fac-e96d-42dd-b9fb-0d07fba09691.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/946073bd-d030-4a3f-ae11-ae1167f4364d.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/291ca6b9-819e-4058-a0c9-99faf9b0bba5.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>