<Game>
	<Name>Boogerman - A Pick and Flick Adventure (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Boogerman: A Pick and Flick Adventure is an action platformer that was initially released for Sega Genesis and SNES. Players control Snotty Ragsdale, an eccentric millionaire with a curious mind. Players burp, flick, fart, and spit their way through the dimension of X Crement. The game takes place in 5 different worlds of unique and disgusting themes; each world ends with a boss fight.Story:On a dark and stormy night Professor Stinkbaum has built a device to rid the world of pollution. This device gets rid of pollution by transexisting it to another dimension that goes by the name of X Crement. Snotty Ragsdale (Boogerman) is an eccentric millionaire who takes a job at Stinkbaum's lab in order to see what is really happening to all the pollution. On this particular night Ragsdale disrupts the machine by sneezing on the crystal that makes the whole thing work. A large hand comes out of the machine and takes the crystal back to dimension X Crement. Ragsdale is left with only one option - He heads into the men's room and comes back out as Boogerman. Following the hand, he finds himself on a quest to save the world.Worlds/BossesWorld 1: Flatulent Swamps -- Boss: HickmanWorld 2: The Pits -- Boss: RevoltaWorld 3: Boogerville -- Boss: Fly BoyWorld 4: Mucous Mountains and Nasal Caverns -- Boss: Deodor AntWorld 5: Pus Palace -- Boss: Boogermeister</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Interplay Entertainment Corp.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>TgfKcr1ujHE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1717</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588226-boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/boogerman-a-pick-and-flick-adventure/3030-16717/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/PJ8c1SH.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/IxBEkmD.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/F77YsGW.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6GDcg7k.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/4TxkWgD.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/mZE5hVq.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/xlM2src.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/eXouT8J.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/heyZCMM.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MrJ5gDX.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/7xdxxUP.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/PsekSeQ.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/WK5o8cd.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/l7FOYL8.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Yc6GJHR.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>He thinks he's a hero, but he's snot! He's mean. He's green. And he nose how to pick a fight! He's BOOGERMAN, as slick as he is deep, and he's on a pick 'n' flick adventure to save the world. He's stretched to the limit of blowing away the vile slimebags who are bent on sticking it to Planet Earth, any way, every way, and everywhere they can. You're his first pick to help him rescue the whole world before it's flushed down the toilet. Join the flick-or-be-flicked race to pull the plug on the Booger Meister and his gang of filthy stinkers who aren't afraid to fight dirty... because yours is the only finger which can wipe 'em out!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9d3a146-5c77-4b0a-bcbc-8026700f6e3f.png</banner2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f05bbba1-a698-4bc2-b094-76400aa5e340.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7378c957-1505-4f34-8e5b-567a3f0376c9.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/90d76baa-9b21-4451-a6c5-3b995a45bd66.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c26dfee6-d9c4-42d4-b5d6-7140b7a890be.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Interplay</Publisher>
</game>