<Game>
	<Name>Brandish (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Once there was a prosperous kingdom, which was protected by a tower, where a mighty dragon was living. The people of the kingdom were secure with such a guardian. But one man wanted the dragon's power for something else, and this man was the king. He went to the tower and tried to kill the dragon, in order to rob his power. But the dragon's fury turned the king into a horrible creature, a demon, and his evil essence made his entire kingdom sink deep under the earth. Many years have passed, and now you take control of a traveler named Varik (Ares in the Japanese version). A young woman accuses him of killing her teacher, and in a desperate fight they both fall underground, to where the lost kingdom was buried. You must guide Varik through underground mazes and help him to escape the wrath of his adversary and the demonic inhabitants of the lost kingdom.The game is an action RPG, a dungeon crawler with plenty of creatures to defeat and many weapons, armor, and other treasure to collect. You can also use magic spells. The camera rotates automatically according to your movements. You also have the ability to jump forwards.Cheat: Alternate EndingInstead of helping Alexis fight him for an alternate ending.Cheat: Alternate EndingFor an easy health refill: tap L+R at the same time-the screen will go black and your HP will slowly refill.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/2/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>KOEI Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>vAEQXPoQ0vE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1723</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588228-brandish</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/brandish</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/brandish/3030-10487/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/BGVGt2t.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/4ATuV8m.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/8dWtO5e.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/P6sZTKy.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/dl6MWDT.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/CX3FFEr.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Mvn3tXL.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/SAHp1wl.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wPb70Yb.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xz7eZZY.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/iOkxFwC.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/EtLQEUb.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/xMtLcoc.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/PZYAZO3.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/hxbLkWn.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/dbzqZ5o.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Zu0gd3c.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/yfU1ZOb.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/x2BBCDQ.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/4YgFdex.png</clearlogo1>
</game>