<Game>
	<Name>Brawl Brothers (USA)</Name>
	<plot>A classic 2-player scrolling beat 'em up is back on the Virtual Console service! People are going missing in Bayside City and the rumors say someone conducting a shady human cloning experiment is responsible. For Rick (a.k.a. Hack) and Doug (a.k.a. Slash) this situation has become personal. Especially after three friends from their martial arts gym get abducted. The duo set off to the enemy's secret air fortress to sort this out. These guys know all the moves, from martial arts to pro wrestling throws, and they don't hesitate to use them. They&#8217;re not afraid of using knives, bats, and other things they find to get the job done. And if that wasn&#8217;t enough, when they get hurt they get angry&#8212;and you really don&#8217;t want to mess with them then. They ignore damage and hit even harder than usual! They&#8217;re ready for the action. The question is: are you?Cheat: CodesDuring the character select screen press and hold the following:Down+L+R and select your character. You now have access to all your hidden special attacks and desperation attack.Cheat: CodesConstantly press B,A,X, and Y during the Jaleco logo until you reach the title screen. When successful you'll reach a black screen. It is actually the title screen. Press start once and then press up once to move to the options because you cannot see the screen properly. When you exit from the options the game will now change to "Brawl Brothers".Cheat: CodesTo play as the easier Japanese version, sequentially and repeatedly press B, A, X, Y at the white screen with the Jaleco logo until it disappears. If done right, you'll arrive at a glitched screen. Now, press Start, then Down three times and Start again. You'll be at the options screen and when you exit, you'll see the Japanese title screen. Now start your game and enjoy the original version of the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>gEJG996HfO0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1523</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588229-brawl-brothers</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/brawl-brothers</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/brawl-brothers/3030-10488/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/d5oNokY.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/0OsjnNz.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/2FpHwmK.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/zgKOMoT.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/K7zzGx2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6BBpyFX.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/cSSj9ky.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/7EWDonE.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/58vVLHc.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/OM2Orvd.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6itWj3z.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/P4kM60a.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/mSIsPJo.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Za3JNuW.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/iytJz3m.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/HVEveT5.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>DOUBLE TROUBLE STREET FIGHTING ACTION! Fists and feet fly as the Brawl Brothers hit the streets in this explosive two player simultaneous fighting game. Score with the thunderous action of body slams, leg sweeps, jabs, hooks uppercuts, punching, kicking and more. Defeat the enemy and take over his role. Brawl Brothers features 10 realistic stages and three levels of difficulty. Blow-by-blow, Brawl Brothers packs a tremendous punch of realistic action. Take your best shot now!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1cf1eb5f-0b8b-452c-93bc-d1a3df0a9c58.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e4d545fc-32bf-43e1-83bd-df3338795cbf.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e4b93bc0-f80c-48e2-b8e4-33374a44b79a.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b98ff926-916b-4dd6-80fe-56ac8c22a2b6.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cc4a8078-5b8b-4cb4-bad6-83bcc5ad8132.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4b1f1ca0-4088-4e27-a33d-137109694de3.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f18d29aa-a4af-4cdd-bff8-0636ef95fcc0.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/43ebadcb-7c11-4fbe-9b72-43f3076094ae.jpg</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Jaleco</Publisher>
</game>