<Game>
	<Name>Breath of Fire (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Breath of Fire was originally developed and released by Capcom in Japan in 1993 for the SNES, and a year later licensed by Squaresoft for release in North America. It was Capcom's first foray into the role-playing genre. The game was mostly well-received by critics, but was criticized for its linear story progression and frequent random enemy encounters.Capcom later released a GBA remake in 2001 that included some minor additions and tweaks to the game. Among these additions were new character portraits, new additional illustrated cutscenes, the ability to dash, and tweaks to the overall difficulty of the game. Players could also swap items between their inventories with the use of a game link cable.Story:Spurned by the evil goddess Tyr, the Light Dragon Clan and the Dark Dragon Clan had been at war for eons, destroying the land they once governed together. Out of the war-torn people arose a young hero and his seven companions. On a treacherous journey, they managed to capture Mila and seal her away in a dungeon locked with six keys. A fragile peace has since returned to the lands as the Light Dragons work to resolve differences with the Dark Dragons. Will the forces of Light and Dark return peace to the land, or will history repeat itself? Join Ryu and his companions as the future of the Dragon Clan unfolds.Main CharactersRyuRyuThe hero of this game. He is a boy from the light Dragon clan who lives with his sister Sara. But his sister get kidnapped and it's Ryu to the rescue. A version of Ryu would go on to appear in every subsequent Breath of Fire game. NinaNinaNina's Bird form.A princess of a foreign kingdom of winged people. She is skilled at using healing magic.Later in the game she learns to transform into a Giant bird and is able to carry the party long distances. Nina is the other recurring character in the series.BoBoA solitary wolf man who is a very skilled hunter.KarnKarnA master thief who is very agile.GobiGobi's fish form.GobiA fish man who is quite greedy. Later in the game can change into a giant fish and can carry the party around to new places.OxOxAn ox man who has been forced into labor by the Dark Dragon clan.BleuBleuAn immortal sorceress with the lower body of a snake. She was the one who sealed Tyr away.MoguMoguA mole man who tries to stand up for his people .VillainsZogEvil Emperor ZogThe evil ruler of the Dark Dragon clan. He wishes to release the Goddess Tyr.JadeLieutenant JadeZog's top lieutenant who is the also the one who kidnapped Ryu's sister.TyrGoddess Tyr in disguiseThe Goddess Tyr's True FormAn ancient Goddess who started the Goddess War. It is said that she can grant wishes. She shows herself to Ryu in the form of a little girl.Her true form however eventually shows through.Cheat: Chun-Li in Breath of FireTo see a cameo of Chun-Li from Street Fighter, go to the town Bleak. Go to the magician kid's house and talk to him. He will say to put 100 GP on the table and he will make them disappear. When he asks you this, say ''yes.'' When he says ''look behind you'' say ''no'' twice then yes. It'll show Chun-Li in a room doing her famous ''Lightning Kick.''</plot>
	<releasedate>10/8/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Square Soft, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>oxmU6rURGvo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>869</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563529-breath-of-fire</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/breath-of-fire</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/breath-of-fire/3030-15629/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/RxHVm3d.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/zJ22cPR.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/NILuL2L.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/rDjEoij.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/NaCDSw2.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/MkXIylq.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/N7n6JxM.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/seYrgcw.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/IQRhRhF.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/orP6gTV.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/cWKLuMV.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/YtUgoYx.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/a7VLAUA.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/2C49iRZ.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/MYea4LK.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/F6FuFjD.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/jYRBpZp.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/3Gx9Vp7.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/LlTaD4Q.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/cbQVpXk.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/bqUpz4U.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>In a distant land, peace was maintained for thousands of years by a fearful dragon clan who could transform into powerful monsters. One day they discovered a goddess who could fulfill their every wish. Greed split the clan into Dark and Light Dragons, each battling the other to win her magic. One member of the Light Dragons, along with seven of his companions, emerged to keep the opposing forces from destroying their world. Using six magical keys, they sealed the goddess into another realm. Centuries have passed. The Dark Dragons are destroying the land in search of the keys. When they find the keys, they will once again release the magic goddess. Light Dragon... the time has come to draw your sword and fight for the future of your people.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>jg9agVIPMhI</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fefc70cb-19d1-4c6d-88d1-d5ac2aee5d43.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/11f4d055-091f-432a-87e0-f1ca3d5d9843.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ce0f3d6-2237-471d-89a7-04f6140447ca.png</boxart8>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ffc1ca85-23b2-4f83-ad65-9fa69b5d3734.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e6834a54-464f-4106-8da9-87a5f642f0e3.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23ee83be-2b69-42b9-ae6d-3a9dae86ed0c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2e125e26-6681-496e-8737-632957aa114b.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0c10ac6b-8837-48e7-a36c-c4b20709de51.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/063bee9b-90af-477e-ae1e-68c820430d84.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/403182d0-996b-475e-8c60-3a7abca1e65d.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/da941d3d-be18-4872-bf87-ba3bbbee7f49.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f78fcb53-6695-42cb-8e2c-6b15582a9998.jpg</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e1666bb2-9882-4705-a220-4affbad6ff7e.jpg</snapshot18>
	<snapshot19>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fca369e6-5363-4484-83a7-66e5f092ab9c.jpg</snapshot19>
	<Publisher>Squaresoft</Publisher>
</game>