<Game>
	<Name>Brett Hull Hockey (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Brett Hull Hockey is a licensed ice hockey game featuring the famous hockey player Brett Hull, who at the time was playing for the St. Louis Blues. The rest of the season rosters for 1994 are also included, as the game is licensed by the NHLPA (National Hockey League Players' Association), but are only referred to by their jersey numbers by the announcer. Like EA's NHL franchise, the game depicts the rink from a vertical perspective. It also makes use of low-res movie clips.Brett Hull Hockey was released on the Super Nintendo and PC MS-DOS in 1994. A Genesis version was planned but canceled. Brett Hull Hockey '95 was an incrementally improved sequel that was released the following year.Cheat: CPUs Goalie DisappearsIn the pause menu, select the Goalie option. Press Right on controller two, and the opponent's goalie option will be "On Bench", though the change isn't seeable. Resume the game and the opponent's goalie won't be there!</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Accolade, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1591</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588231-brett-hull-hockey</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/brett-hull-hockey</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/brett-hull-hockey/3030-22497/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/KEn0Iso.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/xflnUw9.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/1RBG1lw.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/GdEXU99.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/T21PEuG.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/2VmAAJA.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ssLsV2S.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/YZBfXm9.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Id10HyA.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/k3vfypz.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/NSNpMEt.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/YEbTgwi.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ckdkkjq.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/bWJCtUO.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>"Score On These Guys, You're A Hero. Miss It, And You're History." "Playing with the big boys is simple. Take the puck up the ice, throw a deke on the defenseman, and let it go. If you're quick, you'll catch the goalie napping and put in the five hole. In this game, you're playing against all the same players I do. Oates, Lindros, Messier, Modano, Mogilny, Belfour, and McSorley... Guys who skate fast and hit hard. So if you feel like a hero, go for it. But remember. If they catch you with your head down, you're history. - Brett Hull - See Brett Hull and over 600 NHLPA stars in 16 Mega-bit, digitized Mode 7 action. - Use your complete arsenal of slapshots, wrist shots, and full-force body checks. - Hear pro sports announcer Al Michaels call the play-by-play. - Shut 'em down on "D" from a realistic, rink-side perspective. - Spend time in the "Sin Bin" for slashing, cross-checking, holding...all the penalties the refs love to call. - Play a full 84-game season, half season, 11-game short, exhibition, or even a 7-game playoff for the championship. - Go against the computer, against a friend, or in a winner-take-all shootout. - Set up your own lines for scoring and power-plays.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/62f9f5d5-3b03-454f-aa77-04560840120a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/93639543-d333-4b93-b65d-28a2f63ec63e.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Accolade</Publisher>
</game>