<Game>
	<Name>Bronkie the Bronchiasaurus (USA) (En,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Years ago, meteors struck San Saurian, filling the air with thick and filthy dust. So a mighty wind machine was made to help everyone breathe. But Mr. Rexo has stolen the parts for the machine, forcing other dinosaurs to guard the pieces!You must help Bronkie and Rexo find the lost machine pieces by blowing away dust with your lungs, and hitting enemies with your dusters, before the dust returns and everyone chokes on the dust! But don't run into cigarrette smoke or dust storms, otherwise your vision will get darker, and you'll have a hard time finding out where to go, running into enemies all around!Along the way you'll learn about asthma and how to prevent it, as well as how to react if you're suffering from an asthma attack.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, Educational</genre>
	<Developer>Health Hero Network, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>1719</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588233-bronkie-the-bronchiasaurus</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/bronkie-the-bronchiasaurus</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bronkie-the-bronchiasaurus/3030-12535/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/jy6ym9X.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/HTZ51V3.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/KTLgppj.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/dXHTme7.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/SfgzYYC.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/7yBH9es.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xqMfUch.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/PwT6dmT.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/JWUsqtT.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/LqJ2oi4.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Ex2jc4f.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/HcNoZSE.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/mu3dpbl.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/W0gz786.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/06eWzbm.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>A dinomite asthma adventure! Meteors have hit San Saurian and kicked up clouds of trouble. Now it's up to dinosaur friends Bronkie and Trakie, and their sidekicks Sam and Kyla, to clear the air with the mighty wind machine. But first they have to find missing machine parts, dodge dinothugs, and avoid asthma triggers like dust, pollen, cold viruses, and more! Can you help them save their planet and manage their asthma, too? Find out in this breath-boosting Health Hero video game.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fbdc4770-19c8-46f6-b7c8-6d45efc09e1e.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f5ad223f-fc6d-4a88-98e3-0d6e1e5c3918.png</clearlogo2>
	<rating>5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Raya Systems</Publisher>
</game>