<Game>
	<Name>Bubsy in - Claws Encounters of the Furred Kind (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bubsy in: Claws Encounters of the Furred Kind (known in Japan as Yamaneko Bubsy no Daibouken, translated to The Adventures of Bubsy Wildcat) is a 2D platformer developed and published by Accolade for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System and Sega Genesis in 1993. This pun-filled game stars an anthropomorphic wise-cracking bobcat named Bubsy, as he tries to stop enemy aliens (called Woolies) from stealing Earth's supply of yarn balls.The game later spawned a series of platformers (ending with Bubsy 3D). An enhanced version for the PC, titled Super Bubsy, was released in 1995. Super Bubsy contained upscaled graphics, new sound effects, and the unsuccessful pilot episode for the Bubsy animated series.Gameplay:The game plays like a traditional 2D sidescrolling platformer similar to Sonic the Hedgehog. Players run through levels, attempting to reach the end of the level (before the time runs out) while eliminating enemies, gaining score, collecting powerups, and avoiding deadly obstacles. The game includes fifteen main levels (called "chapters") split up into six main areas (ranging from forests to the Wild West) and one final level (set in space).Bubsy has two abilities at his disposal: jumping (by pressing the Jump button) and gliding (by pressing the Glide button). Gliding reduces his downward falling speed, and activating it at the right time before bouncing up allows Bubsy to be propelled much higher than usual.Running into enemies, touching deadly obstacles (such as water, spiked pits), and fall damage can kill Bubsy in one hit (as he has no health system whatsoever). However, jumping or gliding onto enemies can eliminate them (getting them out of Bubsy's way while giving the player score). Due to the difficulty, there are plenty of checkpoints (for Bubsy to respawn at) and extra lives (as if starting with nine lives, like the cat mythology, is easy enough) scattered around levels.Cheat: Debug Mode, Stage Select, Sound Test and Sprite Viewer ModeAt the title screen, enter the "1st Enable Code" sequence. If done right, a fanfare will be heard and the music will get really loud. Now, enter the next three codes one after the other (it's mandatory to enter all the codes). If done right, the music will go back to normal and it will restart each time a code is entered correctly (if you make a mistake, you'll have to start all over again). Now, you can do two things:Cheat: Debug Mode, Stage Select, Sound Test and Sprite Viewer Mode 1) on the title screen, you can press Up or Down on controller 2 to select levels (don't go below level 1 or above 21 or the game will crash), or press Right/Left to select levels in increments of 3. You can also press B to make the computer play the level for you.Cheat: Debug Mode, Stage Select, Sound Test and Sprite Viewer Mode2) start the game and while playing, press R + Select to enable the debug menu. You can use the crosspad to move around the stage, Select or R to move bit by bit, A or Y to increase or decrease the selected item, X to place an object and L to delete an object. Also, while the debug is enabled and after moving around a bit, press L + Select to enable the Sound Test and Sprite Viewer. You can press Up and Down with B or X to play different songs, or press Left and Right with A or Y to play different sound effects.Cheat: Bubsy PasswordsLevel - CodesCheat: Bubsy PasswordsThe Japanese version uses different passwords than the English version, and like the English version not all of them all revealed ingame.Push Select on the title screen to enter the options screen. Select the "Enter password" option and push Select, then use the D-Pad to enter and push Select when finished. The password option will change to display the level number if you entered it right. Push Start to play.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/5/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Accolade, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>kTaA7exWIjU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2232</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563532-bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bubsy-in-claws-encounters-of-the-furred-kind/3030-20205/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/q5u6RJc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/wBZuw5T.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/67z04Rn.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/gBLX6R8.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/SGiVLbm.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/oRpx3U2.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/m63csDk.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/XG9plxY.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/vqEWesu.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/7fUGeWN.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/UK4uCJE.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DQZ6qw7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/poLQQQC.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/paefG8W.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/cRjSWLU.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/rWPHzDm.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/iiPM5nN.png</clearlogo1>
</game>