<Game>
	<Name>Bugs Bunny - Rabbit Rampage (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bugs Bunny Rabbit Rampage is a SNES action platformer, pitting the player as  Bugs Bunny as he fights through traditional Looney Tunes locales and villains in order to confront and defeat the vile animator,  Daffy Duck. The game is based loosely upon the 1955 animated short, Rabbit Rampage, where Bugs is similarly placed at the mercy of an antagonistic animator attempting to annoy and upset him.Levels:Following a traditional action platformer gameplay mechanic, each level is themed around a distinct Looney Tunes cartoon, with the enemies and environments representative of the source material.Level 1.1 Pitting Bugs against his traditional enemy, Elmer Fudd and his hunting dogs, the first level is reminiscent of many classic Looney Tunes cartoons. Taking place in a snowy forest, Bugs must defeat Elmer and his hunting dogs to continue unscathed.Level 2.1Taking place in a saloon bar, this level is based upon the cartoon Drip-Along Daffy. As Bugs attempts to navigate the saloon to approach Nasty Canasta, he must dodge barmen sliding beers down counter-tops, TNT barrels and holes in the floor.Level 400Based on the animated short Bully for Bugs, Bugs is placed in a bull-fighting ring and must square off against Toro the Bull. By dodging the bull's charges and making it run into conveniently-placed targets around the arena, Bugs is able to defeat Toro and proceed.Level 1.3Based around the Bewitched Bunny short, Bugs finds himself in a medieval witches house, being attacked by Witch Hazel and her army of Gingerbread Men. Witch Hazel's magic transforms Bugs into a variety of classic Looney Tunes characters. After successfully evading Witch Hazel, Hansel and Gretel, the Three Little Pigs and The Big Bad Wolf, Bugs is forced to square off against Yosemite Sam, riding a dragon in his full knight costume from the animated short Knighty Knight Bugs.Level 2001Taking place in space on board martian spaceships, Bugs is forced to square off against Instant Martians with Shrink guns,fighting against Marvin the Martian.Level 9.1Taking place in Tasmania, Bugs must square off against native-Australian animal, the Tasmanian Devil. Avoiding his trademark tornado-spin attack, Bugs must combat Taz by forcing him to eat exploding turkeys. After several turkeys have been engorged, Bugs will dress up as a female Tasmanian Devil, which Taz falls in love with. Level "Cube-Root x Divided by y divided by c-z to the power of negative 10 (In symbols)" Taking place within the factory of the ACME corporation, Bugs must fight Wile. E. Coyote and his various armaments and weapons from within the factory. Round 42.379 "And three eighths (In symbols)" Following the storyline of the short Bunny Hugged, Bugs must fight wrestling champion, The Crusher, making him fall into a hole.  Level 13  Based around the idea of the unluckiness of Black Cats, Bugs is forced to navigate a level filled with them. If Bugs touches one, bad luck (in the form of falling piano's) occurs. If Bugs is able to hit one of the many cats with a paintbrush pickup, Pepe Le Pew will show up and remove the cat. At various points in the level, Sylvester appears riding a train Is this trip really necessary?  In the final level, after discovering that Daffy Duck has been animating the entire game, Bugs must spill Daffy's paint canisters so he cannot draw anymore.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/2/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sun Corporation of America</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>p7qyqs_Sf8k</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>278</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588235-bugs-bunny-rabbit-rampage</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/bugs-bunny-rabbit-rampage</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bugs-bunny-rabbit-rampage/3030-11860/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/IXDMDSl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/CE8zZal.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/GD68U9G.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/D6qByPu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/vopQhvL.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/jWoVZgn.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/3Pu5va6.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/AedahiR.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/SxhQXfk.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Kt9EdEF.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MhRLUVh.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/kU2zzNJ.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/4X1x3Jz.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/bAlhli3.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4JUe0EK.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/pxdKTN9.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>"What's up, Doc?" The rip-roaringest, cartoon adventure you've ever seen! It stars Bug Bunny and the rest of your favorite Looney Tunes characters. And you're in control every uproarious minute! The BIGGEST Looney Tunes characters ever in SNES! 12 Megs of awesome animated action! Genuine character voices, orchestrated music and cartoon sound effects! 10 levels of excitement, each a different side-splitting cartoon escapade! Animated exploits abound when a demented cartoonist "paints" Bugs Bunny into every perilous predicament imaginable! Be on the risky end of Elmer Fudd "wabbit" hunt. Then "Draw pardner!" in a showdown with Yosemite Sam. But don't flinch. Because the entire ACME arsenal is at your command. Exploding dog bones, pies in your face, loaded paint brushes and more! Finally coem nose to "beak" with the mystery cartoonist. You're certain to agree: Saturday mornings were never like this!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6ce4efb2-e8d6-49b8-bcbd-9fe709a0ac6e.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d3eef9cf-6d01-4a28-9dd2-5007a378d875.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a4ca59b6-4402-4bfa-b8b8-8e9b268711c3.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c5927438-dcf6-4abe-b6fe-944bd0284910.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/708f1f5c-2d49-466c-a3ea-86aa82572c02.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/272569c4-cef3-4015-927a-862388656bbc.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e70d5896-badb-4103-a1b7-8f2d5d794371.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/03e1b0f9-3e3b-4d8e-8691-f665547c4a75.jpg</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Sunsoft</Publisher>
</game>