<Game>
	<Name>Bust-A-Move (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bust-A-Move is a match three puzzle game developed and published by Taito Corporation for multiple platforms. The game is also known as Puzzle Bobble.Gameplay:The player shoots colored bubbles from the bottom of the screen. The bubbles are released from an arrow in the center of the screen that the player can change the angle of. Bubbles bounce off walls until they make contact with another bubble or the ceiling. When three bubbles of the same color touch they burst and are removed from the game board. If there are now bubbles which are not connected to the ceiling or another bubble those will also be removed from the game board. Bubbles removed in this way are worth more points.A split screen multiplayer match.The game features a single player set of challenge levels, and split screen multiplayer. In multiplayer the players are given identical boards and bubble order. Whenever a player removes four or more bubbles with a single shot extra bubbles are added to his or her opponent's board.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/3/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>2ozV5039m58</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2040</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588237-bust-a-move</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/bust-a-move</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bust-a-move/3030-14228/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Puzzle_Bobble</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/xOxwqLl.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/7bFvzQr.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/M4IHIcu.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/eEuQIhu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6GOIrmQ.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/4nI7NPe.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/3DY16jb.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VCBhRDX.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/cVxYImO.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/myj4LeD.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/i1EcX4W.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Y2qBeHR.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/xzGkM6t.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/fFk5sEK.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/jnZ6L4X.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/fO3tQ7w.png</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/0ft2Tga.png</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/lV3fJcH.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/qwtgWk7.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/ZQ0ezfZ.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>Bust-A-Move (also known as Puzzle Bobble) is a real-time puzzle game in which the player controls a device called "pointer" at the bottom of the screen, aiming and releasing randomly colored bubbles upwards. Depending on the aiming, the bubbles may float up directly or bounce off the walls, changing their trajectory. The goal is to aim the bubbles in such a way that they will touch identically colored ones. When such bubbles form a group of three or more, they pop and disappear from the screen. If the ceiling of the area is covered by too many bubbles, it will gradually descend; the game is over when it nearly reaches the player-controlled pointer. Should the player fail to release the bubbles within a specific time limit, they will be released automatically, unaffected by the pointer's aiming. A two-player mode is included as well. Each player competes on an area occupying half of the screen, dealing with identically generated bubbles. Whenever a player successfully disposes of a bubble group, a part of it is transferred onto the opponent's part of the screen. The game features the two dinosaur protagonists (Bob and Bub) as well as other characters from Bubble Bobble, even though the two games have distinctly different gameplay.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/88222ca6-9432-4051-af02-e118b6bbe6ed.png</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/29c2ae85-3584-4c7c-9484-aa2aed0356f5.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/096ec2d0-2ae9-488c-95ac-c0d96e9cb00c.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a2ca993b-fbda-43bb-9e0c-010837bc07a6.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/32b41d23-7dd0-4c78-abfb-d142a47ae489.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c6b834d1-8eb8-4501-a450-c51bc8ea81ed.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Taito Corporation</Publisher>
</game>