<Game>
	<Name>Capcom's Soccer Shootout (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Capcom's Soccer Shootout is the US version of Japan's J. League Excite Stage '94. While both versions are identical in gameplay and modes, the US release excised the officially licensed Japanese League soccer players and teams of J. League Excite Stage '94 in favor of generic national teams and players. The Japanese release also included Barcode Battler cards for each team.Teams:Each team in Capcom's Soccer Shootout is adapted from an equivalent team in J. League Excite Stage '94. The team with the best overall stats is Germany/Shimizu S-Pulse.Capcom's Soccer ShootoutJ.League Excite Stage '94United StatesKashima AntlersBrazilJEF UnitedRussiaRed DiamondsArgentinaVerdy KawasakiMexicoYokohama MarinosFranceYokohama FlugelsGreat BritainBellmare HiratsukaGermanyShimizu S-PulseSpainJubilo IwataHolland Nagoya GrampusItaly Gamba OsakaCameroonSanfrecce HiroshimaCheat: Ending PasswordAt the Main Game mode, enter the following password: 0, Orange 4, Orange 7, Green 7, 1, 4, 0, Orange 0, Orange 5, Purple 1, Orange 3, Light Blue 2, Light Blue 4, Yellow 6, Red 3, 3, 0, Red 0, Blue 0, Green 0, Blue 0, 3.Cheat: Ending PasswordAt the Main Game mode, enter the following password: 0, Yellow 0, Orange 7, Blue 7, Red 2, 0, 0, Yellow 0, Light Blue 6, Red 7, Green 6, Purple 7, Blue 4, Purple 3, Green 4, Blue 1, 0, Green 4, Light Blue 0, Yellow 5, Light Blue 5, 2.Cheat: Ending PasswordInput the following password at the main Game mode: 0, 0, Pink 1, Orange 7, Blue 7, 5, Pink 1, 1, Green 0, Red 1, Light Blue 1, Yellow 2, Blue 0, Orange 7, Light Blue 4, Pink 7, Yellow 7, Light Blue 0, Red 0, Orange 0, Red 2, 1</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>By5I2G-ZU4c</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3166</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588669-capcoms-soccer-shootout</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/capcoms-soccer-shootout</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/capcoms-soccer-shootout/3030-25661/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/RcdumUc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/xLfa1iM.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/pcT9u6b.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/8FUjOup.png</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/DFMt4B6.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/EOtcfIO.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/YoQ0WGy.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/30u57j0.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/pZHJOta.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/uykk1HB.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/VJ7t29L.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/mKmtbFB.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/v8hKRPA.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/3fi2EuO.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/63QnhjX.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/8XPfsbR.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>This Is Real Soccer! Flags waving, fans screaming, confetti flying. Everyone awaits the referee's whistle to kickoff the soccer shootout. It's come down to this: the most anticipated match-up of the year. For real soccer kicks here's CAPCOM's Soccer Shootout. Corner kicks, free kicks, throw-ins, yellow cards, the whole 110-yards. You want to win? Teamwork is the key. Cut your opponent's defense to shreds with crisp passes, hit the open man and boom - it's in the net! The crowds are here, the teams are here, the referee is here. Now all that's needed is you. Lace up your cleats because no matter how you play it, you've scored with. CAPCOM's Soccer Shootout.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e5d77139-7f89-480c-b58a-a55aaa2b6117.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ef56b742-0e38-4f03-886e-b7e8086af225.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2240ae32-8b5f-4df7-8b04-bc9c9fec0f70.png</boxart7>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5037f82d-f420-4da3-b6b2-5ebc2357358f.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8e147570-13f3-4549-ba42-8d0452fa0087.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fc43bd10-0e06-4b59-85d4-825e24ddd446.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bc4af4e4-72f0-4027-b0a2-7b7489486940.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>