<Game>
	<Name>Capcom's MVP Football (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This is an American Football game which features four different game modes. There is the Custom mode which let's the player set up an exhibition game between two teams. The player can either choose to directly control the football players on the field or choose to just coach the team by selecting plays and letting the computer control the on field action. Other parameters that can be adjusted are the quarter length, the field conditions, and the difficulty of the computer opponent.There is also a Tournament mode where the player tries to take a team through a playoff bracket in order to get to the Super Bowl.MVP mode puts the player in game situations in which the player has to try to overcome.Demo mode lets the player watch the computer play against itself.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3165</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588506-capcoms-mvp-football</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/capcoms-mvp-football</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/capcoms-mvp-football/3030-33818/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ulryRfN.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/tDz5VPY.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/9Xd9ABE.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/98OSwFl.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/cw7tgxD.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/9O45AZ2.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/MaDoGhv.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/NhNL0H8.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/8HSsy0Q.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/4uEOMWK.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Jc5hDy7.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/wxCDxXE.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/4AJOAwI.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/uoc1Y7x.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/kodnZu0.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Un5IRuf.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>BRUISING NFL FOOTBALL ACTION! It's 4th and goal with 5 seconds left on the clock and you're down by 4 points. But you are faced with the toughest defense in the NFL. You take the hike, roll to the right, and find a wide open receiver. You rifle the ball towards him... You call the shots in CAPCOM's MVP FOOTBALL! It's real NFL action that you won't find anywhere else. Choose any team from the AFC or the NFC. You can also play in different types of weather and field conditions. It's the closest thing to real football without getting dirty. - Features three game plays: Team vs. Team - pick your teams for-head to-head games. Playoffs - Take your team through the playoffs to the championship game. Unique MVP Mode - Work your way out of an increasingly difficult series of challenges. - Choose from over 30 offensive plays and 25 defensive plays. - Officially licensed by the National Football League.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b0259643-7552-49b3-8760-8a09de948fa6.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd514a0c-48c8-4e59-8e49-b64f12aafb35.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a0b26a99-8593-45bb-bcb7-2e4f1af41b18.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3b269fe6-19d7-4f95-ad7a-252bc8335277.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>