<Game>
	<Name>Captain Tsubasa IV - Pro no Rival-tachi (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Captain Tsubasa IV: Pro no Rival Tachi is the fourth game in Tecmo's series of soccer RPGs based on the Captain Tsubasa anime and manga, the first of which was localized as Tecmo Cup Soccer Game. Pro no Rival Tachi is also the second of four Captain Tsubasa games created for the Super Famicom.The player can select between Kick Off, which continues the story from where Captain Tsubasa III: Koutei no Chousen left off and features many story cutscenes between matches, and the All-Star mode, which just takes the player to a single match against the CPU.The game was followed by Captain Tsubasa V: Hasha no Shougou Campione in late 1994. Captain Tsubasa IV was not released outside of Japan. Cheat: More special moves for KazuFinish the game using different routes to get more special moves for Kazu.Cheat: Sound TestOn the main menu press L and R (at the same time) to access the sound test menu.</plot>
	<releasedate>3/4/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Tecmo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>VEpQB6HhMJs</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/562648-captain-tsubasa-iv-pro-no-rival-tachi</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/captain-tsubasa-iv-pro-no-rival-tachi/3030-38261/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/rRmVACP.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/EqBm9eH.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/0buV80K.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/pIxjXvO.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/0EDMnIW.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/3PWcDdp.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/7Mc6Ni3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/khVak7v.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/pVHgc99.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/aG13KlU.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Wi5ayus.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/pcNUqrN.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/hSybxoi.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/KqMbKyq.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Captain Tsubasa 4: Pro no Rival Tachi (キャプテン翼Ⅳ プロのライバルたち?) is the fourth sequel of the original Captain Tsubasa videogame series by Tecmo. It's a direct sequel of Captain Tsubasa 3: Koutei no Chousen and released exclusively in Japan for Nintendo's Super Famicom on April 3, 1993.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f6db9e0d-b087-4e4e-81f7-11c7860f179b.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b7335ba4-c2e8-4bd3-b43c-19a36ebc9750.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Tecmo</Publisher>
</game>