<Game>
	<Name>Captain Tsubasa V - Hasha no Shougou Campione (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Captain Tsubasa V: Hasha no Shougou Campione ("Captain Tsubasa V: Campione Champion Titleholder") is a soccer game based on the anime Captain Tsubasa that utilizes a turn-based system for tackles, passes and kicks. It is the fifth such game developed by Tecmo, as well as the last.Unlike its four predecessors, Captain Tsubasa V adopts a new gameplay format with a classic view of the pitch. Various characters were based on real-life footballers of the time. Some examples are Peter Schmeichel, Ruud Gullit, Dennis Bergkamp, Gabriel Batistuta and Marco Van Basten.The Story mode is divided into three major parts: Tsubasa's adventure in the Italian football league, the international campaign with Japan's national football team, and finally Japan in the World Tournament. In addition, there are other playable mini-stories with other original characters from the anime/manga.Cheat: Secret ShotsDuring matchs, try doing this in order to get extra shots.Cheat: Sound TestOn the main menu press Up, Y and B (all at the same time!) to acess the sound test menu.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Tecmo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>nKMUWABBQT8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>28685</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575661-captain-tsubasa-v-hasha-no-shougou-campione</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/captain-tsubasa-v-hasha-no-shougou-campione/3030-37229/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Captain_Tsubasa_5:_Hasha_no_Sh%C5%8Dg%C5%8D_Campione</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/uTm4Kpy.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/VYAJ2fZ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/gJn0B9X.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wBu3xUT.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/gEW3FAj.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/n5uJTgS.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/0dyPaSB.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/E6RqC3R.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/NsV11qO.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/r8wXxNP.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/8fRRipx.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/l1kae8x.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/BLJHvSE.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/hSybxoi.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/2CKfPhp.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The fifth and final instalment of the original Captain Tsubasa video game series by Tecmo. It's a sequel of Captain Tsubasa 4: Pro no Rival Tachi and the game differs greatly from its "Cinematic Soccer" oriented predecessors. It adopts a new gameplay with a classic view of the pitch and improved graphics. It features various RPG elements with special techniques of characters, known from Captain Tsubasa manga and anime series. The game's story mode focuses mainly on Tsubasa's Serie A season with Lecce and international campaign with Japan. In addition, other characters like Kojiro Hyuga, Genzo Wakabayashi, Lui Napoleón, Carlos Santana or Karl-Heinz Schneider have their less-expanded scenarios as well. The competitions in the game are based on real major international tournaments, like Asian Cup, Copa América and World Cup. In the All-star mode, the players can create new characters, arrange a friendly match (with all the teams, or by composing an own squad from all the players available in the game) and create a league with national or club teams.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23921962-515d-4b63-ab81-c1d3dbf785c3.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23084715-d40f-440d-b4ad-22a7131f7c4b.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Tecmo</Publisher>
</game>