<Game>
	<Name>Captain Commando (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Captain Commando is an arcade beat-em-up developed and released by Capcom for arcades (running on CPS-1 hardware) on September 28, 1991. The game stars a futuristic superhero named Captain Commando (originally the fictional spokesman for Capcom USA's console games during the late 1980s) who, along with his three Commando Companions, must protect the Galaxy from super-powered criminals. These companions include the Mummy Commando (Mack the Knife, a mummy-like alien from outer space, known in the Japanese version as Jennety), the Ninja Commando (Ginzu the Ninja, a highly-trained ninja, known in the Japanese version as Sho), and the Baby Commando (Baby Head, a super genius infant who uses a robot of his own design, known in the Japanese version as Hoover).The gameplay builds upon Capcom's previous brawler, Final Fight, by including four-player simultaneous multiplayer, firearms as usable weaponry, and allowing the player to run (and perform running attacks). The game received a port to the Super Nintendo Entertainment System in 1995 (restricting the amount of players that can be played simultaneously to two players) and the PlayStation in 1998 (for Japan only, keeping the four-player simultanenous multiplayer with the use of multitap hardware). The game was also released in two compilations: Capcom Classics Collection Remixed (for the PSP in March 22, 2006) and Capcom Classics Collection: Volume 2 (for the Xbox and PlayStation 2 in November 24, 2006).Gameplay:The first stage.Captain Commando was a one to four player Co-Op game, each player has an eight-way joystick and two buttons. Like other Capcom beat'em ups such as Final Fight and Cadillacs and Dinosaurs, the player has a special move that can be done by pressing the attack and jump button. An original element to the beat'em up formula, was the dash mechanic that is done by tapping forward twice; it is useful for getting out of dangerous situations. The player can also perform a dash attack, or dash jump attack; for example, Captain Commando could unleash his flamethrower upon enemies.Other means of defense are presented for the player. Combat vehicles - armored mechs - can be used, each mech has a certain ability; one mech can freeze enemies while another can set them on fire. Weapons like melee and firearms also appear. Some weapons that are available are missile launcher, M-16, ray gun, throwing ninja stars, giant mallet and many others can be use.							</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>uPTS_AwWDwk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1735</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588242-captain-commando</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/captain-commando</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/captain-commando/3030-9663/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/VdX4Mxa.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/5LwYP7J.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/D96qduB.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/kWZQy8b.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/1k2zHEp.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/aFF6wM7.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/AmMlnNR.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/0SKhpiT.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/WijFvrB.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/u8aKTP0.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/veC7Cuf.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Cpd8SfF.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/x6zNWIF.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/f2kO6VF.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/REY1s2g.png</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/0ysGaRh.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/IaRsYv9.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/iNI6rzs.png</clearlogo1>
</game>