<Game>
	<Name>Castlevania - Dracula X (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: Richter Belmont, the game's main protagonistCastlevania: Dracula X (known in Europe as Castlevania: Vampire's Kiss and in Japan as Devil's Castle Dracula XX) is an action horror platformer developed and published by Konami for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System in September 1995.Based on the PC-Engine Super CD-ROM&#178; game Castlevania: Rondo of Blood (originally Japanese-exclusive), the game shares most of its graphics, gameplay, storyline, and music. However, some components (such as the levels) were completely redesigned.Taking place sometime in 1792 (one hundred years after the events of the original Castlevania, the player controls Richter Belmont, descendant of Simon Belmont, as he sets out to seal the fate of Count Dracula while rescuing his beloved Annette Renard (along with her sister, Maria).Gameplay:Castlevania: Dracula X plays like a traditional Castlevania game. Players guide Richter through seven stages, increasing their score by defeating enemies and collecting bags of money (dropped by enemies or destroying scenery). Players will also find heart-shaped jewels, which serve as ammunition for Richter's sub-weapons and super attacks (known as "Item Crashes"). Unlike Super Castlevania IV, released four years earlier, the player cannot do any special tricks with his Vampire Killer whip (such as whip in eight directions, hold out the whip freely to block projectiles, and use the whip to grapple onto special points). However, Richter can perform a backflip dodge (by double-tapping the jump button). Richter can also maintain his position while getting hit simply by crouching (preventing him from being knocked back), and can jump on and off stairs (by holding up or down on the d-pad and pressing the jump button).Other than jewels and bags of money, players can also find pendants (which clears the screen of all enemies), transparency elixirs (which grant Richter temporary invulnerability), and food (which restores some of Richter's health). Defeating a boss causes a Mystic Sphere to drop from the sky, refilling Richter's health completely and clearing the stage. Players earn extra lives by finding 1-Up items scattered throughout the game and clearing stages without getting hit, as well as for every time the player earns 20,000 points.Sub-Weapons/Item CrashesAlong the way, Richter can pick up unique sub-weapons that consume the jewel meter for a special attack (performed by holding up on the directional pad and pressing the attack button). Richter can also perform "Item Crushes", which sacrifice more jewels for a super attack (by pressing the special Item Crush button). All of the sub-weapons and Item Crushes perform like they did in Castlevania: Rondo of Blood. However, this game is missing the Holy Bible sub-weapon. Dagger - At the cost of one jewel, Richter throws three very fast (but very weak) daggers. The Item Crush, at the cost of 10 jewels, produces a rapid stream of daggers. Axe - At the cost of one jewel, Richter tosses an axe in the air in an arced path (going through both walls and enemies). The Item Crash, at the cost of 10 jewels, causes Richter to float up in the air and produce a circle of axes that fan out around him. Holy Cross - At the cost of one jewel, Richter throws a cross-shaped object forward, which will return in the other direction like a  boomerang, damaging enemies along the way. The Item Crash, at the cost of 15 jewels, causes the screen to be bombarded with large crucifixes.Holy Water rain! Holy Water - At the cost of three jewels, Richter throws a bottle of holy water on the ground, creating a small area-of-effect attack with the flames it creates. Its Item Crash, at the cost of 20 jewels, causes holy water to rain from the sky all over the screen. Pocket Watch - At the cost of five jewels, Richter freezes most enemies in their place for five seconds. The Item Crash, at the cost of 30 jewels, grants Richter a temporary shield of pocket watches (causing a lot of damage when inflicted upon enemies). Key - Found in Stage 3, it is used for unlocking certain doors (allowing the player to rescue Annette and Maria). The Item Crash, which can only be performed if Richter has 15 jewels or more (it does not consume any jewels), causes Richter to hold the key out in front of him, causing major damage at the cost of its close range.Pressing the Item Crush button without carrying a sub-weapon causes Richter to throw a giant flaming whip attack (at the cost of 15 jewels).Cheat: Extra 1-upsTo get an extra 1-up, beat each stage without getting hit. If you come out unscathed (no, you cannot get hit and eat a frankfurter), you will recieve a 1-up after every stage you complete.Cheat: Extra 1-upsAfter collecting the Key item which goes into your sub-weapon box in Stage 3, if you have 15 hearts or more, use the ItemCrash button. While to most people it seems to do nothing more than make a question mark appear over your head, if the key itself makes contact with an enemy or boss during this brief animation, they'll sustain heavy damage. The best part of this secret is while you must have 15 hearts or more to enable the itemcrash, actually using it consumes ZERO hearts allowing the attack to be used continuously! It also has the highest attack power killing most enemies in a single hit even if used regularly as well (Up + Attack) and once again consumes no hearts however to balance it's attack power, it's also the closest range "weapon" in the game needing to be used immediately in front of the enemy.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami (America), Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>nuxgAAPXKk4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1553</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563534-castlevania-dracula-x</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/castlevania-dracula-x</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/castlevania-dracula-x/3030-10975/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/bZYXEoE.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mtxs2L6.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/sjk4Fiq.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/l9HELNY.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/X6DXLs1.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/nQXDTK4.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/o2gMfks.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/8mZEdju.jpg</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://i.imgur.com/p8solIW.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://i.imgur.com/4v70AL9.jpg</boxart10>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/4Gdb04b.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/cmRvlLy.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/szZ41uR.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/BpSUMN0.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/sx1JUZG.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Olb18Fq.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/6EoJJt2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/4NM8U02.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/usB0vzi.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JohnlEg.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/iWyJ6oZ.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/19UMBGd.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/yN3t4TB.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/kjuJOwX.png</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UWLQ5VD.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/sYfT2av.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/30QmlwJ.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>The Legend Returns... Rising up from his eternal sleep, Count Dracula is back again to battle the descendants of the great vampire-stalking Belmont family of the Castlevania series. He has summoned his dark minions-Cerberus, Minaurus, and the Salamander-to bring a reign of terror on the land. Grab your whip and try to defeat these dark forces in this new conversion of the hit Japanese game: DRACULA X. The 7+ stages unfold with myriad possibilities depending on the choices you make during the game. This multi-ending, multi-story feature takes you through many levels of adventure. You must strategically use magical tomes, mystical power-ups and titanic weapons to defeat the horrifying bosses and discover secret bonus levels.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>nuxgAAPXKk4</VideoURL1>
	<boxart11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab4828a1-482d-4b41-86e0-41b0100039be.jpg</boxart11>
	<boxart12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b5ed58d0-72fb-422a-a1d8-2ea2ed2a9241.jpg</boxart12>
	<boxart13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/030feacd-1cd2-4bea-ac84-d57b34466bc8.png</boxart13>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c524efe1-f26b-4c17-af8b-3037093aac7c.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/58e08f8d-daa8-4069-b00a-d84f997609f5.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fa66609c-f42e-45c5-9ea5-8bab123d5e9b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6d43c6d9-0b29-4ec5-b4f1-7a1f9777dfaa.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/18f44c25-aba2-46ca-ba4f-15f5e4dfe29b.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/42a28676-5d4e-4ac4-acfb-f66322edd85f.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d616c95-1ce3-447f-9ef5-3d9530236b90.png</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8798b446-0cf0-4ac1-bc75-15ac5d5b6ef9.png</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/70b3c92c-8519-414d-ad90-7c22218704b9.png</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d2243da0-063e-408b-99de-bc33c6d255aa.png</snapshot18>
	<snapshot19>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fbba4a0f-2ea6-4be2-bce7-07286943c01f.png</snapshot19>
	<snapshot20>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f579dec6-ddbd-436d-9eeb-b9799c847850.png</snapshot20>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>