<Game>
	<Name>Champions - World Class Soccer (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Champions World Class Soccer is a soccer game developed by Park Place Productions and published by both Acclaim Entertainment (SNES and Japanese Genesis versions) and Flying Edge (US and EU Genesis versions) for the Sega Genesis and Super Nintendo Entertainment System platforms.The Super Nintendo version received three separate endorsements when it was released in Europe: Manchester United winger Ryan Giggs for the UK, former Bayern Munich goalkeeper Sepp Maier for Germany and the French league team Paris Saint-Germain for France.Gameplay:Champions World Class Soccer features 32 different national teams to choose from. They include: Argentina, Australia, Austria, Belgium, Bolivia, Brazil, Cameroon, Canada, Chile, Colombia, Denmark, England, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Israel, Italy, Japan, Mexico, Netherlands, Peru, Portugal, Russia, Scotland, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, United Arab Emirates, Uruguay, USA and Wales.Cheat: Final Match PasswordsOn the main menu go down to 1P Tournament, press Right on the D-Pad three times, press Start, and enter any one of the following:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1736</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588246-champions-world-class-soccer</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/champions-world-class-soccer</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/champions-world-class-soccer/3030-19135/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/iSY2Of0.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/xdlXXVN.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/K5fsZj7.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lRmXYTy.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/DQueaxz.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/LVfim60.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Fe1NZW4.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/sPWE2Fo.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/U6o2Em3.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/bA1Z3hm.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/iiP04cD.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/BfvEN45.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/d3naD9C.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/9WKrk5N.png</clearlogo1>
</game>