<Game>
	<Name>Chavez (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Chavez is a standard boxing game that is considered the Spanish version of Riddick Bowe Boxing with Spanish only in-game menus and 24 professional boxers including Speedo Garcia, Ron Ronaldo and the game's namesake, Julio Cesar Chavez, among many other latino boxers each with their own strengths and weaknessesStandard modes like Exhibition and Career are present including the ability to create seven custom-made boxers and save them to a battery backup.  The game screen is shown in side-scrolling fashion with a miniature ring at the top of the screen to show players their position in the ring and the "power" and "health" meters at the bottom of the screen.Cheat: Hidden CharactersIn Career Mode, create a new boxer by selecting the question mark, then enter RIKKY, IIIAN, or FRIEDA as your character name. Select OK, then press Start to skip all customization options. This will turn your character into Riddick Bowe with all stats maxed out... and odd colored skin.Cheat: Play Invincible Characters (Only for the Chavez Version)At the main menu, go to Career Mode, and select a question mark to create a new character. Enter either AXY or SPOT as the character name (which are two different characters). Skip everything else in the character creation by pressing Start. The character with maximum stats and invincibility will be created.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>American Softworks Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>CEGxAzxGRq0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1554</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588613-riddick-bowe-boxing</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/chavez</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/riddick-bowe-boxing/3030-17218/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/WPJM4At.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/b7mhrRt.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/2RITqtt.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/x1RodQv.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8Cab79W.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/03FPz1w.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/9wEUwc8.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VVWh5Qf.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/sPaWsZX.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/kpPy30a.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/FilA8TH.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Pfhuae0.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/txpalSR.png</banner1>
</game>