<Game>
	<Name>Chou Mahou Tairiku Wozz (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Chou Mahou Tairiku Wozz (The Magical Land of Wozz) is a JRPG developed by Red Company and was published by Bullet-Proof Software in 1995 for the Super Famicom. The game's defining feature is the ability to choose from three different protagonists that lead to one of the game's three endings. The Magical Land of Wozz was never officially released in English but a translation patch was released by Translation Corporation on December 3, 2006.									</plot>
	<releasedate>4/8/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>RED Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>HhGtO3uWQbQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14822</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581899-chou-mahou-tairiku-wozz</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ch-mah-tairiku-wozz</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/chou-mahou-tairiku-wozz/3030-9199/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/HBegDta.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/8jJULKx.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/KAIuadJ.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ssqf88z.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/g30p0E9.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/O09Q3Z8.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/wcn1ruA.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/rS4MdRb.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Qb7P1GU.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ytPAl9v.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rQYy34I.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/LacYoEv.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JNg45le.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/raRHN9s.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/l2VIg8w.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The magic world of Wozz, populated by magicians, alchemists, and other kinds of people - including simple town and village inhabitants - was a seemingly peaceful place, until one day, a poisonous rain started turning its inhabitants into monsters. The chief wizard realizes that the demon Balaam is trying to link the world of Wozz with the world of humans. Only a human hero can stop Balaam, and the wizard's teleporting magic brings... three young humans: the Japanese girl Reona Kitazato, and two boys: the American Shot Phoenix and the Chinese Chun Chingtao. Will those youngsters be able to stop Balaam? The game is a traditional Japanese-style RPG similar to Breath of Fire: turn-based battles are viewed from an isometric perspective. You control all three characters as a party, but in the beginning of the game you choose one of them as the main character, and therefore will see the game from his/her perspective. In case the characters split up, you'll be able to control only the one you chose.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/15332afc-34ae-4c15-8c86-b3ba32d05298.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/45e4f5ae-d684-4af4-bb9b-039d2b73e4f3.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f315d1d8-3a68-4c97-93db-fb52582ae561.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/126ba737-f82a-4b65-94d1-767dad29e7f2.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6902f733-6c5f-4f5b-983c-5359f5a8a2e6.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Bullet Proof Software</Publisher>
</game>