<Game>
	<Name>Chou Makai Taisen! Dorabocchan (Japan) (Beta) (1992-12-21)</Name>
	<plot>Can Spike McFang, junior magician and vampire in training, rescure his island kingdom from the evil hands of Von Hesler? Help Spike use his magical powers to conquer the sinister leaders of 9 island areas and restore his father, Dracuman, to power.Spike's weapons? A magical hat and cape that spin at high speeds. Sure, they're unusual, but you have to get creative when you're facing killer garlic and zombies! Along the way, Spike will need to find plenty of gold and magic cards to keep going, so keep your eyes peeled. It's Spike's first chance to test his skills in real action!Cheat: Debug MenuAt title screen, press Right, Y, B, Left, B, Y, Up, Y, B, Down, B, Y, Select, Select, Select, Left, Right. If done correctly, you will hear a sound. Start the game normally, and press L + R + Start.Cheat: Play As RudyGo to the title screen and press Down, B, Left, B, Up, Y, Right, Y. If the trick worked, you'll hear a chime. Now when you beat Felina, Rudy comes to your rescue. As you return to town, you can control him with Controller Two.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/6/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>RED Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>REDMraAFowQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2673</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588814-the-twisted-tales-of-spike-mcfang</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-twisted-tales-of-spike-mcfang/3030-2626/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/7vswg5Z.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/L9MEjjO.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/MrXDzrj.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/4RBKvWp.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/D44OdJx.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/9lk8liN.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/3wzHlJr.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/DP7V8yM.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/zIEBjAK.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/YxVvoxQ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/lW9mdaD.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/abRmtiK.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/tU9st2s.png</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/bipzj0V.png</clearlogo1>
</game>