<Game>
	<Name>Clay Fighter - Tournament Edition (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The Tournament Edition of Clay Fighter fixes some glitches and adds new features to the original 2D fighting game. Most scenarios were changed or redone, the graphics are brighter and the gameplay is faster. The characters can now perform three and four-hit combos. More voice-overs and a new introduction cut-scene were added.Three kinds of tournaments are now available: double elimination, single elimination and sudden death. One, four or eight players can join the tournaments, with the option of renaming their characters for customization.Cheat: CodesChoose ''Tournament'' mode and then select a four-player ''Double Elimination'' game.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/5/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Interplay Productions, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1788</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588257-clayfighter-tournament-edition</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/clay-fighter-tournament-edition</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/clayfighter-tournament-edition/3030-16199/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/rgd34IS.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/gNUyHkV.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/qWO7xLx.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/EAcw50H.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/CeI3dWJ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/b7zmrfa.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/qbLvVCI.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/1o3PvKU.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/SXLWnOX.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/WOvyvTf.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/rHLQF73.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Al2X9PG.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/MaS0UGw.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/snFsyln.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Clay never had it so good. This outrageous new Clay Fighter Tournament Edition lets you smack it out with up to eight friends at a time. So, let the clay fly. More punching power with three and four hit combos and faster game speed (twice as fast as the original!) More balanced game play increases your chance of survival. Set up single elimination, double elimination and sudden death tournaments with four or eight of your friends - or use the tournament format to match your skills against the computer. Keep track of your tournament with the Tournament Ladder - complete with winners and losers brackets. Expanded voice over gives you more trash talking and blow-by-blow descriptions throughout the game. Brighter bolder graphics and awesome new clay backgrounds. Pick a name, any name, to customize your character.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fe9b42ad-5e35-4832-95ce-5e797a1d0053.png</banner2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ed292c67-4fe8-49ab-bd61-61acc6d7207f.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ee9030c-38ac-42ee-84f6-5bc95f0a5faf.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7bce3305-1b04-4cca-9c20-a6e490f9d1e7.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/41cb1e1e-3721-4cad-9c5c-e9b1434f6319.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Interplay</Publisher>
</game>