<Game>
	<Name>Cliffhanger (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Standard side-scrolling fighter based off of the Stallone film of the same name. Sly must fight thugs and the elements as he tracks down suitcases of stolen cash dropped around the peaks of the Rockies. Combat follows the Final Fight standard, broken up by some mountain climbing and running (or 3-D snowboarding on the Sega CD) from avalanches. Enemies are the standard brawler crooks, occasionally carrying guns and knives the player can pick up. The game tends to follow a pattern of having you deal with a natural hazard (scaling a cliff, leaping over gaps), then locking the screen down for a fighting segment, nature again, fighting again, etc. The available fighting moves is limited, compared to other games of this type, and the ability to hit an enemy character is noticeably less accurate.The plot is identical to the film, with levels based off of, or inspired by, scenes in the movie. Animated cutscenes move the story along on the cartridge systems, while brief clips from the film play between levels on the Sega CD.Cheat: 2 Player Beat em up ModeIn game menu press the following keys 5 times with control pad 2:B, Up, Down, Up, Down, Left, Right, ACheat: 2 Player Beat em up ModeA sound will confirm the code. After that press Start on "Start Game". Now you are able to fight against player 2("Walker"). To exit the mode press Start + Select on any controller.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>LL2H87PpI5g</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2853</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588259-cliffhanger</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/cliffhanger</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/cliffhanger/3030-4616/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/L3GlEY5.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/rEz5Ujw.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/BdGEteE.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7FHRGnv.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/gxaXb4B.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/mVHazsl.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/NENm1UD.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/fDypdE9.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/XBoTDGr.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/wuBvm0K.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/mArry7K.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/dYORT4y.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Ugzl1YL.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/lMzdJl4.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/fDS3T8Y.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7lBLqIn.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/De45u9v.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Based on the white-knuckle action-adventure movie starring Sylvester Stallone, Cliffhanger challenges you to brave thundering avalanches, icy cliffs, and the head-spinning heights of the Rocky Mountains while you combat a vicious group of well-armed, extremely dangerous fugitives. You'll hang on for dear life through 7 exciting levels requiring all your strength and skill just to survive. Experience wild new forms of game play like mountain climbing and cave exploration, along with all the excitement of all the incredible hand-to-hand and armed combat action. The adventure isn't over until you find $100 million in stolen loot, defeat the fugitives, and reunite with your friends!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/188ae076-bebc-4c25-b2d9-9fb3f52034ed.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/431d0232-d224-4fa0-ab8a-31dd8bf1e063.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a40626f0-3544-4fd9-a109-982bb037d653.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/56872dfd-8db7-44c3-9f59-267c218118e6.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7e1008f7-2ee8-4420-a6a5-be8313769c77.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sony</Publisher>
</game>