<Game>
	<Name>College Slam (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:College Slam is an arcade style basketball game.Power-Ups!3: Increases your ability to make the three-point outside shot!D: Allows you to perform Monster Jams from anywhere on the court!S: Increases your overall speed to astounding levels!P: Increases your power to a degree you can hardly imagine!T: Provides you with temporary unlimited boost action!F: Causes you to be temporarily "on fire"!B: The bomb knocks over everyone on the court - except you!?: Randomly activates the effects of one of the other icons!R: Reverses the direction of the ball if it's in mid-shot!Z: Prevents your opponents from scoring by zapping your hoop with a flash of lightning!I: Causes your teammate to become invisible for a brief period of time!C: Causes the ball to chaotically bounce in random directions every time it hits the floor!W: Causes you to become a whirlwind that will knock over any player who comes in contact with you! [Note your controller will be affected such that you will keep moving in one direction until you press another direction on the control pad. If you are in possession of the ball, shooting or passing will neutralize the whirlwind.]Teams in College SlamAlabamaArizonaArkansasBoston CollegeCal BerkeleyCincinnatiConnecticutDukeFloridaFlorida StateGeorgetownGeorgiaGeorgia TechIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisiana State UniversityMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMichigan StateMissouriNebraskaNorth CarolinaNorth Carolina StateOhio StateOklahomaOklahoma StatePenn StatePurdueSt. John'sSouth CarolinaSyracuseTexasThe University of MemphisUCLAUNLVUSCVillanovaVirginiaWake ForestWisconsin			</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>wBYAW-aCaBU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3542</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563541-college-slam</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/college-slam</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/college-slam/3030-125/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/College_Slam</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/katCAvF.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/jz9l7yP.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/j1VQQ3b.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lfqGuj8.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SYk1F6o.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/XiirCVM.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/TBiWqqG.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/chWZddE.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YVJf8Bs.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/iG8S6uQ.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/dFmymO1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/8MVjs4l.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/mXeLRkr.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/U8UiJU5.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Welcome to the College Slam arena! The crowd's on their feet... over 40 college teams, cheerleaders... authentic fight songs... all the rivalry... all the madness! There's a wild dunk... the backboard shatters! This is the slammingest hoops action ever... and there's more... head-to-head, tournament, and season-long play! College Slam is gonna take you to school!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>wBYAW-aCaBU</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c28f7841-ba86-4d1d-a195-282ffc4ce0ff.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33ec9366-7290-42f0-a411-dbc7243a6de7.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e4534c5-2c13-4f28-80d0-ec7dfa0b2b24.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/05544b14-5045-4775-a781-e5e6cf09a626.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>