<Game>
	<Name>Columns (Japan) (NP)</Name>
	<plot>Columns is loosely derived from Tetris, as it involves arranging falling blocks in such a way as to clear them. However, in columns they are groups of 3 same-size but varying color blocks, which must be arranged into sequences of 3 or more, either horizontally, vertically or diagonally. Sequences of 4 or 5 count for double or triple points, and diagonal sequences score the most. The real trick is to set up 'combos' - where one line causes other blocks to drop so as to create other lines.As well as the normal game mode, there is also a 'flash' mode, in which the aim is simply to remove a particular block from the base of the pre-formed pile of bricks. The difficulty of this can be determined by increasing the number of complete rows which are already in place.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/8/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Media Factory</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>2.2</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/952114-columns</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/columns</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/columns/3030-5487/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/BukX8zg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/wcr5gjy.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Ys6894b.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Mxu4TrG.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/NvzHHBC.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/lOdQGk3.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Dt39GbY.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/6HB2ULz.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/YzEklwu.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/o6mhC4B.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Eee3LCb.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/vgkJ1tK.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ztASNQS.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/IteOwDT.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/YJF4Q4N.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Drift back to ancient Phoenicia and challenge yourself with Columns, a game favored by middle eastern merchants. In this mesmerizing pastime, tinker with your riches to align glittering jewels across, down, or diagonally. As you line up colors, the gems vanish and more sparklers drop from above. The challenge increases as the jewels fall more rapidly. You must quickly align them before the columns reach the top. Imagine yourself on the warm Mediterranean coast, or drifting over a languid sea. Forget the passage of time, and tickle your mind with Columns, the brilliant game of strategy and skill.</Notes>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9e2390a0-04b8-411c-9e04-9dc69c08141b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33fe72fe-c1f5-4b41-a3ca-c99962ebc357.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Media Factory</Publisher>
</game>