<Game>
	<Name>Conveni Wars Barcode Battler Senki - Super Senshi Shutsugeki seyo! (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Conveni Wars Barcode Battler Senki: Super Senshi Shutsugeki Seyo! ("Chronicles of the Convenience Store Wars Barcode Battlers: Roll Out, Super Soldier!") is a strategy RPG from Epoch (developed by SAS Sakata) that is built to work with their Barcode Battler handheld device: a machine that scans barcodes and creates soldiers/monsters with their own individual stats from the data.Versions of Conveni Wars Barcode Battler Senki were bundled with an adapter device that allowed the Super Famicom to read the Barcode Battler's output and add the creatures it generated to the hero's army in-game. The game also provided default characters for players without the Barcode Battler device (which was sold separately, unlike the adapter).The game is a spiritual sequel to Epoch's Barcode World, which provided the same symbiosis between the Barcode Battler and the Famicom.Many of Epoch's later Super Famicom games would have some degree of connectivity with the Barcode Battler, usually providing optional enhanced functions if the right codes are scanned.</plot>
	<releasedate>14/5/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Sci-Fi</genre>
	<Developer>SAS Sakata</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575679-conveni-wars-barcode-battler-senki-super-senshi</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/conveni-wars-barcode-battler-senki-super-senshi-sh/3030-46456/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/BClhABd.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/SX0zm5h.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/YqsDPwl.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/qhqX2Yc.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/V4Mit2R.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Se7Z5DV.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/B6NisHY.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/4sMDtIA.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/yqIZ6S6.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/c72nYi8.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/B4ZNz2u.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/PHo8FTH.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Conveni Wars Barcode Battler Senki: Super Senshi Shutsugeki Seyo! ("Chronicles of the Convenience Store Wars Barcode Battlers: Roll Out, Super Soldier!") is a strategy RPG that is built to work with their Barcode Battler handheld device: a machine that scans barcodes and creates soldiers/monsters with their own individual stats from the data. Versions of Conveni Wars Barcode Battler Senki were bundled with an adapter device that allowed the Super Famicom to read the Barcode Battler's output and add the creatures it generated to the hero's army in-game. The game also provided default characters for players without the Barcode Battler device (which was sold separately, unlike the adapter). The game is a spiritual sequel to Epoch's Barcode World, which provided the same symbiosis between the Barcode Battler and the Famicom. Many of Epoch's later Super Famicom games would have some degree of connectivity with the Barcode Battler, usually providing optional enhanced functions if the right codes are scanned.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/02d0a981-09af-45a1-a6a1-e20d29299639.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/472f55f8-d3c8-40a9-a21e-6576e62cfd37.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0568345-661f-4340-b341-282c80367ea3.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/822e2560-7683-4ef1-b7e7-dbbd0b459cf6.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f21e80ee-9b9a-4167-b984-e808c7e49d2c.png</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Epoch</Publisher>
</game>