<Game>
	<Name>Cool World (Spain)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Cool World is a platformer/adventure game based on the movie of the same name. The player must navigate Cool World as either cop Frank Harris or cartoonist Jack Deebs (played by Brad Pitt and Gabriel Byrne respectively in the movie), depending on the version, and prevent Holli Would from passing over to the real world.The game was released on many platforms between 1992-93, around the time the movie was released. Like most licensed movie tie-in games of the era, it was not well received critically.Super Nintendo VersionIn the Super Nintendo version the player assumes the role of Jack Deebs and is trying to find a way to escape Cool World and return to the real world. A large part of the gameplay involves solving adventure game puzzles and avoiding the "Popper Police" for as long as possible. If the player collects enough coins, they can pay the fine and keep playing.					</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ocean Software Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<VideoURL>s6ijsDn3i2U</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2860</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588263-cool-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/cool-world</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/cool-world/3030-20024/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/0wZw548.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/HHrJ96W.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/y6Sj5Z5.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/twZpYiH.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/iOI1g6E.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ZrG1jh6.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/8jKal0e.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/mJFEOjl.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/vVhjaup.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/2awU6Nf.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/mQ1Wsq8.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2l9oRCU.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/tYODDWy.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/qGMeEMe.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/yp2oRqD.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/SxB7UQL.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>It's an imaginary world that's real. It exists in another dimension, where cartoon characters, called Doodles are alive. It's Cool World. For cartoonist Jack Deebs, who's been carried across the boundary, it's a wild and amazing place; and he's discovered that only some of the Doodles are friendly. Take Holli Would. She's a knockout Doodle who's really interested in Jack. She's interested in using him to get herself and real body and transfer into this world. She just needs to get her hands on one special piece of magic. The Golden Spike of Power, hidden atop the Ocean Hotel in Las Vegas, is the powerful wedge between Cool World and this world. And Holli's trying to steal it. If she removes it, she may destroy both her world and Jack's. As Jack, you're got to stop her from doing it -- because you know she will if she can!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63fc411f-bdec-47fe-8618-74fab5eea614.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/897043a5-8a40-448d-8bf6-e8e1a1bcfab4.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f657937d-8571-4844-b982-75f829d9cd47.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/44b4a242-43fc-4b87-a2b5-aa3da32a3a97.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8d307b7d-f7e0-44d4-9035-1a5c053c10ef.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/167f449a-94d1-4c6f-b6dd-32c83cfe868d.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Ocean</Publisher>
</game>