<Game>
	<Name>Cybernator (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Cybernator (Assault Suits Valken in Japan) is a side scrolling mech combat game from NCS, which was published in Japan by Masaya, by Konami in the US and by Palcom in Europe. It is the second game in the Assault Suits series and follows Assault Suit Leynos, best known in the West as the Sega Genesis game Target Earth.The player plays as Jake Brain, a soldier in the Pacific States Marine Corps and pilot of a hulking assault suit, on a mission to destroy the Axis.Gameplay:The game has a number of features that characterize it and separate it from other side scrolling platformers of the day. There is a detailed aiming system, with multiple degrees possible, more than the standard up/down/diagonals in most shooters. The suit also has a limited jump/flight capacity, giving a sense of weight to the player's movements and making it important to consider the environment. There are also special stages, where the player is tasked to fly at speed through asteroids, or maneuver through the Earth's atmosphere on re-entry.The game has two endings, good and bad, achieved through completing or failing a majority of the side missions in the game respectively.Release DifferencesThe game was edited for its US localization, a notable scene where the leader of the enemy forces commits suicide being censored, and other details like character portraits being removed from in game conversations.Critical ReceptionWhen released, the SNES version was given the scores of 8,8,8,8 and an Editor's Choice Gold Award from Electronic Gaming Monthly. They added, "...the soundtrack is really kickin', and it's easy to get lost in the beat. Graphically it uses astounding detail and colors. The Mode 7explosions need work however, and the control is a little choppy at first".					</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>GveShUl5rdk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1557</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588266-cybernator</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/cybernator</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/cybernator/3030-19209/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cybernator</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/M7bWuSc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ODiID1L.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/mJPnP7R.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/jpIg3ty.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/RWXho74.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/d6oVW2O.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/9i1J7fn.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Loqm8SN.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/hzDVfHa.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/fNnPcCo.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/iX935q8.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/n3WWD73.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/bWHdxAZ.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/EMqAEeS.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/JZJeYyo.jpg</banner1>
	<banner2>http://i.imgur.com/QIjI1bw.png</banner2>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/PpZd8Ni.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/6wq5wNR.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>2065 AD. The nations of Earth have once again split into two major powers. The line dividing these new arch enemies reaches as far as the lunar frontier, where axis forces have constructed a moon base capable of launching monolithic intergalactic battle cruisers. To thwart this threat, a covert strike team consisting of the marines' elite Cybernator force has been mobilized. The Cybernator is a giant mechanical warrior controlled by a marine who sits in the command cockpit within the unit's chromium cranium. Nuclear Fission Thrusters allow the Cybernator to wreak total havoc while soaring from ground zero to the infinity of space. Your mission is to take command of the Cybernator and confront the most powerful enemy ever to explode onto the Super NES scene. You'll face an awesome display of graphic destruction and realistic carnage so intense you'll fell compelled to run and hide. The sound effects alone will make your guts shake as if they were in front of a cranked-up heavy metal concert speaker. But you must fight on, toughing it out through 7 war zones stretching from the moon, through the expanses of space, to the fringes of Earth's fragile atmosphere. Crush Axis Cybertroops. Find your way through a dark mountain maze with only your wits and a small light. And capture power-ups that you can allocate to the Cybernator's four different weapons systems. Until you accomplish your mission. Or have your nuts and bolts splattered from here to eternity.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>GveShUl5rdk</VideoURL1>
	<banner3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d588bddc-29c6-4ca3-9f99-8ea8e1ddfd8f.png</banner3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ad4b1149-9beb-4249-aa89-db369e3cb60d.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/683a3a86-8fa9-44bd-bcf7-f4e87c7a03f9.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/41bc165e-8c7f-460d-8499-11a7c32b16ac.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cb1f1b59-4d4e-4188-8327-2964a4a7f0f2.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/234d5907-f425-4b6f-b6b3-a476b56f1a8d.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d9588896-37e9-4731-af39-0e64a98f1a83.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a40dacfa-70b5-4c32-b1b4-80b1bc0c77c0.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/145b8d19-58fb-4be4-9169-88ac3920a49b.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>