<Game>
	<Name>Cyber Spin (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Cyber Spin is a sci-fi racing game known in Japan as Shinseiki ("New Century") GPX: Cyber Formula, based on the anime Future GPX Cyber Formula. While the Japanese version retains the characters and world of the anime, including cutscenes, the US version mostly excludes them to focus on the racing.The game is shown from a top-down perspective, with icons to inform the player when a turn is approaching. The player must qualify for each race with a time trial before taking part in the race proper. Due to the futuristic nature of the game (it's set in 2015), the player has access to speed boosts which greatly increases their speed for short bursts, but employing this boost uses up some of the player's finite energy bar.Cheat: Level PasswordsGPX ModeCheat: Level PasswordsScenario Mode and Free Mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>TAKARA Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>ZklbiDRcxfM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1791</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588268-cyber-spin</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/cyber-spin</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/cyber-spin/3030-37253/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Q3h12K1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/M2HGto8.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/G5w1AVU.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/WaXlfwo.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Tp3MKaK.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/rSxRlw0.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/V3tluun.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/QokMINR.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SN2sJlg.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7dHLVf3.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/OM4ZQVm.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/NdGRcrn.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/s1ai4Xg.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/uS7beNd.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/S8ns5Uh.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/GNs7KYL.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/clvzCgI.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/0Mi06iL.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The Grand Prix Championship ain't for wimps! Sever drivers from around the World all want that #1 spot. Take the Cyber Car to victory over some of the meanest courses ever devised? Competing requires fast reflexes and cool nerves. Swerve through tight curves, past bottomless canyons and high above City streets. Don't let a single car get past you - to win you gotta drive as if your life depends on it. Every course is increasingly more difficult. Rise to the challenge and make our way through the toughest terrain that countries as Peru, Kenya, Spain, England, and America have to offer.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/59baf374-a825-45d6-ad15-11082a72d42e.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/114780fe-bf4d-4d29-8976-2167ea6f02c2.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/989a9613-3ea5-4ba4-8a91-22a42b103427.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5cd1783c-6657-4664-a5eb-80db4133c0a6.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c73cde5b-96b9-4e04-b31b-0d94b4348461.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Takara</Publisher>
</game>