<Game>
	<Name>Daffy Duck - The Marvin Missions (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Daffy Duck: The Marvin Missions is an action game from ICOM Simulations which was published by SunSoft. Daffy Duck stars as Duck Dodgers and has to fight his way through a variety of levels filled with traps set by Marvin the Martian in order to restore order to the galaxy.Daffy Duck: The Marvin Missions was released on the Super Nintendo and the Game Boy. The Game Boy version was named Daffy Duck in Europe, and Looney Tunes Series: Daffy Duck in Japan.Gameplay:Mixing platformer and shooter gameplay, like Contra or Earthworm Jim, Daffy Duck: The Marvin Missions features the irascible duck in his space hero Duck Dodgers persona heading across stages on Mars with his trusty blaster. In addition to the default gun, which has an infinite number of bullets, Duck Dodger can also pick up special guns with limited ammo that he can switch between. Duck Dodgers also has a jet pack with limited fuel, which can be used to fly over trickier platforming sequences.The extra fuel and weapons can be found in stages, either lying around or after defeating enemies, and can also be purchased before each mission with funds the player can collect. The player can also buy Continue Gems and Extra Lives before each stage, but they have a relatively high cost.Cheat: Codes</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sun Corporation of America</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>FyFCDlN0YNo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>283</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588270-daffy-duck-the-marvin-missions</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/daffy-duck-the-marvin-missions</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/daffy-duck-the-marvin-missions/3030-18031/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/cz0OV78.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/3Kg66b2.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/NH2TeVp.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/1KRFLrd.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wiFxr0f.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/soUSkMR.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/QciMtIM.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/8LRfcFo.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/6wfb32y.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/2mtYoCL.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/zUSdd5w.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/dxP8MGr.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/XuFyfvo.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/ncOSuaR.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/vadKkpx.png</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/YklADQ3.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Xemft7M.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Get ready to duck and cover. Because the fate of the planets rests squarely on Duck Dodgers--alias Daffy Duck--the fearless space crusader from the cartoon adventure series. Marvin Martian, the extra-fiendish extraterrestrial, is poised to obliterate the galaxy! So choose your weapon. Then help Daffy race from planet to planet in hot pursuit of the outrageous alien. Search secret chambers and caverns for mystery bonuses! Help Daffy shield himself from needles fired by crazed cactus! Block an onslaught of enemy space mines! Battle an undersea army of Instant Martians (just add water). Finally, look down the barrel of Marvin Martian's P-38 Space Modulator--with its destructive sights set on Earth!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3ca7116f-236a-4e34-9edf-e0c1535932ea.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/634b0a1f-1360-48e1-861d-e35601ff86e4.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e42983a5-cafc-4568-a49b-3bd6b9f440e0.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/686b05c7-1535-457f-b3b1-6a169dc40be1.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/087f450c-9c46-4899-9b98-89688b88299f.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fa91c9e3-b99b-4371-8486-a5ae642cbc7b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/22117122-8e6c-433f-a496-81d40fa64a1d.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sunsoft</Publisher>
</game>