<Game>
	<Name>Dai-3-ji Super Robot Taisen (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dai-3-Ji Super Robot Taisen ("3rd Super Robot Wars") is the third game in Banpresto's immense Super Robot Wars/Taisen series. It was originally released on the Super Famicom in 1993, the first in the series for that particular console, and was rereleased in a compilation for the PlayStation in 1999 (it was also released on PlayStation as a standalone game).Story:Six months after the DC War (as chronicled in Super Robot Wars 2), the DC seems to be regaining their former combat strength thanks to the Zabi family. In response, the United Nations has decided to reorganize itself into the Earth Federation.The heroes of the last war are formed into a unit known as Londo Bell; however, the Earth Federation distrusts them due to their immense power, and provides them with as few resources as they can...Featured SeriesA list of the anime series which are featured in the game. Series that premiered in the Super Robot Wars series in this game are marked with "(new)".Mobile Suit GundamMobile Suit Gundam 0080: War in the Pocket (new)Mobile Suit Gundam 0083: Stardust Memory (new)Mobile Suit Zeta GundamMobile Suit Gundam ZZMobile Suit Gundam: Char's CounterattackMobile Suit Gundam F91Mazinger ZGreat MazingerUFO Robo GrendizerGetter RoboGetter Robo GBrave Raideen (new)Super Electromagnetic Robot Combattler V (new)Invincible Steel Man Daitarn 3 (new)Banpresto Originals (original characters created for the game)New FeaturesInterchangeable Pilots: Pilots from the same timeline can use just about any mecha from their respective timeline. For example, Amuro Ray can pilot the Zeta Gundam and Sayaka Yumi (Mazinger Z) can pilot Great Mazinger.Pilot and Robot Stats: Because of the feature above, pilot and robot stats have been split. For example, HP is handled by the robot while Spirit Commands (seishin) are handled by the pilot.Ammo and EN System: Many attacks are now limited by ammo count or the robot's EN rating. EN is also drained by moving while flying in the air or in space.Upgradeable Robots: The player can use their funds to upgrade a robot's HP, EN, Armor, and Limit.Branching Paths: This game often has seperate paths. The path that the player embarks on is usually chosen in a cutscene, although some are also based on actions on the battlefield. Branching paths have been included in almost every Super Robot Wars game since.Alternate Endings: There are three endings in this game, one of which includes a secret stage.Battle Backgrounds: While battles in the first two games took place on a blank screen, SRW 3 uses backgrounds based on where the current unit is standing.Cheat: Sound TestDuring any scenario, go to an empty square and press A (menu button), third-last option (SYSTEM), press A (confirm), and go to third option (SOUND).</plot>
	<releasedate>23/7/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Sci-Fi</genre>
	<Developer>WinkySoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>W88v9q3sgbc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3546</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581822-dai-3-ji-super-robot-taisen</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/dai-3-ji-super-robot-taisen_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dai-3-ji-super-robot-taisen/3030-23084/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/auCna75.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/jecceWz.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/QRtGbyv.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qzHZLos.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/JQUIKa0.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Aacmgy8.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/5ldRLFl.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/YfbrFQy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ABYVFGS.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/cmCch3z.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/RAX9zFR.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/I5ESFfm.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ANTCE2h.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/0QMt79l.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dai-3-Ji Super Robot Taisen ("3rd Super Robot Wars") is the third game in Banpresto's immense Super Robot Wars/Taisen series.Six months after the DC War (as chronicled in Super Robot Wars 2), the DC seems to be regaining their former combat strength thanks to the Zabi family. In response, the United Nations has decided to reorganize itself into the Earth Federation. The heroes of the last war are formed into a unit known as Londo Bell; however, the Earth Federation distrusts them due to their immense power, and provides them with as few resources as they can...</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2f54fb9d-8a39-401b-bc6e-606e68805aab.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dcfd040a-0087-48ec-b273-b440e91d9a0b.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Banpresto</Publisher>
</game>