<Game>
	<Name>Dai-4-ji Super Robot Taisen (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Dai-4-Ji Super Robot Taisen is a Strategy game, developed by WinkySoft and published by Banpresto,which was released in Japan in 1995.Cheat: Quick loadWhile the word Banpresto is being displayed in the screen, hold the select button. The game will then bring you directly into your last save. </plot>
	<releasedate>17/3/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Sci-Fi</genre>
	<Developer>WinkySoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3547</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588179-dai-4-ji-super-robot-taisen</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/dai-3-ji-super-robot-taisen_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dai-3-ji-super-robot-taisen/3030-23084/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/auCna75.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/i5Xr0nA.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/QRtGbyv.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qzHZLos.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/JQUIKa0.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Aacmgy8.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/5ldRLFl.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/sIbDGYs.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/JejoTIf.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/4GiJifL.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/CsZdxJ4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/g525X4X.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ANTCE2h.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/w49VwFU.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dai-4-Ji Super Robot Taisen (literally "4th Super Robot Wars") is a strategy RPG and the fifth game - including the previous "gaiden" Super Robot Taisen EX - in their Super Robot Taisen (Super Robot Wars) crossover series which brings together characters from various mecha anime, including but not limited to Gundam, Mazinger and Getter Robo. A few months after the battle with the Inspectors (Super Robot Wars 3), the Earth Federation's economy is in shambles; to add to the problem, spacenoids (people living in space colonies) have begun to commit terrorist attacks. To counter these acts, Jamitov Hymem creates the Titans, an elite group whose strength gives them a great deal of influence in the Federation. A huge contributing factor to the Titans' swift rise to power is the drastic downscaling of the Londo Bell unit due to their sudden disappearance during the La Gias incident (Super Robot Wars EX). To make matters worse, the ever-scheming Haman Karn creates the Neue Divine Crusaders on the asteroid Axis. The spacenoids fully support the Neue DC due to their treatment by the Earth Federation, which makes this group extremely powerful. However, the old DC is still not dead. Under the command of Don Zauser, the original DC has amazingly regained its power once again; they are ready to strike a third time. Fortunately, there is hope. Quattro Bajeena, who was chased out of the Federation Army, forms the Anti-Earth Union Group to oppose the Earth's current government...</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4d2e2a33-fcce-468d-94f5-83bdb19d5f6c.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e7a821ab-f84f-4e37-b434-0a0c0551fdb1.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a019df38-327f-4f27-b58f-6bc52f323ddf.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Banpresto</Publisher>
</game>