<Game>
	<Name>Daikaijuu Monogatari (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Daikaijuu Monogatari ("Great Shell Monster Story") is a RPG with monster-recruiting elements and the sequel to the Famicom game Kaijuu Monogatari. Like its predecessor, the player controls the player-named Fire Shell Champion, which grants them dominion over the element of fire. The Champion recruits shell creatures to fight alongside them as he attempts to protect the rest of the shell creature race. Combat follows the standard Dragon Quest turn-based format.In Daikaijuu Monogatari the Fire Shell Champion is once again summoned into service when a mysterious alien entity crash lands into an ocean, causing a catastrophic tidal wave and spawning mysterious eggs across the world.The game was followed by a Daikaijuu Monogatari RPG sequel: Daikaijuu Monogatari II. Later sequels would adopt a trading card game format.												</plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson Soft Company, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>29689</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581805-daikaijyuu-monogatari</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/daikaij-monogatari</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/daikaijuu-monogatari/3030-7470/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/vtHuvpM.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/dUaRoXN.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/lsHb7fe.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/1cUk6f8.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/9YqIRDv.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/HJhqHxb.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/evoka8j.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/wTwxk2p.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/zrTAJpA.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/GtBokx1.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/SoHg2IM.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JhgCmGC.gif</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/L57pn5l.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In this clone of Dragon Quest, there are a series of natural disasters that are devastating the planet; causing the great Demon King Fattobajah to emerge from his elemental shell-induced slumber. A hero who carries a fire shell must save the world from a series of truly bad events. Up to ten playable characters can be used as allies in order to stop villains like Dr. Doan, Jalamar, Jodan, and Darkness Knight. The people who inhabit the land of Shelldorado are very smart despite looking like savage monsters.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2fe9c710-c6af-43a1-a0fb-f30f0442415c.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3ecda7c1-b6dc-4270-a1b5-c6f09fc7fb05.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>