<Game>
	<Name>Daisenryaku Expert (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Daisenryaku ("Great Strategy") Expert is a military strategy game from SystemSoft and the eighth in their Daisenryaku series. As with many others in the series, the goal is to defeat the other side by taking over key strategic locations, use those locations to produce new units and overwhelm the enemy forces who are busy attempting to do the same to the player. These scenarios play out with one player moving all their units, and then allowing the opponent to take their turn. In these respects, it is not dissimilar to Intelligent Systems' Nintendo Wars series.The "Expert" subtitle was added to the Super Famicom games in the series. The next (and last) Super Famicom game was titled Daisenryaku Expert WWII: War in Europe, which was released four years later.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/9/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Wargame, Turn-Based</genre>
	<Developer>SystemSoft</Developer>
	<VideoURL>Q33aKMeI1KU</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581883-daisenryaku-expert</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/daisenryaku-expert/3030-44362/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/BMdOURm.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/XVudGmo.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/A7QhQNB.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ZEsbWUJ.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wzU8N82.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Z0QZscR.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/QwVXbDE.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ygqGXAX.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/XFtTIZt.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/10eI4ix.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/NBENDyz.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/6NaF5IT.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/NPS9mYd.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/BPUqJoJ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Daisenryaku ("Great Strategy") Expert is a military strategy game from SystemSoft and the eighth in their Daisenryaku series. As with many others in the series, the goal is to defeat the other side by taking over key strategic locations, use those locations to produce new units and overwhelm the enemy forces who are busy attempting to do the same to the player. These scenarios play out with one player moving all their units, and then allowing the opponent to take their turn. In these respects, it is not dissimilar to Intelligent Systems' Nintendo Wars series. The "Expert" subtitle was added to the Super Famicom games in the series. The next (and last) Super Famicom game was titled Daisenryaku Expert WWII: War in Europe, which was released four years later</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8f292436-de99-4840-be6c-181b8895868f.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b23536f5-b110-4ff3-9510-3d56a1301e47.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/208081c5-72c6-4a3e-9cc9-2e4625473d8f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ce631649-8e49-41b6-8fe3-49528cd339f9.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>ASCII Entertainment Software</Publisher>
</game>