<Game>
	<Name>Daisenryaku Expert WWII - War in Europe (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Daisenryaku Expert WWII - War in Europe is a Strategy game, developed by SystemSoft and published by ASCII Entertainment,which was released in Japan in 1996.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/8/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Wargame, Turn-Based</genre>
	<Developer>SystemSoft</Developer>
	<VideoURL>I02gtU5sqc0</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581884-daisenryaku-expert-wwii-war-in-europe</gamefaqs_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daisenryaku#Daisenryaku_Expert_WWII:_War_in_Europe</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Tdg0cPl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/7c1JMsd.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/2QepWLi.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/eL3OT98.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/AbZEQLJ.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/57FrQKK.jpg</snapshot4>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/rewAV9f.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>A military turn based strategy game. it’s played on a hex based map where units can moved around. There is a scenario mode and a campaign mode. The player usually controls the Third Reich as a default but it can be changed prior to the game. The action takes place on both the Eastern Front and the Western front. The final battle involves either defending Berlin or attempting to occupy it. Like most Daisenryaku games, airplanes can only be manufactured on airports, ships can only be manufactured on docks, and land-based units can only be manufactured on urban hexes that are closest to the headquarters. Dive bombers can destroy cities and airports, destroying people and supplies. Even when retreating, enemy combatants can still catch up to the retreating units and knock them out, providing that they have enough ammo and gasoline to do the job.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b4a91fe9-12bd-4310-bca5-aef4581c1dd3.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b815148f-0dc9-4ce3-bfb9-6a84b5e416cb.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1f2c709f-5efa-484d-bb4e-aa751083414d.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8ce4feaa-97b8-44da-8525-9894bf51955c.png</snapshot6>
	<Publisher>ASCII Entertaintment</Publisher>
</game>