<Game>
	<Name>Dark Kingdom (Japan) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Dark Kingdom lets you experience a traditional story of a Japanese RPG from "the other side". In this game, you play the role of a mercenary named Gene Dorman. Instead of becoming a world-saving paladin, Gene joins forces with the Demon King himself! He offers his services to him and receives from him various assignments. Gene doesn't yet know that fate will make his path cross with that of the "good" hero Lux, with whom he shares a mysterious connection...Gene must complete the missions of the Demon King in a specified order, and each time he completes a mission, his rank raises, allowing him access to higher levels of the hierarchy of the Demon King Castle, new abilities, etc. Other servants of the Demon King join him on his mission, and fight together with him as a party. The battles are turn-based and are viewed from first-person perspective. The game has an internal clock with day and night cycle.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/4/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Telenet Japan Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>oNbXmwSjLnw</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571071-dark-kingdom</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/dark-kingdom</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dark-kingdom/3030-9291/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/R5iQUt2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/CjESjmj.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/RXMoEGk.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/zX31MES.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/o4n4h7b.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/UkOSXTj.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/PT7ls1v.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/du3d5O5.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/S2sGFof.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/QHWZje4.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/zGZnSZZ.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/pQM74nc.gif</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/biYOH4L.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The object is to play an evil mercenary named Gene Dorman. Instead of trying to save the world from an evil demon king, he joins forces with him in order to complete missions. Accomplishing each mission allows access to stronger allies, better abilities in addition to promotions in military rank. Sometime in the game, Gene meets up with the so-called "hero" Lux; sharing an undiscovered connection in the process. There is an external clock than can differentiate between day and night. Statues of the Demon King can be found in villages where the people pledge their allegiance to their leader. Players must also engage in random combat; ranging from wildlife to hostile castle guards.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>oNbXmwSjLnw</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f6ddc9d4-6d1a-4925-b14a-457a7c484ba7.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/455048a5-f366-42fc-bba2-3d24ec9d6df7.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Telenet Japan</Publisher>
</game>