<Game>
	<Name>David Crane's Amazing Tennis (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:David Crane's Amazing Tennis is a tennis simulation game from Absolute Entertainment and Imagineering for the Genesis and Super Nintendo platforms. Legendary game designer David Crane, creator of Pitfall, lends his name to this trailblazing take on a truly 3D version of tennis in which the camera behind the court and players can move on a z-axis to simulate depth of field, rather than having a fixed bird's eye view of the court as was the standard at the time. The game's realism also demands greater accuracy from the player, with them having to choose the right moment to serve the ball and return volleys.The single-player mode has a selection of fictional seeded tennis players to compete against on grass, clay or hard courts in single matches or in tournaments. There is also a two-player mode available for both console versions. Regardless of how many human players are playing, the serving player is always in the foreground with the receiving player in the far background.Cheat: Easy ModeWhen selecting your oppenent, enter _CRANE_DUDE_ as your name.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Absolute Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>1745</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588272-david-cranes-amazing-tennis</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/david-cranes-amazing-tennis</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/david-cranes-amazing-tennis/3030-22384/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/04wxyXq.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/FoDzjx3.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/TVOar9T.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/h3DKweT.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/so4K8rY.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/7jJxKmH.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/qxco4xo.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/j2vRGto.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/H2EAmNJ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/9iS31TP.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/BhV5jBt.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/iniKi2R.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/TkL4Udi.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/6Lqiwz9.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Trade in your racquet for a game controller. The category of sports home video games has just taken a quantum leap forward into a new dimension of realism - David Crane's Amazing Tennis! Developed by David Crane, an industry pioneer and one of the best-selling game designers of all time, Amazing Tennis redefines the term "state of the art." Every aspect of play has been re-created to ensure a precision feel and accuracy other tennis video games can't match. Amazing Tennis utilizes 22 different planes of depth and motion-picture-quality animation to provide a revolutionary gaming experience - the next best thing to being out there on the court yourself!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cfe9b907-095c-4e9f-af25-fddfb521816e.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/52b5e2b4-ef10-4297-8967-a176b85a7200.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/208c45b6-c1aa-4517-8980-d124d00a070f.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8fd65591-6893-4871-8939-1ff722c406fd.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d17ed9f0-8197-4c88-b576-b508d45c2dbb.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Absolute Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>