<Game>
	<Name>Dead Dance (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Tuff E Nuff is an Action game, developed and published by Jaleco Entertainment,which was released in Japan in 1993.Cheat: CodesIn Story mode or vs. CPU, start a game. Select your character and any boss character on the 2P side. When the round starts, pause the game and press Select on both controllers simultaneously. If done correctly, you will hear an explosion sound. When you unpause the game the 2nd player can control the boss character. You can play as any boss in vs CPU except for Jado. You have to play story mode and reach him to play as him. Note when you activate the code the 2nd player bosses are playable including in story mode and stay that way. So you can easily beat the game in Hard Mode. If you want to reverse it and have the CPU control the character again. Same process, pause, select on both controllers, explosion sound.Cheat: CodesThis is to allow Bosses to be playable in the Two-Player ModeInput the Boss code, hit the Reset button, then input the code listed below.Note:  The Boss code for One Player MUST be inputed first or the Two-Player code will not work.Cheat: CodesCheat: Kotonos PasswordsThe password screen can be found after choosing Story Mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>KpEqklvgeM0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2211</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588812-tuff-e-nuff</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XBlrOsg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/apOEqb8.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/J5ZlJsL.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/bN195Hs.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/9wBlErh.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/L3LxsMw.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/7UBhM1x.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VWPjCHJ.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ALNOIez.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/b96rQa6.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/3XHQxXB.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ZucLXyK.png</clearlogo1>
</game>