<Game>
	<Name>Dear Boys (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dear Boys is a 1994 Super Famicom basketball game based on the manga of the same name. The game features both a story mode, which follows the plot of the manga, and an exhibition mode that allows the player to go straight into a match.The game features a "dramatic" perspective that is also slightly turn-based, similar to the Captain Tsubasa games. A window demonstrates what is happening - a ball is passed, a shot is thrown, the tip-off - in dramatic comic book style that is reminiscent of the manga. While a player's athlete has the ball, the player can pull up a menu that allows them to choose to pass, shoot or look at the present characters stats - each character has their own strengths and weaknesses that the player should keep in mind.Dear Boys would eventually be followed by a Konami PS2 game based on the same property named Dear Boys: Fast Break!, which was released in 2003. The manga has no exposure outside of Japan, and so neither game would see an international release.Cheat: Mizuho womens team (Exhibition mode)At the team selection screen... press A while holding Select and X. The jersey will change to white-pink, meaning that the Mizuho women's team was chosen.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Kan's</Developer>
	<VideoURL>_qgmz5wi4rU</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581966-dear-boys</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dear-boys/3030-37381/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/AjqUSok.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/1iNB5DR.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Gpi2Hrb.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/vT09YcH.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/kyRUnet.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Jmfi0Iu.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/gMqn0ZB.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/XtIogY7.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/aBIN2kA.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/0weWckP.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/WQrM4by.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/3jgj5yO.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/aIeTqRQ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dear Boys is a 1994 Super Famicom basketball game based on the manga of the same name. The game features both a story mode, which follows the plot of the manga, and an exhibition mode that allows the player to go straight into a match. The game features a "dramatic" perspective that is also slightly turn-based, similar to the Captain Tsubasa games. A window demonstrates what is happening - a ball is passed, a shot is thrown, the tip-off - in dramatic comic book style that is reminiscent of the manga. While a player's athlete has the ball, the player can pull up a menu that allows them to choose to pass, shoot or look at the present characters stats - each character has their own strengths and weaknesses that the player should keep in mind. Dear Boys would eventually be followed by a Konami PS2 game based on the same property named Dear Boys: Fast Break!, which was released in 2003. The manga has no exposure outside of Japan, and so neither game would see an international release.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e57df3aa-a76a-4741-b05b-86dce3a2a900.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/001e20e2-9f86-4ba2-9dba-b6d2e21d32db.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99e0a062-8a19-44fa-908b-25e1a9e3dcc9.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f8caab03-3ced-4d8a-8672-2a6fee35b872.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f4d50bcf-9bbf-4d4a-9135-dcf73b197bef.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Yutaka</Publisher>
</game>