<Game>
	<Name>Dennis the Menace (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Before the actual playing takes place, Dennis has just discovered that he left Mr. Wilson's door unlocked, and a thief has stolen Mr. Wilson's entire coin collection. Dennis must retrieve all of the coins before Mr. Wilson finds out. The games starts out in Mr. Wilson's house, in which there are 4 main coins that must be found. However, there are smaller coins which do not affect gameplay, only score. Once the four main coins are found, the final coin (which cannot be attained until the previous 4 coins are found) is touchable, leading Dennis onto the next stage. The next set of stages are given titles, with the naming process being as such: "Name #", replacing "Name" with the title of the set, and "#" with the subsequent level of the set (up to 6).The same coin-collection game is present throughout the rest of the game (with the exception of two stages in the first park stage set, wherein Dennis must traverse the park on a wagon led by his dog). After each sixth level, there is a boss stage, followed by a new set of levels. The sets of levels are, in order, Mr. Wilson's House, Park, Boiler Room, Sewers, and finally, Woods. The end of the woods levels, and the subsequent beating of the final boss, marks the end of the game.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dennis_the_Menace_(video_game)</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform, Side-Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Ocean Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>ZvAOG4DHOPE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1749</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588276-dennis-the-menace</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/dennis-the-menace</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dennis-the-menace/3030-35799/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/fPJjSbH.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/1RRqqRa.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/egFOEYR.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/pLfrx3I.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/eho7CeH.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/RmoLErX.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/nMYVjCZ.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/6rNP9oY.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/A0aPevN.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/qJvkxUx.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ZH06XEo.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Zooggb7.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/mpiAvDk.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/TuBWZfb.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/rEanEfv.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/eFVLXkf.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Yipes! Grab your slingshot, water pistol and peashooter. Margaret and Joey, Dennis' loyal friends, are missing and so is Mr. Wilson's valuable coin collection! Can Dennis sneak into Mr. Wilson's house and find his slingshot and peashooter without being spotted? Uh oh, he's got rope ladders to climb and hidden switches to find - it's going to be tough. But he's gonna need those weapons bad as he faces off with enemies like the the crazed Coach, and the scary Switchblade Sam. On this late-night escapade, bees, bulldogs, birds, frogs and even bunnies will be a menace to Dennis. Finding Joey, Margaret and Mr. Wilson's coin collection will be an adventure more harrowing than a garden full of cheek pinchers - and you know what Mr. Wilson says, "that's no g. d. (gosh darn) joke!"</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a6c99986-a934-4967-be2a-09864613956d.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3fb1d0d2-2466-4e77-b47b-8c957bf62d58.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a0878a6e-f8bc-4f57-ba8f-5b7a50144fff.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/61e5d151-faa4-4c96-a3b4-f0ee7b6cb6d7.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a948e73-61aa-4c5a-a673-92817c177319.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Ocean Software</Publisher>
</game>