<Game>
	<Name>Dig & Spike Volleyball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:This game offers both indoor volleyball and beach volleyball. Players can compete solo against the computer or against another player in indoor volleyball. The same two options are available for beach volleyball in addition to competing with another player against the computer.The indoor volleyball side also features a training mode and a World Cup tournament mode while the beach volleyball side has a World Challenge mode.The game features eight playable teams for indoor volleyball:AlgeriaBrazilCubaCommonwealth of Independent States (former Soviet Union countries)ItalyJapanThe NetherlandsUnited StatesFor beach volleyball, there are eight teams named Spikers, Diggers, etc. that have different Power, Jump, and Speed ratings.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson Soft USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>Aa-d3b4x8BM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3552</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588279-dig-and-spike-volleyball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/dig-spike-volleyball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dig-spike-volleyball/3030-37346/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/nOZIBFK.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/eGtLuGm.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Gjlb3Ae.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/eaztPXM.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/7zZfdTU.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/tYhvqwo.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/mGhDt40.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/XNldl74.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/2xMbxKW.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/OGHst6H.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2uj4hSr.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/J5BaJc4.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Bugs3VF.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/X6Xgh5P.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/OEEAXbU.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Two Volleyball Games In One! Run to the net for a last-second block - drive in the sand for an unbelievable save - launch a power-serve that aces right past your opponents - and smash the ball into the hardwood floor with a killer spike! All this and more is yours in Dig &amp; Spike Volleyball! Take to the courts with a 6-man team and compete against teams from around the world - each one willing to sacrifice all for the hold! Or, pick the hottest babes in 2-man teams and play for the ultimate glory on the Beach Volleyball Circuit! Either game offers the thrillers and challenges of Pro-Volleyball! Master the multiple serving techniques to keep your opponent guessing. Play close to the net to block a spike right back at the other team! Choose the exact moment to sail the return into the far corner of the other side. Strategy, timing and and a little luck will take you all the way to the top in Dig &amp; Spike Volleyball!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/07b994cb-2d24-487d-a276-01e8d7db6a12.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e53fa65d-6d72-4ba1-be69-e68c384359fe.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/017f447f-c671-452a-8082-c95bbf48a7eb.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2e165a10-8491-4e96-9c1d-7bb734bcf6c1.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>