<Game>
	<Name>Dolucky no A.League Soccer (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dolucky no A.League Soccer is a 1994 soccer game featuring the Coca-Cola mascot Dolucky, and his other soft drink mascot pals. Like Capcom's Mega Man Soccer, the game uses a horizontal perspective of the pitch and gives players certain special abilities they can use while playing, though they're limited by a recharging power bar.The player can select between a Tour Mode, which also features story cutscenes and boss fights, or the standard Vs. Mode. They have a choice of four teams: The Red Hot Doluckies (cats), the Pochi Funky Dogs (dogs), the Devid Rabbit Rockers (rabbits) and the Goro Wild Bears (bears).The game was exclusive to Japan and the Super Famicom.Soundtrack:01Title Screen00:1302Storyline02:4403Team Profile01:2404Main Menu01:0305Theme of Red Hot Doluckys02:0806Theme of Pochi Funky Dogs02:4607Theme of Debid Rabbit Rockers03:5308Theme of Goro Wild Bears02:4809Goal!00:0410Goal Celebration ~ Red Hot Doluckys00:0711Goal Celebration ~ Pochi Funky Dogs00:0812Goal Celebration ~ Debid Rabbit Rockers00:0813Goal Celebration ~ Goro Wild Bears00:0714Own Goal ~ Red Hot Doluckys00:0315Own Goal ~ Pochi Funky Dogs00:0416Own Goal ~ Debid Rabbit Rockers00:0417Own Goal ~ Goro Wild Bears00:0418Half Time Status02:3619Half Time Show01:2520P.K.00:1321P.K. ~ Goalie Blocks!00:0222P.K. ~ Goal!00:0323End of Game00:0424Next Tour Mode Game00:0725A New Rival Has Arrived!00:0226Stop Dr. Yamada's Evil Scheme!02:2027Defeated Dr. Yamada!00:0428Theme of Jet Mole Dangerous03:1729Goal Celebration ~ Jet Mole Dangerous00:0830Own Goal ~ Jet Mole Dangerous00:0431Ending03:47Cheat: Bonus ModeWait for the logo to start to appear. The code you should enter at the Title Screen is: Up left down right B right down left up Y left right up down X L R. If done correctly, you will hear a piece of sound effect. Then you can press Start and you will access the Bonus Mode. The Bonus Mode appears to allow you to modify the speed. It also allows you to unlock Jet Mole Dangerous, which is the last opponent you face and is normally not playable. Plus, it has a setting to activate VS. All-Star (which turns each team in VS. Mode into a set of team captains from each team and disables the team selection screen), and the bottom-most option appears to allow all team members to become the Captain character.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/7/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Zoom</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>GCE8WK5OINM</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571088-doluckys-a-league-soccer</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dolucky-no-aleague-soccer/3030-37840/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/z2LhuAj.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/xIPvIhi.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Cz8z1Ug.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lJVy6NK.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/pRHxGfI.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/KWpa3uk.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vgzO7TW.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/FLcQOii.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BwJWZ3T.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/55NZBzA.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/06S6CSn.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/2DCOtzY.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/zQiPXJv.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The Wild Bears have issued at challenge, and the whole town is down with soccer. Neco Dolucky isn't about to lay in the sun and sit this one out. He assembles his friends and enters his team, The Red Hot Doluckies, to challenge all on-comers to a heated battle.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9f1e70df-8e5b-424b-b376-f7a902e25a19.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bed05e07-7890-41f7-8b9b-22e879e03478.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Imagineer</Publisher>
</game>