<Game>
	<Name>Dolucky no Puzzle Tour '94 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dolucky no Puzzle Tour '94 is a puzzle game featuring Zoom Inc.'s mascot character Dolucky the cat. It was released for the Super Famicom in 1994 and would be the last ever game featuring Dolucky.The game is a mix of Bust-a-Move and Tetris, where the goal is to fire colored blocks at an encroaching wave of same. If five blocks of the same color are touching, they vanish. Certain blocks, gray in color, cannot be removed unless they're touching five colored blocks as they vanish: the goal is to quickly fire five blocks to remove these before they reach the player character at the bottom of the screen. There are also random power-ups that can be acquired. The blocks have facial expressions that change depending on the number of similar blocks they're touching, allowing the player to see how close they are to clearing them if the top of the screen cuts it off. Smiling or grinning suggests that there's three or four in contact.Cheat: Computer operating your character...VS Battle... in the character selection screen, choose your character by... pressing A while holding down the X... and the gameplay will be done by the computer.Cheat: Computer operating your character...VS Battle... after selecting your character, the screen showing the rules will appear. Choose them and then just press the Start by holding down the Select... and you will hear a different piece of sound effect.Cheat: Computer operating your character...Options mode... Move the cursor to the music... then hold L or R while selecting the tracks... and the number 12 and 13 will appear.Cheat: Computer operating your character...Title screen... when the music starts playing just press L R L R L R... If done correctly, you will hear a piece of sound effect... and the character will be selectable in VS mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Zoom</Developer>
	<VideoURL>kF3jQqGk0CU</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571160-dolucky-no-puzzle-tour-94</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dolucky-no-puzzle-tour-94/3030-37873/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/vKpgfgJ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/hdvkd9l.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/kqieXTJ.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/BC76iLb.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Y0YdRd6.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/izLCpOh.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/GTNmRCg.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/htZ0pLL.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IF9WSu9.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/48UnApA.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/9TpPvPd.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/F2EfzdU.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NORtB8C.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/JU6OzAh.png</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/9Oeu5cC.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dolucky no Puzzle Tour '94 is a puzzle game featuring Zoom Inc.'s mascot character Dolucky the cat. It was released for the Super Famicom in 1994 and would be the last ever game featuring Dolucky. The game is a mix of Bust-a-Move and Tetris, where the goal is to fire colored blocks at an encroaching wave of same. If five blocks of the same color are touching, they vanish. Certain blocks, gray in color, cannot be removed unless they're touching five colored blocks as they vanish: the goal is to quickly fire five blocks to remove these before they reach the player character at the bottom of the screen. There are also random power-ups that can be acquired. The blocks have facial expressions that change depending on the number of similar blocks they're touching, allowing the player to see how close they are to clearing them if the top of the screen cuts it off. Smiling or grinning suggests that there's three or four in contact.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d57ef2d7-4bfb-463c-86da-13a0a53223a0.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/79057e68-33e2-44c2-a6d3-46960de1fc0d.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/571a9e7a-4377-45a1-9efb-81bbbf80e1a7.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6e7b4cac-fab2-43e8-918f-935953063f97.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/90cbb311-e142-432e-a5ff-3e23aafcff96.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Imagineer</Publisher>
</game>