<Game>
	<Name>Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest (USA) (En,Fr) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Donkey Kong Country 2: Diddy's Kong Quest a 2D platformer released in 1995 for the SNES, developed by Rare and published by Nintendo. The game consists of many levels divided into different worlds ending with boss battles. As the player clears more and more worlds they'll climb higher and higher on the island called Crocodile Isle until they reach the final boss, Kaptain K. Rool. All the worlds look very different and they all have their own themes. The game also contains multiple bonus stages and secret levels giving the game more diversity than it's sequel.DKC2 has sold almost 4.4 million copies (making it the 6th best-selling game for SNES) and was released on the Wii Virtual Console on May 21, 2007 for 800 points. It has also been ported to the Game Boy Advance with notable changes in the gameplay, added levels, and an extra boss.It's worth noting that the grammatically incorrect title is a play on words. The title can be read either as Diddy's Kong Quest or Diddy's Conquest.Story:The story begins as Diddy Kong discovers a ransom note left by long-time villain King K. Rool (now going by Kaptain K. Rool) demanding that the banana horde stolen by the Kong gang in the previous game be returned, in exchange for Donkey Kong. Diddy and his girlfriend Dixie Kong must run, roll and jump their way through the many stages set on Crocodile Isle and the various bosses sent at them from K. Rool. The duo must occasionally call upon their gang of Animal Buddies introduced in the previous game to make their way across more difficult areas.ItemsBananas: A common item in the DKC universe that come in singles and bunches of 10. Collecting 100 bananas will earn the player an extra life.Banana Coins: Used as currency to purchase services from various members of the Kong family (i.e. Swanky Kong's Bonus Bonanza). In the Game Boy Advance version they can also be used to fight a rematch against a defeated boss. They can be found throughout most of the levels of the game.Kremkoins: Used to bribe Klubba into allowing Diddy and Dixie access to the Lost World. These are given as rewards for completing bonus games that are accessed via bonus barrels. Typically there are two to three bonus barrels to be found in each level.Characters:Kong FamilyDixie Kong: Diddy Kong's girlfriend and one of the protagonists of the game. Dixie is slower than Diddy but can twirl her long ponytail to slow her decent helping her reach further distances. She can also use her pony tail to defeat enemies.Diddy Kong: Donkey Kong's sidekick and boyfriend of Dixie Kong. Diddy Kong is quick and can use a cartwheel attack to defeat enemies.Cranky Kong: Donkey Kong's father and the original Donkey Kong from the arcade game. He helps Diddy and Dixie by giving them tips and hints on levels. He is also the host of the minigame Expresso Racing in the Game Boy Advance version.Wrinkly Kong: Wife of Cranky Kong. She provides a place for Diddy and Dixie to save their game.Funky Kong: Owner of the Funky Flights service which allows Diddy and Dixie to travel to other areas of Crocodile Isle.Swanky Kong: Host of the game show Swanky's Bonus Bonanza where Diddy and Dixie can earn extra lives by answering quiz questions.Candy Kong: Only appears in the Game Boy Advance version as Swanky's assistant.Animal BuddiesRambi: A rhinoceros who also appeared in the original Donkey Kong Country. Rambi is able to use his horn to ram into enemies and has the ability to jump on any type of enemy (including Zingers) without getting hurt. He can also use a special charge attack which increases his speed for a short amount of time and gives him the ability to destroy breakable walls revealing secrets.Enguarde: A swordfish who, like Rambi, also appears in the first game. Also like Rambi, Enguarde possesses a special charge attack that increases his speed for a short amount of time and gives him the ability to destroy breakable walls. He can also use his pointy nose to pierce enemies.Squawks: A parrot who also appears in the original game. Squawks can fly and is able to attack enemies by shooting pellets out of his mouth. He can also aid the Kongs by holding a lantern in his talons to light up dark areas.Rattly: A Rattlesnake who makes his debut appearance in Donkey Kong Country 2. He can jump high and reach areas that the Kongs cannot. His special move is a charge jump that gives him the ability to jump extra high. He can jump on enemies to defeat them and, like Rambi, can jump on any type of enemy.Squitter: A spider who also makes his debut in this game. Squitter has the ability to create platforms made out of web helping him cross large gaps or reach new heights. He also has a web attack that can be used to defeat enemies, and he cannot jump on enemies without getting hurt.Clapper: A seal who, in Lava levels, can cool down the water for a short period of time making it safe to swim in for the Kongs. In one other level he actually freezes the water instead of cooling it down. This allows the Kongs to travel over the water avoiding the Snapjaws who lurk in the waterExpresso II: Not to be confused with the animal buddy named Expresso, Expresso II is an ostrich who is exclusive to the Game Boy Advance version of the game. Cranky Kong bought Expresso II in hopes of turning him into a racing bird. However, he starts out very weak and in order to build up his stats and increase his size the Kongs must collect golden feathers. Once he is strong enough he can be used to race against other ostriches in the minigame Expresso Racing.Glimmer: An angelfish who only appears in one level. He helps light the way for the Kongs in the dark waters of Glimmer's Galleon.Flapper: A parrot who is similar in appearance to Squawks except he is blue instead of green. Like Glimmer, Flapper only appears in one level where he helps the Kong descend through a hive of Zingers.BossesKrow: The boss of Gangplank Galleon, Krow is a large Mini Necky who wears a pirate hat. Krow will first attempt to drop an egg on the Kongs, then attempt to ram into them. He can be damaged by throwing his own eggs back at him. After taking a few hits he will begin ramming into his nest causing several eggs to fall out of it which can hurt the Kongs if they come into contact with them.Kleever: The boss of Crocodile Cauldron, Kleever is a giant sword who is possessed by a lava spirit. Kleever will attack the Kongs by throwing fireballs at them and after a set a number of fireballs have been thrown and cannonball will spawn. This cannonball can be thrown at Kleever to damage him. After being hit several hooks will appear spreading out along the top of the screen and Kleever will begin chasing after the Kongs attempting to slash them. The hooks can be used to avoid this attack.Kudgel: The boss of Krem Quay, Kudgel is a large kremling who looks similar to Klubba. He jumps into the air and attempts to land on the Kongs, when he lands he creates a shockwave which can paralyze the Kongs for a short period of time if they do not jump to avoid it. After doing this a few times he will swing his club then do a small jump which makes a TNT barrel appear. This barrel can be thrown at Kudgel to damage him. When low on health he will begin doing shorter jumps in quicker succession.King Zing: The boss of Krazy Kremland, King Zing is a giant Zinger who is fought using the animal buddy Squawks. In the first phase of the fight he will fly around the room in a pattern, Squawks can hurt him by firing a pellet at his stinger. Once hit he well turn red (making him temporarily invincible) and fire 3 sets of spikes in all directions. After a number of hits, the second phase of the fight will begin. King Zing turn into a normal sized red Zinger and he will be surrounded by normal Zingers. In order to make him vulnerable to attacks, all the Zingers surrounding him must be defeated. Once they are defeated King Zing will turn yellow and can be finished off.Kreepy Krow: The boss of Gloomy Gulch, Kreepy Krow is the undead ghost of the first boss in the game, Krow. He summons three ghost Mini Neckies to attack the Kongs, then one real one. After the Kongs defeat the real Mini Necky a barrel will appear that can be thrown at Kreepy Krow to hurt him. After he his hit he will fly upwards and the Kongs must climb up a ways to reach him. While climbing up, eggs will be falling from the sky which can hurt the Kongs. This pattern is repeated until the Kongs reach the top of his nest where one more hit will defeat him.Kaptain K. Rool: The final boss and main antagonist of the game, Kaptain K. Rool is King K. Rool in disguise. He attacks the Kongs by shooting cannon balls from his gun in various patterns and by sliding from one side of the room to the other. He can be hurt by throwing one of his cannonballs back into his gun causing it to explode in his face. After he is defeated Donkey Kong will break free from his ropes and uppercut King K. Rool into the waters of the Lost World. After beating all the levels of the Lost World, the Kongs can battle King K. Rool again and defeat him for good.MiscellaneousKlubba: A large kremling who guards the entrance to the Lost World. He can be bribed with fifteen Kremkoins in order to gain entrance to the Lost World. Attempting to fight Klubba will cause him to whack Diddy and Dixie out of the area with his large club.Worlds and LevelsDDK2 has a total of 7 worlds containing 41 levels. There is also a secret bonus world titled "Lost World" where there are 5 levels and a Boss fight.Gangplank GalleonPirate PanicMainbrace MayhemGangplank GalleyLockjaw's LockerTopsail TroubleBoss: Krow's NestCrocodile CauldronHot-Head HopKannon's KlaimLava LagoonRedhot RideSquawk's ShaftBoss: Kleaver's KilnKrem QuayBarrel BayouGlimmer's GalleonKrockhead KlamberRattle BattleSlime ClimbBramble BlastBoss: Kudgel's KontestKrazy KremlandHornet HoleTarget TerrorBramble ScrambleRickety RaceMudhole MarshRambi RumbleBoss: King Zing StingGloomy GulchGhostly GroveHaunted HallGusty GladeParrot Chute PanicWeb WoodsBoss: Kreepy KrowK. Rool's KeepArctic AbyssWindy WellCastle CrushClapper's CavernChain Link ChamberToxic TowerBoss: Stronghold ShowdownThe Flying KrockScreech's SprintBoss: K. Rool DuelSecret Area: Lost WorldJungle JinxBlack Ice BattleKlobber KarnageFiery FurnaceAnimal AnticsBoss: Krocodile KoreSoundtrack:Cover art of soundtrackThe musical score for Donkey Kong Country 2 is, like the first game, highly praised. The soundtrack was composed by David Wise and released in 1995.track listOpening FanfareK. Rool ReturnsWelcome to Crocodile IsleKlomp's RompLockjaw's SagaJib JigSwanky's SwingSnakey ChanteyBayou BoogieSchool House HarmonyForest InterludeFunky the Main MonkeyFlight of the ZingerCranky's CongaHot-Head BopRun, Rambi, Run!Token TangoStickerbush SymphonyBad Bird RagDisco TrainBoss BossanovaSteel Drum RhumbaKrook's MarchKlubba's ReveilleHaunted ChaseIn a Snow-Bound LandLost World AnthemPrimal RaveCrocodile CacophonyDonkey Kong RescuedStronghold ShowdownThe Flying KrockKannon's KlaimBonus IntroBonus DefeatBonus VictoryGame OverCheat: Access the Sound testWhen you get to the game select screen highlight two player contest and press down 5 times to get to music test and another 5 times to get to cheat mode. Once in cheat mode, press these buttons to activate the cheats:Cheat: Beat Screechs Sprint Without RacingOnce you get half way through "Screech's Sprint" you will transform into the bird, and, normally, you will fly up to Screech and the race will start.  If you come up right behind Screech to where the race will not start yet, and you fly upwards (you must have both characters at this point for this to work), you will then hit the the ceiling and hurt yourself causeing yourself to blink.  Quickly, while you are still blinking, pass Screech and head off to the rest of the level without having to worry about doing it in good time.Cheat: Extra ending Deafet K.K.Rool in the secret lost world boss to see an extra ending.Additionally, collect all 40 DK coins for an alterate extra ending.Cheat: Extra endingTo unlock the Lost World, you must pass the first world. In the all the other worlds, you will start to find a ''Klubba's Koisk'' in each world. When you visit one, a Kremling named Klubba will ask you to give him 15 Kremcoins to enter The Lost World. If you do give 15 Kremcoins to Klubba in a particular world, you will unlock one particular level of the Lost World.Cheat: Rickety Race - Boost BarrelIn Rickety Race, when you jump into the minecart, hold left. When the light turns green you will go backwards and hit a hidden "+" barrel which will cause your cart to drastically speed up -- even allowing you to plow through the first three racers instead of having to jump over them.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>O8X_RwTFvmM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1525</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588283-donkey-kong-country-2-diddys-kong-quest</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/donkey-kong-country-2-diddys-kong-quest</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/donkey-kong-country-2-diddys-kong-quest/3030-16889/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/LhgQkyi.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OM8ztbD.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/iFbbLaD.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/3hJdrvA.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/K6T6BAq.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/XJoT2Co.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/bVjOZH3.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/rSZ3ZFv.jpg</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://i.imgur.com/hZPAyxv.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://i.imgur.com/ffXhHFQ.jpg</boxart10>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/I9NgHSR.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Vgqhl2m.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wyipkDa.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/iyF7EXc.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/TCD8yXs.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/2JwaMxA.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/VBW65wy.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/vFlvoU0.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/CDPSd4t.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/6xT0Eba.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/hrrZzlm.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/BoAWAJo.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/XeXDwWc.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/IW9iYJl.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/VdkLuvX.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/14NxFbC.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>http://i.imgur.com/u4WExtA.jpg</fanart7>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/2xwcpqF.png</banner1>
	<banner2>http://i.imgur.com/gXUwIuK.png</banner2>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/b5B9Hkm.png</clearlogo1>
</game>