<Game>
	<Name>Doom (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Doom is a science-fiction/horror first-person shooter developed and published by id for the PC on December 10, 1993. As a nameless space marine, players trek through 27 levels (split up into three episodes), where they liberate space stations from demon infestation in both Phobos and Deimos, only to take on Hell. The game's engine (later known as id Tech 1) is known to pioneer new features to the genre, including non-perpendicular walls, complex rooms (known as "sectors") with varying height differences, multiplayer (both co-operatively and competitively, for up to four players at a time) and the concept of packaging the game's content (levels, sounds, and music) into singular files (WAD files) for easier modification and distribution (leading to the birth of the modern mod-making community).The lore of the game, set sometime into the future, involves the Union Aerospace Corporation (U.A.C.), a multi-planetary conglomerate that has been utilized by the Earth military to secretly experiment on alien teleportation technology discovered on the moons of Mars. As they try to establish a gateway between the two moons using this technology, the experiment goes awry and the demons of Hell use the portals to invade the two moons. As the last man standing guarding the Hangar of the U.A.C. space station on Phobos, the lone space marine must fight through the onslaught to keep them from attacking Earth.Gameplay:In Doom, players progress through each level, blasting away enemies while solving puzzles (involving switches, keycards, and skull-shaped key devices), avoiding environmental hazards (such as crushing ceilings, radioactive acid, and burning lava), and collecting weapons, ammo, and other items (including first-aid kits, body armor, suits that protect from radiation, night-vision goggles, computer maps, and supernatural orbs that grant a special bonus to the player). Unlike id's previous first-person shooter, Spear of Destiny, Doom does not include a scoring or lives system. Players who die can retry the level at the cost of resetting their inventory and stats.Episodes and DifficultiesThe game's campaign is split up into three episodes (each with eight normal levels and one secret level):Knee-Deep in the Dead - The only episode playable in the shareware version, the first episode deals with the marine's journey through the base established on Phobos.The Shores of Hell - After defeating the two big bruisers guarding the teleportation gateway, the marine passes through into Deimos. As the invasion continues, the base becomes more distorted with hellish architecture. The second episode deals with the marine's liberation of demons from the Deimos base.Inferno - Eventually, the marine fights a giant anomaly of flesh and metal (known as the Cyberdemon) in the "Tower of Babel", only to find out Deimos has been teleported to the infernal afterlife, and that the tower connects the moon to Hell itself! The third (and final) episode has the marine blindly wreaking havoc in Hell until he can find the mastermind behind the invasion.Players who are starting a new game can start at the beginning of an episode (starting with no armor and a pistol with 50 bullets). Starting from the second episode, players can find two new cell energy weapons (the uncommon Plasma Gun and the rare BFG-9000) and two new common enemies (the Cacodemon and the Lost Soul). Players can pick between five (four before game version 1.2) difficulties (known as "skill levels"):I'm too young to die. - Fewer monsters (and more items) than normal. Double ammo granted on weapon and ammo pickups. Players take half damage.Hey, not too rough. - Fewer monsters (and more items) than normal.Hurt me plenty. - Normal difficulty.Ultra-Violence. - More monsters (and fewer items) than normal.Nightmare! - Added in v1.2. Cheat codes are disabled. More monsters (and fewer items) than normal. Double ammo granted on weapon and ammo pickups. Monsters react and move faster, and respawn shortly after death.Weapons:FistFistDamage: 10 per punch, 200 with Berserk PackOne of two starting weapons. The fist is simple and effective against weaker enemies but when a Berserk Pack power up is activated it boosts the attack power of the fist considerably allowing you to tear through and even gib many enemies with ease.From the manual: Can be used to punch enemies. It will always be with you.ChainsawChainsawDamage: 20 per 'hit'A powerful melee weapon capable of stunning some enemies.From the manual: Cuts down the baddies like standing timber, but you have to get close.PistolPistolDamage: 10 per bulletThe second starting weapon. The pistol is one of two weapons to utilize bullets as its ammunition.From the manual: Your standard military-issue weapon. It will stay with you, so don't forget about it if things get tough.ShotgunShotgunDamage: 10 per pellet, 7 pellets per shell, 70 damage maximumThe shotgun is a very effective weapon to use on most enemies you will encounter. its multi-pellet spread is very useful for crowds. The shotgun is the only weapon to use shells as its ammunition.From the manual: Deliver a heavy punch at close range and a generous pelting from a distance.ChaingunChaingunDamage: 10 per bulletThe chaingun, like the pistol uses bullets as its source of ammunition. This rapid-firing machine gun can stun some enemies so it is most effective against a single enemy.From the manual: Direct heavy firepower into your opponent, making him do the chaingun cha-cha.Rocket LauncherRocket LauncherDamage: 200 per rocketThe Rocket Launcher is one of three weapons capable of gibbing enemies. Rockets deliver splash damage very well so they are ideal for dealing with crowds. This weapon is the only one in the game to use rockets as its ammunitonFrom the manual: Deliver an explosive rocket that can turn one bad dude inside-out.Plasma RiflePlasma RifleDamage: 20 per cellThe fastest firing weapon in the game, this weapon is very powerful and effective against whatever it is you may encounter. The plasma rifle is one of two weapons to utilize cells as its ammunition.From the manual: Shoot multiple rounds of plasma energy - frying some demon butt!BFG 9000BFG 9000Damage: 1000 per blast, 40 cells expendedThe BFG 9000 fires a huge plasma ball which moves slowly through the air. Upon impact, the target it hits receives a huge amount of damage and lots of splash damage as well.From the manual: The prize of the military arsenal. Great for clearing the room of an unwelcome guest. Shoot it and see for yourself.Enemies:Former HumanHealth: 20Total in single player (ultra violence) : 311From the manual: Once a marine, always a marine-- except in this case. These guys may look like your old buddies, but now they're nothing more than pistol-toting bi-pedal maggots. Waste em!Former Human SergeantHealth: 30Total in single player (ultra violence) : 426From the manual: Ditto. Except these guys are meaner and tougher. These walking shotguns will provide you with a few extra holes if you're not careful.ImpHealth: 60Total in single player (ultra violence) : 719From the manual: You though an imp was a cute little dude in a red suit with a pitchfork. Think again. This Imp heaves balls of fire down your throat and takes several bullets to die. It's time to find a better weapon than a pistol if you're going to face more than one of these mutants.DemonHealth: 140Total in single player (ultra violence) : 389From the manual: Sorta like shaved gorillas, except with big heads and lots of teeth. They don't kill easy. Get too close and they'll rip your sorry head off.SpectreHealth: 140Total in single player (ultra violence) : 114From the manual: Great. Just what you needed. An invisible (nearly) monster. Did you expect a walk in the park?Lost SoulHealth: 100Total in single player (ultra violence) : 242From the manual: Dumb. Tough. Flies. On Fire. 'Nuff said.CacodemonHealth: 400Total in single player (ultra violence) : 126From the manual: They float in the air, belch ball lightning, and have one horrendously big mouth. If you get too close to one of these monstrosities, You're Toast.Baron of HellHealth: 1000Total in single player (ultra violence) : 37From the manual: Tough as a dump truck and nearly as big, these goliaths are the worst thing on two legs since Tyrannosaurs Rex.CyberdemonHealth: 4000Total in single player (ultra violence) : 2From the manual: Half unfeeling machine, half raging horned devil. This walking nightmare has a rocket launcher for an arm and will definitely reach out and touch you. Make sure you're loaded for bear before you get to this guy.Spiderdemon (Spider Mastermind)Health: 3000Total in single player (ultra violence) : 1From the manual: Maybe cybernetics wasn't such a great idea after all. Look what the demons have done with it. It somehow seems unfair that you're not the only guy in Hell with a chaingun. Nope, she has a Super-Chaingun don't you just love it?Episodes and MapsKnee-Deep in the Dead (E1)Level NameMap SlotDesignerPar TimeHangerE1M1John Romero0:30Nuclear PlantE1M2John Romero1:15Toxin RefineryE1M3John Romero2:00Command ControlE1M4Tom Hall, John Romero1:30Phobos LabE1M5John Romero2:45Central ProcessingE1M6John Romero3:00Computer StationE1M7John Romero3:00Phobos AnomalyE1M8Sandy Petersen, Tom HallN/AMilitary Base (secret level)E1M9John Romero2:45Sewers (Xbox only secret map)E1M10David Calvin0:00The Shores of Hell (E2)Level NameMap SlotDesignerPar timeDeimos AnomalyE2M1Sandy Petersen, Tom Hall1:30Containment AreaE2M2Tom Hall, Sandy Petersen1:30RefineryE2M3Tom Hall, Sandy Petersen1:30Deimos LabE2M4Tom Hall, Sandy Petersen2:00Command CenterE2M5Sandy Petersen1:30Hall of the DamnedE2M6Sandy Petersen6:00Spawning VatsE2M7Tom Hall, Sandy Petersen4:00Tower of BabelE2M8Sandy PetersenN/AFortress of MysteryE2M9Sandy Petersen2:50Inferno (E3)Level NameMap SlotDesignerPar TimeHell KeepE3M1Sandy Petersen1:30Slough of DespairE3M2Sandy Petersen0:45PandemoniumE3M3Tom Hall, Sandy Petersen1:30House of PainE3M4Sandy Petersen2:30Unholy CathedralE3M5Sandy Petersen1:30Mt. ErebusE3M6Sandy Petersen1:30LimboE3M7Tom Hall, Sandy Petersen2:45DisE3M8Sandy PetersenN/AWarrensE3M9Sandy Petersen2:15Official PortsAtari JaguarThe first console port developed by id Software, the Jaguar version of Doom was released in 1994. The game engine was largely developed by John Carmack. 22 of the original 27 levels are included, though modified and simplified, and two new maps are included. Music is only included during the title screen and between-level screens. Two player multiplayer Deathmatch and Co-op modes are available through JagLink.The code developed for this port served as the basis for future ports including the Sega 32X (which was released before the Jaguar version), the 3DO, GameBoy Advance, and PlayStation.Game Boy AdvanceBased on the Jaguar port, the GBA version of Doom was released by David A. Palmer Productions in 2001. Five new multiplayer-only maps were designed for this version.iPhone / iPod TouchAn official iOS port of Doom, titled Classic Doom, was released by id Software in 2009. The port is based on the source port PrBoom which allows for OpenGL rendering.LinuxThe Linux port of Doom was created by Dave Taylor of id Software and released in 1994. The source code of this port was made available to the public in 1997 and is the basis for all subsequent source ports.MS-DOSThe original version of doom.PlaystationDoom on the Sony Playstation is more of a re-imagining. It features slight variations of levels from The Ultimate Doom and Doom II: Hell on Earth. This version of the game uses modified versions of the Jaguar maps.There was more of an emphasis on mood and atomsphere compared to the PC version and utilized colored lighting. The game's soundtrack differs from the PC version and many enemy and weapon sounds were also changed to make them more intimidating. These changes made for a more darker and atmospheric tone for the franchise which carried forward into DOOM 3.Enemies from Doom II were added to levels from the first game for an added challenge. Fans of the game in Doom's active modding community have brought it to the PC using the ZDoom source port to add in the various graphical enhancements unique to this version of Doom.Playstation 3Released in 2012 in a collection called "Doom Classic Complete" which features The Ultimate Doom, Doom 2, Master Levels for Doom 2. This collection also includes the previously exclusive No Rest for the Living bonus episode from the Xbox 360 release of Doom 2. This port features a stripped down version of idtech 5 for networking and other PSN specific code written during the development of RAGE.Sega 32xPublished by Sega in 1994 this version of the game features 17 levels from episodes 1 and 2 but none from episode 3. The port was criticized for not running in full screen and not including the BFG-9000 weapon although it can be acquired using cheat codes. Just like the Super Nintendo version only the front facing sprites for monsters were included thus eliminating the possibility of monster infighting.When the player finishes level 15 while using cheat codes they are presented with a standard DOS prompt which will remain on screen until the console's reset button is pressed. Only when the player has progressed to level 16 without using cheat codes the gameplay will continue properly. The manual states that the player will start again at level 1 with cheat codes disabled after this point but it does not.Sega SaturnThe Saturn version is very similar to the Playstation version but does not include the colored lighting. The low frame rate compared to the Playstation version has this version lacking Doom's trademark fast-paced gameplay. It was said to include link support for Deathmatch and Cooperative multiplayer but was only included in the European and Japanese releases.SNESDoom on the Super Nintendo was released in September 1995 by Williams Entertainment is one of the few games to include a Super-FX 2 chip. This version includes 22 levels from the PC version and features the 5 missing levels from the Jaguar version but instead is missing 5 different levels and does not include support for saving your game progress.Due to hardware limitations monsters can only be viewed from the front making monster infighting impossible, floors and ceilings are not texture mapped and the spectre enemy is not included being replaced by the regular demon instead. Other limitations include not being able to play Episode 2: The Shores of Hell on I'm too young to die (very easy), and hey not too rough (easy), Episode 3: Inferno can only be played on the ultra violence (very hard) and nightmare (hardest) difficulties. Nightmare difficulty was changed to not have respawning monsters although they are still fast like in the PC version. The shotgun does not spread out but instead fires a single projectile equal to a hit from all particles in the PC version.Automap support utilizes Mode 7 scaling and rotation to allow the map to rotate around the player instead of the player's icon rotating inside of the automap itself a feature unique to this version of the game.The 2 boss demons, the spider mastermind and the cyberdemon are included in this version of the game which were missing from other ports of that era. Multiplayer support was included for gamers with X-BAND modems.WindowsBill Gates at a Microsoft event in 1995Known as WinDoom or Doom95, developed for Windows, unveiled in 1995 and released in 1996, this port capitalized on the popularity of Doom and was used by Microsoft to showcase their new DirectX technology. It supports screen resolutions up to 640x480 and features a GUI launcher allowing easy selection of episode, map, difficulty, custom wads, and multiplayer settings.XboxThis version of Doom was included on the disc with the collectors edition of Doom 3 along with Doom II. This version includes an exclusive secret map in episode 1.Xbox 360Released in 2006, this port was developed by Nerve Software and was made available for download in the Xbox Live Arcade. Single player contains all four episodes and supports multiplayer (splitscreen or online via Xbox Live) Deathmatch and Co-op with up to four players. The Xbox version includes achievements and leaderboards.Source Code ReleaseAlso see: Source PortOn December 23 1997, Doom's source code was made available to the public. This has now spawned many new 'Doom' engines, such as Boom, ZDoom, GZDoom (OpenGL), and Legacy, these engines and many like them have been developed to 'update' id Software's original engine and most now support all modern windows platforms, run in high resolutions, have optimized online code, free-look (up/down), jumping &amp; crouching, a console, and cross-hairs.These engines require the original DOOM.wad or IWADs to run, and are of course able to play modifications of these files such as NeoDoom.Unofficial Source PortsThese ports were done after the release of idtech 1's Source Code in 1997. Some of these ports may require additional hardware or software to function.AmigaDoom was ported to the Amiga sometime in 1998 after the release of the source code.AndroidThere are a variety of ports available on the google play store which can be converted into the full version with the WAD files from the PC version.Sega DreamcastThe Sega Dreamcast has several source ports available. DoomDC, last updated in 2002 this source port was the first to be released. This version requires the Dreamcast Keyboard to use some functions such as switching weapons.Another source port is nxDoom which is based on DoomDC. nxDoom runs faster than DoomDC and supports saving, user WADs, .MOD music files, and has all of the games actions mapped to the controller.GP2xPrBoom and ZDoom were ported to this platform.Nintendo DSDSDoom is a port of Doom for the Nintendo DS. This version displays the game on the top screen while displaying the UI as well as automap or console output on the bottom screen. This version supports network play with any prBoom server. Music and custom control layouts are not supported.Nintendo WiiWiiDoom is a port of PrBoom. Doom, Doom 2, Ultimate Doom and Final Doom are supported. The only available control scheme utilizes the Wii Remote and Nunchuck attachment.Sony Playstation 3PrBoom was ported to this platform. This was the only way to play Doom on the Playstation 3 before the release of Doom Classic Complete.Sony Playstation PortableThe original Doom source code as well as Doom Legacy have been ported to this platform.Tapwave ZodiacZdoomZ, a PalmOS port of Linux Doom, runs on the Tapwave Zodiac.Microsoft XboxDoomX is a port of the original source code to the Microsoft Xbox. System Link is supported unlike the port included with Doom 3 Collectors Edition.Microsoft Zune HDDoom for the Zune HD was ported in 2010. Movement is controlled by either tilt or touch controls along with touch buttons for other game actions.Esoteric Source PortsKodak DigitaOS Digital CamerasA dedicated Doom handheld was created using this port as a hackaday project.Doom 3 TerminalsPerhaps the strangest of them all this port requires a copy of the original release of Doom 3 and a PWAD. Once installed the mod includes a test map with a terminal which runs the original doom. Try it out.Garry's ModGMDoom is a partial source port of Doom to Garry's Mod. Weapons, enemies and their behavior can be added in while playing. The mod was released in march 2013 on Steam Workshop.iPodThis source port requires the RockBox alternative firmware. Due to the iPod's media-centric button layout harder difficulties such as ultra violence and nightmare may prove more difficult to play in this versions of the game. Installation instructions can be found here.TI-Nspire CalculatorsnDoom supports all retail wads for Doom, Doom 2, Ultimate Doom, and Final Doom.System RequirementsMinimum System Requirements386sx IBM compatible computerMS-DOS v3.3 or higherVGA (320x200x256) graphics4mb RAMHard Drive - 4.8 MB (Shareware), 12 MB (Mail-order)Original Release VersionsShareware VersionIncludes one of the three episodesIncludes network and modem supportMail-order VersionAll shareware featuresIncludes all three episodes (three episodes each with eight levels and a secret level)Includes Plasma rifleIncludes BFG 9000Versionsv0.2 - February 4, 1993 (alpha version)v0.4 - April 2, 1993 (alpha version)v0.5 - May 22, 1993 (alpha version)v1.0 - December 10, 1993 (uses v0.99 engine)v1.1 - December 16, 1993v1.2 - February 17, 1994 (introduced modem support and Nightmare mode)v1.3 - undocumented / never releasedv1.4 - June 1994 (Internet Beta version)v1.5 - July 8, 1994 (Internet Beta version)v1.6 - August 1994 (Internet Beta version)v1.666 - September 1994v1.7 - October 11, 1994v1.7a - November 8, 1994v1.8 - January 23, 1995v1.9 - February 1, 1995 (the final version)Ultimate Doom, released April 1995, used a slightly modified version of the engine however the version number was not updated.On December 23 1997 the Doom source code was released, this code has the version number 1.10Referencing this new version, source port authors (e.g., ZDoom) often began their versions with 1.11On October 4, 1993 an early beta version of the game was made available to journalists. While this version of the game is similar to the final version (unlike the earlier alpha versions) their are still several key differences most notably the BFG9000 which fired 40 quick bursts of plasma gun ammo. This was changed due to the large number of sprites on screen causing the PC to slowdown. Also, this version has a scoring system. The player could gain score by killing enemies and collecting score giving items such as the Demonic Dagger. The scoring system and scoring items did not make it into the final version of the game.							</plot>
	<releasedate>29/2/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Williams Entertainment Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<ESRB>M - Mature</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>g5x1qUWrzm4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2880</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588285-doom</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/doom</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/doom/3030-7326/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/CC3ESKC.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/F1nGBPY.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/KXIE8Dd.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/ZdWwe1C.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/lLAF5y4.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/eaFP1ty.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/LUbgZl8.jpg</boxart7>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/HhONsH0.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/rX93kWB.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/yNSEXGd.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/L3fxLBF.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/oUJjehV.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4PqTdy5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BnDWZVj.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/XmOUOHV.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/gNJV8ow.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Ww21pUG.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/raSlO2M.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/at1OdRp.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/a03vsMp.png</banner1>
	<banner2>http://i.imgur.com/JY63CvT.png</banner2>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/dVO68dp.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Welcome to Doom, soldier. Now shut up and start fighting because there's no time to waste! We're talking total war against the forces of evil with the only thing standing between civilization and the end of everything as we know it is you -- one angry Marine with a handgun and a bad attitude. This is the full-auto, 16-meg faithful version of the PC original. Which means all the same monsters, levels, weapons and surprises are around for a screaming fast descent into danger with sudden death lurking around every corner. Strap on your ammo and prepare to spit lead. Because now's your chance to be a hero. Or die trying.</Notes>
	<banner3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f414935d-834f-4bd3-a411-03aa0a6031f6.jpg</banner3>
	<banner4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/88a528ea-aa93-4e6e-b2b9-80e7630d0034.png</banner4>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d77d90d1-a1b7-48a5-b2d8-592ae1e52a8b.jpg</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c6e58061-b984-45ff-860a-ddc535f5f88a.png</boxart9>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c8fc45b5-de4a-47aa-9684-c81eb41876fe.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f6ca9ff0-e238-4cf7-9d13-68fc40735fda.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5acf1225-d418-4d2b-b2bf-6ca06b50304d.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Williams Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>