<Game>
	<Name>Doom Troopers - Mutant Chronicles (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Based on the popular role-playing and card game, DOOM TROOPERS casts you as a fearless commando who's been commissioned to save the world from an invading force of mutants. Play as either Mitch Hunter or Max Steiner as you embark on the most important mission of your life--the complete annihilation of the Dark Legion. Work your way through eight detailed levels filled with all kinds of evil and dangerous mutants, as you unload with a barrage of high-powered weapons that are readily available. If the pressure is a little too much for you to handle alone, recruit a friend and try to eliminate the Dark Legion together. The world is in grave danger, and only the Doom Troopers can make things right.Cheat: Level PasswordsEnter this in the password screen in the Options menu to skip to any part of any level when you start your game.Cheat: Level PasswordsEnter SYMMETRY as a password on the password screen. You will see a secret picture while starting the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Playmates Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.1</rating>
	<ESRB>M - Mature</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>YFqor_7xVOU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1580</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/564300-doom-troopers</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/doom-troopers-mutant-chronicles</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/doom-troopers-mutant-chronicles/3030-1713/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Plx8sCq.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/cEyUg4j.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/O9eI8EV.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ED9u5xq.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6lxmnfp.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/5OF6m2e.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RVYHXsN.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vVN7Y5q.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/zO8UcCr.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/TuOyCjt.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/AagMj7t.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2kwsiyy.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ZM24Dty.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Oa9uHo5.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Cx2E8Xp.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ljepRsr.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You want the rush from taking on an army of mutated warriors single-handed? Then you may have what it takes to make it as a Doomtrooper!!! Take on worlds infested with the mutated hordes of Dark Legion mutants and teach them the true meaning of fear! Join Mitch Hunter and Max Steiner as they take on the galaxy-blazing a trail of smoldering Dark Legion Forces in their onslaught to rid the human outposts of the deadly alien threat. Suit up as a Doomtrooper and get ready for the most action-packed combat you've ever seen! The world is counting on you-don't pass this one up!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bc3fe975-5604-48dd-974d-0975232afb7b.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/78c5097d-731b-4ef4-8383-eca09da1eb6c.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2a0436c3-b0db-4d51-bcda-500d89966fde.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4a1499b0-71f3-483a-a42f-f39ff6fc65cc.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8e11f642-0340-4c14-bb93-727d94e6d4ef.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Playmates</Publisher>
</game>