<Game>
	<Name>Doraemon 3 - Nobita to Toki no Hougyoku (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Doraemon 3: Nobita to Toki no Hougyoku ("Doraemon 3: Nobita and the Jewel of Time") is a 2D platformer for the Super Famicom featuring Doraemon and his human friends. The player can switch between Doraemon, Nobita, and eventually their other friends, each of which has their own special abilities as well as various strengths and weaknesses in terms of jump height and speed. The plot takes them through history via Doraemon's time machine, starting with the prehistoric era and moving forward through time.Doraemon 3 was published by Epoch, like the first two, but the developer changed from SAS Sakata to an uncredited company. The graphics and gameplay are a little different from its two predecessors as a result. AIM (which later became Fortyfive) was discovered to have contributed to the sound design. 	</plot>
	<releasedate>16/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>AIM</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/565224-doraemon-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/doraemon-3-nobita-to-toki-no-hgyoku</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/doraemon-3-nobita-to-toki-no-hougyoku/3030-14494/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/cZY99ke.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/rGEmP91.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/XPtzmFA.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/BPfBY5x.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/2IMVmag.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zGELnEW.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/XrksEd6.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/UCERioy.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Uob1KqY.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FWHTGUq.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/1AVuQQA.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2lHg8h4.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Xtqe6Fz.gif</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/IdryD4I.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Doraemon 3: Nobita to Toki no Hougyoku ("Doraemon 3: Nobita and the Jewel of Time") is a 2D platformer for the Super Famicom featuring Doraemon and his human friends. The player can switch between Doraemon, Nobita, and eventually their other friends, each of which has their own special abilities as well as various strengths and weaknesses in terms of jump height and speed. The plot takes them through history via Doraemon's time machine, starting with the prehistoric era and moving forward through time. Doraemon 3 was published by Epoch, like the first two, but the developer changed from SAS Sakata to an uncredited company. The graphics and gameplay are a little different from its two predecessors as a result. AIM (which later became Fortyfive) was discovered to have contributed to the sound design.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c9fa3613-b993-4108-8ee0-f3cb9c819833.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d3c15d72-6c4b-4773-b885-b6be01e8c318.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/313f84db-902b-41b9-a0f4-e8b30a6b5794.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b673b1d-a38d-4fe6-83ad-e8fefb5428f1.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b24f6bee-7ca4-41ef-acda-d7a48f71fa83.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Epoch</Publisher>
</game>