<Game>
	<Name>Doraemon - Nobita to Yousei no Kuni (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Doraemon: Nobita to Yousei no Kuni (roughly "Doraemon: Nobita and the Land of Fairies") is an adventure game with action sequences for the Super Famicom. It's the first of four Super Famicom Doraemon games, featuring the titular robotic cat who depends on various gadgets to fight enemies and rescue his young human friends.Doraemon must find his friends across town with the help of a friendly fairy, and this involves exploring a large town until he finds a gateway to an action level (usually a trigger event must happen, at which point Doraemon can travel to a blinking part of his mini-map). In these action levels, Doraemon jumps and fights his way through platformer stages.											</plot>
	<releasedate>19/2/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>SAS Sakata</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/565047-doraemon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/doraemon-nobita-to-ysei-no-kuni</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/doraemon-nobita-to-yousei-no-kuni/3030-8686/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/wEc5FtO.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/pJWGBmG.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/U2RGnwf.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ePQpKI0.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/gpcbiRa.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/tJKCUpR.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/5qUn81z.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VUeoV5M.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IqugQNU.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/oZpQsp4.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Hpq8NwQ.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/DLSTPem.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ZETMYZm.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/lwb3i8G.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/PJGD4cB.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Doraemon: Nobita to Yousei no Kuni (roughly "Doraemon: Nobita and the Land of Fairies") is an adventure game with action sequences for the Super Famicom. It's the first of four Super Famicom Doraemon games, featuring the titular robotic cat who depends on various gadgets to fight enemies and rescue his young human friends. Doraemon must find his friends across town with the help of a friendly fairy, and this involves exploring a large town until he finds a gateway to an action level (usually a trigger event must happen, at which point Doraemon can travel to a blinking part of his mini-map). In these action levels, Doraemon jumps and fights his way through platformer stages.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/499dd84a-45cc-4b95-a3ed-64d82196223d.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d129649-de1c-4d56-a4d5-132ea4ab7a8a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/019f52d5-b648-419f-a5ad-fb06a2e0416f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/12a32575-172b-4d87-8d16-33efbd00b498.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Epoch</Publisher>
</game>