<Game>
	<Name>Dragon Quest I & II (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>This is a remake of two classic NES RPGs - an exclusively Japanese release of the two first Dragon Quest titles on one cartridge.In Dragon Quest (known as Dragon Warrior in the US), you play as the descendant of the legendary warrior Erdrick, and your goal is to recover the magical Ball of Light from Erdrick's and the humanity's arch-enemy, the Dragon Lord. In Dragon Quest II, you assume the role of the descendant of the hero of the first game, and must join forces with two other characters in order to defeat a demon lord who destroyed a nearby city and killed its inhabitants. Both RPGs feature random battles and turn-based combat viewed from first-person perspective. In Dragon Quest you fight alone, while in the sequel two other characters can join your party, and you also fight against multiple enemies at once.The remake includes updated graphics (although they still retain the original NES look), sound of SNES quality, and some changes in the gameplay and in the game world. Certain locations are larger, some menu commands (such as "Stairs") are omitted, and there is a larger variety of items.Cheat: Rename the Prince and PrincessTo rename the Prince (2nd character) to whatever you want, start the game up, then choose to Continue an Adventure. When you are at the ''file screen'', put the cursor to the left of the file you want to change the name. Hold the directional pad to the Left and also hold the Start button and push the A button with them still held down. A naming prompt will then appear for you to enter in the new name. To change the name of the Princess (3rd character), put the cursor to the left of the file you want to change her name in, and this time hold Right on the directional pad along with the Start button, and then press the A button while still holding right+Start. A naming prompt will then appear for her. You must have the Prince in the party for the code to change his name work, and the same for the Princess.Cheat: Borrow the Sword of Destruction attack power to Falcon SwordAt the gate of Hargon's Castle equip the Falcon Sword &amp; take the Sword of Destruction in the Hero inventory too.Walk into the castle. In the castle it look like Midenhall, then equip the Sword of Destruction &amp; you will cursed.After that use the Charm of Rubiss, then you will change the equip weapon automatically back to Falcon Sword.But the attack power in the battle will equal the Sword of Destruction.Ex. Hero lv.40 hit with Falcon = about 60-80/turn = 120-160 totalHero lv.30 hit with Falcon + SOD (Sword of Destruction) power = about 85-125/turn = 170-250 totalplus the high % of critical from SOD if you luck enough to critical twice ~ 280-320 totalCheat: Dragon Warrior 1 for NES modifies your starting stats and growth by the name you choose.Only the first 4 letters count for this calculationYou can use this website to see what names work for you:http://www.woodus.com/den/games/web/dwsim/calc.htmJust make sure your short-term modifier is at least a 3 for the best growth :)A more complete list of names can be found here:http://www.gamefaqs.com/boards/563408-dragon-warrior/72498979Most of the names below were tested with this calculator.  You can test them yourself for more details.Names are case sensitive; a hypen ( - ) is used to seperate names meaning you can use any of those names for the same result.Cheat: At the password screen, press Right 7 times and enter the Japanese character. Left 7 times, Down 6 times and enter the Japanese character. Up 2 times, Right 5 times and enter the Japanese character. Left 2 times, Up 2 times and enter the Japanese character. Press Left 1 time, Down 1 time and enter the Japanese character 2 times. Down 3 times, Left 1 time and enter the Japanese character. Up 3 times and enter the Japanese character. Down 1 time, Left 1 time and enter the Japanese character. Up 4 times, Right 4 times and enter the Japanese character. Down 1 time and enter the Japanese character. Left 1 time, Down 1 time and enter the Japanese character. Down 1 time, Left 2 times and enter the Japanese character. Right 2 times, Down 1 time and enter the Japanese character. Left 1 time, Down 1 time and enter the Japanese character. Up 5 times, Right 4 times and enter the Japanese character. Right 3 times and enter the Japanese character. Left 5 times, Down 1 time and enter the Japanese character. Left 4 times, Down 2 times and enter the Japanese character. Right 4 times and enter the Japanese character.Cheat: At the start screen when you enter your nameCheat: Go into the mountain cave and get the treasure box at the bottom that gives you 130 GP. Do this over and over about 15 times and you will get the Death Necklace. Go sell it at an item shop in Breconary.Cheat: In the Japanese version, the Prince and Princess' name are already predetermined. If you want to change them, just start a new game, type the Hero's name and before entering the last letter, hold Select + Start and enter the last letter. If done right, you'll be taken to a second name entry screen where you'll be able to name the Prince and then the Princess.Cheat: Go to Zahan, and get the Magic Loom.  After that, go to the Dragon's Horn North Tower, and get the Dew's Yarn on the 3rd floor.   Take these items and see Don Mahone.  After you give him the items for him to make the first Water Flying Cloth, *WITHOUT SAVING*, go back to the Dragon's Horn North Tower on the 3rd floor, and search for the Dew's Yarn.  It *WILL* be there.  After you get the Dew's Yarn the second time, *SAVE*.  After saving, turn the game off (make sure you hold in reset so you don't erase the files) and turn it back on.  Go back to Don Mahone and get your first Water Flying Cloth.  Now go back to Zahan and get the Magic Loom again.  Take the items to Don Mahone once again, and save.  Turn off the power, then turn it back on, then go back to Don Mahone, and get your second Water Flying Cloth. Cheat: (If you saved after giving Don Mahone the Dew's Yarn and Magic Loom, but DIDN'T go back to get the Dew's Yarn again, it will no longer be there.  The Magic Loom however, you can get again at any time.)Cheat: There's a place in the game where you can defeat a clown and win a Staff of Thunder, which sells for 19,500 gold. Once you beat him, go sell the staff, save at the king and reset the game. When you come back, the clown will be there again, and you can get another Staff of Thunder.Continue doing this to get as much gold as you want.Cheat: Normally, when equipped with a cursed item (Sword of Destruction, Gremlin's Armor, or Gremlin's Tail), there is a 50% chance the person wearing the item will freeze in battle, rather than act. This is unfortunate, as the sword and armour are the most powerful in the game.Cheat: However, there is a way to gain the benefits of the items without the curse.Cheat: 1. Equip the item(s). This will give you the increased attack and/or defense of the cursed item(s) and inflict your character with the curse.Cheat: 2. Go to the House of Healing and pay to have the character equipping the item uncursed. This will cost 100 GP per experience level. This will remove the item(s) from your item list and remove the curse, but does NOT cause your attack or defense stat to recalculate.Cheat: 3. Never again look at your equip screen for that character or gain an experience level. The game does not recalculate the character's attack or defense stats until you look at the equip screen or gain a level, so you do not lose the hefty attack or defense bonus granted by equipping the cursed item(s).Cheat: You are free to look in and use other menus, including item and status, or even save and reset, without losing the bonus. However, since leveling up recalculates your attack and defense, you may want to wait until you are ready to defeat the final boss to use this glitch, since it cannot be repeated without finding a new copy of the cursed item.Cheat: Cheat: In the cave to Rhone, on level 5, fall down a hole (any hole).  Go to the lower left corner of level 4. Go one square up and one square right.  You'll fall down a hole, and the sword will be right there.  Best Sword in the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Enix Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>PNYNJx0IeTc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>19047</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/564868-dragon-quest-i-and-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/dragon-quest-i-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dragon-warrior-i-ii/3030-1164/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XiIdqay.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/1RBTVN4.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/fr2epsL.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/hww89us.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/IYKL0Nr.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/T8O0vx8.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Lxdkw7B.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/vwYrIBI.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/86AHPIb.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/2c79onv.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2kcJC2E.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vk1lw9r.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/YoYptoQ.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/y1ymlmG.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Jqfc0r0.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/oVErf32.png</clearlogo1>
</game>