<Game>
	<Name>Dragon Ball Z - Hyper Dimension (France)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dragon Ball Z: Hyper Dimension is a 2D fighting game developed by TOSE and published by Bandai for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System (in Japan only) on March 29, 1996. The last Dragon Ball Z game to be released for the console, Dragon Ball Z: Hyper Dimension featured a darker, less cartoonish art style and traditional fighting game mechanics (with the ability to knock opponents into different areas of the stage).The game features ten playable characters from various points in the franchise (from the Frieza Saga onward). The game's story mode loosely retells key battles from the series.Like some previous installments of the franchise for the SNES, Dragon Ball Z: Hyper Dimension was released in both France and Spain. Released on December 1996, the game's Story Mode was completely disabled due to the lack of translation.Gameplay:What made this addition different to previous Dragon Ball Z fighters was the inclusion of the 'desperate move'. Each character has a desperate move which could be used when their life bar was low (i.e when it is flashing). For example, in Goku's desperate move, he would power up, perform his teleportation technique (Shunkan-Id&#244;s), does a combo, transforms into Super Saiyan 3 and performs his Super Dragonfist move (Ry&#363;-ken). Now the opponent helpless in the air, would be finished with a Spirit Bomb (Genki-Dama).The majority of the stages that would be fought in are multi-tier requiring a specific combo to be executed to knock your opponent into another screen.Characters were also able to perform background attacks and replenish their health.Characters:The game featured 10 playable characters (each from various points in the Dragon Ball Z universe):Goku (Super Saiyan, can transform into Super Saiyan 3 in his "desperation attack")Vegeta (Super Saiyan, possessed by the evil wizard Babidi)Gotenks (Super Saiyan 3)Gohan (full potential unlocked)Vegito (Super Saiyan)PiccoloMajin BuuKid BuuFrieza (final form)Cell (perfect form)						</plot>
	<releasedate>29/3/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>oL9bRN8u6lo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1800</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588288-dragon-ball-z-hyper-dimension</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/dragon-ball-z-hyper-dimension</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dragon-ball-z-hyper-dimension/3030-2428/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/TqaVyqP.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/75x0UWu.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/jwlS4jg.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/X4RBh3Q.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/GOU3g22.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/TNm50BF.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/dfVYehd.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/PZo810k.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/I85XxFp.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/XLpiw8i.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/kiZRFc6.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/xixVQgj.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/TyMguYj.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NFLePTp.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/GQochFF.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/bQA7a8Z.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/haMvC7b.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/7VkDu5e.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/16lnnyC.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Lsy36xb.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Surpassing the original! Battle in three dimensions as the legend continues with more Dragon Ball Z fights! For the first time, Vegita appears and is ready to fight! The fights are more intense than ever, and the battle fields go up, down, right and left! Force your enemies into the ground. THIS IS HYPER DIMENSION!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>G6mDlM8UXCE</VideoURL1>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/48f8c372-2ad8-4995-b30e-e4449ba57e3a.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ddaf2eed-301c-4147-bb02-4ad0d7e264bf.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0a822692-2e58-451a-9e6a-ba565a71a6f9.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98a3d376-1678-48f6-ac41-d9e3699b4dd9.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0aacd1e2-49b3-45e7-b747-52b1e54aa14b.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>