<Game>
	<Name>Dragon Ball Z - Super Saiya Densetsu (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:This game covers the Dragon Ball Z sagas (or seasons) running from the beginning of the series up through the journey to the planet Namek and the battle with Freiza. The game features nearly all the warriors from the anime, mostly in the battles they were involved in within the series.The game uses a somewhat unique (at least for the time) turn-based card battle system wherein one uses cards with different offensive and defensive values to execute different moves, including several special moves unique to each character. The status of the cards are indicated by the Dragon Balls on the corners of it, the more stars on each, the higher the offensive or defensive values. Rather than have the usual RPG stats of ATK, DEF, INT, etc., the characters have actual power levels or Battle Power (denonced as BP in the game) that increases as they level up. As fans of the series are aware, power levels are the backbone of fights.The game features random encounters, somewhat anachronistically fought against varying colors of saibamen even at the very beginning of the game before they were introduced in the series. The game is unique, not only because it's a Dragon Ball Z RPG, but because there are "optional" secret parts to the game which will power up the player if they follow the plot of the anime.Playable CharactersGokuPiccoloKrillinYamchaTienChiaotzuVegeta (on Namek)Nail (for a short time on Namek)Dende (does not fight, however if he reaches Level 3 he can restore 1 character's HP and KI each turn)Enemy CharactersRaditzBubbles the ApeKing KaiNappaVegeta w/ScouterDodoriaZarbonGuldoRecoomeBurterJeiceCapt. GinyuFriezaVarious colors of SaibamenVarious Freiza goonsSecretsPower up Piccolo - After Piccolo is brought back on Namek, go and find Nail. He will be lying on the ground after getting decimated by Frieza. Fuse with him and Piccolo will be at level 48 which is the level cap, although his power level can be temporarily boosted mid-battle by using a King Kai Card or a Guru Card. After fighting beating Freiza's 2nd form he will run away, during this time the player can find the two Namek Warriors that helped them earlier in the game (under the assumption that the player didn't get them killed) and they will be given a choice whether to allow them to fuse with Piccolo. If the player chooses yes, Piccolo gains another large boost in his Battle Power, however this means losing Dende and his healing ability. Choosing "no" allows the player to keep Dende.Unlock the Super Saiyan form and battle Vegeta as a Super Saiyan - In the final battle against Freiza, allow him to kill either Krillin or Chiaou-Tzu then he'll become enraged and transform into the infamous blonde-haired warrior, giving him a massive power level boost and allowing him pretty much dominate Frieza. After Goku flies away, he will be confronted and challenged by Vegeta and Goku will transform into a Super Saiyan and fight him.Easy Levels for Saiyans - Goku, Gohan, and Vegeta can level up mid-battle if they use an item that completely restores their health while their HP is 5 or lower. The player will see a short cutscene of the character powering up and it will say something along the lines of "Gains a Level". It's a nice touch since according to the anime Saiyans grow stronger after recovering from mortal wounds or near death. Take advantage of this in the beginning with Goku. Grind and gain a few more levels with this method before fighting Raditz. It will make the game a lot easier once Goku arrives on Namek. When using this method with Gohan and Vegeta, take full advantage. Same as with Goku, grind, heal, level. Repeat. It will be a lot more satisfying to just finish random battles just by using only one character from the party once strong enough. Not to mention the rest of the party levels up every 1 or 2 battles so that's always good.Cheat: Saiyan Level-UpWhen Goku, Vegeta, or Gohan reaches a health level below 5, use a card like Korin, Kami, or Shenron, that fully heals a character, on them, and they will grow one level. This can be recognized in the show when Vegeta tells Krillin to hurt him badly and then let Dende heal him so he can become stronger.Cheat: Saiyan Level-UpWhen you are fighting Freeza in his fourth and final form, let a weak character like Kuririn or Chao-Zu. My preferred choice will be Chao-Zu. Do not let Son Goku, Vegita, Gohan and Piccolo die. After defeating Freeza in his final scene, the usual credits, showing Goku flying will be seen until Vegita appears. Vegita will then transform to Super Saiyjin Vegita and so will Goku transform to Super Saiyajin Goku. Thus, the ultimate battle among the super saiyajin begins. Super Saiyajin Vegita is by far the toughest boss in the entire game, even stronger than the final form of Freeza. Once you defeat Super Saiyjin Vegita, you get a new ending that is different from the normal.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/1/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>TOSE</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>jo8H1urQC1I</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>13916</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588289-dragon-ball-z-chou-saiya-densetsu</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dragon-ball-z-super-saiya-densetsu/3030-22810/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>http://dragonball.wikia.com/wiki/Dragon_Ball_Z:_Super_Saiya_Densetsu</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/AdaRFFU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/hHqgehS.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7xCGp4f.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/VzCFBQ6.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Uaq4i9L.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/mo6QOtK.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/sUGXKuA.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Oy6XhFI.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/rq3wWTW.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/r6F3Y6H.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/RZUUGej.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/oMtP25Y.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/o7Y591z.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/uj2H8fH.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5DeBEvL.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/syvKmBy.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>This is where the legend of Super Saiya starts. The strongest man in the universe, Son Goku, fights against the terrible threats which threatens our world. Goku's blood is burning!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>jo8H1urQC1I</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e6defbe-eca5-449d-9388-59aa7548ae42.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6a3e43a7-4e55-4012-bfca-91ba69282ca1.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fd547673-74ae-4d7c-a8ed-a6b13f5cadd4.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a60bdc11-bbd5-4cce-afe0-bc68cc09e159.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9da3dee2-1832-4ec8-9afb-c16ab572e08d.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d6e3db3c-daac-49ff-8207-bb6655fd6125.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9609e616-0678-4f34-baa1-ece6ed48e8b6.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6d5195c5-92e4-4d13-ac68-4c44917ebcaa.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2f50fb4f-4313-46b7-9257-58b4543c8157.jpg</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/48dbd97d-4c1d-44e1-a19f-4e739a88f244.jpg</snapshot18>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>