<Game>
	<Name>Dragon View (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dragon View (JP: Super Drakkhen) is a first-person 3D RPG for the Super Nintendo, developed and published by Kemco. It is a SNES-only sequel to the Infogrames computer RPG Drakkhen, which Kemco previously adapted for the Super Nintendo console. Like its predecessor, Dragon View adopts a first-person view with full panoramic movement while travelling on the overworld, and switches to a third-person action RPG perspective for combat and interior locations.The game has mild backtracking and open-world elements, putting up borders between continents and having the player visit a group of locations in each area of the game in any order they choose. They can also come back to earlier areas of the game after they've upgraded and gained levels, allowing them to explore those areas further.Cheat: Sound TestTo access the hidden sound test press Start at the title screen then ABXY simultaneously on controller 2. Upon leaving the sound test you can use the L and R buttons on controller 2 to decrease and increase the brightness of the background.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Kotobuki System Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>tmHM_uvyTyY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1581</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588294-dragon-view</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/dragon-view</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dragon-view/3030-18388/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Bz6kCFA.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/eiUAYNR.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/zV4fnXB.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/0Y8PDoA.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/3ymFK9A.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/bJHXsLs.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/5saiQEf.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/PnKTCPr.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Jta1uVH.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/NemPEgk.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/3w3LB9u.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/sm9NMpg.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/LHSHLVe.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/YwCuMtV.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/KLNgSe4.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Warrior! Open your eyes! This is the future of gaming! Look, before you leap, this isn't some corny collection of cardboard dungeons and dragons. It's a brilliant new vision of RPG action adventure, with real-time 16 meg 3D scrolling like you've never seen. Plus an incredible hero's-eye-view of the danger. Through caves of fire and meadows of ice, against brutal demons and unforeseen evils, all the way to a showdown you'll never forget, bring your bow, your sword, your magic. And don't blink - or you're doomed!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eb2ebf9a-0ca6-4879-85a4-01d9f138c76c.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b785129a-f938-48d0-bafa-4bfadefc6818.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3662328b-1d96-4144-8ee1-74db06361532.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0ef523ac-3a55-4875-b524-4f76df81b1b9.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/51c5a5b4-5572-4058-b579-3d8a6b0667ec.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/36db0220-f4f0-4764-a43d-308d642595c6.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dc0a6af0-0481-4121-b6a8-eb772f0180d3.png</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ce559754-42c1-4c70-9ade-9debdbbe0430.png</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/38e441c1-b2f9-4fb9-9970-5a6bdd760d1b.png</snapshot16>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Kemco</Publisher>
</game>