<Game>
	<Name>Dream Basketball - Dunk & Hoop (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dream Basketball: Dunk &amp; Hoop is a basketball game from Human Entertainment that was released exclusively in Japan for the Super Famicom in late 1994. The player can choose between a regular match of basketball, featuring two baskets and teams of five, or a 3-on-3 mode which is focused on one basket. Up to five human players can join in on either mode, provided a multi-tap peripheral is available.The game features sixteen fictional basketball teams as well as one all-star team that is only available in the Exhibition mode. They include: The Photons, the Comets, the Flames, the Vikings, the Arrows, the Tomahawks, the Rollers, the Stingrays, the Langers (possibly meant to be Rangers), the Rings, the Waves, the Wizards, the Unicorns, the Tridents, the Sprinters, the Serpents. The all-star team is simply called Japan.Cheat: Color of the court (3 on 3 exhibition mode)In the 3 on 3 exhibition mode, when it displays "VS" in big letters (on the screen) if you push the direction key, depending on the direction you push, the color(s) of the court will change.Cheat: Color of the court (3 on 3 exhibition mode)Choose the "Practice Mode", and then while choosing "One on One" press the B button on Controller 1 while holding down the Start button on Controller 2. Now you can play 1 on 1 with Player 2.Cheat: Color of the court (3 on 3 exhibition mode)On the mode selection screen (Main Menu), if you press A, X, and R on Controller 1 and B, Y, and L on Controller 2 at the same time, USA will be added to the Team selection screen. The USA appears in all of the Regular Game and 3 on 3 modes except for Tournament Mode (it does appear on Round Robin).Cheat: Access all the game endingsSelect Password mode, Round Robin, and then enter:Cheat: Access all the game endingsSelect Password mode, Tournament, and then enter:Cheat: Access all the game endingsOn the option screen set "COURT" to B, and then enter the password "SUNSET." When an error appears, blank out the password box and select EXIT, and start the 3 on 3 exhibition, the background will change to sunset. Similarly, if you use the password "YONAKA" the background will change to night.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Human Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-5 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>qguHFtYi8T0</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571171-dream-basketball-dunk-and-hoop</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dream-basketball-dunk-hoop/3030-50450/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dream_Basketball:_Dunk_%26_Hoop</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/5pILrzi.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ljnh4ls.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/OjfcMA9.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/u0LWppd.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ebCcudc.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/VuuAq5h.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/o7xh7UB.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/00zwnVD.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/agGQHdr.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/bESaOzb.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/yvAb0Rw.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/WvHleU5.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/nQXjicg.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/eVIJBWl.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In this basketball game the player can choose between a regular match of basketball, featuring two baskets and teams of five, or a 3-on-3 mode which is focused on one basket. Up to five human players can join in on either mode, provided a multi-tap peripheral is available. The game features sixteen fictional basketball teams as well as one all-star team that is only available in the Exhibition mode. They include: The Photons, the Comets, the Flames, the Vikings, the Arrows, the Tomahawks, the Rollers, the Stingrays, the Langers (possibly meant to be Rangers), the Rings, the Waves, the Wizards, the Unicorns, the Tridents, the Sprinters, the Serpents. The all-star team is simply called Japan.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>VdnyOvOXA6I</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5714c39d-5922-4f52-b292-1a32a0bdcdd8.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/54c101a1-4abc-4f15-94f5-adb2c06e2ea6.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49510a93-c0cc-4114-953c-cc8b871e8ff0.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a4316287-e58f-479d-8946-c1e5e404b74e.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Human Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>