<Game>
	<Name>Dream T.V. (USA)</Name>
	<plot>A mystical television has challenged 2 kids to complete quests on various worlds. The first world is the Medieval World, land of castles, dungeons, undead skeleton warriors, malicious knights, and lots of keys and doors. The goal is to collect a number of puzzle pieces and get out of the world. Other world themes include Egyptian, Prehistoric, and Futuristic.Dream TV is a 2-player action/adventure game with only a single player. The player must alternately control both kids throughout the game. The player can either adopt a split-screen view showing both kids, or a fullscreen view that focuses on one kid. The game includes challenges that require the player to use both kids simultaneously, such as a see-saw where both kids need to bounce on either end in order to propel one up onto a higher platform.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Triffix Entertainment Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.75</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1907</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588298-dream-tv</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/dream-tv</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dream-tv/3030-35318/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/WpB2yRV.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OdlV2x9.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/9aDyiUl.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/GuUteOH.png</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xs2k3C3.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/BA4y9wt.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/nCMXscu.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/k18JliN.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ySd6GWP.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/pvzjbI9.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/iWMrnTr.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/HcPgEce.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/X4mUXCR.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/SAGlBpS.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ubEifHa.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/R9fEYPm.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>It's a video nightmare! While playing a mysterious video game cartridge that arrived in the mail Jimmy and Charlie, national video game champions, were captured and warped to an alternate dimensions by th evil emperor, Critic. For his amusement Jimmy and Charlie are forced to fight Critic's evil creations on the four Dream Worlds: Medieval World, Egyptian World, Prehistoric World, and Future World. If Jimmy and Charlie can successfully collect nine hidden puzzle pieces from each level and overcome the obstacles in their way there is a chance that they can defeat Critic and destroy his power forever. But let it be known, for the thousands of years Critic has been in power no one has ever survived the challenge and none have ever escaped... alive!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/16c628ba-a269-4a0c-820e-132f9c2148ef.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/574f93ea-7cbc-4221-9cfd-33f28dc8b181.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3b1027b8-2f31-4784-9b07-9a14f5cef80c.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d4571279-6a4b-41a5-8d6e-4785386dc5bb.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6897ab60-db1d-4598-8422-86c2b006aee9.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2abd1771-a5fb-47e0-9826-89a3089a00b7.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Triffix</Publisher>
</game>