<Game>
	<Name>Earth Light (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Earth Light is a strategy game for the Super Famicom that features mechs fighting each other in various conflicts on land, in air and in space. Though superficially similar to existing Gundam strategy games, Earth Light is unaffiliated with that franchise (coincidentally enough, a later 1999/2000 Gundam movie had the subtitle "Earth Light"). As with earlier strategy games from Hudson, like Military Madness, the action takes place on a hexagonal grid, with entire sides taking turns moving into position and engaging enemy units within range. The game also takes a leaf from Advance Wars's book by painting the sides in vibrant colors to help make them stand out from one another.Earth Light was eventually followed up with a sequel, Earth Light II: Luna Strike.Cheat: Debug ModeDuring the intro, hold Down+B and press R three times. The following button commands will now be enabled:</plot>
	<releasedate>24/7/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Sci-Fi</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson</Developer>
	<VideoURL>ofA2bIok-kA</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570850-earth-light</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/earth-light/3030-44140/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/EKRqzlK.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/K2slUH0.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ynBeTIK.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/AP14G6W.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6uz5dJO.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/EWC1W1U.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/UzuuaoK.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/JPoMZLL.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/z36olDZ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/g0zls1S.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/fhYW2AF.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/KD8oaPN.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/6d9Jb7u.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/taWIXYj.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Upon its release in 1992, Earth Light was a bit of a novelty in the realm of turn-based war strategy games. In Earth Light, the entire arsenal of weapons and troops at your disposal were decidedly "cute" and cartoon-like in appearance (fittingly adorned, I should add, in wardrobes of powder-blue, canary-yellow, hot-pink, lime-green, and sugarplum-purple).  Yes, Earth Light featured purple space cruisers, pink artillery cannons, and lime-green MECHs.  This unabashedly cheerful approach to war gaming contrasts sharply with the more "serious", "somber", "gritty" and oftentimes clinical atmosphere commonly found in today's (and yesteryear's) war simulations.  Earth Light is cute, through and through (except for the just plain goofy antagonist who stars in the cinema screens</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>http://nectaris.tg-16.com/earth_light_FAQ_SNES_famicom.html</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/08d8df1c-22c0-459f-a24f-0556e7d1cf40.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fdcb16f9-dde1-4911-a5cb-adc42256d8ae.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9fb56e51-4973-4ff6-9a0e-7bb7d01ab686.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>