<Game>
	<Name>Elnard (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The graphics are eye-popping, breath-taking, stunning and unbelievable, not to mention incredible. This is no hack-and-slash, rip-your-guts-out fighter! This is the future of RPGs, right here in your hands! With music this good, you won't turn the sound off--you'll turn it up!No more small elves leading your team! This game contains real, believable figures. You won't be embarrassed to use your own name; you'll be proud. It's just you against six other characters in search of the 7 Sacred Runes. Whoever finds them... Rules the World. It's that simple, that easy. The only problem is you have some enemies, and I don't mean a few. I mean an army of things you've never seen before ready to raise the hair on the back of your neck and take you out the one swing. This is one powerful RPG. Can you handle it?!Cheat: Infinite Stat Boosts (Lux)In the past, with Lux in the party, he is able to get stat boosts for 30 HP, 30 MP, and 20 of the remaining stats. While this cutscene occurs, you can walk four steps. During those steps, if you walk out of bounds (like through a doorway) as the dialogue box appears, you will get the named stat boost. Here in particular, you want to walk right to the wall, let go of Right briefly, and then press it again quickly. By doing this, you can still get another stat boost, with the previous one having already taken effect!Cheat: Defeat Romus in 1 turn.First let Romus kill you, then back in Rablesk and find a man with an upset wife. He will give you a Whistle. Go back to Romus and right at your first turn use the Whistle and he dies instantly. Just remember if using this tip it will cost you half your gold.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Produce</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>icX0iqgShoc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>282</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563501-the-7th-saga</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-7th-saga/3030-20389/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/PmiG6m0.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/FA42lpZ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/foOToUK.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/8rWdn1R.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/d77YNeY.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/y41CcZN.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/1IPJXcO.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Xs7v5gM.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/NbfxrCc.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/q4QB8O4.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/aFTKW30.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/XYqjO1X.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/eS66Xdy.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/0OtZe27.png</clearlogo1>
</game>