<Game>
	<Name>Emmitt Smith Football (USA)</Name>
	<plot>A generic football game, among the many back in the day, Emmitt Smith Football has the standard Exhibition and Season modes along with multiple camera angles.  It also features a 360 degree TV-style instant replay for bone-crunching and ground-breaking plays that are performed.The one thing that sets it apart from others is the ability to create and save (using battery back-up) 64 unique plays that can be accessed at any time during a game along with the standard pre-set plays. While it does not have NFL or NFLPA licenses, it does feature then former Dallas Cowboys running back star Emmitt Smith, who is also on the front cover of the box.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>JVC Musical Industries, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>3563</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588306-emmitt-smith-football</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/emmitt-smith-football</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/emmitt-smith-football/3030-22056/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/drpfsce.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Koj7EuM.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/GNCFzL8.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/j6icMdc.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wj8yacL.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/InGroOP.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/2McPGCD.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/J0dkj53.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/3ogWSwJ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/pvQEU18.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/NyS1ppJ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/IivWSwj.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5cnre5a.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/bFBVIg2.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Emmitt Smith, considered to be one of the greatest running backs in professional football, is now crashing into your living room. His mesmerizing moves and superior speed are rolled-up together with the down and dirty action of a real pro-football game. - Only Emmitt Smith Football has the PLAY EDITOR to create customized offensive and defensive plays! - Save function allows access to 64 custom plays at any one time! - Never miss a move with multiple camera angles and 360 degree instant replays! - Digitized sound effects intensify every bone-crushing blow!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4b8f22c6-8296-4b6c-85a3-dc9153a78683.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d5549063-9cf4-4f93-ae83-2fc1465f4739.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e5f2635-ed4e-4649-af1f-1d182ee2da16.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e44252a2-ace8-4346-9348-8bad4ad95a04.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>JVC</Publisher>
</game>