<Game>
	<Name>ESPN Speedworld (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>ESPN Speed World is a Super NES and Sega Genesis video game that involves the player controlling NASCAR Winston Cup stock cars as they do laps around various oval tracks, road courses, and superspeedways. All stock cars in the game have the capability to go up to 200 miles per hour (approximately 322 kilometers per hour). The object of the game is to get as close to first place as possible. This game uses Dr. Jerry Punch and an interactive pit crew to simulate the feeling of racing during the 1993 Winston Cup season. Like in most racing games, being in the top positions gives the player more points than being in the bottom positions. Stock cars can be customized with a choice of colors and styles.Sponsors in addition to automobile manufacturers are absent due to licensing difficulties. The real-life drivers of this era are also missing because the game only has an ESPN license and not an official NASCAR license. The Sega Genesis version shows more realistic detail in the car decals and advertising billboards than the Super NES version of the game.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/ESPN_Speed_World</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>1.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3565</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588311-espn-speedworld</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/espn-speed-world</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/espn-speedworld/3030-33088/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/WH8PrjS.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/xQ4iTlg.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/vP7LV1p.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ePWdCTv.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/hNRLZPx.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/HLG5EYv.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/2CeaUAU.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/wuwCpDy.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/z2tOBEa.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ZTs3R4c.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Fd4STlS.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/HXJa2XT.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/KEcKSve.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/PHjv3W8.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/w6RIrQv.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/AMfsKf3.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You've got the pedal to the metal. Your 5-liter turbo-charged modified street machine is screaming down the straightaway at 200 mph. Now you're drafting right on the tail of your nemesis. Suddenly you sling-shot past for the lead, blowing into the backstretch and full blast into the tightest corner of the track. Welcome to ESPN SPEEDWORLD, the highest octane stock car racing simulator ever created. It leaves the competition in the pits.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/96fac730-d180-49ce-9172-bebccce48209.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7e296115-b2de-4ebb-afb5-164ef477817a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/55587616-a001-47c7-a173-c97a8ed7d146.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7f41909e-3645-4b7e-a90d-8fd3d3a77e94.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sony</Publisher>
</game>