<Game>
	<Name>ESPN Sunday Night NFL (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:ESPN Sunday Night NFL is a football game based on the TV show of the same name, which aired on the ESPN when the game was out in 1994. It was released on the Super Nintendo, Genesis and the Sega CD. The game uses a vertical perspective common to football games of the era, using sprite scaling as the ball travels the field to zoom in and out on the players.The game has the NFL license, so the player can choose between twenty-eight teams present in the 1994 AFC and NFC leagues. The stats are approximate to the quality of the teams at the time, with certain teams vastly overpowering others in offense and defense. TeamsBuffalo BillsIndianapolis ColtsMiami DolphinsNew England PatriotsNew York JetsCincinnati BengalsCleveland BrownsHouston Oilers (now the Tennessee Titans)Pittsburgh SteelersDenver BroncosKansas City ChiefsLos Angeles Raiders (now the Oakland Raiders)San Diego ChargersSeattle SeahawksDallas CowboysNew York GiantsPhiladelphia EaglesArizona CardinalsWashington RedskinsChicago BearsDetroit LionsGreen Bay PackersMinnesota VikingsTampa Bay BuccaneersAtlanta FalconsLos Angeles Rams (now the St. Louis Rams)New Orleans SaintsSan Francisco 49ers	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>3566</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588312-espn-sunday-night-nfl</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/espn-sunday-night-nfl</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/espn-sunday-night-nfl/3030-50378/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/FIbjuf5.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ovFbj8O.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/2YC6G57.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/IJtEwkm.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/gfmUq5I.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/PdhwQDp.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/0oUfbO9.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7lYn5sq.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/k3R2ZZq.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/UEkw9mZ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/9mZonLW.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/tqrYHiQ.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UyyRi5L.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/bkJ6Q6n.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>ESPN Sunday Night NFL stands head and shoulder pads above the competition with incredible game play features and an end zone to end zone perspective. Hosted by ESPN's own Chris Berman, this 16-meg game puts you in total control of the action with all 28 NFL teams. You'll feel like you just turned on the TV, but there's one BIG difference... you control the action with lots of incredible plays, play-by-plat commentary, plus pre-game, half-time and post game reports, full season playing options and battery backup for saving your stats. Down on the field you'll have unprecedented control over your own players. Battle your way through the playoffs and "you could go all the way" to the Super Bowl!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/557e26d1-0e25-4e33-8863-39bd67214e68.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b313b43a-5fd0-4d29-a6cc-09dfb9f912e0.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2d975ce8-1df1-43ca-b018-44fc8694b284.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/327685f6-c899-48ed-ac37-0a58f1a0f003.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sony Imagesoft</Publisher>
</game>