<Game>
	<Name>ESPN National Hockey Night (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:ESPN National Hockey Night is a hockey game for the Super Nintendo, Sega Genesis and Sega CD released towards the end of 1994. It is licensed by the NHL and features all the actual team names. It is also based on the ESPN TV show of the same name that aired between 1992-2004, and features the voice and digitized likeness of host Bill Clement.The game is the first to provide two different angles of the rink. Players can opt for a horizontal perspective that was popular with earlier hockey games or a vertical perspective which had become the norm for the EA Sports NHL series. The game features all 26 teams of the NHL and allows for up to four players (at least for the SNES version) to take part in Exhibition, Tournament and Season modes.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>3564</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588310-espn-national-hockey-night</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/espn-national-hockey-night_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/espn-national-hockey-night/3030-30852/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/1MOQibx.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/EpkQq1F.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/UE2rWIw.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/W66t4ID.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/tkwiRhh.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/rVy7Dm5.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/jTpsCTd.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/3GVoPNJ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/5pdlBG5.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/8MeupsB.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/pfhj5om.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/T0bH5AU.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/9VuzoPU.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Ubx1bqx.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Now you and up to three friends can face off for an entire 84-game NHL season, including the Stanley Cup Playoffs and NHL Skills Challenge. Featuring the ultra-realistic ESPN look and feel, you can choose from two viewpoints during game play. Make on-ice line changes and save every game and player stats, thanks to battery back-up. Some 2,000 frames of body checks, slap shots and breakaways make you feel like you're into a real ESPN hockey broadcast. ESPN National Hockey Night - everything else is just practice.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ad2f194a-141f-4767-8561-2e9e4413483a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e8b917ad-67c4-4b9c-808a-751803ba16ea.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e46af9a7-94d2-42ff-bc4e-8c308df52f60.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e5d5646-1d78-4eef-9814-605f5b651db1.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sony</Publisher>
</game>