<Game>
	<Name>F-1 Grand Prix (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:F-1 Grand Prix is the first in a series of semi-serious F1 racing games from Video System. Originally released in the Arcades, it was later ported to the Super Famicom.The Super Famicom version uses a top-down view that centers the camera on the player's vehicle. Whenever the player turns or accelerates, the background moves around to compensate while the car sprite says completely static in the center. Before a race begins, the game uses the Super Famicom's mode 7 to show off the track at an angle and give players a sense of the twists and turns ahead. Teams/Drivers (Super Famicom)McLaren: Ayrton Senna, Gerhard BergerWilliams: Nigel Mansell, Riccardo PatreseFerrari: Alain Prost, Jean AlesiBenetton: Nelson Piquet, Michael SchumacherTyrrell: Satoru Nakajima, Stefano ModenaBrabham: Martin Brundle, Mark BlundellFootwork: Michele Alboreto, Alex CaffiLotus: Mika H&#228;kkinen, Johnny HerbertFondmetal: Olivier GrouillardLeyton House: Maur&#237;cio Gugelmin, Ivan CapelliAGS: Gabriele Tarquini, Fabrizio BarbazzaDallara: Emanuele Pirro, JJ LehtoMinardi: Pierluigi Martini, Gianni MorbidelliLigier: Thierry Boutsen, &#201;rik ComasLarrousse: &#201;ric Bernard, Aguri SuzukiColoni: Pedro Matos ChavesJordan: Andrea de Cesaris, Roberto MorenoModena: Nicola Larini, Eric van de Poele</plot>
	<releasedate>28/4/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Video System</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>rdXTXQW4tEw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26328</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581974-f-1-grand-prix</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/f-1-grand-prix</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/f-1-grand-prix/3030-37355/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/8Kf6FFp.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ZF505ID.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/XFArvJJ.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/9beXhWv.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wOrkn6J.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/5TUnKxg.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/1Myo3Qs.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/W6TkEuL.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/hBe4aXg.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/PUHcf5c.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/vj6lM5S.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/5xX6UsG.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/NtCeF4F.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>F-1 Grand Prix is a Racing game, developed and published by Video System, which was released in Japan in 1992.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e1b5749-9b42-47fe-be01-42f095d47881.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c584cb84-780c-43cf-96e6-4d7946665499.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Video System</Publisher>
</game>