<Game>
	<Name>F1 Pole Position (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>This Formula 1 racing game features 3 game modes and 16 tracks to race on. The game modes included are Battle, World Grand Prix, and Test Run.Battle mode allows for an exhibition race where the player can choose any course and its condition plus how many laps the race will be. The player can also choose to race up to 13 other opposing racers,World Grand Prix mode lets the player compete in a season of F1 races. The higher a position a racer finishes in a race, the more points will be awarded to increase their place in the total season standings.Test Run lets the player practice any track without the interference of other racers,Players can fine-tune their car using a variety of settings. Settings include adjusting the steering, tires, gears, brakes, wings, and the suspension. Players can also choose the type of pit work, tachometer (digital or analog), and whether to have either manual or automatic gear shifting.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Ubi Soft Entertainment Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>PhYkwbMOAVA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3569</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588316-f1-pole-position</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/f1-pole-position</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/f-1-pole-position/3030-36323/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/kbElGDl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/cfLCh3V.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/oMdLArI.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/4nwJrNO.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wKVoVS7.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/hutwDsG.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/wzmmKRe.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/LHSBZ6X.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4XB90Yh.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ZokEHf1.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5BVTL92.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/SuMA7Y5.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/2XBhbLw.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/DUD39gW.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/E7Kfbem.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/hdRzS1f.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>REV YOUR ENGINES AND RACE TOWARDS THE CHECKERED FLAG! Experience the excitement of real racing competition. Strap on your crash helmet, settle down into the cockpit, and go head to head against the world's greatest F-1 drivers, including Nigel Mansell &amp; Michael Andretti, on the most challenging race tracks in the world! This IS Formula 1 Racing! - Awesome graphics, smooth control, and incredible speed deliver the most gut wrenching F-1 experience possible. - Customize and fine-tune your car using a variety of settings. Adapt your state-of-the-art racing machine to changing road and weather conditions. - Three different playing modes, with split screen competition, for 1 or 2 players. Test your nerves and hone your racing skills as you fly down straight-aways and feel the tug of the G-forces as you take dangerous hairpin turns. F-1 Pole Position offers non-stop racing excitement and gets your adrenaline pumping!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/faa4a490-e17d-4adc-90ba-3fa4a650a094.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ddb60952-a43a-4757-aa1e-e363fa81bd6d.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/208e64c2-0509-4dfe-b668-ece6d50a1f45.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d0fbb3e2-ffea-419c-8f78-47b78762dd0c.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b9422e19-9920-468c-ae1e-20ca18e04481.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23883599-ea1e-4f74-b927-387024e37c12.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>