<Game>
	<Name>F1 ROC - Race of Champions (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Have you ever dreamed of being a Formula 1 racer? Have you fantasized about modifying your car to go faster and turn sweeter than any of the others? Have you imagined taking your F1 racer all around the world and becoming the best racer ever? Then look no further, because at least you can play a game where you can do all that, 'cause you know it's never gonna happen in real life. I mean honestly, did you really think it would?F1 ROC is a fun racing game that lets you customize your racer and make it better than the other cars on the track. The graphics of this game were good for its time, however it's not the best SNES game as far as graphics go. The music is alright however, much like in other racers, the music only plays on the title and menu screens and is silent during gameplay. Despite that this is a fun racer that I highly recommend.Directions:F-1 ROC is a fun and simple game to play. Start the game by choosing if you want to play Grand Prix or Single race. With Single race you get to choose which track you run, and then you spend a predetermined amount of money modifying you car. You car, however, does not keep its modifications for the next race.In Grand Prix however, you race on all the tracks from America to Japan and even countries like Portugal. You earn money depending on what place you finish the race in, and with that money add modifications to your car such as a better engine, suspension, tires, and other car parts. Then all you do is get racing and have a blast. So sit down, log in, and have fun. Controls:A Button - ACCELERATE / NITROB Button - ACCELERATEX Button - BRAKEY Button - BRAKEStart Button - PAUSESelect Button - REMOVE / REPLACE DISPLAYTips:CodesEnter the following codes at the Select Player screen:OTO Sound TestSETAUSA Start with $10, 000Reviewer: grimjockeyhttp://www.consoleclassix.com/snes/f1_roc.htmlCheat: CodesEnter the following codes at the Select Player screen:Cheat: Check SNES chips version numbersTo check your SNES chips' version, select a new file and use the name XXCHECKXX. Press reset to return to game.Cheat: Check SNES chips version numbersTo play a slot machine mini-game first make sure your game is saved in Monaco. Next select Name Change at the file select screen and change your name to CASINO. After selecting Race, you'll be taken to the slot machine mini-game.ControlsPress "A" to place your wagerPress "B" or "Down" to spinPress "Select" to exit game.Cheat: Use Opponent Names as PlayersWhile at the screen to enter the player's name, press Down or Up on Controller 2 to scroll through opponent names used in the game. This will allow the player to easily obtain a name exactly like an opponent's instead of manually needing to enter it.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Seta</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>R_2CcgshKWQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3602</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588318-f1-roc-race-of-champions</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/f1roc-race-of-champions</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/f1-roc-race-of-champions/3030-22442/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4kBhjV6.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/UCi7ICh.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/wYZ1bmN.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/5SQxCoY.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ElWFdGz.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/n27DFB9.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/oQCVJ3g.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/AJ3xxLC.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/z7aCR3m.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/kzCVyrZ.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/np2X0v0.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/LYvWhtI.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/EpoybHM.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/qGhg2Ny.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Inoi7o7.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5Df2UFi.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/rkuWoJf.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Strap yourself in the cockpit, step on the gas and take a turbo-charged ride through the high-speed world of Formula One racing with F1 ROC. You'll test your skill on the famed hairpins of Monte Carlo. Steel your nerves on the legendary straights of Monza. Race to win on a total of 16 thrilling international courses. Best of all, you can customize your racer millions of different ways. If you're ready for the winner's circle, get ready to ROC!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea2c3b0d-3e0d-4d94-bdf1-108bf22c201b.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fcd6f0e5-219e-4bbd-8c65-82d656ec7c19.png</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e8255882-a194-43a3-858a-e19deab3dba1.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/39ca2c3a-3675-4071-ab1e-f9a24e9ece26.png</boxart8>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/889f5a0b-ae65-4e50-a2a6-a8ff23185316.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7375b18d-e135-4091-984c-cb47db71f53e.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e1c7ab88-2304-4627-8cfc-0becba9b819f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c63c016-51ef-4438-90c7-9c16866282bd.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>SETA Corporation</Publisher>
</game>