<Game>
	<Name>Faceball 2000 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The November 1991 issue of Nintendo Power where Faceball 2000 was reviewed.Faceball 2000 is a first-person shooter developed by Xanth Software and published by Bullet Proof Software for the Game Boy on December 10, 1991 and the Super Nintendo Entertainment System on September 1992. Based on MIDI Maze for the Atari ST, Bullet Proof Software acquired the console publishing rights to the game and released the game in America, Europe and Japan. Players move around a mazed arena as giant floating happy faces, shooting large orbs at enemies to "tag them out". The game was also published for the Game Gear in Japan on December 17, 1993 by Riverhill Software. The Game Boy and Game Gear versions featured local multiplayer via the use of link cables (up to sixteen players on the Game Boy version and two players on the Game Gear version), while the SNES version featured two-player split-screen multiplayer. The four player link cable, which was only packed in with Nintendo&#8217;s F1-race, was necessary for playing the multiplayer.Gameplay:An early level of Cyberzone mode.The game is a first-person shooter, where the player controls a floating head inside of a giant maze. The goal is to eliminate enemy heads by shooting large orbs.The game features two normal modes and one hidden mode. The first mode is called Cyberzone, in which players must eliminate a set number of opponents before an exit opens up and they can progress to the next level of increasing difficulties. The second mode is called Arena, in which players can choose from a variety of enemies and stages to play on, with the goal of defeating all the enemies. The final, and hardest mode, is called Cyperscape. Instead of having to eliminate a set number of enemies, Cyberscape is much more maze-focused, not having a map for players like other modes. This mode can only be unlocked by entering a code in the player select screen. All modes can be played with two players.Cheat: Hiddem Warp RoomsStart a Game in ''Cyberscape'' mode. On Level 1 (''Find the Exit''), when you see the exit (It's a flashing wall) shoot it 5 times. You'll magically warp to another part of the level with a Speedup Pod, an 9 Extra Lives Pod, and exits to levels 10, 15, 20, and 25. If you shoot the Nine Lives Pod three times, there will be a key inside. Take it and another part of the room will open, with a Speedup Pod, a Automag Pod, a Level 3 Armor Pod, Warp doors to levels 30, 35, 40, and a Rover enemy. You'll note that like the Nine Lives Pod before it, the Armor Pod didn't disappear when you took armor from it. Travel around the corner and you should face a dead end. (The exit to level 40 will be at a 90-degree angle to this wall, on the right.) Shoot that wall once, and then touch it. Travel back around the corner to the former Armor Pod, Touch it once, and then shoot it twice to get a key that will open that wall. On the other side are Automag, Speedup and Armor Pods, as well as two Bouncers and warps to levels 60 and 65. Finally, go near the East wall of this room. (It's near the small ''block'' on your map.) Move slightly to the left of the center, then touch that part of the wall five times, then shoot it once to open the final secret portion of the level. Just inside the Room is a warp to Level 71, but also Two Ninjas, a Guard, a Vampire, and a Kamikaze... </plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>3603</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588319-faceball-2000</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/faceball-2000</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/faceball-2000/3030-10852/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/rCd2Ynn.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/TyRqDO5.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/k3MUuxN.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JzBVmfD.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/DpOD6DH.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/CR2W064.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/wEZhJN2.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/zhAtNto.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/rZe8p2O.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/oL6MxOQ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/bgBEppT.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2cLuPAP.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/2CHXU55.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/1o7FFDy.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Qt3CdAR.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/TxNfcSr.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>"Virtual Reality" for your Super NES! Welcome to the exciting new world of FaceBall 2000, where 3D graphics, first person perspective and 360° maneuverability make you feel like you're inside your video game! What you see is where you are, as you team up, compete with a friend or play alone against computer-controlled opponents. Transport yourself inside the walls of CyberZone, where you'll be surrounded by menacing enemies lurking in a series of treacherous mazes. Or, enter the Arena where " Have a Nice Day" takes on a whole new meaning in fast-paced rounds of high-tech combat. Wherever you go in FaceBall 2000, it's your chance to wipe the smiles off those annoying happy faces - and maybe a few of your friends - once and for all!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9092e71-6060-44db-9b8c-8795a64e6603.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e67bcc4-5252-4148-9815-c62068d98545.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99e8374c-2e03-4c4c-8732-6efa6f8c0e9d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fc4b5bab-505a-473b-a6a2-28fe9681547e.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Bullet Proof Software</Publisher>
</game>