<Game>
	<Name>Family Dog (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Based on a short-lived animated prime-time television series created by Steven Spielberg and Tim Burton, you play as the title dog through three levels. The young boy in your family likes to target you for his mischief.  He sets up volleys of tennis balls and lets loose a vacuum cleaner on you which you must avoid.  The cat and other obstacles await you in your house while you collect bones for power.   After all the trouble you cause in the home, you are sent to Obedience School and you have to run a gauntlet of gung-ho instructors and ferocious Dobermans in the heavily-guarded compound.  If successful at escaping, you reach a forest filled with wild animals.You can use flips, spins and barks to make your way through the various obstacles.  A special ball when found will trigger a bonus game that will also teach you how to fetch.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Malibu Games</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.75</rating>
	<VideoURL>-fpwdKbdLUo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3604</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588320-family-dog</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/family-dog</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/family-dog/3030-32152/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4EWuNPY.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Sa7bH1a.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/J64C7n0.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/pvT9axG.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/GbIDh8E.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/lLqv0d5.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/gG9boGr.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vEGyDw4.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/NjRQmfD.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/VKdDcsa.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/XnC7gyh.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/C7E94yE.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Et8gHxF.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/6OxLIsW.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>A CANINE COMIC ADVENTURE!Take a wild look at American life through the eyes of the Family Dog. Dodge the mischievous antics of the prankster son as he teaches the little pup new tricks. "Play Dead" has a whole new meaning as the youth bombards pooch with tennis balls and chases after him with a high powered vacuum cleaner. Just when the hound thinks it's safe - it's off to Obedience school. Here he is surrounded by overly enthusiastic instructors and their very hungry Doberman pinschers. His goal is to escape the compound and make it back to his "loving" family. Dash across the heavily guarded fortress, bound through the limbs of a dark forest and let out powerful barks to ward off creepy creatures. Make it through the cliff-hanging challenges and prove you're the top dog!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0b1e6937-929a-4e2f-8941-891212affc77.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/72421d9f-a041-4e03-922d-285e377c63eb.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4bb06457-1e19-4b03-8af1-54f512296c28.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7d74e9bd-19e9-43d2-8e18-8477034146da.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Malibu Games</Publisher>
</game>