<Game>
	<Name>Family Feud (USA) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Family Feud is an adaptation of the TV game show of the same name, in which two families (five members each) must guess the results of a poll with questions like "What food is commonly eaten at breakfast?". If a team correctly guesses all the answers, or correctly guesses one answer after the other family has given an incorrect answer three times, they win the round.These particular versions were all published by GameTek for various systems, but were functionally similar. The first game to be published by GameTek was the 1991 version for the NES, which was developed by Beam Software (which has since been rebranded as Krome Studios Melbourne). The SNES and Genesis versions were released in October 1993, developed by Imagineering Inc and Eurocom Entertainment Software respectively. The 3DO version from 1994 was also developed by Eurocom Entertainment Software -- this version used digitized actors and clips from the show.This Family Feud is not to be confused with the many other games that have had that title, a complete list of which can be found on the Family Feud franchise page.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>GameTek, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>BkuP7IvxDGo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3605</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588321-family-feud</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/family-feud_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/family-feud/3030-26419/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/SF4vMnU.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/KDFu8jV.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/FXhTriG.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/x4O61ZP.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/yDGm2Ck.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/lLV5lpr.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/dEpVzV5.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VP7pRWf.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Hc1vDmX.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/SQCH5SR.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/V2H9tps.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/1gI8LIP.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/n9J7Dmv.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/s9a2TG1.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/jpDKCra.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Get ready to participate in the wildest feud since the Hatfields and McCoys. Over 4,000 new survey questions taken right from the hit television show. Play alone or with up to nine friends. You battle family against family in guessing the top survey responses from people across the country. This all new version for the Super Nintendo features the Fast-Money Bull's-Eye Round from the newest television format, brilliant graphics and authentic theme music and sound effects. Don't just keep up with the Joneses, beat the pants off 'em, with this all-new FAMILY FEUD.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f3ed92f4-cff5-4541-a81b-83cbe03ed1e3.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/db34ef38-83f4-4c17-8a14-743f470e4b00.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/71b24b3f-08f7-410e-b7d8-6e7bf8f27176.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d695d5c0-7f03-4394-8ded-31fd80e58e51.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>GameTek</Publisher>
</game>