<Game>
	<Name>Fatal Fury Special (Europe) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Fatal Fury Special (known in Japan as Legend of the Hungry Wolf SPECIAL) is a 2D fighting game developed and released by SNK for arcades (using the Neo Geo MVS hardware) and the Neo Geo AES on December 22, 1993.An update to the second installment of the Fatal Fury series (in similar vein to the Street Fighter II updates), Fatal Fury Special improves the game speed, makes it easier to combo attacks together, updates the background stages, makes the four boss characters playable, and adds three new playable characters from the original Fatal Fury (Duck King, Tung Fu Rue, and Geese Howard), as well as a new hidden boss (Ryo Sakazaki from the Art of Fighting series).Along with the standard Neo Geo CD port (by SNK on September 9, 1994), the game received worldwide ports to the Game Gear (in 1994 by TAKARA), Super Nintendo Entertainment System (in 1995 by TAKARA) and Sega CD (in 1995 by JVC). Japan-exclusive ports were also released for the Sharp X68000, PC Engine CD-ROM&#178; (requiring the Arcade Card add-on), and FM Towns. The original Neo Geo version was also included in the Fatal Fury Battle Archives Volume 1 compilation for the PlayStation 2 and was digitally released for the Xbox 360 (via Xbox Live Arcade, featuring online multiplayer, on September 5, 2007), and Wii (via the Wii Virtual Console on November 4, 2009).Characters:Returning CharactersCharacter Select Screen Showing Terry and Andy Terry Bogard Andy Bogard Joe Higashi Mai Shiranui Kim Kaphwan Big Bear Jubei Yamada Cheng Sinzan Billy Kane Axel Hawk Laurence Blood Wolfgang KrauserNew CharactersIn Fatal Fury Special fan favorite characters where added from the the first Fatal Fury. This includes the boss character Geese Howard.CharacterNationalityBrief Stage DescriptionStageTung Fu RueJapaneseMountain top with old bridge Duck KingAmericanAmerican Night ClubueGeese Howard AmericanAncient TempleSecret OpponentRyo Sakazaki is a hidden boss in Fatal Fury Special. To fight Ryo the player must beat the game without losing a single round and after the last boss he will appear for a challenge.CharacterNationalityBrief stage descriptionStageRyo SakazakiAmerican  				</plot>
	<releasedate>1/4/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>TAKARA Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>1GBkiiCcLhk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2858</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588325-fatal-fury-special</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/fatal-fury-special</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fatal-fury-special/3030-19200/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/nTT3i90.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nGjS0uf.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/IWT6fl4.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/zaHFsjS.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/jxMkqK1.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/JPUL7Mx.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/cpadHq6.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/2Xx6i91.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4UD0w1w.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/bv8ZoG2.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/yishKfh.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/rxj66Z0.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JJqg3rZ.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/sHEF6ls.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/MPqEOkI.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/qsXuqsB.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/rMyfa2C.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/vG07hbs.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>They're back... and burning for revenge! Hit the Streets fighting in the ultimate FATAL FURY challenge! - An all-star lineup of FATAL FURY characters, including Geese Howard, Tung Fu Rue and Duck King! - Special guest appearance by Ryo Sakazaki — clear the game without a single loss to come face-to-face with the "Fighting Dragon" for the ultimate battle! - More 3D attack moves than ever before. - New special attacks for non-stop thrills and action. - 'Super Attacks" for inflicting maximum damage on opponents when your life gauge reaches critical. - Mind-blowing Dolby Surround sound and stunning graphics.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e580d114-28fb-469e-91fd-a0bb3cd262be.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/21eb47de-f8b0-4682-8394-a78f6b167394.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7d5b5155-358c-48fc-9801-5905caf92fa9.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/146aabba-e41d-4c8f-8cf0-9ae9508b21ec.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63def82e-03ee-43ed-a20a-b4d60757d730.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/08339dc0-f8b7-4d79-a1e1-dc4fc066a23f.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>SNK</Publisher>
</game>