<Game>
	<Name>Final Fantasy - Mystic Quest (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Chopping down a tree.Final Fantasy Mystic Quest was released on October 5, 1992 for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System in the US. The game was touted as a simplified role-playing game for entry level players. This was done to appeal to people not familiar with the role playing genre, so they could then "graduate" to Squaresoft's other RPGs like Final Fantasy IV or the then-upcoming Secret of Mana. The game was eventually released in its native Japan the following year with the title Final Fantasy USA: Mystic Quest.The game begins with the player controlling a young adult named Benjamin during an adventure to reclaim stolen crystals that represented the world's elemental powers. Unlike most of the Squaresoft RPGs of the time, there are no save points; players are allowed to save at any time. Party size is limited to two with Benjamin and a secondary character slot that rotates as the story progresses. In place of random battles, the player is able to see enemies on the field without the need of an item until a specific point in the game, but all enemies are stationary and incapable of roaming. Also unlike most RPGs, players are not allowed to free roam the world map, making the gameplay mostly linear. The player is required to follow guided paths, some of which could be blocked off until tasks are completed. Characters can jump, and use weapons outside of battle lending it an action-adventure type of gameplay also not found in other Final Fantasies. Mystic Quest includes many puzzles during the gameplay. Mystic Quest does not have the tradition of random enemies like the rest of the Final Fantasy franchise, instead the player battles stationary enemies within dungeons. The player has the choice whether to attack the enemy or not, and can prepare beforehand with restorative items. The battle screen appears after approaching an enemy, turns are awarded back and forth with the fastest character getting the most turns. Players can battle, run, or "control" during the battle menu. Control can allow the player to manually control their allies or have the CPU control them. Battle is influenced by statistics like speed, accuracy, or attacking power. Characters gain experience points and gold pieces from winning battles. The game also includes battlefields that the player can enter and attempt to clear out ten battles against pre-set enemy encounters which rewards the player with a large cash prize or even a unique item.Soundtrack: Soundtrack cover The Soundtrack for Final Fantasy Mystic Quest was composed by Yasuhiro Kawakami and Ryuji Sasai.01 - MYSTIC RE-QUEST I02 - MYSTIC RE-QUEST II03 - Mystic Quest04 - Hill of Fate05 - World06 - Beautiful Forest07 - Battle 108 - Victory Fanfare09 - City of Forest10 - Fossil Labyrinth11 - Battle 212 - Middle Tower13 - Shrine of Light14 - Rock Theme15 - Fanfare of Friendship16 - Dungeon of Ice17 - Dungeon of Waterfall18 - City of Fire - Faeria19 - Rock 'n' Roll20 - Lava Dome21 - City of Wind - Windaria22 - Mountain Range of Whirlwinds23 - The Crystal24 - Last Castle25 - Battle 326 - Mystic Ballad27 - Ending28 - RE-MIXTIC QUESTCheat: Battlefield ResetWhen fighting in a battlefield against an enemy that can selfdestruct, make sure all but that one enemy is dead. Also, make sure your hp is low enough for the selfdestruct to kill you as well. Wait for the enemy to selfdestruct and kill both of you. The battle will end, you will gain all the experience, gp, and even the battle count will decrease, and then it will ask you to try again. Do so and repeat the previous steps until you see that you have won the prize for defeating all the enemies. Win the next battle and exit. The battlefield icon will look like one that has been cleared out and the battlefield will now say: Battlefield Round 255 of 10.Cheat: Battlefield ResetIn the menu screen, press START and SELECT at the same time.  You should then get a box telling you which version number all the chips in your SNES are.  Afterwards, the text in the menu screens might act a bit wacky.  Just exit the menu and enter it again to fix it. Weird little trick for Square to put in the game, eh?Cheat: Battlefield ResetUsable with any battlefield that gives Experience points as a reward.Cheat: Battlefield ResetFight in the battlefield until you have one battle left. Then, go anywhere else, and fight enemies until your experience needed for the next level is within the range that the battlefield gives. (i.e. If the battlefield gives around 200 exp. per battle, get your needed exp. to within 200.)Cheat: Battlefield ResetThen, go back and finish the battlefield. You will gain the level with the exp. gain from the enemies, get the exp. reward, then gain another level.Cheat: Battlefield ResetThis glitch will completely skip getting the fire crystal and/or getting Reuben for the first time.To start, you need your items to be in this order for consumables, Seeds, Cure Potion, Refresher and Heal Potion last. Best way to get this order set up is to get the Seed in Bone Dungeon, getting the Cure Potion right after killing the Flamerus Rex. Get the Refresher in the Ice Pyramid's first room, waiting to get the Heal Potion in the room where you get the second chest armor (It's the right chest of the bottom two.) Okay, now once you beat the Ice Golem, get the coin and make way to Fireburg and go into the Hotel.Use up the last of your seeds so none are left and talk to the npc behind the counter on the right, they sell seeds, set it to buy 0 (ZERO) seeds and accept, open your menu and you'll see the zero seeds, use one and you'll see your Cure Potions turn into the Sun Coin, the final coin to get through Doom Castle.Okay, next thing we'll want to do is talk to the person sitting at the table just to the left and up a bit, they're selling Cure Potions, you want to buy 19 and then open your menu again, actually look at your items, you'll see you've lost both coins you've collected at this point from the first two dungeons, but now, where they were, you now have the last two coins.All you have to do from here is leave fireburg, go back to the focus tower, and enter the next area.Reuben will still pop out of your ass for the little scene at the bridge, but...eh, broken game is broken.Cheat: Battlefield ResetOn American versions of Final Fantasy: Mystic Quest, there is a particular glitch regarding the Life spell. Like in most Final Fantasies (and the EU/JP versions of this game), it is intended to be able to do extreme damage to undead enemies. However, a few flags got mixed up in the US versions of the game: in this version, you can use Life to kill non-undead enemies, although you can't damage undead enemies at all with this spell.Cheat: Battlefield ResetWhen you lose a partner and gain a new one, the new partner will retain resistances from your previous partner if you never turned off the game in between.  Stats are also affected, but do not remain exactly like the previous partner.The new partner will continue to have the incorrect stats and resistances until you restart the game.Cheat: Defeating Doom King EasilyOnce the battle with Doom King has begun, cast Cure on him, and you'll do massive damage to the boss. You'll do about  10,000+ to him. That's an easy win against the final boss, dont you think?Cheat: Defeating Doom King EasilyGo to any town, and if you find a treasure box, open it. Go out of town, then go back in. Open the box again and the item will be available. This can be of great help when you are stocking 99 of each item. </plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Square Soft, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>AyVxBfFc6-c</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1602</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/532476-final-fantasy-mystic-quest</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/final-fantasy-mystic-quest</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/final-fantasy-mystic-quest/3030-3638/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/2c0jokv.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/09g01oc.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/LirxOvh.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/6oocoLh.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/9fFZmUC.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/CrEzaS8.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/Zc8fSgE.jpg</boxart7>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/4RrOGyb.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/MN80O01.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Z9XKzkL.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/WEAByFD.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/M4WwPP4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/KGM4uUM.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/P26VaNV.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/OMYWs5W.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/qEcj8OU.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/fNtsujD.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/jboldUH.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/trcUXP3.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/60IrvEG.png</clearlogo1>
</game>