<Game>
	<Name>Final Fight (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:CPS arcade versionFinal Fight first appeared as a 1989 arcade game released by Capcom for their CPS hardware. It is a side-scrolling beat-em up with attacks consisting mainly of simple punching and kicking, as well as grabs, throws, aerial attacks and special moves which clear the area around the player while draining a small amount of health. Knives, swords and pipes can also be used. In the original arcade release, there are three playable characters: Cody, Haggar , and Guy.Story:Damnd Taunting HaggerThe story revolves around a street gang known as Mad Gear kidnapping Jessica, who is Haggar's daughter and Cody's girlfriend. Instead of giving in to the gang, Haggar, Cody, and Cody's training partner, Guy, take to the streets of Metro City to destroy the gang and rescue Jessica. The player fights through the streets, through the subway system, through a wrestling ring, and eventually fight all the way the leader of the Mad Gear gang's mansion. The final boss is the leader of the Mad Gear gang on a wheelchair with Jessica on his lap rolling around and shooting the heroes with a crossbow. The trio eventually beat him out of his chair and kick him through the large window he is standing next to.HardwareAn original Final Fight arcade machineFinal Fight was originally on Capcom's CPS arcade hardware. It featured a dedicated cabinet with a control panel that had two buttons and a 8-way joystick. Although three characters where selectable only two player could play at a single cabinet. Cabinet Colors varied but where typically black, with large character graphics where featured on the side.Ports Sequels and EmulationThe SNES version of Final FightThe SNES version, released in North America in 1991, disappointed many because it dropped the co-op play, removing arguably the most attractive element of the game and it also removes Guy as a playable character. Though a second version was later released in 1994, called Final Fight: Guy, where Guy was a playable character and Cody was not. This version was available as a rental-only game from Blockbuster video stores.It was recently discovered that two variations of Final Fight: Guy exist- the common "orange box", and the rarer "black box." There is a lot of confusion as to where these black box version came from, and very few have ever been found. Theories express that it could have been the original color of the box until an exclusive deal was later made with Blockbuster or that it was a Canadian variant, despite it being marked as available in the US. This small variation can make these versions of the game very valuable from a collector's standpoint.Two sequels, Final Fight 2 and Final Fight 3, were released on the SNES in 1993 and 1995, respectively.The game was re-released on the Game Boy Advance as Final Fight One. Final Fight: One featured small dialog exchanges before boss fights, unlockable features, and the Street Fighter: Alpha versions of Cody ,and Guy.Final Fight: Double Impact was a PSN and XBLA game that was attached with Magic Sword.The game was also released as part of the 'Capcom Arcade' on iOS ( iPhone, iPod Touch, iPad) in 2011.Playable CharactersHaggarThe big slow strong character of Final Fight. His optimal weapon is the pipe, and has a piledriver and spinning lariat. He is the mayor of Metro City as well as Jessica's Father.CodyThe middle of the road character of Final Fight. His optimal weapon is the knife, he is the only character able to use the knife without throwing it. He uses a jumping spin kick, and is Jessica's boyfriend.GuyThe fast character of Final Fight. His optimal weapon is the Katana. He uses a jumping spin kick similar to Cody's. Guy is a friend of Cody'sStages:Metro City as it appears in Final Fight (CPS arcade version)There are six stages in the first Final Fight all taking place in Metro City.Stage one - SlumStage two - SubwayStage three - West SideStage four - Industrial AreaStage Five - Bay AreaStage six - Up TownBonus Stages:The first bonus stage takes place in a gas station in between level two and three, where the player destroys a thugs car as fast as they can within the time limit.The glass panes factory is the second bonus stage, it takes place between level five and six, where the player is to destroy all of the glass panes in the factory within the time limit.Boss CharactersDamndDamnd is the first level boss, as well as the character that Haggar talks to in the attract screen.*In the SNES version his name was changed to Thrasher.SodomSodom is the Second level boss. He uses two swords that can be knocked out of his hands and used against him. He would later appear as a playable character in Street Fighter Apha.*In some regions he is known as Katana.Edi.EEdi.E is the third stage boss. The gum he spits out at the start of the fight can be eaten to regain health.RolentoThe boss of the fouth stage. He is fought on a elevator while enemies and weapons fall down from above.AbigailAbigail is the boss of the fifth stage. He appears to be a palette swap of Andore with a different head.BelgerHorace Belger is the sixth and final boss. He starts in a electric wheelchair with Jessica in his lap. The chair breaks after a significant amount of damage or a single throw, and Jessica is tossed aside.Cheat: Bonus creditsIf the player initials entered for the top 3 high scores are CAP, COM, GUY and in that order, you will begin a new game with 5 credits instead of 3.Cheat: Bonus creditsHold L+R and press the Start button at the title screen. Press up, down, and X to adjust the options. Press R to play the music and sound effects.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>2qCN-YOi14o</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1913</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588332-final-fight</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/final-fight</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/final-fight/3030-6722/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/LnycXTt.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/4SzydSs.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/WDXb99M.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/YmaaN1A.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/xX8DTtU.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/aCgTTpP.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/myl4lPq.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/vn9wLlU.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/gwsNQkF.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/C5ipmlv.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Jv2LE7w.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/7UXIUer.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Sa1VJMd.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/LOM1ETq.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/cdUZgk5.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/f3tOeqj.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/a3LIq94.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/kihqSy8.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/RrIHNN0.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/SiXtHCL.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/byyG2gf.jpg</fanart6>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/GzRCILf.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/nSg2Vpu.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/ee5P4In.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://i.imgur.com/WpleNbS.png</clearlogo3>
</game>