<Game>
	<Name>Final Fantasy V (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Galuf battling Gilgamesh while using the Dragoon Job.Final Fantasy V is the fifth entry in the long-running Final Fantasy series by Square-Enix, released on December 6, 1992. It follows many of the traditions of the series while experimenting with new ideas. As opposed to the previous game, which featured nearly no character customization, Final Fantasy V had an open-ended "job" system which allowed characters to be customized with different roles, and even use one role's abilities while in another one. The execution was similar to the one that Final Fantasy III had, although less rigid.ReleaseAs originally released, Final Fantasy V only came out for the Super Famicom in Japan. Due to worries from the project team that the game wouldn't be accessible to the average gamer, the translation of Final Fantasy V was shelved, and Final Fantasy VI was translated into American and European regions as "Final Fantasy III" instead. English-speaking countries did not see an official release until the PlayStation port, Final Fantasy Anthology, was released nearly seven years later, on September 30, 1999. Another version, this time ported to the Game Boy Advance, was released on November 6, 2006. It has also seen a release in Japan on Nintendo's Wii Virtual Console in January 2011 and on PSN as a PSOne Classic on April 6th. A European and North American release has been confirmed as a PSOne classic.Story:The story begins as the winds across the worlds begin to slow, bringing ships to a halt. King Tycoon, on the back of his dragon Hiryuu, sets off to the wind shrine to investigate the matter. When the dragon arrives, the crystal shatters, stopping the wind. As this happens, a meteorite plunges into the ground near Tycoon castle, and close to the spot where Bartz and his chocobo, Boko, are relaxing. Bartz and Boko set off to investigate the meteorite, where they encounter a young girl named Lenna, under attack by some monsters. Bartz saves her, and the two investigate further. They encounter someone else at the site, an old man named Galuf. Unfortunately, his name is the only thing he remembers. As the three talk, Lenna tells them that she was traveling to the wind shrine, where her father was. Galuf realizes that he must go to the wind shrine! Of course, he doesn't know why. With that, the three of them set off for the wind shrine.The Water CrystalThe meteorite proves to be quite the obstacle, requiring the trio to travel by sea. They recruit the help of pirate captain Faris Scherwiz, who takes them to the shrine. When they arrive, the situation is bleak. King Tycoon is nowhere to be seen, and the crystal is shattered. The shards of crystal magically react, and an image of the king appears. He tells them they are chosen warriors who are tasked with protecting the crystals from an ancient evil.Further research reveals that the evil King Tycoon spoke of is the great warlock Exdeath. Exdeath had once tried to destroy the world, but was sealed using the crystals. Now, these crystals were being used for their power, and it was being drained, weakening the seal on Exdeath. If Exdeath escapes and the crystals are destroyed, it would mean certain doom, unleashing a great evil and making their world uninhabitable. The four warriors now have their work cut out for them, they must save the crystals of fire, water, and earth from the fate of the wind crystal.Bartz, the main character and his chocobo Boko.Just after encountering Faris, the party notices something odd. Everyone in his crew finds him very attractive, and Bartz does too. An awkward situation. It turns out, there is reason for this: Faris is a woman! Later on, Lenna discovers that Faris is her once thought to be lost sister, the princess of Tycoon!They travel to Walse, Karnak, and Carwen, and ultimately fail to save any of the crystals. Each one shatters as the team arrives, however, they harvest their power in hopes of saving the next crystal. While in Karnak, attempting to save the fire crystal, they meet Krile. Krile has come from another world, looking for Galuf, who is her grandfather! Krile is the key to Galuf's memory, and her arrival brings a flood of knowledge. Galuf is from another world, and with his new memory, he and Krile depart to their home.Bartz, Lenna, and Faris return to consult with the geniuses Cid and Mid at the library of the ancients. What should they do next? They resolve that they must travel to Galuf's world, and save it from Exdeath. Exdeath wants to destroy that world, not this one, and they feel they must help. With the help of Cid and Mid, they travel across worlds.The party arrives at Exdeath's castle, where an intense battle is taken place. The three end up as captives of Exdeath, and are locked up. Galuf comes to their rescue, and the team makes haste. They run across the big bridge, and enounter the great Gilgamesh, who vows to stop them. They take him on and defeat him, and as they escape, the castle's barrier is activated, sending them flying across the planet. Galuf reveals that he is king of Bal, a great city in this world, and was once one of the great warriors who sealed Exdeath. a shock to Bartz and the gang. They set off for Bal, and get there with Krile and her wind drake's help.Unfortunately, the wind drake is dying, and the only cure is dragon grass. The four warriors set off to find some. They meet up with an old comrade of Galuf's, one of the great warriors, Kelger. Kelger reveals to Bartz that his father, who had once left him, was one of the legendary warriors who had once fought with Galuf and Kelger. They travel further, and obtain dragon grass, and heal the drake.Boss BattleIn order to progress further, the team seeks the wisdom of the great sage Ghido. Ghido had warned of the destruction of the crystals before, and could likely recommend a course of action for defeating Exdeath. Misfortune strikes, however, and when the party arrives, Ghido's island sinks into the ocean thanks to Exdeath. Still determined, they seek another way to reach Ghido. The team meets up with the other of the original four warriors, Xezat, and his navy fleet sailing to attack Exdeath. With Xezat's help, they infiltrate and take down the barrier surrounding the castle. Unfortunately, Xezat sacrifices himself in the process. They obtain a submarine, and set off for Ghido's cave.They traverse the underwater cave, and meet the old turtle sage Ghido. Ghido tells them that Exdeath was once a mage named Enuo, who had control over the void. When he was defeated, his evil was sealed in the trees of the Forest of Moore, where after 1,000 years, his evil broke the seal and was reborn into the world as the being known as Exdeath. The party then sets out to the forest to try and find something to help them destroy Exdeath.They travel to and through the forest, and reach the tree. Exdeath, bent on stopping them, shows up to spoil the party. He immobilizes them, and all hope seems lost. Krile arrives in the nick of time to save them, however, she proves no match for Exdeath. Determined, Galuf breaks free of Exdeaths spell, and takes Exdeath on head to head. Galuf fights until Exdeath retreats, when Galuf collapses. Bartz, Krile, Lenna, and Faris rush to his side, but he passes on. His spirit passesA regular random encounteron his power to Krile, who joins our warriors, now out to get Exdeath once and for all.The group heads straight for Exdeath's castle, climb up, and face him in battle. They defeat him, but it is too late. Exdeath accomplishes his goal, and two worlds - Bartz's world and Glauf's - fuse together. The group once again seeks Ghido's counsel, and he advises they collect all of the legendary weapons. The group travels far and wide, breaking the seals on the weapons, and taking each one. Once this task is completed, they head for the rift. They meet Gilgamesh one final time, who gives them his friendship. They go further into the rift, where Exdeath has gained the power of the void, and reveals his true form: a monstrous tree. He shows his true form, Neo Exdeath, and the final battle begins.JobsThe main gameplay feature that Final Fantasy V is remembered for is its open-ended "Job" system. Unlike most games in the series, each character can be assigned to perform any role the player desires, whether that be spellcaster, dual-wielding ninja, or hard to kill knight. At the start of the game, six classes, some based on classic Final Fantasy archetypes ( Black Mage, White Mage, Thief) are given to the player, and a total of 22 are gradually unlocked over the course of the game. Each of these Jobs comes with various advantages and disadvantages; spellcasters are typically weaker, but their ability to cast magic can make them very useful, while classes such as Thief are more adept at subtle advantages (like stealing from enemies) rather than sheer damage dealing.As characters gain the traditional experience levels, they also gain AP, which serve as a sort of "Job experience point" system. As a character levels up their experience in a Job, they unlock various abilities that can then be used while the character is using another class, an example being casting Black Magic while the character is a White Mage, thereby allowing one character to serve both offensive and defensive roles. Characters are limited as to how many abilities they can have equipped at once, however, requiring strategic choices by the player to get past different points in the game.A few of the character types introduced in Final Fantasy V have become staple elements of future games. The Blue Mage is the most prominent, with his ability to learn attacks that enemies have used on him being present in just about every game in the series since, and the concept of Time Mage has lived on in most games since, providing a category for spells like Slow and Haste which were previously placed with Black and White Magic, respectively.Main characters as white magesKnightMonkThiefLancerNinjaSamuraiBerserkerSorcererWhite MageBlack MageTime MageSummonerBlue MageRed MageTrainerChemistGeomancerBardDancerMimeSoundtrack:Disc 1Soundtrack cover art1. Ahead on Our Way2. A Presentiment3. Four Valiant Hearts4. Hurry! Hurry!5. Lenna's Theme6. Fate In Haze7. The Battle8. Victory's Fanfare9. Requiem10. Pirates Ahoy!11. Tenderness in the Air12. Good Night!13. Sealed Away14. Cursed Earth15. Deception16. Harvest17. Walking the Snowy Mountains18. Danger!19. The Fierce Battle20. The Dragon Spreads its Wings21. Royal Palace22. The Fire Powered Ship23. Run!24. Nostalgia25. The Ancient Library26. Reminiscence27. Musica Machina28. The Day Will Come29. What?30. Mambo De Chocobo31. My Home, Sweet Home32. Music Box33. The Airship34. The Evil Lord ExdeathDisc 21. Exdeath's Castle2. The Four Warriors of Dawn3. Battle with Gilgamesh4. Unknown Lands5. Critter Tripper Fritter!?6. The Castle of Dawn7. Beyond the Deep Blue Seas8. As I Feel, You Feel9. Waltz Clavier10. Go Go Boco!11. The Land Unknown12. The Book of Sealings13. Intension of the Earth14. The Prelude of Empty Skies15. Searching the Light16. The Decisive Battle17. The Last Battle18. The Silent Beyond19. Dear Friends20. Final Fantasy21. The New Origin22. The Prelude23. Fanfare 124. Fanfare 225. I'm a Dancer26. Piano Lesson 127. Piano Lesson 228. Piano Lesson 329. Piano Lesson 430. Piano Lesson 531. Piano Lesson 632. Piano Lesson 733. Piano Lesson 8Cheat: 255-Item Duplication GlitchThis glitch will allow you to quickly duplicate items such that you can have 255 (read as "55") of an item; due to its restrictions, it only works on hand-equipped items. Also, note that you will need the ability Throw (Ninja), as well as Steal or Mug (Thief). With the first character being a Ninja or Thief, have them be able to use Throw and Steal (or Throw and Mug). Unequip this character of whatever is in their hands; whatever is unequipped by them, or can be equipped, should then become the first (top-left) slot in the items menu. Enter a random battle where the monster(s) have items you wish to steal an infinite number of items from.Cheat: 255-Item Duplication GlitchFirst have the Thief/Ninja from before equip the first item in your item inventory: whether it is a weapon or shield is irrelevant. Then have the character with the Throw command throw the first item in your inventory, which should be a blank. (If the initially-thrown item cannot be Thrown, such as a shield or armor, Throw this blank twice, but otherwise only do it once.) After doing so, Steal/Mug the target of Throw to steal an item, then Throw the item (if possible). After, end the battle in any desired way. In the field, return to the inventory and you'll notice that you'll have "55" (255) next to the name of the stolen weapon, or 99 if the item was non-Throwable. As long as this item is never moved from this slot - through manual sorting or the Sort command - or other copies ever bought, you can indefinitely sell this item for massive amounts of money (although you'll be selling them one at a time). And, of course, there's also the benefit of cloning unique equipment so that multiple characters can equip the same piece.Cheat: 255-Item Duplication GlitchThis glitch is able to occur when the two worlds of the game have merged after you go through Ghido's Cave and done the events in the Library of the Ancients. At the latter, if you use Teleport after all the cutscenes there are done, you'll find yourself at Ghido's Cave rather than the Library. This will allow you to travel around the world on Boko as you can now head towards Tycoon Castle. You can also skip the Pyramid of Moore sequence for the time being: while you do have to do it eventually, you are able to skip it for now and thereby further optimize your party.Cheat: 255-Item Duplication GlitchThe most important benefit, however, lies in the ability to now access the Mirage Village early to buy powerful equipment, magic, and items. In addition to the Mirage Village, you can also access a number of areas early, such as the Phoenix Tower and the Sealed Castle (where you can earn three of the legendary weapons), and also regain the Black Chocobo.Cheat: 255-Item Duplication GlitchIf you have a mystic knight on your party, cast Fire 3 and in the next round hit Carbuncle with it. It will not show any damage, but it will kill him.Cheat: 255-Item Duplication GlitchThe Mix "Kiss of Blessing" can be made with a Maiden's Kiss and a Holy Water, and in turn grants Image, Haste, and Berserk to the target. However, due to poor coding, the Berserk effect will be unblockable: this means it can affect anyone, even bosses, who are normally immune to Berserk. This in turn is highly abuseable because Berserk will force the afflicted foe's battle routines to simply "Attack", getting rid of any particularly annoying side-effects or highly powerful moves, and also make it easier for one to prevent damage by simply throwing up Protect.Cheat: 255-Item Duplication GlitchHowever, note that it is unwise to do this in the solo battle between Galuf and Exdeath. Aside from this, any boss battle is made simpler: in fact, even the final boss battle can be skipped as you will only need to kill the first form and not the second form of the boss.Cheat: 255-Item Duplication GlitchIn this game, there is a particular Blue Magic spell known as Vampire: it is essentially a Drain spell, in which you damage the target to heal your own HP. If you use it on yourself, though, you are instantly healed to full HP.Cheat: Brave Sword or Chicken Knife ?Before venturing into the Cleft of Dimension, return to the Town of Mua.In the southwest, a door that was previously locked is now open.Through the door is a hidden path that will lead you to a man.He will offer to give you a Brave Sword or a Chicken Knife.The Brave Sword will get stronger as you win battles and the Chicken Knife as you run from battles. Cheat: Brave Sword or Chicken Knife ?In Kelb town, enter the Inn. You'll find a man sitting on a table talk to him then sit on the chair on the LEFT (NOT in front of the man)! He'll give you some kind of wine then he'll give you an after meal gift of 8 Potions! You can repeat this to get 24 potions.Cheat: Brave Sword or Chicken Knife ?Take your airship slightly south of the Town of Karnak and submerge underwater. Enter the cave you see and talk to the man inside. He claims to be a psychic and will tell you how many battles you have fought, the number of enemies you've killed, your party's average experience, the percentage of the game's treasure you have collected, and the number of times you have saved your game.Cheat: Alternate Tycoon Castle SceneIn world one when you get the Hiryuu ( Dragon ) you have access to Tycoon Castle. If you go, there's a scene involving Leena and Faris where Leena suspects Faris may be her long lost sister, Sarisa, and Faris denies it. But, if you wait  until after you get the airship it's an entirley different scene involving Leena's childhood.Cheat: Alternate Tycoon Castle SceneBefore the battle with Catastrophe, equip a Wall Ring on one of your characters, and cast Float on that same character.  Then, go into the battle.  Whenever one of your characters is Floating, Catastrophe will always use Gravity100 to ground that character.  However, because that character has a Wall Ring, the attack will be reflected back at him.  He will continue to use Gravity100 for the entire battle, allowing you to use any attacks you need to beat him without the fear of being killed.</plot>
	<releasedate>6/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Square Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>Z0RtcAi94bQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1762</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588331-final-fantasy-v</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/final-fantasy-v</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/final-fantasy-v/3030-4793/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/MMMZ0Tq.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/E2wexi6.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/VwCWubb.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/4WkwytI.png</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/XZ8eucs.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/9iYESoo.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/XiVMMm9.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/jx7dzm1.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Q0Yyuyp.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/syM7TeY.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/P7ZZct9.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/qpQOvYE.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/tP1LykM.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/TQavw85.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/VhB3UuG.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/42k5JK6.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/2LrVFsC.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/29pCTVr.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/RJDUScL.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jIF3EXP.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ylF4Z4L.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The Elemental Crystals...the life source of the planet. With them, gentle winds blow, the seas are active, fire burns bright, and the earth is full of life. All seems well in the world, until the wind suddenly stops, the sea begin to grow stagnant, the heat of fire becomes scarce, and the earth begins to wither. King Tycoon, sensing a premonition of evil, hurries off to check on the Wind Crystal, only to witness it destroy itself. Meanwhile, a young traveler named Butz is camping in a field when a giant meteor strikes the planet. When he heads out to examine the meteor, he is shocked to find a young girl named Lenna, who is the princess of Tycoon, and a old man named Galuf, who is on a critical mission. Later, joined by Faris, a pirate captain, the foursome must travel the land in search of the destructor of the Crystals, and save the planet at any cost! Final Fantasy V featured many new gameplay options and tactics, including an improved Job/Ability system (like in Final Fantasy Tactics), the return of the ATB (Active Time Battle) turn system, and all of the classic FF gameplay you've come to know and love! Final Fantasy V was released as a stand-alone game in Japan, and again in Final Fantasy Collection. Its U.S. debut was as part of Final Fantasy Anthology. It was also later ported to the Gameboy Advance, adding 4 new Jobs, a new 30-floor dungeon, a bestiary, a music player, the ability to quick save anywhere, a few extra pieces of equipment, and a newly update translation.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1e3cc81f-5b2b-49d3-b6d2-113a50748886.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ce67a18-9e80-480f-9b2e-9ea0bf2caed1.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Squaresoft</Publisher>
</game>