<Game>
	<Name>Final Fight 2 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Final Fight 2 is the sequel to the 1989 arcade beat-em-up,  Final Fight. Released by  Capcom for the  Super Nintendo in 1993. The game features Mike Haggar as the returning character from the original.Plot: Haggar, piledrives his way to victory.After the fall of the Mad Gear gang in the original game, two of the original heroes, Cody and Guy, go their separate ways. Cody goes off on vacation with his girlfriend Jessica, and Guy off on a journey to hone his fighting skills. Mike Haggar remains in Metro City in charge as mayor.The period of peace soon ends as surviving members of Mad Gear join up with a new leader to plot a revenge plan against the heroes of Metro City. They head to Japan and kidnap Guy's fiancee Rena and his sensai Genryusai. Rena's sister and Genryusai's daughter, Maki, gives a call to Mike Haggar to let him known what just happened. Mike Haggar, Maki, and friend Carlos Miyamoto join together to rescue the kidnap victims.Their journey leads them Eurasia where they come across many members of Mad Gear. First there in  Hong Kong, they run into Won Won. After Won Won's defeat, Haggar, Carlos and Maki find out that Mad Gear is in  Europe, and Rena and Genryusai were taken there.Once Haggar, Carlos, and Maki head for another part of Europe. And there they encounter an original member of Mad Gear,  Rolento. The heroes manage to defeat Rolento and got information about the where abouts of Rena and Genryusai. Rolento tells them that they're in Japan with his new leader.They head to Japan and face the new leader of Mad Gear, Retu. Haggar, Carlos and Maki finally save Rena and Genryusai by defeating Retu. Maki is reunited with her family, and the game ends.Gameplay:Final Fight 2 plays very similar to the original game. The player has a choice to pick one of three characters, and goes through six levels with enemies. The objective for the player is to beat up every enemy on screen that appears, and the boss at the end of each level. The game makes use of two buttons, attack and jump. The player can grab an enemy and perform an throwing technique. With the combination of the attack and jump buttons, the player can activate a special move that can attack every enemy that's near the player, but it can drain the player's health.Several enemies differ from each other; for example, one enemy can charge at the player with a device that can electrocute the player, and another can block the player's attack. The bonus stage.The game has two bonus stages. One stage is a returning stage from the first Final Fight, the smash the car stage; the player has a certain amount of time to destroy a car to earn extra points. The other bonus stage is the player has to destroy a certain amount of oil drums before the time runs out, some of the oil drums flame up and can be a hazard to the player.Items such as health items and weapons can be found in the game. The player can restore his or her health with a turkey or with other food items. Weapons can also be use to defend against enemies.Characters: Mike HaggarThe main hero of the original Final Fight. Mike Haggar gets a call from Maki to inform him that Guy's wife and his sensei have been kidnapped and Maki needs Haggar's help. Without hesitation, Haggar agrees. Carlos MiyamotoA warrior of Japanese/South American descent. He fights with two swords against his enemies. Maki GenryusaiThe sister-in-law of Guy. Maki enlists the help of Mike Haggar and Carlos Miyamoto to save her kidnapped father and sister.LocalizationLike the original Final Fight, some censoring has been done to the U.S and European versions of the game. In the Japanese version, two female enemies were presented in the game, but were changed into male enemies much like  Poison and  Roxy in the first Final Fight.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/8/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>qFCzN5wy5M8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1763</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588333-final-fight-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/final-fight-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/final-fight-2/3030-14608/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/SErT8nq.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Vg4jP7F.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/praAYZb.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/pvtM1Al.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/8S5A6uu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/URRbEyn.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/QpTsL7V.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/EMqiVqe.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/NwcbJ0A.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/8BscdhC.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/LCmwGut.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/38FbhrS.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/O4x5zqN.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vLJeH6s.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/3CxjcEu.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/jW9GWDH.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/Xli4DOd.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/iCSH54O.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/I0KavB3.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>It's Mad Gear Madness! They're back stronger than ever and they want revenge. With a new mysterious leader they plan to dominate the entire world. This time they've kidnapped Genryusai and his daughter Rena. Now Haggar must travel around the world to search for Genryusai and Rena. But he's not going alone. Carlos and Rena's sister, Maki, are joining the slam-fest to put the gang away for good. Search for numerous weapons such as knives, nightsticks and 2x4's or find food to recover your strength. Choose from Haggar, Carlos or Maki, each with their own style of fighting. Or have a friend join in for double the power and crush any punk that stands in your way.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb540ace-ad35-4fa0-9487-f6d532b4a3aa.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5fad0977-ab3d-4ea5-b8d3-7a6407de0efa.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5cde4cd1-2f06-4756-836e-347f09c67fec.png</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/75a1dfda-1b64-4e04-b58e-d953b6aa6106.png</boxart8>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/97741a9c-c434-447e-ad4d-274610090463.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a71b1a81-b33f-4669-ada2-a93b163c07a9.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5aff169e-8679-4872-98da-ac6bf1be5056.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e94f7f90-16ed-42bf-8e84-f6b43763c424.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e5479e51-fc32-42fa-b759-e4b019abd92f.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/29792f06-abcf-4609-bb3a-7ac9c79efbb4.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/af07a34a-74ae-4bf6-b609-a982090fca9c.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d4e16194-7a22-4638-9fa6-57d3a90f0660.png</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/843aba66-6396-411a-abde-fc120b2a137b.jpg</snapshot18>
	<snapshot19>http://images.launchbox-app.com/53c364cc-7dc4-465c-801f-c5a96f1d587d.jpg</snapshot19>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>