<Game>
	<Name>Final Fantasy III (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>This is the sixth entry in the  Final Fantasy series. It was called Final Fantasy III because three of the five previous installments of the series were never released outside of Japan.1,000 years ago, the War of the Magi occurred. People remember it as one of the most horrible tragedies in history. Since the War of the Magi, magic has been all but forgotten, technology began to grow, and people returned to seemingly normal lives. The only true worry people had was the Empire, whose leaders were looking to revive the great force once known as "magic".But then...something happened that would change the course of history forever...The Empire had heard word of the remains of a mystical being, known as an "Esper", being found in the mining town of Narshe. Quickly, three soldiers were dispatched to find this Esper and bring it to the Emperor. One of the soldiers, a young girl, triggers a power in the Esper that will begin one of the most dangerous series of events ever. And the only ones who can help her are a rag-tag band of rebels and heroes, whose very hearts and souls are the only ones that can save the world from the mad plans of the Empire.The game maintains the ATB (active time battle) system of the two previous  Final Fantasy games, spicing classic turn-based combat engine with a real-time element. The customization system combines character-specific classes with free-flowing character development. By finding various Espers and equipping them on characters, you can improve their parameters in different ways and choose the magic spells you want to learn for each character.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Square Soft, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>saWMkVw-HHA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1536</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/554041-final-fantasy-iii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/final-fantasy-iii__</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/final-fantasy-vi/3030-6336/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Final_Fantasy_VI</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/LepRPEp.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/bmYL53b.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/1uDW8nq.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/spoZ7DG.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/iZKABLa.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/XiWC9ia.png</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/eSMbW4x.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/KMxK1eI.jpg</boxart8>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ZwddQqI.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/al41JYB.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8xVJzj3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Bp7o5ke.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SxXm6KC.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/rqiZtrV.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/rdzUUcG.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/hjPKZhH.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/26irJeW.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/0SdvimW.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/x7oQuMS.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/ECBD5xL.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/rCso2EG.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/M3J2dcu.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/3av3h2e.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/06WeQTZ.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/IQE5o2B.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>Ages ago, evil beings created powerful creatures called Espers, and unleashed them against each other. The resulting battles left their world a smoldering rubble. Legend has it, the Espers destroyed themselves and most of humanity. Magic disappeared forever. Centuries have passed and a rational world now exists with Espers living only in myths, until one frozen solid since the ancient wars is unearthed. Suddenly, there are reports of magical attacks on civilians. Imperial Commandos launch raids using magic-powered MagiTek weapons. Magic is obviously alive and the world is in danger again. Who or what is behind the rediscovery and redeployment of this legendary power? What chaotic plans exists that will wreak havoc on this orderly world?</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>s_EDnDJvlw8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6504fd85-ab13-47f1-b600-1954a91c7696.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7841c05c-6797-418b-84d1-ccffb367f7ce.png</boxart10>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1545ba9d-4016-4b9e-88c7-aaa70cc1c5d4.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b7684898-4695-4739-af6f-a2498119bf4c.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/39eb37f6-633d-494c-8810-93f13adfe3c2.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c4616a82-5156-4d5b-b60c-91be3f707a04.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99057005-f1cf-4a6d-b294-9bab830937dd.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e98249d8-cd03-49c1-ad4d-895a5eeba8d2.png</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a0bc0677-1092-47ea-bb47-355d48ea676e.png</snapshot15>
	<Publisher>Squaresoft</Publisher>
</game>