<Game>
	<Name>Final Stretch (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Final Stretch is a Formula One racing game developed by Genki. It is the spiritual sequel to their earlier game Aguri Suzuki F-1 Super Driving (rebranded in the US as Redline: F1 Racer), and like that game Final Stretch is licensed by FOCA and supervised by Japanese F1 racer Aguri Suzuki. The game employs a Mode 7-enabled viewpoint close to the ground that has multiple vantage points that the player can switch between and, with the FOCA license, uses many of the then-current F1 teams and racers.Unlike Redline: F1 Racer, Final Stretch was never released outside of Japan.Cheat: Miscellaneous PasswordsEnter the following passwords for the desired effect. NOTE: With the exception of SEX and OMEKO, you must highlight END, hold L + R + X + Down + Left, and press A to activate the codes.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/11/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Genki</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>qtWba6fDHew</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570985-final-stretch</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/final-stretch</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/final-stretch/3030-38925/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/6pjMBYV.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9uv0Ydi.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/oHmzwyM.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ULQJXqK.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/xXi97ye.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/FKuKDNP.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/CVnXsTh.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/s048ojr.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/hU3GSpE.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/opGtOJz.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/BK5qHte.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Cv2okxv.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/2Fz4pmZ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Based on the 1993 Formula One Season, Final Stretch features a GP, 1P VS 2P, and Time Attack modes. In GP mode the player can choose either beginner or expert which have many differences. At beginner any team can be chosen and the player will start all races without having to qualify. There's no machine setting, and one other difference is that during the actual race the vehicles do not collide with each other. In the expert one, there's the qualifying session consisting of nine laps. It is also possible to save data, among other differences. Only a single player is allowed to compete in the GP mode, and the screen is always split. The bottom screen shows the car in the typical chase view while the top can show up to five different views. Just like Redline: F1 Racer, the game was supervised by the Japanese driver Aguri Suzuki.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3890658b-2fec-49b6-94ba-14a8d09afe09.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ed0d5ea8-c4ef-4bbd-a34d-6d4913acf51c.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4dceee03-a19a-40b7-b469-bcecce7fd203.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/636e09fe-afd6-4c30-8a2b-97d1faaaed2d.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>LOZC/G. Amusements</Publisher>
</game>