<Game>
	<Name>Firepower 2000 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super SWIV is the sequel to Silkworm and SWIV, both of which were originally Amiga games. It is known as Firepower 2000 in the US. As was the case with its predecessors, Super SWIV is a top-down vertical-scrolling shoot 'em up that focuses on a helicopter rather than a spaceship or a plane.The game supports 1 to 2 players, whereby Player One would control the Helicopter, whilst Player Two could control the Jeep, or vice versa. The Helicopter is capable of flying over obstacles so by picking the Jeep the player had a large disadvantage and could often get stuck on a building and subsequently die, due to the screen constantly moving upwards. To compensate, the Jeep is capable of firing in many directions.It was also released on the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis under a different title: Mega SWIV, albeit with reduced quality audio and graphics. A different level design is incorporated into the Mega Drive version, but the general premise is the same.Cheat: CodesDuring the game, pause and press the following buttons on the appropriate stage to skip ahead one stage:Cheat: Power UpAt the beginning of Level 1, steer to the far right to find a yellow container. Blast it open and collect the Bullet tokens to power up.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SunSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>oRAmj6-prq0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3617</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588336-firepower-2000</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/firepower-2000</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/firepower-2000/3030-1450/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/eoOaWpH.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/XRlbt3q.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/RpcWRKE.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/ddHn3sg.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/EsjIiu7.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/kvhJGmT.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/FWy1o8b.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/xrXw8Y4.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/4YgkjRk.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VhUbVqW.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/dCWmGmw.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Lk5fJvC.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nZuQ2Fw.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/vUCnYM1.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/VJifn0p.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/dVJ8zCO.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/mP98JSt.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Imagine if all the mega weapons in the world fell into the wrong hands. And then were turned against you. That's the time for major firepower. You've got to take the wheel of a jumping, whirling, gun-heavy jeep that fires in any direction. Or master the controls of a deadly fast, missile-loaded helicopter. Both war machines have special capabilities. Both change into different vehicles on certain levels. It's up to you to pick the right weapon. So get ready to collect your flamethrowers, plasma cannons, lasers, guided missiles, nuclear weapons and more. There's no time to assemble forces -- it's just you or you and a partner going straight into the blazing, blasting heart of enemy territory. Make sure you buckle up. And put your finger on firepower.</Notes>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/af938dbb-1b1e-43c0-963c-50c0ea73657a.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a4013be7-8713-451a-8795-72cce14960c7.png</boxart7>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c3faebe4-dee1-47e3-a302-1c0a76867825.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/436ec7fd-f5e6-4dce-bffb-564c5eb907c7.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/31c9f190-e471-484b-8e4a-ec84118128e8.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sunsoft</Publisher>
</game>