<Game>
	<Name>Fire Emblem - Seisen no Keifu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Fire Emblem: Seisen no Keifu (Genealogy of the Holy War) is the fourth installment in the Fire Emblem franchise, the second to be produced for the Nintendo Super Famicom and was released only in Japan on May 14th, 1996. It was later released on the Japanese Virtual Console service on the Wii in January of 2007. It was followed by Fire Emblem: Thracia 776, which is chronologically set during a gap in time in the middle of Seisen no Keifu's story.Seisen no Keifu was one of the last games produced by Nintendo to be credited to Gunpei Yokoi, who resigned from the company after the failure of the Virtual Boy.Storyline:Seisen no Keifu adopts the usual narration style used in the precedent titles, with the difference that the time from one chapter to the other is much larger than usual. In fact, sometimes, when reaching a new part of the story line, the player learns that several years have passed since his last mission.The title has an extremely large and intricate storyline, even by Fire Emblem standards. This is one of the reasons for the title's fame and fortune. The storyline is, in fact, particularly tragic, and the characters portrayed easily inspire sympathy and compassionate feelings, especially in the case of Sigurd.The prologue of Fire Emblem: Seisen no Keifu begins with Prince Kult, the son of King Azmur of Barhara Castle, making the decision for the Grandbellian army to subdue the Kingdom of Isaac, in response to an invasion of Darna by barbarians of Rivough, Isaac. This is an unforeseen occurrence because the kingdoms of Grandbell and Isaac have been peacefully getting along with each other for many, many years. Lord Sigurd (or Siglud) of Chalphy remains in Chalphy castle while his father Byron (or Vylon) is away. He believes he has nothing to fear, because there are no invasions or threats from the other countries in the continent of Jugdral; unfortunately, Sigurd's assumption is proved incorrect. Prince Gandolf of Marpha, Verdane, and his army invade Grandbell, seizing Jungby Castle, the closest castle to the Grandbell-Verdane boundary. Noblewoman Aideen (Adean), alongside only a few knights that stay at the castle to protect her at Jungby Castle. The Jungby knights are crushingly defeated by Gandolf and his army, except for Mideel (Midayle), the strongest of all Jungby archers, who (despite his skill) is defeated by Gandolf himself. Shortly thereafter, Gandolf leaves Grandbell for Verdane and takes Aideen as his hostage.Sigurd is informed about what has just happened at Jungby and decides to gather the remaining Chalphy knights(Noish, Alec, and Arden) to travel to the Kingdom of Verdane to rescue Edin. While on the road to Jungby Castle, Sigurd is joined first by Azel of Velthomer, who sneaks out of Barhara Castle and drags Lex of Dozel into joining Sigurd, and then his sister Ethlin, her husband (Sigurd's brother-in-law and best friend) Cuan from Lenster, and their loyal and most valuable knight, Fin. Sigurd first met Cuan at the Royal Academy of Barhara, alongside Eltshan. Cuan says that he is always with Sigurd, especially in times of war. Noish and Alec go to where Azel and Lex are and help them save the villages north of Jungby. All together, they battle Demagio, who Gandolf leaves to guard Jungby, and easily retake the castle.In Jungby Castle, Sigurd finds Mideel alive and recuperating. He tries to make Mideel rest, but instead, Mideel joins Sigurd's conquest to rescue Edin. Alvis of Velthomer walks over to Sigurd, who is now on the road to Evans Castle in Verdane, and gives him the Silver Sword from King Azmur. He also tells Sigurd to look after his half-brother Azel. In Evans Castle, Mideel defeats Gerald with his arrows, but Aideen is not in the castle. Lord Filat, King Azmur's messenger, arrives to Evans Castle to inform that Sigurd has been entitled "Holy Knight of Grandbell." With strengthened pride and honor, Sigurd goes deeper into the Kingdom of Verdane.Sometime later, Edin, whom Sigurd and Oifey fail to find in Jungby Castle, is taken by Gandolf of Marpha to Marpha Castle in southern Verdane. King Bator was a pacifist, until Sandima arrived. Until he took the throne of Verdane, the Kingdom of Verdane was a nightmarish land, filled with chaos. He brought peace, order, and freedom to Verdane and it seemed likely to last for many years with his three sons: Gandolf, Kinbois, and Jamka. Matters degenerate after a mysterious magician, Sandima, shows up. Sandima's influence largely causes King Bator to order Grandbell's invasion of Verdane, and he grows more and more aggressive. Gandolf and Kinbois lose heart and do whatever Sandima wishes, but Jamka, alone, does not give into Sandima's influence. The Verdanian people become aware of the loss of peace and the kingdom, engulfed in the flames of war, wishes to have its pacifist king back.Sigurd and his forces reside in Evans Castle, the most northeastern castle of Verdane, bordering the Kingdoms of Grandbell to the east, Verdane, and Agustria the Lords' Dominion to the west, but officially located in Verdane. King of Eltosian (Eltshan) of Nodion, the castle west of Evans, comes to meet with Lord Sigurd to ask him why he is present in Verdane. Sigurd say that the Verdanian army took Aideen hostage with no signs of releasing her and that he was forced to take up arms. After Sigurd speaks with Eltosian, Eltosian says that he will watch and protect Evans Castle from Agustrian raids. Therefore, Sigurd and his forces leave for Genoa Castle to the south of Evans, feeling that Nodion's army will protect them.Meanwhile, in Marpha Castle, located west of Genoa Castle, Gandolf and Jamka stay in the castle with their hostage Aideen. However, Jamka falls in love with Aideen behind Gandolf's back and decides to free her, to Aideen's surprise. He sends her out of Marpha castle with Dew the thief, who he caught some days before this chapter of the game. Dew agrees with Jamka to protect Aideen until she reaches safety. They flee from Marpha Castle and head to Evans Castle together, through the deep Verdanian forests. Along the way, they meet Sigurd and Mideel, and decide to join their army. But immediately after they flee Marpha Castle, Gandolf finds out that Edin is missing from Marpha Castle and sends the Marpha army to capture her and Dew. A division of Sigurd's army that is not heading for Genoa easily crushes this army.Meanwhile, in Genoa Castle, at the approximately the same time, Kinbois feels threatened by Sigurd's army. He decides to attack Sigurd's army himself. He is so afraid to leave his castle empty that he forces Ayra, a mercenary whom he just hired (after she fled from her native country, the Kingdom of Isaac, to escape Isaac's conflict with Grandbell), to guard Genoa Castle. Ayra is not too willing to do so, but Kinbois threatens to kill Ayra's young fraternal nephew, Shanan, if she shirks her duty. Therefore, she is forced to do as Kinbois wishes and begins to fight against her will. However, she threatens him back, saying that she will kill him should he double-cross her. Kinbois and the Genoa army then go after Sigurd's army.After a reunion with Aideen, Sigurd's army crushes both the Marpha and Genoa armies. They go south to Genoa, where they meet Ayra, who fights Sigurd's army alongside the remaining Genoa axe fighters. While his army holds off Ayra, Sigurd immediately enters Genoa Castle to rescue Shanan. He takes Shanan with him and talks to Ayra. Ayra sees that Kinbois is in the grave and that there is no more to fear. She reciprocates Sigurd's trust and (tentatively) decides to join Sigurd's army for rescuing Shanan. Shortly thereafter, Cuan apologizes to Ayra and discusses with her the political situation between the Kingdoms of Isaac and Grandbell. Cuan's father King Lenster has a high opinion of Ayra's father King Mananan, who was assassinated by Lord Reptor on the Grandbellian fronts. At the time, Mananan is journeying to Barhara to explain to Prince Kult about the situation with Rivough.Meanwhile, right as King Eltosian of Nodion expects, Eliot of Heirhein and his army attempts to seize Evans Castle. The board guard informs Eltosian of Eliot's invasion. Eltosian argues with Heirhein, telling Eliot that he is running in direct violation of the Agustrian ruler's orders. Despite this, Eliot still attempts to invade Evans. Eltosian and his army of powerful Cross Knights crush Eliot's army, sending him back to Heirhein. Feeling like Nodion Castle may soon be in further danger, Eltosian and his army leave Evans and return to Nodion.Sigurd continues to travel deep south into the Verdane and enters Marpha castle, where Aideen was held hostage. Gandolf is present at Marpha to fight Sigurd, but only a handful of soldiers are remaining at the castle. Therefore, the capture of Marpha is quick. Prince Jamka is not present at the time of the subjugation, and Aideen believes that he came to the city of Verdane to convince his father Bator to seek peace for Verdane. As Sigurd walks around Marpha city, he meets a beautiful young maiden named Diadora, who knows his name. She says to him that she was held hostage by Gandolf and had spoken to Aideen. At first sight, Sigurd loses his heart to Diadora, but Diadora leaves before he is able to ask her name. An old man steps in and informs Sigurd that she is a maiden of the Spirit Forest, and that she is actually forbidden to associate with anyone outside the forest. He also says that the villagers believe that any man from outside the forest that comes too close to her will be greatly cursed. However, Sigurd does not believe in the legends of the Spirit Forest and he attempts to reunite with her, regardless of the curse.Meanwhile, Prince Jamka is in Verdane Castle to speak with his father Bator about making a peace treaty with Grandbell. His father, still under Sandima's curse, refuses to listen to Prince Jamka. Sandima orders Jamka to depart from Verdane Castle immediately with the remainder of the castle's army and attack Sigurd's army. Jamka reluctantly accepts Sandima's orders. As soon as he exits Verdane Castle, Sandima assassinates King Bator, rendering him useless. Manfroy, Sandima's mystical leader and the head of the Loput Sect, shows up and tells Sandima to attempt to clean up the mess in the Kingdom of Verdane. He also asks Sandima if he has found Cigyun's daughter, whom he needs in order to resurrect the Dark Lord Loputousu. Sandima says that he is still searching for her. Cigyun's son Alvis is already found, but they need the daughter.Prince Jamka is still unhappy about attacking Sigurd's army, because he knows that is not what his father really wants. However, at the battlefield in the forest, he reunites with Aideen, who tells him that Sigurd did not come to Verdane to invade the country, but that he merely came to rescue her. She convinces him that he should listen to his own emotions and do what he believes best. Shortly thereafter, Jamka joins Sigurd's army.As Sigurd's army continues their way to Verdane Castle, they traverse a deep forest. Near the north end, Sigurd meets Diadora, whom he saw at Marpha Castle. She says that she attempted to forget that they ever met each other, but that could only make her more miserable. Sigurd says he requites her love, and that he does not believe in the forest legends, and that he desires to marry her at Evans Castle. Diadora joins Sigurd's army as they continue to go northward to Verdane Castle.Sandima can use a lethal, long range dark spell called "Fenrir." However, Diadora casts Silence on Sandima, rendering his spell useless and victory easy. As Sigurd subjugates the castle, they find the near-death King Bator. For his last words, King Bator says to Sigurd that the evil that is spreading across the continent of Jugdral is the work of the Loput Sect, a dark sect that is bent on destroy everything that is good and on accelerating the resurrection of the Dark Lord Loputousu. After this, he dies in Sigurd's arms. Sigurd and his army then go back to Evans Castle, where he marries Diadora.King Imuka is mysteriously assassinated. Sigurd receives orders from Barhara to take possession of Evans Castle. Months later, Eltosian goes to Agusty Castle to tell King Chagall how cruel war is and how burdensome it is on the citizenry. Chagall shortly casts Eltosian into the Agusty dungeon, accusing him of making him a fool. Then Manfroy arrives, telling him what is needed to resurrect the Dark Lord Loputousu: the children of Cigyun.Meanwhile, in Nodion, Lachesis and her guardian Eve receive word that Eltosian was imprisoned in Agusty. Eltshan leaves three cross paladins to protect his sister Lachesis. One of the paladins says that if Heirhein army finds out that Eltosian is apprehended, they will attack Nodion immediately. In Anphony Castle, Macbeth believes that they have a free reign now that Chagall has taken the throne. He is excited Heirhein army has taken up arms, and he then deploys thieves to strip the villages in the central Agustria forest near Mackilly Castle of all of their valuables and destroy them.In Evans Castle, Sigurd receives word that Eltosian is captured, and tells Diadora that he is heading for Nodion to save Eltosian. Diadora wants to fight alongside him, and promises that she will not leave his side. A division of Heirhein army, led by Boldor and his son Elliot, attacks Nodion and attempts to capture Lachesis. However, Sigurd and his army rescue and recruit Lachesis. Sigurd tells Lachesis that King Azmur approves of Grandbellian invasion of Agustria and that Azmur is aware of the assassination of King Imuka, as well as Chagall's plans invade Grandbell. Sigurd's army then moves on to kill the remainder of the Heirhein army, including Boldor's henchman: Phillip. Sigurd ultimately conquers Heirhein. Chagall goes to Anphony and informs Macbeth about this, saying that Macbeth's avarice costs him Heirhein. Meanwhile, Levin and Sylvia receive word that Macbeth sent bandits to destroy the villages in the central villages. Levin intervenes to fight the bandits, saving the villages, as Sylvia dances to guide him in this mission.Shortly after Sigurd conquers Anphony, Filat arrives to Anphony and tells Sigurd about the rumors going around in the Royal Court of Barhara. Rumors include that Sigurd, Cuan, and Eltosian are conspiring against Prince Kult of Barhara, and that Sigurd hiding Shanan the Prince of Isaac proves this. Filat tells about the late Victor, the Duke of Velthomer, father of Alvis and Azel, and notable philanderer.At Mackily Castle, a dark mage announces the assassination of Prince Kult, part of Manfroy's plan to find Cigyun's children. Chagall deceives Ferry to seize Evans Castle. Ferry and her squad go en route to Evans Castle, but Levin arrives ther firste. Levin talks with Ferry and convinces her to join Sigurd's army. Ferry was to come to Agustria to take Levin back to Silesia, but she wants to stay with Sigurd instead. Sigurd's army then heads to Mackily Castle and stops the army of mercenaries, archers, and mages.At Agusty Castle, after Sigurd subdues Mackily Castle, Chagall sends Zain and his army after Sigurd's. Lachesis then tells Chagall that he is not her king and then wounds him with her lances. However, Eltosian puts Chagall in medical attention and Chagall recovers, only to know that it comes out to be a mistake. Six months later, the leadership that they have been trusted with is broken all too soon. Eltosian and his cross knights are stationed in Silvail Castle. The Orgahil pirates start to raid the villages near Madino Castle. At Agusty Castle, Seliph is born. This time, Diadora cannot leave the castle, and Shanan watches the two. By the end of the battle, Sigurd seizes Madino and to meets Claud of Edda and Tiltyu of Freege. Claud suspects that Sigurd's father Byron is accused of assassinating Prince Kult. Meanwhile, Diadora leaves Agusty Castle to meet Sigurd, leaving Seliph in Shanan's care. Before she can reach Sigurd at Madino Castle, Manfroy appears before her eyes. Manfroy then wipes Diadora's mind, captures her, and leaves her for Alvis to find in order to resurrect the Dark Lord Loputousu.Chagall forces Eltosian to fight against his will and betray Sigurd. He leads the Silvail cross-knight army against Sigurd's army. Lachesis comes to Eltosian and convinces him that betrayal is not the way of a knight. Eltosian returns to Silvail, but he is publicly decapitated by the Silvail guardsmen under Chagall's orders. Trabant arrives at Silvail, Chagall having hired the Thracian army to wipe out Sigurd's. However, the mercenaries fail and Trabant flees the country, leaving Chagall to be defeated once and for all. Shortly after Sigurd conquers Silvail, Prince Shanan, carrying baby Seliph, comes to Sigurd at Silvail and informs him of Diadora's fate. At Madino, Ethlin gives Cuan the Gaeborg. Brigid joins Sigurd's army, and flees from pirates until a division of Sigurd's army fights them off. Aideen meets Brigid for the first time since childhood and gives Brigid the Holy Bow Ichaival after revealing to her her true identity. Claude speaks with Sigurd and tells him that King Mananan, father of Ayra and grandfather of her nephew Prince Shanan, was assassinated by none other than Tiltyu's father Duke Reptor when journeying to tell the truth about the siege on Darna. After Sigurd conquers Orgahil, Langobalt and his army march to Agusty Castle, and Sigurd is deemed a traitor to Grandbell. Ferry's sister Mahnya arrives at Orgahill to take Sigurd and his army to Silesia.Sigurd and his army arrive with Mahnya to Silesia, a country covered with snow. They arrive at Sailane Castle. Ferry and Levin are suspicious of the skirmish there, as Silesia is engulfed in war. Cuan, Ethlin, and Fin leave Sigurd and return to their home kingdom Manster. Levin's uncles Maios and Daccar protest the idea of him ascending to the Silesian throne, throwing the country into civil war. A Loput sectarian marches with a wind mage brigade, while Deet'var travels with her pegasus knight brigade.Soon after conquering Thove castle and killing Maios, Daccar, another one of Levin's uncles, summons Pamela to launch an attack onto Silesia Castle and hold its Queen as a hostage. However, Mahnya, the older sister of Ferry, gathers her brigade to counter-attack the upcoming attack from Pamela. Andorey, the brother of Aideen and Brigid and the father of Scorpio, comes with his army of archer knight to kill Mahnya and her pegasus knights. Sigurd's army can do nothing to prevent Mahnya's death. Silesia Castle is soon taken over by Daccar. Andorey and his army go back to Grandbell. Queen Rahna orders the people of Silesia Castle town to flee to the mountains near Sailane. After Sigurd retakes Silesia Castle from Daccar, Levin talks with his mother Rahna and obtains the holy scroll Holsety. Meanwhile, Daccar hires an all-female mercenary group led by Swordmaster Reimia to take down Sigurd.Things are getting worse and worse for Sigurd and his friends, so he decides that it is time to finish all. He and others, now in Zaxon castle, go stop Langobalt, Lex's father, and the other remaining Dukes from going through with their conspiracy. Vylon has traveled there, too, in order to give Sigurd the Holy weapon of Baldo, the Tyrfing, before dying. Shortly after, Langobalt falls and Sigurd conquers Lubeck Castle. Shanan and Oifey flee with Seliph, along with several other children of the army, to Tilnanogue in the northern country of Isaac. Ayra informs Sigurd that she has finished fulfilling her promise to her late brother Mariccle, and she plans to stay with Sigurd (at least until the Battle of Barhara).Meanwhile, Cuan and Ethlin return form Lenster to aid Sigurd in his cause. Unfortunately, the Thracian Dragon Knights followed them, and even with the Gaeborg in Cuan's hands, they inevitably die. After this event, Trabant takes Altenna and the Gaeborg and returns to Thracia. The other members of the Thracian army are slain by Sigurd's army. After he conquers Phinora, Sigurd hears news about the deaths of Cuan and Ethlin. Afterward, his army ventures across the Yied Desert. Reptor's army waits for Sigurd, not moving until his army is close enough to attack. Once they do, however, the Velthomer army turns against Reptor. Once Reptor is defeated, then the battle is over.Alvis summons Sigurd and his army to perform an assumed victory celebration. However, the Battle of Barhara (aka the Barhara Massacre or the Barhara Incident) commences. The casualties in the Barhara Incident are unclear. The event is discussed in Fire Emblem: Thracia 776, and that game confirms some of the survivors; Aideen, Bridget, Fury, Lachesis, Tiltyu, and Sylvia survived. Aideen retires to Tilnagogue Castle sanctuary and conducts church services. It is rumored that Bridget becomes Eyvel. Fury returns to Silesia, but by the time of Seliph's tale, she dies of natural causes. Lachesis sends her daughter Nanna to Fin in Lenster. She is heading to Isaac in search of her son Delmud, but she can not stand the heat of Yied Desert and dies there. Tiltyu flees to Silesia and gives birth to Tinny, Arthur's younger sister, and gives them both necklaces. She suffers from post-traumatic stress after the Barhara Incident. She eventually returns to Freege and starts crying everyday, unable to withstand the loss of her friends, losing contact with her son Arthur, and enduring abuses from Hilda. Her mind and body can no longer withstand it, and she dies of illness. Sylvia survives the Barhara Incident, but her whereabouts are unknown. Ayra's case involving the Barhara Incident is very unclear and highly debated. She is presumed dead during the game ending. However, many Japanese sources differ on her case, and many Fire Emblem fans believe that she is actually still alive and that she retired to the Isaacian countryside, tilling her father's fields.The death of Sigurd, along with the discovery of Diadora bearing Narga blood, act as catalysts that transform Alvis into Emperor. He successfully creats a peaceful regime in Grandbell that lasts for 17 years. He also has two twin children, Julius (Yurius) and Julia (Yuria), from Diadora. However, after 17 years of peace, things started to change. With the resurrection of the Loput Church, the Grandbellian Empire becomes an authoritarian regime, the people living in total oppression. The ruler of Issac, King Danan, is talking to his general Harold about a group of rebels. Harold says that he has found the rebels hideout and has sent an army to capture and execute them. Meanwhile, at the rebel's hideout, Skasaher (Ayra's son) sees the army and rushes inside to tell his twin sister, Lakche. Lakche wants to fight the army but Skasaha is hesitant to fight. Seliph comes in and says that Skasaher does want to fight; he's just worried about Seliph. Seliph says not worry and the three prepare to go to battle. The priestess Rana wants to come too, but Seliph tells her to stay here. However, he changes his mind when he sees how much she wants to come. Shortly after the battle begins, Oifey, Delmud, and Lester arrive and join Seliph's cause.Upon conquering Ganeishire, the group finds Levin and Princess Julia. Levin leaves Julia with Seliph and his companions to attend other matters, while Kinga Danan orders his sons Johan and his younger brother Johalva to attack. Neither of them really want to attack because Lackche fights alongside the rebels. Eventually, Lakche convinces one of the brothers to join. Almost immediately after conquering Ganeishire, Ferry's daughter Phee, a pegasus knight, and Arthur, a mage and son of Tiltyu arrive near Sophara. Phee set out looking for her brother, Sety and Arthur left to look for his sister Tinny. They both decide to join the rebels and help their cause. The group marches on to defeat King Danan in Rivough. Danan is the son of Langobalt, meaning he inherited Major Neir blood. His first son, Brian, also holds this blood, allowing him to use the Holy Axe Swanchinka. After defeating Danan, the rebels march on to look for their leader, Prince Shanan.After Seliph liberates the Kingdom of Isaac from Danan's reign, they begin to cross the Yied Desert from Rivough Castle. Meanwhile, Fin, Leaf, and Anna defend nearby Lenster. Phee flies into Lenster to help them out, while Seliph, Lakche, and Skasaher meet with Shanan, who, along with Patty, joins Seliph's liberation army. Patty infiltrates Yied Shrine and seizes the Balmunk, which was transferred from Isaac Castle after the Isaacian-Grandbellian War, and gives it to Shanan.After Seliph reclaims Chalphy, he has to face the other Dukedoms of Grandbell, along with Price Julius and Archbishop Manfroy. Meanwhile, Julius finds out that Alvis was killed and Manfroy explains that he would have turned against him anyway and that he is no use of them. Julius then talks to his sister Julia, who says that she misses her brother and that the introduction of the Loputousu book changed Julius. Julius then gives her to Manfroy and goes to each of the Dukedoms to tell them to get ready to face Seliph's army. During the battles, Levin explains to Seliph that Julius is the reincarnation of the Dark Lord Loputousu and that he is planning on reviving the Loput Empire. He also gives background information of how the dark Empire had started and who Loputousu really is.Seliph prepares to take action on the Dukedom of Edda first. He faces the Grauen Ritter along with Brian of Dozel, who swears to avenge his father. However, Seliph's army eventually defeats him. When Seliph captures Dozel, Levin tells him about who the gods are and how the 12 crusaders were created, along with information and history about the last Holy War. He also explains to Seliph that Julia is his younger half-sister and that she was the one who inherited the blood of Narga from Empress Diadora.After Seliph conquers Dozel, he is caught in an ambush between the Gelben Ritter (led by the sinister Queen Hilda of Freege) and the Beigen Ritter (led by Andorey's son, Scorpio of Jungby). When Seliph defeats Hilda's army, he meets someone by the name of Felipe who explains to him that he was an attendant of Emperor Alvis and that he was ordered to protect the children from the child hunts. He also explains that Princess Ishtar volunteered to help out with the children secretly. Seliph is surprised by this and that he was told that Ishtar is a caring person and helped the children escape from the start. Seliph then asks Levin where Julia is. He thinks that she is either in Velthomer or Barhara and that Seliph will have to get her himself. After Seliph captures the House of Freege, Ishtar tells Julius to have her send the Weissen Ritter after Seliph. Julius is not too pleased about Ishtar's idea however. She explains that she wants to do it for the pride of the Freege family and avenging their deaths. Although Julius is not sure about Ishtar sending her troops, he lets her go and tells her that he is not forcing her to do anything. Meanwhile, Manfroy sends a possessed Julia after Seliph's army.When marching toward the capital city of Barhara, Seliph has to deal with the Weissen Ritter (led by Princess Ishtar), Barhara (guarded by the Dark Prince Julius along with the 12 Dark Warlords), Ishtar's army, Julia and Velthomer (guarded by the evil Archbishop Manfroy of the Loput. Sect). Eventually a small army of the Thracian Dragon Knights, led by Prince Arion, gets involved within the final battle. Altenna meets up with him and tries to convince him that what he is doing is not the right way to go. He eventually agrees, not for Seliph, but for his (adopted) sister. Meanwhile, Ishtar sends the Weissen Ritter, along with a trio of difficult-to-defeat Falcon Knights to attack Seliph's army. After they are all defeated, Seliph then faces Ishtar. Tinny is upset that she has to face Ishtar because she is a cousin who has been so kind to her. In the end, though, Seliph's army defeats Ishtar.Seliph then encounters a possessed Julia, seeing that she is placed under a spell by Manfroy. Levin explains to Seliph that they should go and kill Manfroy first and then try to talk to Julia. Seliph finally encounters the wicked Archbishop Manfroy, who explains that the spell he placed on Julia was the same as the one placed on Diadora and that everything was all part of his sinister plot to resurrect the Dark Lord Loputousu. Seliph blames Manfroy for causing grief and sadness to his parents so that he could succeed in his evil ambitions in resurrecting the dark lord. Seliph kills Manfroy and brings Julia back to her senses. When Seliph captures Velthomer, he, along with Levin, learn from Felipe that Alvis had the light tome of Narga locked up to keep Manfroy and the Loput. Sect. from getting their hands it. They learn that the only way for it to be unlocked is to use the Diadora's Circlet that Alvis gave to Julia to protect her from Julius. Julia feels so much power when using and feels that she has a strong relationship with her mother.Seliph and Julia rush back to Barhara to face Julius in the final battle. Seliph is unable to defeat Julius alone due to the effect of the dark tome of Loputousu, which severely weakens most warriors. However, with the help of Julia's Narga tome, they defeat Julius and the evil within him. The battle between the dragon of darkness and the dragon of light seems to take forever, but Seliph and Julia manage to defeat Julius and release Loputousu from his body. Loputousu's last words are that Narga has ruined everything for him. He appears in the form of a black dragon after Julius is killed and eventually disappears from the world. Seliph then successfully takes the throne of Barhara, becoming the emperor of Grandbell, with Julia by his side.Gameplay:Building upon the basic gameplay of the games that preceded it, Seisen no Keifu introduced a long list of innovations, many of which became standards for the entries that followed. Some of these improvements are listed below.Arguably the most important new feature introduced is a robust character relationship system that affects both elements of the gameplay and story. Playable characters can converse with each other in the middle of the battlefield, possibly forming strong relationships or even falling in love with each other. Characters with strong bonds also raise each other's stats when fighting together on the battlefield. For example, if one character attacks an enemy while close to his/her lover, the character has a much higher chance of landing a critical hit, which deals three times the normal damage.As an additional feature, characters of opposite sex who had fallen in love during the first half of the game could generate children that became playable characters in the second part of the story, taking characteristics such as stats and growth rates from both parents. Given its heavy tie to the storyline, this feature was dropped in subsequent titles in the series. Later games used the Support System, a system that carried the same ideas that the Love System started. However, Fire Emblem: Awakening brings back the marriage concept, as it too features a storyline that makes it possible to play as a second generation of characters descended from the original cast.Seisen no Keifu is also the first game in the series to feature the Weapon Triangle System, an important strategy concept that gives each weapon a Rock-Paper-Scissors like property. The game similarly introduced the trinity of magic among Fire, Wind, and Thunder magics seen later in Path of Radiance and again in Radiant Dawn.However, some ideas presented in this game were not used in future entries. When characters fight in the arena, they do not die (as they do in other games), but rather lose the match and go back to battle with one hit point remaining. Also, weapons can be repaired, with more powerful weapons requiring more gold to repair. Each character also carries their own gold supply, as opposed to the use of a more standard collective pool of gold from which all characters could draw.Cheat: Lackche with BalmunkFirst, you need Lackche to have major Odo blood by pairing with Holyn, or she will not be able to wield it. To start the glitch, equip Shanon with the Balmunk, and get killed. Have Corple use the Valkyrie Staff, and press L or R on Shanon. Shanon's Balmunk should change to an Iron Lance. Now Save your game, and reset. Load your game back up, and go to the Shop in your castle. Balmunk should be for sale. Now have Lackche buy it. Normally she wouldn't be able to buy it, but if you did the above steps it should work. </plot>
	<releasedate>14/5/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>qO4AVL-ZFJ4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3615</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/564404-fire-emblem-seisen-no-keifu</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/fire-emblem-seisen-no-keifu</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fire-emblem-seisen-no-keifu/3030-18005/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/lREfOAU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/JHLeKLQ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/AUbEzN4.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/FzbrKvJ.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/TiDx1hV.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/gpUs0lm.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/dE4mocF.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/KFj3UZf.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/9QNCmzv.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/YYt0ysF.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/BCgl7Is.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/kQDlBz9.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/hW96gAr.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/mvZwBKl.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/gsOKrTV.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/JRNQRRX.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Fire Emblem: Seisen no Keifu (Fire Emblem: Genealogy of Holy-War) is a Japanese Super Famicom tactical role-playing game developed by Intelligent Systems and published by Nintendo. It was released on May 14, 1996 in Japan. It is the fourth title in the Fire Emblem series, the second Fire Emblem title for the Super Famicom and was the last game produced by Gunpei Yokoi. The game has received recognition outside Japan through imports and console emulation, including an unofficial emulation fan translation into English.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/11ba0f6d-d15c-4252-86de-45e153d6e532.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9d5beffa-3ab0-437e-8a7c-f654a2115342.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0bd3241c-9059-4076-a73b-64dbf41b2ab2.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>