<Game>
	<Name>First Samurai (USA)</Name>
	<plot>"The Demon King descends from his mountain domain to you, the First Samurai and your master. Defenceless against the Demon's magic, you succumb to his powers, leaving the your Master to fight the Demon King alone. Your master falls in combat, dying. But, with his last breath, he summons the Wizard Mage. The Demon King fearing defeat, escapes to the future. Tormented, the young samurai seeks the teachings of the Wizard Mage in the ways of magic. Boiled with revenge and armed with a magical sword, the young samurai follows the Demon King into the future and the unknown..."The First Samurai is a platform action game very much similar to other platform games, but with a medieval oriental touch to it in addition to various unique features.Arriving in the new unknown land, you are defenceless hence your fists and kicks. But as you journey forth, you'll find your trusty magical sword as well as throwing weapons such as knives and axes. With your martial art skills, your enemy best beware with those sudden moves that may prove fatal!The First Samurai offers a wide array of weapons, special items and other objects. Combat is usually melee, either relying on your punch or kicks or using the magical sword to slash some pretty skillful blows in whatever direction possible.Monsters are forever regenerating but food for health is plentiful. It actually takes an effort to be killed...Cheat: Level selectSelect Options from the title screen and:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Kotobuki System Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>vsxSlajobE8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1915</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588338-first-samurai</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/first-samurai</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/first-samurai/3030-1371/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/First_Samurai_(video_game)</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/aZmZ6HD.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OakK8bi.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/zMrkFQb.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/QO6xNRI.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/SnYJcDJ.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/GmHDyiL.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/npNOQc3.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/X5aySZA.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/V0uqZ3m.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/1174SSh.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/CWsCAyC.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/8WDzN2S.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/YQtY3FA.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/alsnWVp.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/jAByAnW.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/kt2lfUG.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/VrVuW67.png</clearlogo1>
</game>