<Game>
	<Name>First Queen - Ornic Senki (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Ornic Senki is a remake of  First Queen. The game retains the basic gameplay and the story of the original. Some scenes and dialogues were added (for example, the intro features a detailed account of what happened in different kingdoms after the Ornic invasion, which was absent in the original version). The battle system remains the same, but the player has more options to customize the party AI. Also, instead of choosing locations from a menu and being able to view the world map only before major battles, the player is actually navigating the world map now, physically moving to the dots that represent locations. The remake features new musical compositions and sound effects, as well as more detailed 16-bit graphics.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Culture Brain Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571049-first-queen</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/first-queen-ornic-senki</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/first-queen/3030-40506/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/vzqxSxC.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9aobjuj.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/5BmXE3n.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/YAH0DUG.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/OYNv1rl.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/l7zTDoe.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/8lFtrxA.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/XkCCcA3.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Jm4zgWz.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/O9n29Ex.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/d1LFM9V.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/dpIrNqp.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/UAJNsaQ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>First Queen (ファーストクイーン, "First Queen") is a real-time strategy-action RPG video game developed by Kure Software. It was first released on the Sharp X68000 and NEC PC-9801 computer platforms in Japan in 1988, and then subsequently released on the Super Famicom as First Queen: Ornic Senki in 1994. The game had three sequels. The series was also notable for featuring art work by Yoshitaka Amano, who would later gain fame for the Final Fantasy series.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/15ef176c-fc76-4c67-94bd-b808186cb29d.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fbded440-f31d-4d2f-82d2-27a7b61c9b58.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6c63efe5-24df-408d-b819-70ec8136173c.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea777be6-8791-4c50-a8d1-e5b50ac95b56.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Culture Brain</Publisher>
</game>