<Game>
	<Name>Flying Hero - Bugyuru no Daibouken (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Flying Hero: Bugyuru no Daibouken ("Bugyuru's Great Adventure") is a vertically scrolling shoot 'em up with a bright, cartoony style, similar to games like Sega's Fantasy Zone or Konami's TwinBee series. The game features Bugyuru, a flying ball, whose girlfriend Pao gets kidnapped by a mysterious vampire named Biblio. Bugyuru takes off in close pursuit, flying across various worlds and taking down bizarre enemies like flying monkeys and giant rhino beetles.The game was released exclusively in Japan for the Super Famicom and never officially localized, however a fan translation patch exists.Cheat: Access the Option mode (and select the Stage, Lives, and Continues)During the opening scenes (or at the title screen) press the Select button. You will have access to the Option Mode. Now use the controller 2 and press the following buttons:</plot>
	<releasedate>18/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Side Scroller</genre>
	<Developer>Sting</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570886-flying-hero</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/flying-hero-bugyuru-no-daibouken/3030-39936/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/IVH0ObP.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/NAWVWY9.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/s8jfgfm.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/SCr6AOk.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Di4OkIG.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/EpDDBUA.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/cHi7MbZ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/AlvqHMl.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FCHwJJD.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/AVAf6aK.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/NIDqo5S.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/hITXVZG.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/37M0EUE.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/vgFCedR.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Flying Hero: Bugyuru no Daibouken ("Bugyuru's Great Adventure") is a vertically scrolling shoot 'em up with a bright, cartoony style, similar to games like Sega's Fantasy Zone or Konami's TwinBee series. The game features Bugyuru, a flying ball, whose girlfriend Pao gets kidnapped by a mysterious vampire named Biblio. Bugyuru takes off in close pursuit, flying across various worlds and taking down bizarre enemies like flying monkeys and giant rhino beetles. The game was released exclusively in Japan for the Super Famicom and never officially localized, however a fan translation patch exists.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0ee4756b-0ae9-4dc6-83c0-a5ddc8fe3999.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9ae1568a-fd55-4081-a222-ef6d687af2bf.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>SOFEL Co Ltd</Publisher>
</game>