<Game>
	<Name>Frantic Flea (Europe) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Frantic Flea has the player take control of a flea warrior out to protect his Flea World from an evil race of bugs called the Insideos who are enslaving his friends and family.The gameplay is a side-scroller with six different levels, where the player explores each stage, freeing fellow captive fleas and utilizing weapons and devices to aid in their missions such as the Hoverpod which enables flight and the Stikko which can give the player the ability to climb walls.  The graphics are done up in a cartoon-style with over 100 animation frames to give sprites a more fluid life-like feel.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/4/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>GameTek, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>1765</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588346-frantic-flea</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/frantic-flea</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/frantic-flea/3030-27050/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/jHznBMt.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/u8EOGsC.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/XZMrMrD.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/GhoDVqz.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/VoOamwc.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ZbBoweq.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/oc1PUIa.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/pxgQ7xG.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6WBCIAs.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/BnpsbSo.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/L7PwVEv.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/MyC14Zd.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Xvrz2ej.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Take control of Frantic Flea and save your Miniflea buddies from the Evil Insideos that are slowly taking over the Flea Homeworld! Only your expert gameplaying skills can rid the planet of the purple alien menace...are you up to the challenge? Frantic Flea features amazing cartoon-quality graphics...making it feel like you're playing a real animated cartoon! Some of the features within the game include... - Massive sprites with hundreds of animation frames for a fluid, lifelike quality. - Interactive 'Insideo' villians - you'll actually see them pick up and carry away your Miniflea buddies! - Unique level designs and 6 completely different zones of action - taking you on a guided tour of the Flea Homeworld! - Amazing devices to find and use - including a Hoverpod, which enables Frantic to fly and Stikko, which gives him the ability to climb walls and hang from the roof!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/34d758aa-4e37-44f8-bc36-99f44f8ac0c0.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be3b0488-76e5-40a5-8781-d13b96ad044d.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6e564a41-fe7f-444c-8f2d-3af1b6aeb27c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bbec3338-7520-42c5-90d0-6574083f7615.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>GameTek</Publisher>
</game>