<Game>
	<Name>From TV Animation Slam Dunk - SD Heat Up!! (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Among the most famous Japanese comics of the 90s are definitely Slam Dunk. The manga tells of the running track that will make the young hoodlum Hanamichi Sakuragi who joined the basketball club in Shohoku high school just because initially interested in the sister of the captain Akagi but later this sport will conquer him so much that he becomes a real basketman.The game is essentially an arcade sports title basketball basically. The main screen there will be little choice given the presence of only three modes: Story mode and classic friendly tournament. In the first we follow the events of the television series whose plot differs slightly from the original one: using Shohoku then we will qualify for the national championship. The second and third but I think there is a need for further explanation.Executable field operations would also be different, you can also feint shots and blow up their opponents markers. Then successfully accumulating a sequence of 'affirmative action' row (steps succeeded, baskets made or avoided), will fill a horizontal bar at the top of the screen and, as he did a little 'in the playroom with the SNK Street Hoop, pressing simultaneously the three keys will not dorsal (except B), you can make a super nice shooting with supplemental animations depending on the player used.Cheat: Sakuragi with his old hairstyleIn the choice of exhibition teams, when you move the cursor to Shohoku, and press A while holding LR, Sakuragi gets his old hairstyle (known as "Regent perm").Cheat: Access the game ending/creditsWhen you enter "we are strong" (see the screenshots section for more details) as password, you get to the ending (credits).</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<VideoURL>bfJQN6Hg-Q0</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571369-from-tv-animation-slam-dunk-sd-heat-up</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/from-tv-animation-slam-dunk-sd-heat-up</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/from-tv-animation-slam-dunk-sd-heat-up/3030-36646/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ol1wawl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/eXiEF4n.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/2ZOLJx6.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/C8zavPg.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/ABCSgm5.png</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/HD46BmZ.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/bZFA619.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/V30UQ6a.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/7byaQKt.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/71h8TVJ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/m39fNH0.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/qrgUDtz.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/NAokxEa.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/tyF76Re.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/TDzPLUa.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/ZXPpRSd.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/u0O2nwk.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/9Wsqqez.png</clearlogo2>
</game>