<Game>
	<Name>Galaxy Robo (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Galaxy Robo is a sci-fi strategy game from Copya System and Imagineer. The player directs a group of mech pilots, each riding distinctive bi-pedal suits and other vehicles. The game is structurally similar to Fire Emblem: the player moves all their units for their turn, either fighting enemy units or performing other tasks, and then control switches to the opponent. When two units meet in combat, a cutaway cutscene shows the aggressor landing (or missing) a hit, and the unit statistics underneath tell the player how much damage was caused.The game was a Japanese exclusive. It was one of a handful of games to use the SNES Mouse peripheral.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Copya Systems</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571048-galaxy-robo</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/galaxy-robo/3030-49221/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/uppqzPN.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/KAXjyqo.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/jccokwJ.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/TcCfqNt.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/g5GfNAN.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/KUVukTV.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/7MHzWFo.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/rzrPyPS.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/i5oeATY.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/gdtg9RO.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ty1XcIu.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/pHZhLlB.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/gsRbF2y.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In 1994 Copya Systems released a detailed strategy title for Nintendo’s 16-bit platform which drew inspiration from the likes of Fire Emblem and Famicom Wars. Despite the turn-based tactical warfare gameplay being rather impressive, GalaxyRobo remained a Japanese exclusive Super Famicom release - one which has since been fan translated into English. Featuring the much loved mech-style story and visuals, GalaxyRobo was one of the select games on the platform to make use of the Super Nintendo Mouse. With cursor based precision and control over your units, turn-by-turn you’re tasked with moving your mechs and taking down the opposing force. Those colliding or in range of projectiles will find the game switches to a side on view to show the damage dealt to each force. Despite being near identical to its inspiration from a gameplay point of view, GalaxyRobo is without a doubt worth a looking if you’re a fan of the genre.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6c2759e2-6a01-441e-8bc0-997300af70b9.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/805c0468-f09f-452a-8fcc-1c6c9864a054.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/30503db4-9e21-4872-a226-8839d5b5b373.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/22e9ecee-66e1-4288-9769-3e95ec274e04.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Imagineer</Publisher>
</game>