<Game>
	<Name>Ganbare Goemon 3 - Shishi Juurokubee no Karakuri Manjigatame (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ganbare Goemon 3: Shishijyuurokubei no Karakuri Manji Katame is the third Super Famicom Ganbare Goemon game (of five) and the twelfth overall. The plot concerns the Wise Man, the lecherous genius who built Sasuke and the other ninja mechanical dolls (Katakuri), who discovers a means to travel to the future to hit on modern Japanese girls. While in the future he is taken hostage by a familiar-looking nun and it's up to Goemon, Ebisumaru, Sasuke and the newly playable Yae to chase through time after him. Goemon's enormous robot doppelganger Impact also makes an appearance.The game is the first in the Goemon series to do away with the stage structure of earlier games, in which the player would have an "adventure stage" where Goemon and co. explore overworld sections and then an "action stage" which had more overt 2D side-scrolling platformer gameplay. The overworld is now a lot larger and interconnected, and entering certain areas lead to their action stages.Cheat: Hidden Pipe MoveWhile in the first person Impact battles, whenever your energy is below 50 points, press Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Left, Right and X. If done right, you'll perform a hidden move in which Impact will take out his pipe and throw a powerful bomb.Cheat: Unlock An Extra Last Boss And Alternative EndingCollect all the Cat Statues in the game and at the end, you'll face an extra last boss and get an alternative ending. There are 20 in the Overworld and 4 in each stage, for a total of 44 Cat Statues.Cheat: Alternate ColorsIn order to get alternate coloring for the characters, hold down the attack button when switching characters.Cheat: Alternate ColorsIn 2 players mode, you can turn yourself or the other player into a Vase that circles the remaining character by pressing A+ L + R at the same time. This way you can go through the levels without injuring the other player.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.625</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>VWClU1hk7iA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18796</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588358-ganbare-goemon-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ganbare-goemon-3-shishi-jrokubee-no-karakuri-manji-gatame</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ganbare-goemon-3-shishijyuurokubei-no-karakuri-man/3030-4765/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/VWNy1DZ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/qnraz6g.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/hGF5IYU.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/MQEp7yq.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/H4WycAB.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/dLMcuDR.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VOhJw5M.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/bNRcBNv.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DCXZVP8.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Dr9MsOi.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/40zcswo.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/rRTWZ1v.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7w4v4Yp.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/GWrVaGD.png</clearlogo1>
</game>