<Game>
	<Name>Ganbare Goemon 2 - Kiteretsu Shougun Magginesu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Ganbare Goemon 2 is an Action game, developed and published by Konami,which was released in Japan in 1993.Cheat: Access The Hidden Forest And Amusement Park StageIn world 2, enter the town. Go all the way right and enter the house with the purple drapes. Buy the pass for 480 gold. Now leave the store and go right to where the guards are. With the pass they will let you go through. Go all the way up, then all the way left and smash the last barrel you see. It will open a hidden underground level which will lead you out of the town and will open up the hidden Forest level. Pass that stage and you'll reach the hidden Amusement Park stage. In that stage, you can play a bunch of minigames and see some cameos from other Konami games.Cheat: Access The Hidden Forest And Amusement Park StageAfter finishing the game, load the save file, go back to the 2nd world and enter the hidden Amusement Park stage. Once in the stage, go one screen up and enter the castle in the center. Talk to the girl and then go out. You now have to get 4 demon heads to access the hidden Hell stage where Dracula (from Castlevania) is the boss. To get them, you have to play the hard versions of the Goemon Memory Game, Devil Bazooka, Floor Sweeper and XEXEX. After finishing a minigame, press Start to see the demon head you have received. It's extremely hard to achieve, but once you get 4 of them, go back to the castle and talk to the girl. She'll send you to the Hell level.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>9.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ob648xBCMEw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18795</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575508-ganbare-goemon-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ganbare-goemon-2-kiteretsu-shogun-magginesu</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ganbare-goemon-2-kiteretsu-shogun-magginesu/3030-22151/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/65tcWeS.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/RRiexfp.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/lQOgkVc.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/4qJK3iy.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/KiLX43t.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/yGVK7du.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/GHWY3uI.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/5ETP8ry.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/9SDDo1O.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Gecas9C.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/emIriup.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/0irBJwi.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7mcDk1W.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Uczf5k9.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>As you may have guessed from the number 2 in the title, this is the second SNES game in the popular blend of the adventure and jump and run genres which is the Goemon series. Again, you (and your partner, in 2 player mode) control Goemon, his friend Ebisu-Maru and, new to the bunch, robot Sasuke, through loads of action stages and villages. Another new feature comes with 3D boss fights, featuring the giant mech type robot called "Goemon Impact".</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>isvAXyMfvxg</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/58e4072f-2e5f-4824-86ed-0bf7d6e95466.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd243775-cb64-4a5e-a7f7-226ab7b64e1b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3911da93-f791-445f-8964-94807ee7279a.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e765e024-4567-40dc-9b41-29a714681c88.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6929317c-3ebd-4918-9009-04c59ed699db.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>