<Game>
	<Name>Genghis Khan II - Clan of the Gray Wolf (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Genghis Khan II: Clan of the Gray Wolf (JP: Aoki Ookami to Shiroki Meshika: Genchou Hishi, or "Blue/Gray Wolf and White Doe: The Secret History of the Yuan Dynasty", the subtitle referring to the ancient literary work of the same name) is a strategy simulation game from Koei and a sequel to the 1987 strategy game Genghis Khan. Like its predecessor, Clan of the Gray Wolf allows the player to follow Temujin, later Genghis Khan, as he conquers various parts of the world with his Mongolian horde. The game plays similarly to Koei's other Historical Simulation games, like Romance of the Three Kingdoms and Nobunaga's Ambition.The game was released on the PC-8801 and ported to various other systems. The SNES version was later rereleased on the Wii's Virtual Console in Japan and the US in 2009 and again in 2015 for the Wii U eShop.ScenariosScenario 1: The Conquest of Mongolia [Mongolia, 1184 AD]Scenario 2: Genghis Khan's Grand Ambition [Greater Eurasia, 1206 AD]Scenario 3: The Yuan Dynasty of China [Greater Eurasia, 1271 AD]Scenario 4: World Conquest [Greater Eurasia]Cheat: Unlock the World Conquest ScenarioSuccessfully complete the 1st scenario (Mongol Conquest) before the year 1214 and you'll unlock a 4th scenario (World Conquest).</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Fantasy</genre>
	<Developer>Koei</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>7.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>JhhM0LYewtc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3630</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588353-genghis-khan-ii-clan-of-the-gray-wolf</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/genghis-khan-ii-clan-of-the-gray-wolf</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/genghis-khan-ii-clan-of-the-gray-wolf/3030-5679/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/BBs3pXA.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ye46uDQ.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/G7qD4PR.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/CqltaBa.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zD7gbGh.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/sgNtPmT.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/MJwJyTL.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/iYyMwnO.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/JZwcuQK.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/X8VZfkS.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/sW3Nmuf.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/bPG7Bi2.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/yJN7HeK.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KyqLMav.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/j19aSq4.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Unleash Mongol Hordes! In an age of conflict, you have been chosen to rule. Military strength, as well as political artistry must be used to build an empire that spans the continents. Legendary sages and warriors will be your companions - or your bitter foes! Lead your knights, samurai and elephants across the blazing sands of Arabia, through the Burmese jungle and into the grassy hills of the British Isles. Cross the Silk Road with Marco Polo and debate policy with Thomas Aquinas. Give the order to attack from the safety of your fortress or march to war at the head of your legions. Be careful to groom a successor and your great dynasty will live on. Soon all will bow before your might!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a5b21541-1caf-482c-bba1-05d604623fa9.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fa03b327-656b-4872-aa8c-1ed3a2229aa9.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f36ce709-fb17-4fb7-a2ea-88036fa917ac.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9fc5915-36c5-437c-8404-654c6abbbc21.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
</game>