<Game>
	<Name>Ghost Chaser Densei (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Ghost Chaser Densei doesn't take any dramatic departures from the standard scrolling-brawler plot-line. A city twenty minutes in the future must be saved from a terrorist organization, and between salvation and you is a long, straight line full of goons who must be punched. Aside from receiving orders from your boss before each level, and the quick conversation with a boss or rare NPC, the story won't attempt to get in the way of beat-downs.There are three playable characters in Ghost Chaser Densei: the martial artist Makai, the mace wielding cat-girl Iyo, and the autonomous robot Belva. Each has unique moves as well as the basic abilities of attacking, jumping, blocking, throwing, and using a special if attack and jump are pressed together. Unlike most brawlers these special moves deplete a recharging special bar, not your health. Makai can throw fireballs and do a flying kick in midair, Iyo can triangle jump and preform a spinning piledriver, and Belva can double jump and preform a grapple special. Characters also have a team up special if playing in two player mode. Enemies range from armored soldiers to lizard men to robots, but most break down into the same hierarchy: weaker types will rush at you while stronger types will shoot projectiles then rush at you. Each level ends with a unique boss with multiple short and long range attacks.Cheat: Change Costume ColourLet your character die, then push L and R when selecting and hold until your character reappears.Cheat: Change Costume ColourOn the Main Menu screen, move the cursor to the number of players you will be using, push L, R, &amp;gt;, &amp;gt;, &amp;lt;, &amp;lt;, and then L and R together and hold. Continue holding L and R until the Character Select screen appears.Cheat: Change Costume ColourEnter the following when on the Mission Briefing screen with a controller inserted into the 2P slot.Cheat: Change Costume ColourYou must hold all the buttons, including the final directional button until the screen ends.Cheat: Change Costume ColourHold down L and R when selecting a character to allow the same character to be used by both players.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/9/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>aNC6iiRGnk0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>24810</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/567027-ghost-chaser-densei</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ghost-chaser-densei</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/denjin-makai/3030-22926/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/gKgmsXg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/HtAGStq.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/0XVKRIA.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/KeC7Swk.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/LgJ5UfZ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/XQNciet.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/xJau5OF.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/xSibnWm.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/9ISckip.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/4c6gpQv.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/iRoFOgh.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/PcDH5tr.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/VDd7lX4.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Ghost Chaser Densei doesn't take any dramatic departures from the standard scrolling-brawler plot-line. A city twenty minutes in the future must be saved from a terrorist organization, and between salvation and you is a long, straight line full of goons who must be punched. Aside from receiving orders from your boss before each level, and the quick conversation with a boss or rare NPC, the story won't attempt to get in the way of beat-downs. There are three playable characters in Ghost Chaser Densei: the martial artist Makai, the mace wielding cat-girl Iyo, and the autonomous robot Belva. Each has unique moves as well as the basic abilities of attacking, jumping, blocking, throwing, and using a special if attack and jump are pressed together. Unlike most brawlers these special moves deplete a recharging special bar, not your health. Makai can throw fireballs and do a flying kick in midair, Iyo can triangle jump and preform a spinning piledriver, and Belva can double jump and preform a grapple special. Characters also have a team up special if playing in two player mode. Enemies range from armored soldiers to lizard men to robots, but most break down into the same hierarchy: weaker types will rush at you while stronger types will shoot projectiles then rush at you. Each level ends with a unique boss with multiple short and long range attacks.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b14bc66-f5de-44ef-93d6-1568a5fafeb0.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/494c67cd-910e-4e3d-abf7-58a73466a691.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Banpresto</Publisher>
</game>