<Game>
	<Name>Go Go Ackman 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Go Go Ackman 2 is mostly the same as its predecessor, with a few small tweaks. The angel Tenshi is still determined to end Ackman's nefarious ways, and this time he has enlisted the help of the angelic rock band Metal Angel. Ackman still murders at whim and has his companion Godon collect the souls of his slain, but this time Ackman can keep the weapons he finds, either sword, boomerang, or gun. Each weapon can be upgraded twice, but upgrades will be lost if Ackman is hit or finds a new weapon. Ackman can also now throw smaller enemies, although he can't move while holding them.Ackman 2 takes place over 5 stages filled with new bosses and enemies.Cheat: Start at any levelAt the title screen while holding Select on both controllers, press A to start on Stage 2, B for Stage 3, Y for Stage 4, and X for Stage 5.</plot>
	<releasedate>21/7/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>zEnKbmxgzTA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>25501</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575763-go-go-ackman-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/go-go-ackman-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/go-go-ackman-2/3030-34120/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/elE1ucJ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/vRcFCgK.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/UuU3qs3.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/LaRRRVM.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ad9l0JI.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/27tLsQN.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/mOrYbRe.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/APdCEIV.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/hH25iAi.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/dgVbris.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/0MyKyjI.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/keRMpa2.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/R9W4dxK.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/KPxMURw.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The second installment in the Go Go Ackman series, concerning a young demon and his cherubic nemesis who tries to rein in the destruction he causes. Ackman is now pitted against the Metal Angels, a rock band of Angels inspired by the voice of God, Metatron.Ackman is capable of a wide variety of actions, which often vary depending on the weapon being wielded at the time.Go Ackman 2 is an Action game, developed by Aspect and published by Banpresto, which was released in Japan in 1995.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1dc7b7cf-b688-45dc-b510-f5bd5e018749.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3ab05899-3327-430d-88f3-bfc0603441ed.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Banpresto</Publisher>
</game>