<Game>
	<Name>Go Go Ackman 3 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Yet again Tenshi is hard at work on finding a way to kill off Ackman for good. But, what's this, it seems there's been a shake up in the chain of command, and now Tenshi is wanted by the Angel Police! Will Tenshi be able to clear his good name? Who's really pulling the strings here? And, most importantly, does Ackman care about any of this at all?The last of the Ackman games, Go Go Ackman 3 makes very few changes from Go Go Ackman 2, although Tenshi is now a playable character. Both Ackman and Tenshi can be switched between at special points in a level, but they share the same health meter and weapon. Unlike Ackman Tenshi can fly, but as he is an angel he can not collect the souls of enemies he kills. Souls have changed too, and are now used as currency in shops where Ackman can buy temporary powerups or healing. Finally Ackman has lost the ability to slide enemies along the ground, but he can now move while holding a stunned enemy.Cheat: Level SelectAt the title screen while holding Up, L, and R at the same time, press Start to access the Level Select screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>15/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>lXKqpX9OJW0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>25502</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581982-go-go-ackman-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/go-go-ackman-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/go-go-ackman-3/3030-41029/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/cwD2Atc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/zsDgyU7.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/LFfSjK3.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/HuflGv6.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/YLYzpjs.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/0OjvX5E.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/MTmmwOa.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ZdTla7g.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/IxOfOKJ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ivUqkZW.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/J1qg2f3.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Pj0LW2M.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CTOMWZH.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/GulTM9X.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The third and final Super Famicom video game adaptation of Akira Toriyama's manga about the 200 year old "devil child" Ackman and his culling of human souls on Earth. On hand to stop him from hurting humans, though he rarely succeeds in doing so, is the cherubic angel Tenshi.The third game has the pair teaming up to take on Tenshi's flamboyant rival, who employs an army of mechanized angels in order to complete Tenshi's job in taking down Ackman after kicking the cherub to the curb. Tenshi is now a selectable character that the player can switch between at any point.As with the two previous games, Go Go Ackman 3 is a side-scrolling platformer that offers a number of different weapons Ackman can use to destroy the angelic hordes on his tail.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f0efefda-947f-492e-89bd-d76bc9da092d.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/13d60cf0-ce03-4eb4-b2e3-984cccf4c308.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Banpresto</Publisher>
</game>