<Game>
	<Name>Gon (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Gon is a side-scrolling platformer starring the tiny dinosaur Gon. Like the manga the little dino hails from, the game is completely devoid of narration or dialogue. The story is told through contextual scenes - such as Gon getting annoyed by an ape that steals his fruit and chases after it - and continues to provide excuses for Gon to travel the globe in search for food.Gon is invincible, due to his incredibly thick skin and skull, so instead the game eventually ends when Gon gets so agitated by the local fauna (by taking too much damage, for instance) that he destroys the planet. The player is extended the option to restart from the last checkpoint if this should happen.The game is exclusive to the Super Famicom. Gon would next appear in a video game with the 1998 PlayStation version of Tekken 3 where he cameos as a hidden fighter.Cheat: Level PasswordsAt the start screen select password and enter the following</plot>
	<releasedate>11/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>TOSE</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>2XolMS_N9VU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>21359</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571164-gon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/gon</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/gon/3030-23077/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/eLszKsq.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/MQBnoc9.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/G1uOI9T.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/84Ubbzy.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ewnXh6q.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8PTEV7p.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/rfy9sMp.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/g2fq7RB.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/e0PmY11.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/0t4jNF2.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/efA63fw.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/kezcEZE.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/kSBv1jR.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/swbjt9K.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/gpB1gqp.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Gon is a Japan-exclusive side-scrolling action video game with platforming elements for the Super Famicom published by Bandai. The game is an adaptation of the manga series Gon by Masashi Tanaka, about the daily life of a super-deformed orange carnosaur named Gon. Like the manga, the video game features a minimal plot and no dialogue. Instead it focuses on the cartoonish, comedic situations Gon gets himself into, particularly when searching for food and interacting with other animals. Gon would venture into different ecosystems that made up the prehistoric world.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b2ec1dd9-930b-422c-addc-b9daa8b9f8b5.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2fa3bab2-c9bd-4f80-9e74-d1d81158acae.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49b0f0c8-60df-46df-b976-654e6d758e6a.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>