<Game>
	<Name>Goof Troop (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Goof Troop is an action-adventure game created by Capcom, and released in 1993 for the Super Nintendo. The game is based on the children's cartoon of the same name by Disney. One of the game's key features is that two players can play cooperatively as Goofy and his son Max.Goof Troop was designed by Shinji Mikami, who later became famous for his work on games like Resident Evil 4 and Viewtiful Joe.Story:Max and some piratesGoofy and Max, the game's protagonaists, are heading out to fish on an absolutely gorgeous day in Spoonerville. As the two relax along the seashore, they witness a massive pirate ship sailing towards Spoonerville, with their friends Pete and P.J. aboard. They realize that their friends are aboard against their will, and they must have been kidnapped. Goofy makes a heroic attempt to pursue the boat, but ultimately is unable to catch the pirates before they arrive on their home island.Goofy and Max make haste to the Pirate island, and upon arrival encounter a group of pirates. Once they defeat their attackers, they learn that the pirates have mistaken their friend Pete for pirate captain Keelhaul Pete, who was swallowed by a massive whale long ago. Goofy and Max set off to save their friends from these delusional pirates.Unfortunately for Goofy and Max, Pete and P.J. decide that they enjoy being pirate royalty. The longer that Goofy and Max take to reach them, the more Pete wants to stay captain of these pirates.Goofy and Max, after much adventuring, find themselves at the pirate's ship. They find who they think is Pete, but when Goofy attempts to save him, he knocks him cold on accident. Upon furtherIn a caveinvestigation, Goofy and Max realize they have found the real Keelhaul Pete, who had recently been spat out by the whale! Goofy and Max venture into the pirate ship, still looking to save their friends. Keelhaul Pete appears again, hoping to put an end to their quest. Goofy and Max prove a formidable opponent, however, and once again knock him flat on his back. Goofy and Max arrive just in time to save Pete and P.J. from the jaws of a large gator, who Goofy finds suspcious, as the Gator is eating before supper time. Trapping Keelhaul Pete to make sure he causes no more trouble, Goofy and company leave the ship to finally relax and do a little fishing.Gameplay:Goof Troop takes players through five various areas on Spoonerville Island. Players begin on a beach, followed by a village under siege, then move on to a spooky haunted castle, a mountain valley, and finally end up on a Pirate Ship where their friends Pete and PJ are being held captive.Players have a variety of options when taking on enemies by throwing items such as barrels or pots. There are also other items with more novel uses, such as a grappling hook to grab on to far off items or a bell that will catch the enemy's attention. The grappling hook comes especially in handy for crossing obstacles. Only one player can have each item at any particular time, and players must work together to get the best use out of all the game's equipment.A maze of a bridgeIf players come into contact with an enemy or fall prey to other hazards in the game, they lose a life. Once enough lives have been lost, they must use a continue to get back in the game. Goofy and Max can pick up red diamonds for extra lives, or special white diamonds to gain an extra continue.One of Goof Troop's main aspects are the numerous puzzles throughout each level. There are many puzzles that include kicking sliding blocks in order to press switches to open passages. Players must also search for special keys to open doors to bosses. Many of the game's items come in handy for the game's puzzles.Critical ReceptionWhen reviewed by Electronic Gaming Monthly the game received scores of 7,8,8 and 8 adding, "...I can't stand games that have beaten enemies reappear when you enter the room again. Also, the game is just too easy! It seems strongly geared toward the younger playing audience". Mike Weigand disagreed, "...this game requires enough skill and brains to keep you busy, plus it keeps you coming back for more".		</plot>
	<releasedate>11/7/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>sddd-mgDbC0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3200</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588359-disneys-goof-troop</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/goof-troop</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/goof-troop/3030-11349/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/PyLbcSJ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/chCidSH.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/WvqXYZH.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/cMn6Ssa.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Y4hDRlV.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/7FucW3L.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/42wDcp9.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/0ANPFYn.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/RgwPwgd.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/MH8nigi.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/cc6vre5.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/GxHbSuP.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/6Y4N0po.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/P9wCUFo.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/hvzzia3.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/NKcP1AF.png</clearlogo1>
</game>