<Game>
	<Name>GP-1 RS - Rapid Stream (Japan) (En)</Name>
	<plot>The sequel to GP-1, the player once again can race with motorcycles on 17 different tracks located across 14 different countries. The player also has six different bikes to choose from.  Players can also upgrade their bikes by winning races and earn points, earning enough points will let the player obtain better parts for their bike.The season mode, otherwise known as the Grand Prix is present along with a Practice and Race mode, but there is also a Battle mode that allows two friends to duke it out head-to-head on the track of their choice.  A password feature is also present to allow players to pick up and play at their leisure.Cheat: Hidden Sound TestWhen the main title "GP Part II" comes out, but before any music heard, Hold L+R button on Controller 2, and press "Start" button on Controller 1. The screen will changed to dark  with only "Sound Test" text appear. To choose the music, tap the D-pad left or right to make the music titles appear. To plays the music, just tap B or A button.Cheat: Level PasswordsA the title screen, select GP Race, then enter the following passwords at the Continue screen:Cheat: Speed BoostTo get speed boost at the beginning of race, just try to make the speedometer's needle-hand pointing at the line between number "8" and "10" when the green light's up. If you time it correctly, you will get extra boost which may passed all the opponents when the racing just starts. This trick is working almost the same like Speed Boost trick in Mario Kart.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Arcade</genre>
	<Developer>Genki</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>DYSc6OHA7fs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3636</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588361-gp-1-part-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/gp-1-part-ii/3030-37312/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/tthnSxS.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OZHD94l.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/A571HJq.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Hp5VsN0.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/bkWEyn9.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/hEcKOcx.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SM4yeqi.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CRR4mWq.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/eTSSKjr.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/wFViQkM.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/rc4jbvk.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/u67o8qb.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/uVCrHT8.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/PliNZgD.png</clearlogo1>
</game>