<Game>
	<Name>Gradius III (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Arcade title screen.The ten stage, third installment to Konami's popular Gradius franchise, aptly titled Gradius III, originally appeared in 1989 at Japanese game centers (aka Japanese Video Arcades). Of the ten stages, Stage 4 was infamous as being the first to offer 2.5D action. Gradius III was also the first title in the series to offer customizable weapon sets. Most recently, Gradius III has been made widely available through Nintendo's Wii Shop as well as a PSP release in the Gradius Collection.Gameplay:The game is infamous as being one of the hardest of the series, as the original arcade version had no way to continue the game upon losing all lives, and a continue system wasn't even in place to be used at the discretion of the owner and operator. The biggest addition is the ability for the player to edit their weapon load-out, that will come with power ups collected through the game. Players can choose predetermined setups or opt to customize their own, though certain variations of weapons are not available between modes.Stages:There are a few differences between the Arcade and SNES versions of the game including some stages being switched around to the SNES having less stages then the ArcadeStage #ArcadeSNESStage 1DesertDesertStage 2BubbleBubbleStage 3Volcano, UndergroundVolcano, UndergroundStage 43D High SpeedMoaiStage 5MoaiFireStage 6CellPlantStage 7FireHigh Speed ZoneStage 8PlantBoss RushStage 9CrystalMechanical Base10 (Part I for Arcade)Boss RushCell10 (Part II, Arcade only)Basen/aHidden Stage 1 (Arcade only)Gradiusn/aHidden Stage 2 (Arcade only)Salamandern/aBosses (SNES)Stage 1GoliathStage 2Bubble EyeStage 3Big Core MK III / Iron MaidenStage 4Twin VaifStage 5Vulture DragonStage 6Choking WeedStage 7BeaconStage 8Zub Rush, Death MK II, Crystal Core, Big Core MK II , Covered Core, Dellinger CoreStage 9Disrupt, Shadow Dancer X2Final StageBacterionPortsSuper NESThe SNES version of Gradius III was released in 1991 and included a reduced difficulty setting and additional load-outs. The slowdown from the arcade version is replicated on this version and doesn't include the 2.5D and Crystal levels present in the arcade version. This version is the only version to include a method to continue the game once all lives are lost. A port was released for Virtual Console on April 23, 2007.Playstation 2The Playstation 2 version of Gradius III was bundled with Gradius IV and was closer to the arcade version of the game and includes the feature that allows you to edit your weapon load-out. Because of the PS2's superior processing speed, an option is included to simulate the slow down of the original arcade game or to let the game play without any lag. This version doesn't have a continue option, but it does let you select any stage you have already cleared.PSPThis version was released in 2006 as part of the Gradius Collection. This version keeps the arcade tradition of not allowing you to continue once you have lost all lives.Soundtrack:A soundtrack containing original music and arranged tracks was released by Konami on the Kings Records label on February 21, 1990. This music has been included on other Gradius themed albums, all released by Konami.				Cheat: Bonus StageThere is a bonus stage located in the game. It is located in Level 2. When you fly into the section that is lined with the blue bubbles, look for a hole in the bottom and go in it. Cheat: Bonus StageThere are five bonus stages in the game. Here is how to access each one: &amp;lt;B&amp;gt;Stage 2&amp;lt;/B&amp;gt; - When you see a hole in the wall at the bottom of the screen, fly down there. Prerequisite: None &amp;lt;B&amp;gt;Stage 3&amp;lt;/B&amp;gt; - When you reach the lower level of the stage, there is a platform in the ceiling that drops down. When it drops down, fly just below the part where the platform was. Prerequisite: Destroy all of the ground targets in the stage up to that point. &amp;lt;B&amp;gt;Stage 4&amp;lt;/B&amp;gt; - In the last set of Moai heads (they look like Easter Island heads), there is one laying down which will lift itself up. Fly behind it. Prerequisite: Nothing must be highlighted on your powerup bar. &amp;lt;B&amp;gt;Stage 5&amp;lt;/B&amp;gt; - Fly just below the ceiling before the narrow corridor. Prerequisite: The hundreds digit of your score reads 5, 7, or 3. &amp;lt;B&amp;gt;Stage 7&amp;lt;/B&amp;gt; - Just after the long downward slope in the second half of the level, stay close to the ground and fly into the wall formation shaped like this: ......../ ........\ ____*/ (key: dots are empty space, lines are walls, the asterisk is there your ship should be.). Prerequisite: Unknown When you clear a bonus stage, you will end up in the next level. That's right, you don't have to fight the boss of the level you were in previously. However, if you get killed in the bonus stage, you will be taken back to the regular level, and will not be able to reenter the bonus stage.Cheat: Bonus StageThe Final Boss, Bacterion, will die regardless of whether you attack it or not. Just dodge his blasts, and in fifteen or so seconds, he will spontaneously die. Even cheaper, park your ship in the bottom center of the screen, and the shots can't aim towards you!Cheat: Bonus StageContinue to hold A through the initial demo, and you'll see the entire first stage including the boss.Cheat: Bonus StageChoose "speed down" for the "!" option in the weapon select screen,if you can get enough power ups to highlight the last weapon, which will not be visible, and using it without powering up on speed up, you will get all four options, missiles, and the shield.  But if you have the laser already, it will be taken away.Cheat: Bonus StageActivate the F-Option or R-Option and collect enough power-ups so that the option selection is highlighted. Now press and hold the A button.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>oCR-m9q2YdY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1918</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588362-gradius-iii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/gradius-iii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/gradius-iii/3030-7617/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/S7EN0kl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Awv3cxg.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/fQN9ju4.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/TfkDUnc.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ABjdrV0.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/uLbvLKQ.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/4KZnF1w.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/w959Hpo.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/E3naJjt.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/r7M9zbU.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/QkYI4n2.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/hNo5PT7.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Fzq2mw2.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ljT4Bbp.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/dLX8i3B.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/NUeatXu.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/9LPO881.png</clearlogo1>
</game>