<Game>
	<Name>Great Circus Mystery Starring Mickey & Minnie, The (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The Great Circus Mystery Starring Mickey &amp; Minnie (JP: Mickey to Minnie Magical Adventure 2) is a Disney-themed video game starring Mickey and Minnie Mouse. The duo track down the missing people at the circus, tracking them across six different stages. Mickey and Minnie have the unique ability to change outfits during the game to use different powers. The player can choose to play as either Mickey or Minnie, the latter becoming playable for the first time.Though not clear in the US/European title, the game is a sequel to the 1992 SNES game Magical Quest Starring Mickey Mouse. It saw a GBA rerelease in 2003 titled Disney's Magical Quest 2 Starring Mickey &amp; Minnie, which made the Magical Quest connection clearer.Cheat: Hidden 2-UpsWhen in Stage One, the Haunted Circus, you will start the game on the fairgrounds. Just ahead is a small pond with an enemy fish swimming in it. At about halfway through the water, there is a wooden support beam in the background. Swim past this and you will receive a 2-Up. In Stage Two, the Jungle, there is another opportunity for a hidden 2-Up. After beating the halfway boss (the giant turtle), you'll go a couple more screens and come to a section where you'll use the Safari outfit to slide down a number of vines. After reaching the bottom vine, swim in the water beneath, all the way to the left.  The word ''2-Up'' will appear when you have found it.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>_7Iu_GOxsE0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2786</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588363-the-great-circus-mystery-starring-mickey-and</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/great-circus-mystery-starring-mickey-minnie</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-great-circus-mystery-starring-mickey-and-minni/3030-5735/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/lNmuqm2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OqKe4Er.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/T7BzAyz.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/DnsTnMh.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/eiLtFSK.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JEPeIWk.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/cizh62r.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/z6RDXef.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/yJrSulK.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/hqwPoAy.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/dn4txIm.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/rOorMwS.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/FYafQh6.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/gINrsSj.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/LPbbnlQ.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/ofPdgUq.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/x0NyL1S.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/RF20KBt.png</clearlogo1>
</game>