<Game>
	<Name>HAL's Hole in One Golf (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>STROKE PLAY - One to four players. Best result after the 18 holes wins.MATCH PLAY - Two players compete against eachother by every hole, the one that finished most holes wins.TOURNAMENT - One to four players plays against 60 computer-controlled players 18 holes.VS HAL - Compete with the Pro-player Hal. If you win you'll receive a password that ables you to use the same kinda metal-clubs he uses. When you've got the password you can use the clubs in every game.--From the SNES Hal's Hole in One Golf instruction manual.Tips:Music testType BGM at the Memory Shot screen for a music test.Play with Metal ClubsEnter METAL PLAY as your name.Watch Hole in One ReplaysEnter CQJB83CFDFJ#H?LBBT7BJCF or B!5B9GB5SFGB3J5BB?GBMYQ as a memory shot password.Slow Ball or Shorter ShotHold Down while the ball is mid-air to force it to fall sooner.Play 19th HoleSelect practice mode and play to the end. Another hole is here, although there is no pin displayed. Movetowards the out-of-bounds area in top portion of the course. Aim for the point approximately in the top left and middle portion of the screen.http://www.consoleclassix.com/snes/hals_hole_in_one_golf.htmlCheat: Slow BallTo slow the ball while it is in air simply press down.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>HAL America</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>4Lz1asaFsts</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3765</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588372-hals-hole-in-one-golf</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hals-hole-in-one-golf/3030-30540/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/x4eGnWh.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/PKGn8BB.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/VfVQ60I.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Nap8xHa.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/bsxZnVS.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/C2wt9zf.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/z1Fuzts.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4ZjtVOc.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/pFMwsK2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/fA2zRLA.jpg</snapshot8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KuPLGha.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/dPlhUug.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>It's the 18th hole-Hal Open Tournament. Sixty of the best golfers in the country are gathered in one place to determine who will walk away with the Grand Prize trophy. You're 7 under par, tied for first. This 22-food putt is all that stands between you and glory. A hush falls over the gallery... you address the ball... you measure your stroke... Hal America brings the excitement of golf competition to the SNES. Multiple play options and a demanding course will challenge beginners and seasoned pros alike!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/065a5629-c951-4ad3-9fac-a1cb80fc74fd.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d425adc8-d846-4026-acbf-9a0453db32e2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8acaa585-9f6c-4b14-8caa-63dbc2939f90.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e380d1bd-c5f8-4bb4-9e18-f513f41c07b5.png</snapshot10>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>HAL America</Publisher>
</game>