<Game>
	<Name>Hammer Lock Wrestling (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:HammerLock Wrestling is a Super Nintendo wrestling game and features fictional professional wrestlers performing movesets similar to real pro wrestlers like Hulk Hogan and Lex Luger. The game greatly emphasizes the exciting TV spectacle of professional wrestling, dedicating parts of the screen to close-ups of moves and wrestlers. Pins, especially, will take over most of the screen, pushing the gameplay view to the sidelines.In Japan the game is known as Tenryu Genichiro no Pro Wrestling Revolution: Wrestle and Romance and is a video game adaptation of the WAR (Wrestle and Romance, later renamed to Wrestling Association R) Japanese wrestling promotion, which was created by Genichiro Tenryu. For the US version, the various WAR wrestlers received fictional names and minor cosmetic changes.Gameplay Modes:Exhibition: Up to four players compete in singles or tag team matches.Top Ranking Match: Players face 11 other wrestlers to become the champion.Tournament: A tournament of up to 8 players to determine a champion.Round Robin Tournament: Up to six players compete in a round robin to determine a champion.Cheat: Title Match Passwords (Japanese Version)Enter any one of the following Passwords to play the final match in Top Ranking Match Mode:Cheat: Title Match Passwords (Japanese Version)To play the final match in Top Ranking Match mode, enter any one of the following passwords:</plot>
	<releasedate>30/9/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco Ltd., Jaleco USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>4+</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>pK4aE8H6b-w</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3639</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588367-hammerlock-wrestling</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/hammerlock-wrestling</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hammerlock-wrestling/3030-38662/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/BKFrCHh.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/5qCoV6h.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/E8RpVTO.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/H9BHU7B.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/xePk0nx.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/UNiny0g.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/kxZX2fs.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/WDsHGU5.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/AjsZckr.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5FJBoZK.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ALBIMeq.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/TJ9xLfg.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6A8fSk4.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/qoWOGJt.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Plug in Hammerlock and get a look at in-your-face, action-packed wrestling like you've never seen it before: up close. How close? Jaleco's exclusive ringside perspective brings the action right under your eyelids. In addition to the main screen, you get two ringside screens. See your opponent's hand pull back for a punch so you can time your dodge perfectly. Then watch the close-up screen explode to twice its regular size as you grab his legs and throw him into a spine splintering suplex. See it all like it's just inches away - closer than you've ever seen it before. - 12 wrestlers and over 60 joint-wrenching moves! - Up to 4 players can compete in tag team matches AT THE SAME TIME! - Tournament, tag team, and exhibition matches for a wide variety of fun. - Different arenas, out-of-the-ring fighting, referee calls, and all the other thrills of a real wrestling match!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/53b2df9c-a9fc-4bda-b3e9-0f1ce2b86963.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/16d0881b-e960-4916-b1c1-2acdf924b05b.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/970b9f1d-6f71-4927-a5e3-849e79990ba5.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/abec5512-abc6-4a72-b921-0a377292563c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/36e9bbbe-a72e-4a48-a491-7a8d084bee46.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Jaleco</Publisher>
</game>