<Game>
	<Name>Heisei Shin Onigashima - Kouhen (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>This is an adventure game based on the old Japanese fairy tale about Momotaro, a boy who was found by an old couple inside of a huge peach (hence the name Momotaro - "Peach Guy"). Momotaro grows up and embarks on a journey to rid the land of the vicious tribe of ogres, and to take their treasures. On his way he meets three animals - a dog, a monkey, and a pheasant, who help him to defeat the ogres. This game is the first part of the story, and is divided into two large chapters, the first telling the story of the dog Ringo, the second the story of the monkey Matsunosuke. In this adventure, you interact with the world by selecting various commands from a menu. Along with traditional commands such as "Look" or "Take" there are situation-specific commands, for example "Smell" for the dog. In certain places it is possible to move by navigating the character physically.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/12/1997</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571523-heisei-shin-oniga-shima-kouhen</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/heisei-shin-onigashima-khen</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/heisei-shin-onigashima-kouhen/3030-8715/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/5ghO5gP.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mweeg9j.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/gcqHQaf.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/eEXO97E.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/WY0uvxb.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/YWbj5Mt.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/e9JOJXj.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/psYQ2hM.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/0Khb3R3.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/JDo6LtA.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/lnQ4Yyp.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/skZsuPc.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/7wajGgq.png</fanart1>
	<Notes>Once upon a time, there was an elderly couple living in Nagakushi village, a small village located far up in the mountains. The couple had no children, until one day, they were entrusted with the care of an infant boy and girl, as prophesied in a dream. The years went by, and when the two children were 8 years old, there was a terrible occurrence in the western capital. An evil dragon suddenly appeared in the city, turning humans into oni, ogres that suck away the souls of other humans. The oni advanced as far as Nagakushi village, stealing away the souls of the elderly couple. Fortunately the two children were left unharmed, and they set out on a quest to save their adopted parents, not realizing that this adventure would reveal the secret of their true origins... The game is played by selecting commands which make the characters talk to, use, or examine various objects or characters. Progress is marked by changes in the illustrative image in the top-right corner of the screen. One of the most distinctive features of the game is the "Change Character" command, used to switch between the two main characters (Donbe, the boy, and Hikari, the girl). The characters can move through the story separately at times, and may be called upon to do tasks that the other main character cannot accomplish on their own. The use of this command in certain situations can trigger dialogue particular to each character, bringing out the peculiarities of each.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e4fceef7-3540-4709-b88a-b916fa142dd7.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e47711fb-ab8e-4345-823d-a52f3ce64b8b.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>