<Game>
	<Name>Hello! Pac-Man (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Enter an original animated adventure--with the world's first video game hero! But the star of your cartoon has a mind of his own, and it's going to take all your skills and patience to carefully guide Pac-man through this hilarious, action-packed cartoon adventure.With a revolutionary new Character Guidance Interface&amp;trade; (CGI&amp;trade;), Pac-Man2 is a game unlike anything you've ever experienced before! So Step into Pac-Man's new and exciting interactive cartoon world... It's a whole new way to play!Cheat: Level 1 passwordsSelect the password option on the main menu and enter.  Note that "pac" denotes using the Pac-Man symbol.  These passwords are great if you're hunting for percentages.Cheat: Level 1 passwordsIn the "Hello! Pac-Man" password screen, enter the following to play the arcade games.Cheat: Secret PathWhen you're in the sewers on the way to the Ghost Witch's lair, remain happy. Hit Pac-Man with your slingshot once to make him angry , and then use the slingshot to direct him to a big hole in the wall. This hole in the wall contains 2 burglars. Pac-Man will chase them out. Have Pac-Man go to the left by pressing the D-pad left and the Y button at the same time. Use the slingshot on the left most wall until it spins,and ''Voila''. A secret path with a mine cart appears. Cheat: Secret PathPress start to go to the item screen, and then hold Select and X.  The percentage of the number of secrets you've found will be displayed above your current password.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<rating>6.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>-kKtpRjkGuU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3234</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588556-pac-man-2-the-new-adventures</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/whGvLzm.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/hcp0nGG.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/nNbGUrp.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/We1ZdJ5.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/tXh747H.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/1PidTsp.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/UFg665Z.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/0FiNAuz.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DNIhAmw.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/dRx6skF.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/TGKLviN.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Erit3B2.png</clearlogo1>
</game>