<Game>
	<Name>Heracles no Eikou IV - Kamigami kara no Okurimono (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Heracles no Eikou IV: Kamigami kara no Okurimono ("Glory of Heracles IV: Gift from the Gods") is an Ancient Greek-themed RPG from Data East and the fourth (technically fifth, including the Game Boy spin-off Heracles no Eikou: Ugokidashita Kamigami) installment in their Heracles no Eikou series.It features a player-named young man who has his spirit separated from his body. He can use his spirit form to possess creatures and other people, using this mechanic to solve puzzles to make progress. The game incorporates various Ancient Greek myths and characters into its scenarios.Like the previous games in the series, the game was never localized into English. After this game, the Heracles no Eikou series went quiet for several years. Paon Corporation (who presently own a lot of Data East's properties after that developer went defunct) would eventually release a NDS sequel, Glory of Heracles, as well as add this game to the Wii's Virtual Console in 2008, and again to the Wii U's Virtual Console in 2015.					</plot>
	<releasedate>21/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Data East</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>xrtekX-f5ZA</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571153-hercules-no-eikou-iv</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/heracles-no-eikou-iv-kamigami-kara-no-okurimono/3030-17798/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4akvNxU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OItiIei.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/cn7Sl5H.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/7WrDXRN.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Kdmsm37.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/GbKipHP.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/UZ7ORBh.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/dxRPYXI.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/j8lJMOj.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MSbiiBG.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/EbyKmPf.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/nhOyPoC.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/KkB4YOU.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/MThyvxF.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The fifth installment of the series (fourth game in the main series), released after the portable spinoff Heracles no Eiko: Ugokidashita Kamigami. The player takes the role of a young man whose spirit was separated from his body. The player must progress by having the spirit enter and take control over the bodies of various humans and animals encountered along the way.The game's plot and setting are very loosely based around various episodes from Greek mythology, with a particular focus on Atlantis and the tale of Pandora's box.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d74c1304-0eb0-4222-8b13-0c9b735cb865.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5de0c070-e22f-43bb-bebc-a06105a468eb.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23530ab6-c56a-4899-be6b-df82b774ecdf.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/846fa6c2-5746-419f-a0e1-d19b0162be6e.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67a461e0-2fee-4231-aa40-3c19233c474a.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/af4026f5-9b9d-4231-85ec-fa251b95e9e2.jpg</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Data East</Publisher>
</game>