<Game>
	<Name>Heracles no Eikou III - Kamigami no Chinmoku (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Heracles no Eikou 3: Kamigami no Chinmoku ("Glory of Heracles 3: Silence of the Gods") is the third game in Data East's Heracles no Eikou / Glory of Heracles series of turn-based RPGs that are built around Ancient Greek mythology. Kamigami no Chinmoku is the first game in the series to be released on the Super Famicom (the previous two were Famicom games). It would also eventually be rereleased on the Wii's Virtual Console.The game is best remembered for its plot, which was fairly unique for its time. Written by Kazushige Nojima (who would later go on to write Final Fantasy VII), the plot revolves around an amnesiac immortal (many years before Planescape: Torment or Lost Odyssey). Because of its plot, this is arguably the best known entry in the series, along with the more recent Glory of Heracles DS game, which is mainly based on this game.Kamigami no Chinmoku's gameplay is retained from the previous Heracles no Eikou game: combat is entirely directed through turn-based, menu-driven commands, as was common for JRPGs of the era.Plot:The story is focused around discovering the main character's identity, as he wakes up without his memory. He discovers early on that he is effectively immortal: he cannot be badly hurt, and he is able to use this unique ability to perform actions others cannot. The protagonist eventually meets various Greek gods and other famous mythological figures in his quest to discover who he is.					</plot>
	<releasedate>24/4/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Data East</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>HOE3iVMFfY8</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570839-heracles-no-eikou-iii-kamigami-no-chinmoku</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/herakles-no-eik-3-kamigami-no-chinmoku</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/heracles-no-eikou-3-kamigami-no-chinmoku/3030-19694/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/buHckEs.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/WUsvVXF.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/eK3K7ky.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/rCuRoGR.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/MIcVwPK.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/cLGokCe.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Hgq0cWp.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/eTpcmPd.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VVHEgTG.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vvJ3Maw.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/xsMkHsw.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/A8jISuT.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ezhdaDb.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5C7NXpx.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Ijepjze.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Heracles no Eikō III: Kamigami no Chinmoku (ヘラクレスの栄光III 神々の沈黙?, "Glory of Heracles III: Silence of the Gods") is the third installment of the series. Originally released for the Super Famicom, it was released on the Japanese Virtual Console in 2007 and a mobile phone in 2008 by G-Mode. The game's plot and setting are loosely based around various episodes included in Greek mythology. The hero begins the game in a state of total memory-loss, but discovers that he has somehow acquired a mysterious power that shields him from all bodily harm, essentially making him immortal. The only clue the hero has in discovering his own identity is a mysterious dream that he sees every night, and he begins his journey in search of the location shown in the dream. The gameplay borrows various motifs from ancient mythology, particularly the concept of immortality. An immortal character can execute certain actions that other characters cannot, like jumping off high cliffs without being injured. The game's writer, Kazushige Nojima, composed a storyline where the hero encounters the Greek gods while trying to discover his own true identity. Like the game's predecessor, Heracles no Eikō II: Titan no Metsubō, the game focuses on its rich storyline rather than the game system, which does not differ significantly from other role-playing video games of the period.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>HOE3iVMFfY8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5f51c546-75e1-4de3-8603-efc831448117.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0171bf23-139c-4303-b892-c28dd1e8c666.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Data East</Publisher>
</game>