<Game>
	<Name>Home Alone 2 - Lost in New York (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Though based on the movie in terms of plotline and additional dialogue, the game was in ways worlds different from the movie. Certain changes made the game more interesting in an interactive game than in a static movie, such as use of different weapons and power-ups for protection, level layouts with enemies not seen in the movie, and for the Uncle's House level, usage of hidden keys and locked doors gained only after luring Marv or Harry into specific traps laid out in the various rooms (aka the first two Home Alone movies), as well as an active scene involving the Bird Woman and her birdseed attacks.The SNES version, while boasting a soundtrack with the SNES' traditionally realistic sounding instrument synth, suffered due to slightly post-8-bit graphics and sound effects, as well as a disjointed feel of incontinuity between stages.LevelsLevel 1 - The Plaza HotelKevin's first entry to New York is the Plaza Hotel, where his father's stolen credit card helps pay the way for a nice, posh room and ideal room service. But after the hotel workers discover his ruse, he attempts to escape.Kevin leaps out of the hotel and right into the arms of his old enemies Marv and Harry, who, as well as escaping from prison and attempting to rob the Christmas toy store, have a bone to pick with Kevin and take him away. But after a quick goose on a woman, who in turn socks Marv, Kevin escapes into the confines of Central Park.Level 2 - Central ParkOne of New York's most popular tourist attractions, Central Park is a haven for both glamour (in the daytime) and filth (at night). Kevin enters the park at one of the worst times, having to contend with vermin and urban leeches.Level 3 - The Uncle's HouseKevin knew he had an uncle who lived in New York and, after much searching, finds his house, noticing it in a state of disrepair and decay. Stones and plaster drop from the ceiling, there are holes in the floors, and several of the doors to get out are locked. Not only that, Harry and Marv have tracked him down and are both searching diligently for him and attempting to steal what remains in the house. But Kevin's set a few of his trademark traps for them to stumble across.Level 4 - The ChaseAfter escaping from the house, Marv and Harry give chase to Kevin through the streets of New York. There are two segments to this level.Segment 1: The player must run away from Harry and Marv while avoiding the additional baddies along the way. The player must must keep running until reaching the giant Christmas tree.Segment 2: Once inside the Christmas tree, the player needs to climb to the very top and grab the flashing star in order to receive the help of the pigeon lady. The player needs to call for help for her to throw bird seeds on Marv and Harry three times each to properly defeat them and win the game. The player can bounce on the ends of the Christmas tree branches to get higher up on the screen.ReceptionThe game has had very low critical reception. Most reviewers complain that various elements of the game change depending on what part of a level the player is on. A prominent example is made by The Angry Video Game Nerd, stating that when a key falls towards the player, the player's impulse is to collect it, Instead the key inflicts damage to the player.Cheat: Partial InvincibilityThis glitch is exploited in that, it will make you invincible to everything in the game that attacks you, and not to those enemies that grab you and cause you to instantly die, like marv and harry, and the hotel guy etc.Cheat: Partial InvincibilityTo gain this, you must find a room with a maid who throws pillows at you in the plaza hotel, and get your life all the way down to 1 cookie. Then, go into the room with the maid who throws the pillows, and stand right in front of the door, as soon as the pillow hits you, the very second (it makes a sound) you go through the door, you know you did it correctly when you will have no more cookies, but you will still be alive, now get hit by her again, and you will be at full life, and will no longer loose cookies when you are attacked.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3788</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588374-home-alone-2-lost-in-new-york</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/home-alone-2-lost-in-new-york_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/home-alone-2-lost-in-new-york/3030-7239/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ZrtQ67Y.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/6AkW8PJ.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/uycrMYv.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7fRP3b1.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/9cvExeT.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/UnLlyTG.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/VgSIr5M.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/RhQcp7s.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/XiFvJk3.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/NgdTcbY.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/WzLiO3I.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/XFgTRLb.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/d77Wu1y.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/DciZ3kB.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/NbsqScn.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/8zUjaGC.png</clearlogo1>
</game>