<Game>
	<Name>Home Improvement - Power Tool Pursuit! (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Home Improvement is a video game adaptation of the TV show featuring Tim Allen about a TV DIY showman and his family that aired between 1991-99 on ABC. It was released exclusively for the Super Nintendo and for the US market.When Tim "The Tool Man" Taylor is tasked by Binford Tool with demonstrating a new line of "Taylor-Turbo Power Tools," on his show Tool Time they are quickly stolen from the set before he can get his hands on them. Following a mysterious clue left behind with the empty crates he pursues the tools across the various sets of other TV shows being aired in the same studio. Eight ultra-powerful tools are at his disposal, with notable mentions being a nail gun, blowtorch, jackhammer and chainsaw. Tim's cohost Al and his children are also present to help rescue his tools and bring back justice to the Binford brand.Fun FactThe game was not packaged with a manual. Instead, loading screens read, "Real men do not use instructions."			</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Absolute Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>PlJmZBHFr3s</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1923</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588375-home-improvement</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/home-improvement-power-tool-pursuit</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/home-improvement-power-tool-pursuit/3030-512/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Home_Improvement:_Power_Tool_Pursuit!</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/IJUdYLh.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/z0b6kzF.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/oxieR1T.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lhjkB73.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ubcVSjN.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/yt3q1De.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/lplsVOr.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/kcGcfrY.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ar2ieUz.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/bYBmXn8.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/EgNpoAK.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vc9fs0L.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/VoTqEfn.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/iOjf9cm.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/JOHqN79.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Power Tool Pursuit! Handyman extraordinaire Tim Taylor has just received the greatest honor any real man could hope for: Binford has named its new line of Taylor-Turbo Power Tools after him! But before Tim can unveil these monuments to his masculinity, industrial spies pilfer the prototypes from the "Tool Time" set! Now Tim's grunting man, and he's out to track down the tool-swiping punks by himself! - The Heartiest Hardware! Use 8 unstoppable, ultra-macho tools! - The Weirdest, Wildest Worlds! Battle 22 types of special effects robots through 4 of the craziest TV studios ever! - The Gang's All Here! Al and the Taylor boys are on the scene to help Tim with his quest!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>F272FVmU9g0</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd4f3e93-0a3b-4d79-ac6b-6c4486c126f3.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/65417c5b-7f3a-4f23-8ad7-01266240f459.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/494be64c-d17a-44c3-9c0c-d1b547cd7e9f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0524608a-3efc-47db-86f9-f4466ec02dcb.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Absolute Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>