<Game>
	<Name>Honkakuha Igo - Gosei (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Honkakuha Igo: Gosei ("Real Go: Gosei", where Gosei is the name of a national Go competition in Japan, and also the title conferred to its winner) is a Go game for the Super Famicom developed by Aisystem Tokyo and published by Taito. As the name suggests, the AI in this game is competition level and is designed to improve the game of advanced players. There is also an option to play against a second human being.Like most games based on this board game, Honkakuha Igo was only released in Japan. It is unaffiliated with the Honkaku Mahjong series.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>Aisystem Tokyo</Developer>
	<VideoURL>rEzB4yz7y0Y</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581866-honkakuha-igo-gosei</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/honkakuha-igo-gosei/3030-50065/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/F1cyfqV.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/TgTRgDh.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/OM7XcIM.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/IW9YDw4.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/BrJluUc.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Notes>Honkakuha Igo: Gosei ("Real Go: Gosei", where Gosei is the name of a national Go competition in Japan, and also the title conferred to its winner) is a Go game for the Super Famicom developed by Aisystem Tokyo and published by Taito. As the name suggests, the AI in this game is competition level and is designed to improve the game of advanced players. There is also an option to play against a second human being. Like most games based on this board game, Honkakuha Igo was only released in Japan. It is unaffiliated with the Honkaku Mahjong series.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f416144a-122f-4e25-a009-1ab0fb0e64d9.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab15b223-4e73-487f-9151-d28eeb1e55cb.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7495ad52-c59b-48cc-9687-b4f767ed628a.png</snapshot6>
	<Publisher>Taito Corporation</Publisher>
</game>