<Game>
	<Name>Hook (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>In this video game adaption of the Steven Spielberg film Hook, the player takes the role of a grown-up Peter Pan, whose kids have been kidnapped by Captain Hook. Tinker Bell takes Peter back to Neverland where he must again become Pan and reclaim his children.This particular interpretation is a side-scrolling action game, in which players must hack their way past Hook's denizens through 11 levels.  These include forests, icy regions, and towns which Peter will have to jump, climb, and swim through. Magic items such as apples and pixie dust can be collected for special powers. When enemies are attacked, they simply put their hands up in surrender rather than dying, so as to make the game more child-friendly.Cheat: Walk through walls on the ice caveYou can easily advance through this level of the game by exploiting the walk through walls glitch.  Recharge your pan meter from the first Tinkerbell you find then return to the start of the stage and fly upward.  Pan will disappear and actually be in the ceiling.  From there you can just walk to the right and you will not be effected by walls or enemies.Cheat: 99 LivesFly into the spike filled cave in level 1. Once you see the 3-Up grab it and then allow yourself to die. Repeat this process until you get 99 lives.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>dLJNaINbxWc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3201</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588376-hook</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/hook</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hook/3030-23656/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/b0FHkKC.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/INhH2Zh.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/YWyrI4u.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/PpowNeS.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/PePw4MX.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/4dPfGon.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FUDEbBL.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/SRiuOE2.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/OTacS3e.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/GqDUk2f.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/CGinOMQ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6dlZGof.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/EDw72cA.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/yw3rdS7.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/hAYYZuQ.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DtQQTuB.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/5pDSOPE.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Your blood is pumping and a chill races down your spine. You've finally come face-to-face with the most infamous pirate of them all, Captain Hook, the fiend who's kidnapped your children and sworn never to let them go. As Peter Pan, this is the fight of your life. Everything that came before - you duel with Rufio, your battles against the pirates, even your soaring flights high above Neverland - are nothing compared to this moment.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8c925a1c-14db-4d8a-b141-a069518d6a48.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e60469f7-3627-4ff9-b3c4-df33998081ad.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5088acc7-3211-45f2-adff-39c6c6812530.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7883b0b8-6c24-467b-b677-70953b1b0848.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7eb6ec55-da60-44ac-89a4-6309f60526b8.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sony Imagesoft</Publisher>
</game>