<Game>
	<Name>Hyper V-Ball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Hyper V-Ball is a side-scrolling volleyball game that features a dozen different nations to choose from. It is the sequel to Super Volleyball, which was available on the Sega Genesis and NEC TurboGrafx-16, and this is reflected in its Japanese name, Super Volley II.The player can choose from twelve male teams and eight female teams. In addition, there is a "Hyper" league which includes eight teams comprised of robots and cyborgs which allows player to play a less realistic version of the sport. Each of the three categories has four empty spaces for player-edited teams as well.The male teams represent the following nations (those marked with an asterisk also have female teams):AlgeriaBrazil*CanadaChina*FranceGermany*Great Britain*ItalyJapan*Netherlands*Spain*United States*Critical ReceptionElectronic Gaming Monthly's Mike Weigand gave Hyper V-Ball a score of 7 out of 10. He wrote, "...This is the Super Baseball 2020 of the volleyball circuit. You can select either human or robotic players. This game did an excellent job of conveying the sport of volleyball on a video game format and is sure to delight sports fans. This is one of the best volleyball video games".				</plot>
	<releasedate>20/6/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>McO'River</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>FCGkAnTas4Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1983</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588380-hyper-v-ball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/hyper-v-ball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hyper-v-ball/3030-13138/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/GDgu5Yw.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/LuslyFt.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/4Z4B6D7.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/tcBLSjT.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/n0TdNCb.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/7RJYWrI.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/gmpAe3R.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/IpL9rk9.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/N1HkNvT.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/nh3PnCN.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/WHZ5T3P.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MelTy92.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Tmc0lsb.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/xSb9T1T.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/SeprbSm.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/U96ekeS.png</clearlogo1>
</game>