<Game>
	<Name>HyperZone (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:HyperZone plays like a cross between a racing game and shooter. The object of the game is to navigate each level while shooting enemies and earning points, until finally an encounter with a    boss ends each level. After enough points are acquired, the player earns an "extend" and his or her ship is upgraded in the next stage. The player's ship can receive up to six upgrades.  As a racing game, the resemblance is visual. The     mode 7 "tracks" bear a resemblance to the well-known progenitor of mode 7 racing,   F-Zero. As a rail shooter, in the same vein as  Star Fox, the player's ship is constantly pushed forward through each level. While it is possible to slow down, doing so eventually causes damage to the player's ship.  HyperZone contains eight levels in total. After the initial game is finished, it restarts from the beginning with the player continuing in the same ship and keeping score; the game loops infinitely.Cheat: 3D effectWhen the title screen has finished loading (the words Start and Normal are displayed), enter the code.  The title screen will turn red to confirm success.  During gameplay, press Select to toggle the effect on or off.Cheat: Unlockable shipsAfter you accumulate a certain amount of points in this game, you will gain a new ship (which you will pilot after the level switches).  You will also gain one stock (life) along with the ship (after you have got all the upgrades, you will no longer gain any stock).</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>HAL Laboratory, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>6noAegZx8vw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1984</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588381-hyperzone</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/hyperzone</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hyperzone/3030-889/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/So0F9oE.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/y85IurA.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Sv1FUIp.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/AwBIAIA.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/khnkeOD.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/V5Abeuz.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/cYwwOc0.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/c1G2Kz8.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RVdGJM2.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/EpHy346.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/es2bYsS.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/77YqmsN.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/jBrICJt.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Qt5bm8q.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/HhZnk7N.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4hJRYe3.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Fy139gU.png</clearlogo1>
</game>