<Game>
	<Name>Incantation (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Story:Incantation is a game with an incredibly simple story: Play as a young boy wizard to defeat some evil. Gameplay:The game is an action side-scroller set in a medieval fantasy world. The boy wizard you play as carries a large wand that has different projectiles based upon what power-ups you've picked up. The goal of each level is to find three golden feathers to then pass a gate and fight a boss, thus ending the level. Cheat: Cheat menuAt the title screen, press shoulder buttons R, L, L, R, R, R, L, L, L, L, up, down, up, down.  The screen blinks.  Start the game, and during gameplay press X to bring up the cheat menu.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Titus France SA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>xl3qsp-Qvso</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3792</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/915491-incantation</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/incantation</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/incantation/3030-450/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Bylnyme.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/KITxFzi.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/B2hq2Ku.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/J5VrjBp.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/IiGHOBD.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/6EWjCo1.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/bAj3D8A.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ZNz0s77.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/rLN4vmH.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/KcBVkfn.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/jsDikKr.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/EL6kTVn.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Eu255HA.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/2k1L596.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You live in a place of peace and harmony called the Magic Kingdom. The Magic Kingdom consists of seven worlds: the enchanted forest, mountains, swamps, cursed cliffs, and the palace of the evil wizard, Necroman. From the dawn of time, the peace within the seven worlds of the kingdom was controlled by a line of very good and very powerful magicians. It was one of these magicians who was chosen to inherit the power of his ancestors and thus became the guardian of the strange Book of Sorcery, which enabled him to hold absolute power in his hands. Alas, the peace of the kingdom was not to last as in the shadows, dark forces under the control of Necroman stole the Book of Sorcery and kidnapped the guardian magician. The kingdom fell under the control of the evil Necroman and from that day forward, green devils, wicked genies, and other demons have haunted the once beautiful and peaceful kingdom.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fbf3785b-a888-4a82-8875-7ad9ff2817a5.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8657a00b-ac7d-4980-84a7-658abe4bef1c.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a8fec170-46a1-4bb0-aff9-518e4b510c4d.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e1851b5e-88be-4da5-a6f0-733949cde80a.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/084ffa0f-1eb7-4793-bf36-c993e0734aea.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Titus Software</Publisher>
</game>