<Game>
	<Name>Indiana Jones' Greatest Adventures (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Indiana Jones' Greatest Adventures is a 1994 SNES action platformer that chronicles the three Indiana Jones films released at the time. The player, as  Dr. Henry "Indiana" Jones Jr., must progress through a series of stages inspired by the three movies via his fists, whip or with his pistol. The latter two must be found first before they can be used. The pistol is used to defeat enemies, while the whip can be used this way but can also be used as a grappling tool, for the platforming elements of the game.Indiana Jones' Greatest Adventures is inspired by JVC's earlier Super Star Wars series. The game makes special emphasis on the sound and look of the movies, with action that is fast-paced and Arcade-like.Story:The first level of the game takes place in South America, 1936, the setting of the introduction of Raiders of the Lost Ark. It takes Indy through the cavern fighting the tribe Rene Belloq sends after him. The player makes it to the idol and the next level starts where Indy has to outrun the giant boulder. The second level takes place trudging through the snow in Napal. The following level has Indy progressing to the top of the bar which in the game has multiple floors. He has to outrun the fire while the bar begins to disintegrate. Indy makes it to the top where he battles Toht and saves Marion, and obtain the medallion from Toht who escapes. Indy then has to go through Cairo and then the next level has him fighting a strongman on a barrel of hay in the back of a moving truck using only his fists. He then goes towards the Well of Souls and fight the Nazis who are invading Cairo. Indy progresses through a few more levels and ends the Raiders of the Lost Ark portion with a fight with Belloq who uses the Ark as his weapon.Cheat: Level Skip, Level Select and Game Over CodesEnter these codes while the game is paused on Controller 1.  You must unpause and pause again in order to enter a different code.  Please note that the codes will quit working if the game is reset.  Notes:Level Skip - after entering the code, you must pause the game then Press the B Button on Controller 1 to skip the current level.Level Select - after entering the code, you must get a Game Over and return to the Options screen to use the Level Select.  You can do this by losing all of your lives or by entering the Game Over code.Cheat: Level passwordsEnter these codes at the password screen to access the corresponding levels. The code symbols are Greek, but here is information on how they can be identified: Delta - triangle Phi - shaped like an oval intersected by a vertical line Sigma - appears like the letter ''E'' Psi - trident-shaped symbol Omega - looks like a set of earphones </plot>
	<releasedate>11/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>JVC Musical Industries, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>bf4Yxa6lSt0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1989</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588387-indiana-jones-greatest-adventures</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/indiana-jones-greatest-adventures</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/indiana-jones-greatest-adventures/3030-6329/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/5JZTF1w.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/hFHv1i1.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/iC8QrbX.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/wlEgyrm.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/xb07U2J.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/npczDeB.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/g0obDIm.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/dgK7Js4.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Igs1BnT.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/facU5XQ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/88CLI5o.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/0ZbtFfR.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/fhFh6Hl.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/7RqGnOs.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/u9rBEPS.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/4b3SKe9.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/HvlOfbW.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/CrfGoJz.png</clearlogo1>
</game>