<Game>
	<Name>Inindo - Way of the Ninja (USA)</Name>
	<plot>1581, Japan. Fearing a rebellion and striving to conquer the entire country,  the warlock Nobunaga orders to attack the Iga ninja clan. The ninjas bravely defend their village, but, being vastly outnumbered, are mercilessly slain by Nobunaga's men. Only one survived: you,  the hero of the game. Shortly before the assault you were sent to a nearby village to warn the elder of Nobunaga's attack. However, the other village is also destroyed by Nobunaga's army. You swear to avenge his crime. But for now, you are just an inexperienced young men, and are "wanted" by Nobunaga's men and ruthless bounty hunters. Will you be able to unite Japan in the ultimate struggle against Nobunaga?"Inindo: Way of the Ninja" is a console-style RPG with a touch of strategy. You navigate your hero on the world map, visit towns, and descend into dungeons. The battles are turn-based and are viewed from a third-person perspective, like in Final Fantasy games. You can move on the battle field and use melee or long-ranged attacks. You'll be able to recruit characters of various classes to your party, who will join you for profit or for other reasons. After you gain enough experience, you'll also be able to talk to daimyos (feudal rulers) of various castles and to convince them to work together against Nobunaga. You can also perform various tasks for the daimyos, such as spying.Cheat: Gain Money Without Passing TimeThis method is a lengthy, but otherwise practical way to earn money without having to fight in battles or performing tasks that all use game time. First off, you need a Healer Companion on your team (Like a Sage or Hermit), and they have to have the Special Skill(s) Cure 1 and/or Cure 2. Second, you have to be in a Castle/Village that sells Health Food and/or Energy Pills. All skills in this game do not use magic, making this moneymaking method very practical. With the Cure 1, you can convert Health Food (that costs 40) into Body Healer items (that costs 80) and with the Cure 2, you can convert Energy Pills to Energy Ups. Stock up on Health Food (Or Energy Pills if you have Cure 2), give them to your Healer, and use Cure 1 so that all Health Food turn into Body Healers. Once you have all converted Health Food to Body Healers, sell these Body Healers for 56 Gold, earning a 16 gold piece profit. Same thing with Energy Pills, convert with Cure 2, and sell the Energy Ups for profits. Repeat the Buy, Convert, and Sell process as many times as you need to so you have all the money you can ever have so you can buy strong weapons and items in a town.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/3/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>KOEI Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>IfjJEuNMApI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1990</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588388-inindo-way-of-the-ninja</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/inindo-way-of-the-ninja</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/inindo-way-of-the-ninja/3030-4729/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inindo:_Way_of_the_Ninja</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/PBNSp7W.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/iyxj2SM.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/xkafgVI.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Au6M2xe.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/fDtFCf7.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/DCJgzTn.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/SYbPlod.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/OGYtGX5.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/0qB7MwZ.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YAMZDra.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MuQbJj2.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2ULcL9l.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JYW743F.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/d9ACB6b.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/c3EOQEt.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/zpSYG0L.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You're a young ninja hungry for adventure and revenge. Travel on foot or by boat to famous training grounds where you will learn Ninjutsu, the secret art of stealth fighting! Use your trusty sword, throwing stars or even magic spells against vicious monsters inside Japan's treacherous dungeons. As spying and sabotage are your expertise, infiltrate castles to gather information and then set them ablaze! Soon, you'll be powerful enough to lead your own army against enemy warlords. In the end, you must seek revenge on Nobunaga, the powerful ruler who destroyed your home village in his ruthless quest to become Shogun. Times are tough, but remember, you are a ninja and anything is possible.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/01e552a4-8f7f-4521-8cdc-c07dc464c2ea.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ea7ccd1-eecd-4c1a-a0c3-272d935a2734.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c1295c65-5cba-449f-bd3c-1bd79cdf5338.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/538ae190-481c-4a4a-8f1b-2179571b5422.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
</game>