<Game>
	<Name>International Superstar Soccer (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:International Superstar Soccer (JP: Jikkyou World Soccer: Perfect Eleven) is a soccer game featuring international sides and is the first game in the series of the same name. It was released on the Super Famicom in late 1994 and on Super Nintendo in mid-1995. The game introduces the franchise's trademark view of the pitch, using a slightly askew angled view that nonetheless scrolls horizontally. It also uses realistic proportions for its athletes and focuses more on realism than many of its contemporaries.The game would be followed by International Superstar Soccer Deluxe the subsequent year. In Japan the game is a sequel, where it is known as Jikkyou World Soccer 2: Fighting Eleven, but is treated more of an enhanced edition of the original overseas. Many sequels would follow on the N64, PS1, Saturn and PS2. International Superstar Soccer and its sequels would later go on to influence Konami's later ISS Pro and PES (Pro Evolution Soccer) franchises.Cheat: CodesThe 2 codes will last until you turn off the SNES (you can reset it and the codes still will be working).Cheat: Special GameReach the end of the 2nd season on 1st place to play a game against the Super Star Team. If not, then you'll play a Championship game against whoever is in 1st place.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/6/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Konami (America), Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>Euuve4cruAU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3794</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588390-international-superstar-soccer</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/international-superstar-soccer__</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/international-superstar-soccer/3030-6106/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/1xM5s5i.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/phRBkxK.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/IQFdgRl.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Vwr32nG.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/WsA44lv.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/COPxptX.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/SHjUMTs.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/5kGH4gG.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/xf5lSm0.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/RrVQbW4.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/JL97u0g.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/U03IH0d.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/lXu7Wj1.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/11t2TWN.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/K1SqlNU.png</clearlogo1>
</game>