<Game>
	<Name>International Superstar Soccer Deluxe (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: ISS Deluxe, known as Jikkyou World Soccer 2: Fighting Eleven in Japan, was the 1995 follow-up to International Superstar Soccer. The game was released the same year as the original ISS and featured several incremental improvements including: Improved grpahicsAdditional commentaryTwo players (instead of one) were able to compete co-operatively against the computer AI.Teams Asia / AfricaEurope 1Europe 2Europe 3 Cameroon  Japan  Morocco  Nigeria  South Korea  Turkey England  Germany  Italy  Northern Ireland  Scotland  Wales   France  Holland  Ireland  Norway  Portugal  Spain  Austria  Belgium  Czech Republic Denmark  Poland  Sweden Europe 4North &amp; South AmericaAll Stars * Bulgaria Croatia Greece Romania Russia Switzerland Argentina Brazil Columbia Mexcio United States Uruguay African Stars All Star Americans All Stars Asian Stars Euro Stars A Euro Stars B  *secret unlockCheat: All Star TeamAt the title screen press R, Up, Down, L, X, B, Left, A, Right, Y, if you did it correctly you will hear a dog's bark. Note: You have to use the 2nd controller (1st doesn't work at all for this code)Cheat: Play last game vs World All Stars in International CupPlay last game vs World All Stars in International CupCheat: Extra skill pointsEnter edit players mode before the match and use all available skill points. Highlight the "Cancel" option and press Y for 200 additional skill points.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Konami (America), Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>6DLhCjqzZwc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3795</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588391-international-superstar-soccer-deluxe</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/international-superstar-soccer-deluxe</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/international-superstar-soccer-deluxe/3030-7025/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/V80FIEe.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/V7iVNNy.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/fpsnw9Z.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/1XedCL0.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/cAHx7P1.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/4WRJWXS.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lhiHxJd.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/7GzdRnK.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/dhB2Qx7.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/khLt2Js.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CscmfMP.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Z4TSTWX.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rBtHjTn.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ebpbFJH.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NNYvQJH.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/XilkNqw.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/WT1eACH.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/iUZHVCz.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/bRQA1u1.png</clearlogo1>
</game>