<Game>
	<Name>J.R.R. Tolkien's The Lord of the Rings - Volume One (Germany)</Name>
	<plot>Based on the book by J.R.R. Tolkien, Frodo Baggins is a young man from the Shire who receives a "ring". He must bring it to Rivendell, where no evil force can touch it! So get ready for some great sword-fighting, mystical action!Directions:You'll start your quest alone, but along the way, you'll get companions to help, but they can die real easily, so be sure to hold those L or R buttons! There are many monsters to prevent Frodo from getting to Rivendell, but just keep trying! You'll be doing things like searching for an item or looking for a character or monster! By pushing L and R together at the same time, you get a password so you can return to a part of the game where you left off.Controls:A Button - Use equipped itemB Button - Block enemy attacksX Button - Status screenY Button - Attack with weaponL Button - Hold to control companionsR Button - Hold to control companionsStart Button - Pause/UnpauseSelect Button - Bring up menuTips:Character selectionEnter the following passwordL22M22, YK5K14, J4T4B5, N8WBCW. Then press start then delete the code and press start to get all characters.Start game with all Characters, Rings, and GemsF82G2O 3K5G2O G2T02W W4W... BX7995 CY9J91 PMYCZR 7SYH9DStart the game with all itemsLQWLQW LQWLQWhttp://www.consoleclassix.com/snes/lord_of_rings_volume_1.html</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Interplay</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>2.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>emEkdxq5aBA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3215</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588449-jrr-tolkiens-the-lord-of-the-rings-volume-1</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/jrr-tolkiens-lord-of-the-rings-volume-one</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/j-r-r-tolkien-s-lord-of-the-rings-volume-one/3030-8815/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/oxi5jQI.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/FcTuT4w.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/plgjE8o.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Y0dyfZL.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/10eubIL.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/PXeAfDX.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/upzvWv8.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/rAizuSd.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Y7Na4ud.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vL1Jyrk.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/7qsSJVf.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/qSWNwCD.jpg</snapshot9>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/O1Xtjlo.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/VFa6N6Y.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/tJDGfrz.png</clearlogo1>
</game>