<Game>
	<Name>Jack Nicklaus Golf (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Jack Nicklaus Golf is a golf sim developed in 1992 for the SNES and Game Boy Nintendo platforms. It is named for and features the likeness of prodigious professional golfer Jack Nicklaus, and frequently references his nickname "the Golden Bear" in the game.The game has a lot of customization options and two 18-hole courses. The player can create their own course by selecting holes from either course in any order. The player can also select to practice by either choosing a hole to try out, a putting green on which to practice putting or a driving range to get used to the swing controls.Before each hole, Jack Nicklaus dispenses some advice. It can be related to the hole, or just a useful tip in general. </plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Sculptured Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>3799</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588394-jack-nicklaus-golf</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/jack-nicklaus-golf/3030-31021/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/QYGB33n.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/STx6dLt.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/soVjnoY.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/d1wOgDQ.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FuWii2Z.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/PwLZ6Nf.jpg</snapshot4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/U8zLWDS.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/dU5qt0W.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The biggest name in golf brings you the most realistic and feature-backed golf simulation ever! Play eighteen holes on two of Jack Nicklaus' favorite courses or design an unlimited number of courses to play. One to four players can compete on beginner and expert levels, choosing between Skins Play and the very competitive Stroke Play. You control every detail of the action: read the break of the green for your approach shots; play a long iron out of the fairway bunkers; chip or putt it in from the fringe; practice your short game on the green - or just hit a bucket of balls out on the driving range. The password feature even lets your take a break at the turn. If you're ready to play against the best, Jack Nicklaus is your man - and  JACK NICKLAUS GOLF is your game!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9a025584-0439-428a-b33a-6dc5b0e0cdb8.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c5f69286-0213-407d-9581-b286100f18ed.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4d27478e-72a8-4fdf-9564-ce37694e08ac.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/839fb538-d954-4600-bb77-030236509143.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/17f0c66f-7887-476d-b5ff-e48df80294c4.png</snapshot6>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Tradewest</Publisher>
</game>