<Game>
	<Name>Jeopardy! - Sports Edition (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This version of Jeopardy! focuses more on sports related themes with 700 different categories and 3,500 questions to answer related to sports such as baseball, football, hockey, etc., along with many other sub-categories such as players, sports equipment and the like.The rules are still the same as the others, there are three rounds where the player buzzes in to answer and spells out the answers using the D-pad.  It features digitized photography of sports-themed clad contestants such as baseball, football, volleyball and the like along with authentic digitized studio surroundings and the likeness and voice of long time Jeopardy! host, Alex Trebek.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>GameTek, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3804</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588400-jeopardy-sports-edition</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/jeopardy-sports-edition</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/jeopardy-sports-edition/3030-23740/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XUMe6ag.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/clJYepM.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/7odYQ4T.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/KAECz3T.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/T6G4KaY.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/syFPPtx.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/wOLZV1J.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/uWzrhvv.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/hYqGQU7.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JjH8N3H.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/s5uWqJC.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/GDOgf3y.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ZGyJQaa.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/AmglppC.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Listen up sports fans! Here's your chance to prove that armchair athletes have the most fun. If you're a sports trivia buff, or you just love the challenge of a good contest, then this edition of Jeopardy! is just for you. Delve into past and current trivia in Baseball, Basketball, Football and Hockey or explore categories like Bowl Games, Boxing, Coaches, College Standouts, Equipment, Golf Greats, Horse Racing, Olympic Events, Pitchers, Players, Rookies and Rules. The Sports Edition of Jeopardy! is a whole new ball game! With over 3,500 questions in sports-related categories, Jeopardy! Sports Edition will challenge your brain cells and leave you cheering. This new edition of Jeopardy! contains a variety of sports contestants, photography of Jeopardy's set and Alex Trebek's digitized voice. It's a truly authentic Jeopardy! experience. Take the Jeopardy! challenge today.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/96dcf189-e364-46c8-84af-9e0fa4f1b1ab.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e90bcbdf-8d2c-454a-8153-b9072b776b3f.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a43440e5-382f-4f90-9a92-b16398b857e8.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/21dcf4fc-fc96-4513-a656-fbb7953e74d1.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>GameTek</Publisher>
</game>