<Game>
	<Name>Jikkyou Powerful Pro Yakyuu 3 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: Jikkyou Powerful Pro Yakyuu 3 is the third major game in the Powerful Pro series. This game was released on February 29, 1996 for the Super Famicom only in Japan by Konami. The game was developed by Diamond Head, a developer behind many Jikkyou Powerful Pro games. Powerful Pro 3 is a traditional baseball simulator, in the "super deformed" or "chibi" style that makes the franchise well-known.  The game is fairly similar to its predecessors, Jikkyou Powerful Pro Yakyuu '94 and Jikkyou Powerful Pro Yakyuu 2, although it does add some new features, such as Success Mode. Success Mode is an RPG-esque mode where players develop a baseball player, guiding them through situations and forming them into a "powerful pro." Gameplay:  Pitching and batting are done from the same angle.     At its core, Powerful Pro 3 is a traditional baseball simulator. There are a variety of modes to play in, allowing players to either play versus a second player, a computer, or pit two computers against each other. Players control pitching, batting, and fielding, as well as some organization due to the wealth of customization options.  During pitching, players can move the directional pad to influence the throw. It must stay within a box to be a strike, as throwing outside of the box makes it a ball. During batting, players can either bunt or swing, controlling the location where the batter swings. In fielding, players control a single player at a time, switching manually or automatically (depending on the location of the ball).  Yakyuu 3 introduced "Success Mode."     There are several other modes than the traditional baseball modes. Players can practice batting, pitching, fielding, and play practice games. There is a wide variety of customization options, particularly in terms of players and teams.   The real draw of the Powerful Pro series is the Success Mode, which was started with this game. It puts the player in control of a pre-made character who the player must develop into a powerful athlete. This is done by guiding the player through situations, making decisions, etc. As a more "role-playing game"-esque part of the game, this actually provides players with multiple save slots and options.    </plot>
	<releasedate>29/2/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Diamond Head</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>o9r37qauH_o</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>24737</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571429-jikkyou-powerful-pro-yakyuu-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/jikkyou-powerful-pro-yakyuu-3/3030-25267/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/kEeS4gh.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/e1KelL7.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Px9fKHm.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/NbBdPFG.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/kvhmNTy.jpg</snapshot3>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/TpHnYh9.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The third iteration in the main Power Pro series for the Super Nintendo. This game retains the gameplay of its predecessors, and adds the Success Mode.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e4c8125e-f600-4531-ab7d-f6d1d84fc822.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9ff2c1f-d77b-4a6c-a4f5-e8a25b4a303e.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6af86504-ed5f-42c3-beab-a1b426b755af.png</snapshot4>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami Corporation</Publisher>
</game>