<Game>
	<Name>Jim Power - The Lost Dimension in 3D (Europe) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Jim Power: The Lost Dimension in 3D is a sci-fi action game from French company Loriciels and is a sequel/remake to their earlier Jim Powers in Mutant Planet. Major updates were made to the game, including more gameplay modes and a graphical facelift. The game also makes ample use of parallax scrolling, creating a lot of visually intense stages.Loriciels developed the game in part to be an homage/spiritual successor to Factor 5's Turrican series. They even brought on the original composer for Turrican: Chris H&#252;lsbeck.Jim Power: The Lost Dimension in 3D was developed for the SNES and PC-DOS. A Genesis version (called Jim Power: The Arcade Game) was planned but ultimately canceled.Cheat: Bonus CodesWhen you begin a game, find a place safe from enemy attacks and then press X, A, B, Y, A, B, Y, X, B, Y, X, A, Y, X, A and B on Controller 2. You should hear a tone. Now press these buttons on Controller 2 to get the respective bonus:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Loriciel SA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>8tN_TPTIrYs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1994</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588402-jim-power-lost-dimension-in-3d</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/jim-power-the-lost-dimension-in-3d</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/jim-power-the-lost-dimension-in-3d/3030-9095/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Mz7oPjf.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/o2hTCGw.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/FjI7TN5.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/EKs6oS5.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/4Hik4kG.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/dAmm4DY.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/QsH9bu2.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/zxP9L3Y.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/UjLwAQU.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/JDfocOs.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/0TEXwBT.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/UdX5SWV.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/H1f9KKV.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/lk2YPNI.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>"JIm Power: The Lost Dimension in 3-D" utilizes the revolutionary NUOPTIX 3D graphics, allowing you to experience the thrill of virtual reality without a virtual reality system. 3D glasses facilitate the incredible depth experience, but the thrill and the horror of "The Lost Dimension" may be fully experienced with or without 3-D glasses. Special Agent Jim Power-The supernatural alien, Vaprak, threatens to defeat our world which is the last planet that stands between him and a dimensional vortex. This vortex leads to a fifth and, up until now, lost dimension. If he succeeds in defeating us, he will destroy our world, opening a gateway for his kind as well as the strange mutating effect that this dimension has on all organic life forms. His forces are far too strong for us to defeat in a frontal attack which is why we must send you to slip past his Omni-eye scanners and make an assassination attempt on the greatest evil that man has ever known. It will take absolutely all of your wits and skill but it is imperative you reach his fortress and send him back to the sulphurous plane from whence he came.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e99808d-b073-46ed-a446-c32112fb0505.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5539677f-f78d-4a65-869d-d2df4f1d42d3.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d6e357e2-559d-4842-b8f1-210f1b359023.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3b0bd69f-732d-496f-83cf-288b18ae30a0.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Electro Brain</Publisher>
</game>