<Game>
	<Name>Jimmy Connors Pro Tennis Tour (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Jimmy Connors Pro Tennis Tour is a competitive tennis game featuring Jimmy Connors. European developer Blue Byte created several versions of the game originally for home systems before acquiring the Jimmy Connors license for its Super Nintendo incarnation. Previously, it was known as Great Courts and Pro Tennis Tour. Play single matches or full tournaments on multiple court types in singles or doubles. There are several playable tennis athletes to choose from with different strengths, though all are fictional save for Jimmy Connors himself. The game allows the player to choose an "easy type" control system which takes over the playable athlete's movement, so that the player can focus solely on aiming and powering their swings.				</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Simulation, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Ubi Soft Entertainment Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>1995</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588403-jimmy-connors-pro-tennis-tour</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/jimmy-connors-pro-tennis-tour</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/jimmy-connors-pro-tennis-tour/3030-5740/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XaWnaMB.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/2HgewiW.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Eg8reYP.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/RIJE86q.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/7JKmcmk.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/E5izmbL.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/8KFO1mf.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/2czvkZx.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/s2ZT9uJ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/lj3rOQ8.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/mnZls73.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/TelTiP4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/RqGUV13.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/SfKBMaQ.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/0n9y32X.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/X3IGfE7.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Jimmy Connors, ranked Number 1 for 159 weeks, holder of EIGHT Grand Slam titles and a record 109 single titles - more than any other male player in history - is the GREATEST tennis champion ever! Now YOU'RE Jimmy Connors, battling your way to the Number 1 spot. Past sixteen professional opponents. On center court of the most prestigious tournaments on the world circuit. Put a topspin on your serve and smash it past your opponent. Ace! Learn the strengths and weaknesses of each player as you climb the ranks to the top. Work with five professional coaches to hone your shots - lob, volley, forehand, backhand, net, and serve. Play one or two player against one, two, or three computer opponents. Realistic graphics and awesome sound. This is professional tennis at its very best!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ef8847fe-4833-4fa1-b322-c10a9d162459.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/db7a5f3f-43c7-4172-9d3d-c725274c792a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/88b409f4-42b3-4ea5-84b9-05ec366e4abd.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/81a487b9-6b1f-411f-bc0c-f027aee1242e.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>