<Game>
	<Name>Joe & Mac (USA)</Name>
	<plot>So has this ever happened to you? You're sitting there with your bud, and you just got finished with a dinosaur demolition derby (Tyrannasaurus Wrecks), and a bunch of Neandrithals storm into your village and scare away all the cave babes. No?! Well, that's what happened with our pre-historic heroes, Joe and Mac. Now they have to run our pre-history and save the beautiful cave babes.Joe and Mac is a fun game with excellent graphics that keep you chuckling and a sound track that fits the game's zany nature. This game is fun and humorous, so have fun, Gamer.Directions:Joe and Mac is a beat-em-up / platformer that takes place in the Stone Age. Start out in the "level select" area which is much like Super Mario 3. Run to the grey circles to save your progress and the red circles to play the level.Run around each level beating up on Neandrithals and little dinosaurs. Your health is marked on the upper left hand corner of the screen and can be increased by food that can be found along your way or dropped by the bad guys.Use your club and other weapons you find along the way that you can throw, such as bones, fire, and boomerangs. Fight your way through each level to get to the boss, a huge dinosaur like a T-Rex or Pterodactyl, and save a cave babe. Save all the cave babes and you win!Just for you people that don't like playing alone, team up with a friend and play two player mode. Play as both Joe and Mac, although there is no difference in the way either of them play, and save the babes together. Good Luck, Cave Man, and go get your girls back. Controls:A Button - JUMPB Button - JUMPX Button - ATTACKY Button - ATTACKStart Button - PAUSESelect Button - SWITCH SUB-WEAPONTips:Replay levelTo replay a level that you have already beaten, simply go to that level on the map and press START, SELECT!Extra livesTo get extra lives, simply play those levels that have them again. Once you've collected them, press START, SELECT to return back to the world map. Repeat as required!Bonus levelsKill all the small dinosaurs before cracking the red egg in the middle of level 8. A bonus level will begin where your weapon may be powered up. The bonus level also contains a key that allows entry to the blue dots on the map. Another red egg that leads to a bonus level is at the beginning of level 9.Continue at dinosaur in last levelIf you lose a life inside the dinosaur, select 'Yes' to continue. The map with the last continue location willappear. Begin game play at that location, then press Start, Select. The game will resume inside the dinosaur.Reviewer: grimjockeyhttp://www.consoleclassix.com/snes/joe_mac.htmlCheat: Sound testOn the title screen, move the cursor to Option.  On controller 2, hold d-pad right and L shoulder button.  On controller 1, hold d-pad left, R shoulder button, and press Start.Cheat: Alternate ending sequenceWhen the text Sound Creator Atomic Hanada scrolls into view during the ending, hold X + A + L + R shoulder buttons, and keep those buttons held to change the final cutscene of Joe and Mac being chased off the screen.Cheat: Alternate ending sequenceTo get extra lives, simply play those levels that have them again. Once you've collected them, press START, SELECT to return back to the world map. Repeat as required!Cheat: Alternate ending sequenceTo replay a level that you have already beaten, simply go to that level on the map and press START, SELECT!</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Data East</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>7.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>VnnhNPQZ-iA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>17855</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588405-joe-and-mac</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/L4cBTLd.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/WmJcKin.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/FzP0Y4i.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/cjlIDmU.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Dxj3JEn.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/4qzrjxS.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/aaF3prB.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/MhSEulQ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/uY5H6G7.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/g9RcCS9.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/uU8tvFy.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/b6VgtYE.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/HclFdqh.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/tX3FJIx.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UVRL0GV.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/GaITwey.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Back in the distant past (way back - like when “rock and roll” was just rock and fast food was dinner you couldn’t catch), lived two cave dudes named Joe and Mac.  Whether it was dinosaur demolition or pterodactyl hang-glidin’, life for the boys was pretty cool. Cool, that is, until a bogus bunch of neanderthal nerds crashed their village and scared off all the cave-babes.  Now the cave-babes are out there - SOMEWHERE, lost and reeeeally lonely… so what are you waitin’ for?  It’s up to Joe and Mac to get ‘em back. * Fight flying pterodactyls in one or two-player simultaneous play. * 12 cliff-hangin’ levels with more than 6 bonus levels to find… * Amazing arcade graphics will keep you clubbin’ to find your babes… * Joe &amp; Mac’s pre-hysterical escapades will keep you comin’ back for more!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8afa1b10-0877-42ca-90d6-f6c4756e5c7d.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a808c25c-f891-4ebf-9d69-720f22bb48e6.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/80b232f5-7536-4d8a-bd76-4b40ffa9e608.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ef9927c-f7d4-4109-a561-72541cb886a8.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/46869275-fbfc-4ee3-8eef-4873c98251ec.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6a3564f9-67e2-4c40-bd02-2446fd9b73d6.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9d7aa91-4d90-4d90-98e7-843c59546e59.png</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/13d7c1e3-ea5b-4fd1-a89a-5f22078eb6ac.png</snapshot15>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Data East</Publisher>
</game>