<Game>
	<Name>John Madden Football '93 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Another update in the Madden football series. New this time are some graphics and animations, including an animated coin toss and some player moves. New gameplay features are no-huddle offense and a stop clock play.There are 28 teams from the '92-'93 season, two All Madden teams and 8 Greatest Ever teams.Game modes are the usual pre-season, regular season, sudden death and playoffs. A special playoff mode for the 8 greatest teams is also available.The Genesis version features John Madden's digitized commentary speech and a battery-backed RAM for saving playoff results and player stats.Cheat: Easy defenseTake control of your fastest defender and line him up directly in between the offense's guard and center, but a hair above where they are standing. If done correctly, you will not be called offsides when the play begins. The line of scrimmage in Madden 93 is parallel to the feet of the offensive lineman as opposed to the ball, which is why you're able to line up so close to the offense in the first place.Cheat: Easy defenseWhen the ball is snapped, you'll usually have plenty of time to blast your defender through the line untouched, and you'll be able to stop virtually every play in the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>AQX-g0FR-OE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3810</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588455-john-madden-football-93</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/john-madden-football-93</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/john-madden-football-93/3030-4511/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/NOxV18g.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ncUvkj5.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/vKrwaNx.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/S2TphAT.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/OWAgebu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/rSv25F3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/vsBNCes.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/cPeRWxW.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/mJJAQVt.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/texbAY2.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/kXsEamT.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/MW5CzZu.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/paCJCES.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/GZuqpMc.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/E9yj67p.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Football's greatest lineup ever! Now with 38 Pro Teams! Faster Gameplay and Smoother Graphics! Now Faster than a Safety Blitz! Pressure the defense with a "No Huddle" offense. Beat em' to the line with split screen play calling. Which four-time champion will dominate?</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6b23cd8e-05a9-4f4a-b7db-4bdf0c2458d1.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f266b1b1-30e6-45c9-a801-83f08ebf96fc.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/121a5575-3b1f-4017-83ad-ecc6fb6ce5c1.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1241cb5a-dca0-4a5e-a7d9-af40b1137cf4.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b2e14313-60dd-4352-83de-af49494b3054.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/999768b7-d3e7-4c1b-ad6e-3bab6a85c656.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>