<Game>
	<Name>John Madden Football (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: John Madden Football was developed after EA saw how well Earl Weaver Baseball did a few years before. The game was the first in the long-running Madden NFL franchise. The game featured John Madden on the cover however the franchise started featuring NFL athletes on the cover in 2000 on the cover of Madden NFL 2001.John Madden Football is also the only Madden game to release on the Commodore 64 and Apple II. Features:No Real Teams Although the Madden games are now known for their up-to-date rosters of real NFL teams and players, John Madden Football does not include actual NFL teams or players because no NFL or NFLPA licenses existed for the franchise at the time. There are, however, teams that are based off of actual NFL teams.No Season PlayReal teams aren't the only difference between this version of Madden and latter day versions; there is also no season play in John Madden Football. The only mode of play is single games. Create-A-TeamThe game has a "blank" team that the player can create from scratch and either play as them or let the computer take over. It's possible to change player numbers, names, positions, and ratings.Field ConditionsThe game has four different field conditions options: hot, rain, snow, or cold and windy. Quarter LengthThere are four different quarter length options: 8, 10, 12, or 15 minute quarters. Playbook CreatorAlthough the game comes with two playbooks, one for offense and one for defense, there is a play creator for anybody to create their own.Save SystemPlayers can save their games at any time using a separate disk.Other OptionsThe game featured other options that disabled fatigue, penalties, injuries, cross-hair passing, or the 30 second clock. Cheat: Easy defenseTake control of your fastest defender and line him up directly in between the offense's guard and center, but a hair above where they are standing. If done correctly, you will not be called offsides when the play begins. The line of scrimmage in Madden 92 is parallel to the feet of the offensive lineman as opposed to the ball, which is why you're able to line up so close to the offense in the first place.Cheat: Easy defenseWhen the ball is snapped, you'll usually have plenty of time to blast your defender through the line untouched, and you'll be able to stop virtually every play in the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>kYgmmnzoVjU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2839</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588454-john-madden-football</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/john-madden-football_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/john-madden-football/3030-1234/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/YUEtJJY.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/n87B54r.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/0bCsj5Z.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/LO9Dc2f.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/LpqCx8J.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wRBzRg8.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/49OpuVO.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/lblq0sc.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/PYBsc4R.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BYqiGvM.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/uLYvIUS.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/rdUcQhN.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ih43ctj.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/2VM1GuO.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/jBvMLch.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>"Football is a game of one-on-one matchups. Real guys going at it. Win the matchups, win the game. That's what my game is all about." Call over 100 real pro plays from John Madden's playbook. If you don't like what you see, call an audible. Analyze big plays and blown assignments with instant replays. Feel the heat! First and long on your own 15 - and it's a mud bowl. IsoVision helps you spot the open receiver.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/12269314-059a-4253-aa8c-4f1dae7f31a0.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3aa8fa70-6617-4cd1-9286-41e73dacd3b0.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9ca72cc6-f0a5-4e13-abc3-dfd040d8e19b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/552c52a3-c5e0-48b7-9113-4ff4f55992a8.png</snapshot12>
	<rating>1</rating>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>