<Game>
	<Name>Justice League Task Force (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Justice League Task Force was a 2D fighting game, very similar to the Street Fighter series. It was actually the last game Blizzard developed that was not part of one of its three big franchises: Warcraft, Starcraft, and Diablo.In Story Mode you can play as one of the six heroes: Wonder Woman, Flash, Aquaman, Superman, Batman and Green Arrow. In Battle Mode and VS Mode beside the heroes, the three villains Cheetah, Despero and Darkseid, also are playable.Story:The story begins with an attack on Earth by Darkseid that destroys a military base. Your chosen hero sets out to find information and gather the Justice League, only to be attacked by each hero in their respective locations. Your hero finds out that these are not the true Justice League members, and then goes to find Despero and Cheetah. After they are defeated they lead the hero to Darkseid, who has captured the rest of the team, and he forces them to fight an android replica of themselves. They then face Darkseid himself. After he is defeated, the rest of the League is freed and the military base is restored.			</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>I6pNBZq9V0g</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1998</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588412-justice-league-task-force</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/justice-league-task-force</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/justice-league-task-force/3030-16349/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/CvbvuAF.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ueziyPL.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/1sDJZsH.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/EnKXRqg.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ztOHEsf.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/TRQopMD.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/mG2g9hD.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/svoR1Z4.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4ojaEIR.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/fPxsxSo.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/3GX0ZSK.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/lj0E54S.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/SJNmdrZ.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/JHjaamH.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/LcmrGTa.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/O23pzGJ.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/iSGCQ4B.jpg</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>Batman vs. Superman! Wonder Woman vs. The Flash! Aquaman vs. Green Arrow! Are you reading this right? For the first time ever, the DC super heroes battle head-to-head! Become your favorite Justice League super hero or choose evil villains Darkseid, Cheetah, or Despero! Pit your hero's special powers and awesome signature moves against any character you choose... even Superman vs. Superman! Battle from the ends of the earth to Metropolis, Gotham City, Apokolips and more! Incredible, pulse-pounding one-on-one fighting action and super sound FX put this game in a league of its own!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/539224d7-32f1-4031-85ce-da5ec22ba754.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0cc0f8a1-7dec-4df4-bd89-c511e1fc7563.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c9b47f9-6413-4958-9225-e4df05c6cde9.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aca05018-1de4-4a5b-a25e-bc7b2d326eea.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a8f66b42-9484-48b8-868c-850f93719269.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>