<Game>
	<Name>Kaite Tsukutte Asoberu Dezaemon (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dezaemon, or Kaite Tsukutte Asoberu ("Draw, Make, Ready to Play") Dezaemon is a shoot 'em up construction kit from Athena. It allows players to draw their own ships, including additional frames of animation for moving right and left, as well as creating enemies and bosses, customizing weapon types and other elements. The game comes with a built-in "demo" project: Daioh Gale, a pseudo-sequel to Athena's 1983 Arcade game Daioh.Dezaemon is a rebuilt version of Athena's original 1991 Famicom game Game Designer Yusei Soft: Dezaemon. This version of Dezaemon would later see an enhanced PlayStation edition named Dezaemon Plus in 1996, which in 2010 became the first Dezaemon game available in the US when it was added to the US PSN store.Cheat: Font SelectHold A button then turn the power on to access the font select screen. Holding A, use left or right direction keys to select font.Cheat: Font SelectAt the edit screen of the music editor, move the cursor to the song select number and holding Select, press B to change BGM. This will allow access to the hidden tunes #33 - #51.Cheat: Font SelectAt the option screen of either the sample game or a user created game, move the cursor to the difficulty select and holding Select, press down to access "Difficult"</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Side Scroller</genre>
	<Developer>Athena</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>xDPkqpygCl8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3551</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/574821-dezaemon</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kaite-tsukutte-asoberu-dezaemon/3030-28296/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/QTsMmMg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/zSWWK6T.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/cs4HopL.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Ja1BMvZ.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/G888Hwy.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Jl1pEvz.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/eCsTzjf.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/eKfGWtU.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/mwgXjbn.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/JQgJWVW.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/lL7QmWS.jpg</snapshot8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/e5FcTM1.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/SsXagqj.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Japan-only shooter construction kit for the Super Famicom system. Use a simple, icon-based menu system to execute commands. A paint program-style sprite editor lets you design your own friendly and enemy avatars from scratch and give them specific properties. You can also design your own title screen and use a BGM studio editor to compose music for use in the game. Music input is handled via instrument icons that can be assigned to music sheets. Dezaemon includes a sample shooting game called DAIOH.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>xDPkqpygCl8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/87239e2d-67bb-4fd1-b446-23fa4e51eb4f.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f819363d-7dbe-46fe-9c44-e2642dc4ce1d.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Athena</Publisher>
</game>