<Game>
	<Name>Kamaitachi no Yoru (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Kamaitachi no Yoru is an Adventure game, published by ChunSoft,which was released in Japan in 1994.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>ChunSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581932-kamaitachi-no-yoru</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/kamaitachi-no-yoru</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/banshee-s-last-cry/3030-28241/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/eGqp1U7.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/RCgsCdA.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/uAqeltt.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/7zpqWzv.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/z9FZfke.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Lr5RtwZ.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vswz7Fu.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6vtI9n1.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/De7GD1M.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The second sound novel created by Chunsoft after the release of Otogirisou. Like most visual novels, the gameplay involves the player reading the text from the game screen, and making decisions which will affect the path and outcome of the narrative. The choices and consequences form a big part of the gameplay, with the narrative often branching out in completely different directions depending on what choices the player makes, with even seemingly minor decisions having a big impact on how the narrative unfolds. In total, the game has over forty different endings. The game follows a psychological horror narrative that revolves around Toru and his girlfriend Mari, who are suddenly drawn into a horrible murder mystery while on vacation at a skiing lodge. The story unfolds as the characters attempt to solve the mystery. Additional murders occur if the player is unable to find clues, and the story culminates in a number of endings befitting a horror tale.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/10680e44-5d73-4ea9-a8bb-f9242332b505.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8e5f0bab-0bba-466e-b565-94339f7f5525.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Chunsoft</Publisher>
</game>