<Game>
	<Name>Kawasaki Superbike Challenge (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Kawasaki Superbike Challenge is a motorcycle racing game that uses the same engine as F1. It includes 14 standard-length race tracks, plus the Suzuka 8 Hours endurance race, available in both training and Championship modes. The game is unlicensed (except by Kawasaki), so all riders and teams are fictional.The game now has more polygonal roadside objects than F1, and there is still a Turbo mode, allowing for faster racing at the expense of some of the detail. You have the ability to turn on or off weather (during rainy days the graphics are darker and the bike has less traction). The number of laps on each course can be 5, 10 or 15, and there are 4 skill levels. Some changes have been made to how the vehicle handles, to emphasize the switch from cars to bikes.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Time Warner Interactive, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>3820</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588415-kawasaki-superbike-challenge</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/kawasaki-superbike-challenge</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kawasaki-superbike-challenge/3030-1348/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/yWFTbKL.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/EedXJ9a.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/UhbNbxk.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/knuaMSs.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/laeAGJt.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/OE512NJ.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/iWbos7K.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/PYNco26.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/k1BXLub.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/thf7X8i.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/gdSuHth.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/RX4kID0.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/VJJiurU.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/uy9nmpj.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/DthXHxF.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Get ready for the biggest adrenaline rush of your life - Kawasaki SuperBike Challenge! Straddle real, high-powered Kawasaki motorcycles, then bury the throttle, lay low on the seat and scream. This game provides superior graphics, sound, speed and handling. Choose from 15 circuits, including the Suzuka 8-hour Endurance Race. Experience realistic motorcycle racing with weather changes which affect performance and tire wear. Kawasaki SuperBike Challenge is motorcycle racing at its fastest!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dae37da6-6ca1-4931-8218-8c6a950faa7a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5069bbf0-a601-475d-bbea-f55fea7ae9d2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e3055380-d76d-451f-af7a-98b92f8ce366.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/50e66e01-b5e6-46d4-bbbe-463b486d28c3.png</snapshot12>
	<rating>4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Time Warner Interactive</Publisher>
</game>