<Game>
	<Name>Kawa no Nushi Tsuri 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Kawa no Nushi Tsuri 2 ("Fishing the River Master 2") is a Japan-exclusive fishing RPG from Natsume and the third game in their long-running Nushi Tsuri/River King franchise. Like its predecessor, released on the Famicom in 1990, the game crosses fishing game elements such as finding bait and ideal fishing spots with RPG elements such as fighting wildlife in turn-based battles and growing more experienced over time. Cash and XP earned while fishing or roaming around contribute to the player's angling ability.The player can select one of four family members, a trademark of the series. Each character has slightly different goals, but they usually culminate in becoming a strong enough fisherperson to catch "the River King": a legendary freshwater fish.Though the game is labelled as Kawa no Nushi Tsuri 2, the second game in the series was actually the 1992 game Kawa no Nushi Tsuri: Shizenha for the PC Engine.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/4/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Pack-In-Video</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571280-kawa-no-nushi-tsuri-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kawa-no-nushi-tsuri-2/3030-28246/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Verpq6W.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/1w36jHK.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/5WvafPg.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/pSEcDMT.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/I6ib7qW.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Notes>Kawa no Nushi Tsuri 2 ("Fishing the River Master 2") is a Japan-exclusive fishing RPG from Natsume and the third game in their long-running Nushi Tsuri/River King franchise. Like its predecessor, released on the Famicom in 1990, the game crosses fishing game elements such as finding bait and ideal fishing spots with RPG elements such as fighting wildlife in turn-based battles and growing more experienced over time. Cash and XP earned while fishing or roaming around contribute to the player's angling ability. The player can select one of four family members, a trademark of the series. Each character has slightly different goals, but they usually culminate in becoming a strong enough fisherperson to catch "the River King": a legendary freshwater fish. Though the game is labelled as Kawa no Nushi Tsuri 2, the second game in the series was actually the 1992 game Kawa no Nushi Tsuri: Shizenha for the PC Engine.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/21c3f24d-dfc6-4257-8924-b1abf62b8396.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/46483bb7-96eb-4fa9-a24c-6c759ab2d80a.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<Publisher>Pack-In-Video Co</Publisher>
</game>