<Game>
	<Name>Ken Griffey Jr.'s Winning Run (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Ken Griffey Jr.'s Winning Run is a licensed arcade baseball  game featuring MLB's own Ken Griffey Jr. Released in 1996, it contains all 28 MLB teams and logos from that time, with rosters containing fictitious names for the players (Ken Griffey Jr being the only real player in the game).Next to exhibition games, there are different game modes to compete in. In the MLB Challenge, players start with a weak team and go against every major MLB club to go up the rankings. There is also a complete World Series, All-Star games and the MLB League. In the league modes up to eight players can choose a team and play a season of 26, 52 or 162 games. Between matches players can change the line-up and rotation, and trade away players.Gameplay: is fairly tradition, with fielding, pitching, batting and baserunning. Next to fastball and curveballs, there are six different pitches such as Super Fast, Screwball, Super Curve, Slider, Change Up and Knuckleball.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/6/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>8PDJ3-QC8Dk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3822</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588417-ken-griffey-jrs-winning-run</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ken-griffey-jrs-winning-run</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ken-griffey-jrs-winning-run/3030-3894/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/kkrZRAJ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/CUaiiqr.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/nfoXbBt.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/fhFXL8F.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/gIKPDED.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/VCaNv2e.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/QgAxTZN.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/JYwL49a.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/siAl2Q8.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/eqbhhPq.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/nzjIn8G.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/CZzW4Ty.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vePskph.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/h6VQZ1B.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Now you can make baseball history with Ken Griffey Jr.s Winning Run! Play with all 28 Major League teams and challenge your baseball skills over a full season. Capture the pennant and you're off to the World Series! Incredible 3-D rendered stadiums have views of the field that are so realistic you'll swear that you're really there. Step up to bat and you'll feel like a major league hitter. There has never been a sports game like this one. With more stats, more realism and more baseball thrills, it's a grand slam home run!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/305708b7-2edd-4842-a345-b9f9a1095ba4.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/44b1d603-5c9a-4ba3-ae1d-9e928612335f.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a346d25-fede-4df0-9861-5b6bab9a4fca.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6f2e4762-5395-447b-afab-e7bae18e8c66.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>