<Game>
	<Name>Ken Griffey Jr. Presents Major League Baseball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ken Griffey Jr. Presents Major League Baseball was released for the SNES in 1994. It had the MLB license but not the license of the Player's Union, so fictionalized names (other than Griffey's) were used for the athletes. The fictional names are notable for the various themes that teams were given. For example, the Kansas City Royals were all named after United States presidents and the Baltimore Orioles are named after famous Baltimoreans.Gameplay:The game features exhibition and season play, as well as a 1 or 2-player Home Run Derby mode. When pitching, the player can control the path of the ball in midair, which can make 2-player competitive play sometimes infuriating. Aside from this, basic gameplay is fairly straightforward. In-game stadiums resemble their real-life equivalents and include well-known features like Fenway Park's left field wall (the Green Monster) and Baltimore's brick facade of the B &amp; O warehouse beyond right field that Ken Griffey struck with a ball during 1993's Home Run Derby.Fictional Name Team ThemesAtlanta Braves - Famous DJsBaltimore Orioles - Baltimore nativesBoston Red Sox - Cheers (TV Show) characters and Boston landmarksCalifornia Angels - Famous actorsChicago White Sox - Basketball players from St. John's UniversityChicago Cubs - Sports actions or nicknamesCincinnati Reds - Prolific writersCleveland Indians - Famous ActressesColorado Rockies - Famous people associated with horror moviesDetroit Tigers - Motown singersHouston Astros - CartoonistsKansas City Royals - Presidents of the United States of AmericaLos Angeles Dodgers - Punk rockers and other musicians from CaliforniaMilwaukee Brewers - Secret agents, detectives, and superhero secret identitiesMinnesota Twins - Book charactersMontreal Expos - 1980's English musiciansNew York Mets - Punk rockers from New YorkNew York Yankees - Former Yankee greatsOakland Athletics - Prolific authorsPhiladelphia Phillies - Philly landmarks and characters from the Rocky moviesSan Francisco Giants - Workers from Software CreationsSan Diego Padres - Punk rockers from EnglandSeattle Mariners - Workers from Nintendo of AmericaSt. Louis Cardinals - ComediansTexas Rangers - Western motifToronto Blue Jays - Wigan Warriors rugby team membersCheat: Play as Ken Griffey Jr. in Home Run DerbyHold the R button while selecting a batter in the Home Run Derby mode.Cheat: Play as Ken Griffey Jr. in Home Run DerbyAt The title screen, press B, A, Down, B, Up, B, B, A </plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>nd-MKrM1vpo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3821</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588416-ken-griffey-jr-presents-major-league-baseball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ken-griffey-jr-presents-major-league-baseball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ken-griffey-jr-presents-major-league-baseball/3030-7266/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/f3PK3oa.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Hk4xgLf.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/gupDyUd.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Ygv2EqP.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ZCUObQi.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/WqXsUke.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/tYSVFAG.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/PVhEE8Q.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/myvSqGa.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/D07A9DE.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/GD6NhKI.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/9rP1wJY.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/bzP37Ym.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DmYpEBQ.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/3ZuoVsL.png</clearlogo1>
</game>