<Game>
	<Name>Kendo Rage (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Kendo Rage is a side-scrolling action title developed by Affect and published by Datam Polystar for SNES that was released in 1993. In the game, the player controls Josephine, a schoolgirl who recently came to live with her grandfather in rural Japan, at his kendo dojo. After her summer vacation, she leaves for her first day at school. However, her kendo skills will be tested as she faces all sorts of bizarre enemies on the way.Kendo Rage has an anime art style, complete with characters engaging in melodramatic posturing, and Josephine becomes briefly super-deformed when hit. The game also features a persistent timer that runs over the course of the game, displayed in the upper-left corner. If the player doesn't beat the final boss by the time the clock reads 9:00, Josephine will be late for school and a bad ending will result.The game is known as Makeruna! Makendou in Japan and has several Japan-only sequels.StagesThe game has seven stages, each with different environmental themes.Stage 1 &#8211; Cliff HangerJosephine must get from her house to her bus stop and catch her bus. At the bus stop she must defeat a robotic Super-Deformed duplicate of herself.Stage 2 &#8211; Ice QueenJosephine must navigate a snow-covered mountain pass to reach her next bus connection, and defeat a crazed karaoke singer who unleashes ice attacks.Stage 3 &#8211; The PondJosephine must get through various underwater caves and defeat 3 vicious fish to continue along her way.Stage 4 &#8211; TechnodyneJosephine now must get through a construction site and fight a transforming giant robot in order to catch the cable car from the mountain to the city.Stage 5 &#8211; CommuteJosephine must fend off attackers as she rides the cable car down to the bottom of the mountain, and then while taking the train.Stage 6 &#8211; TriathlonOnce she's reached her stop, Josephine must fend off three groups of athletes bent on stopping her from making it to school on time, including a dark magical girl with tennis themed attacks.Stage 7 &#8211; School DazeAs she races to school, Josephine faces a final boss rush, and one last demonic opponent hell-bent on keeping her from getting to school on time.				</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SETA U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.375</rating>
	<VideoURL>XGOOdUn03MM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2000</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588418-kendo-rage</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/kendo-rage</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kendo-rage/3030-13210/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/qae7XCn.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/RVKViIw.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/zMjWTZ9.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/0cCT1L8.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/BObdCBb.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/8mU2ZR0.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/OcjrrLb.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/msfCz2K.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/sF5BCKJ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/bEMbUJ4.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/T8H3moQ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/PThfrMd.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/ILJB52t.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/skQvi4p.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/YS7MptX.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/W5B3uQ5.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>OutRAGEous Kendo Action! Join Jo on the world's weirdest summer vacation. Jo is into kendo, Japanese fencing, so her parents sent her to Japan to study under Osaki sensei. Osaki is the greatest sword master of all time, but he looks like a green haired cyperpunk. Just to crank up the strangeness Osaki gives you a talisman that transforms you into a seventies super hero. You've never seen action this crazy or fun. Kendo Rage is the rage. - 7 rounds of non-stop action - 8 mega packed with adventure, fun and cool animation. - Multi-directional attacks for 360 degrees of sword swinging! - Intense power up attacks! - Gaggles of goofy goons to bash!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/74f73907-9f41-4590-9fdc-8d8519d15e01.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/587b5df5-4a51-4715-9846-139e199189a3.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3065b1a0-4d65-4278-85f3-c4dea66078ed.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82cd37f1-3c43-4327-ae6b-b2fcb2aeec77.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ec5cd00-b072-4c3d-8e1f-363be7b74cab.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6b089e5c-535f-4005-bc52-c781a49a6579.png</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82f52cc7-ad25-49b3-8465-b9f12300c92c.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2b053904-8670-4219-9a28-8e352aed2b82.png</snapshot16>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>SETA</Publisher>
</game>