<Game>
	<Name>Kenyuu Densetsu Yaiba (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Kenyuu Densetsu Yaiba ("Legend of the Swordmaster Yaiba") is a video game adaptation of the anime and manga of the same name about the samurai youth Yaiba who is the latest incarnation of the Thunder God. The lighthearted manga/anime takes its inspiration from Japanese folklore, but transplants it into a modern setting.The game is an action RPG, where the protagonist fights monsters in real-time without transitioning to a separate battle screen. The game loosely follows the first arc of its source material, in which Yaiba must defeat his rival Onimaru and the various demons he summons (many of whom end up joining Yaiba's party after being defeated, becoming support characters). Yaiba has a number of AI support characters, including his faithful vulture companion Shonosuke, who will fly Yaiba back to the nearest safehouse for healing/saving. Others include Yaiba's love interest Sayaka, who can use cure magic to heal Yaiba, and Kagetora, Yaiba's tiger companion who fights alongside him. The game also has a two-player mode where the second player controls Rai; a character created for the game.Banpresto published Kenyuu Densetsu Yaiba for the Super Famicom, Game Boy and Sega Game Gear in 1994. The portable versions are side-scrolling action games, whereas the Super Famicom action RPG uses a top-down perspective.	</plot>
	<releasedate>25/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Atelier Double</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571061-kenyuu-densetsu-yaiba</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/keny-densetsu-yaiba</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kenyuu-densetsu-yaiba/3030-4906/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/EgDfeTI.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/zmfPXho.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/PfiKNDX.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/8p7Fsn2.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/2WcHR5Z.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/AUmoex6.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Hu8RILs.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/mZBNdGD.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/7Xo1sjr.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/VYnaq2t.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/vzsqxNr.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ySrmxax.gif</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Av5Carq.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Kenyuu Densetsu Yaiba is a Role-Playing game, developed by Atelier Double and published by Banpresto, which was released in Japan in 1994.  Based off the shōnen manga series, Legend of the Swordmaster Yaiba, by Gosho Aoyama.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/93fd1605-ef96-470f-96fb-12b8b5844cc8.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea4f1ffc-1fc8-4f29-b0d0-8b664186c071.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99d7de47-caf4-4944-80ba-2c22343ab29b.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dcdc141d-0dd4-47e1-b9a2-f6ead77b4448.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Banpresto Co., ltd</Publisher>
</game>