<Game>
	<Name>Kevin Keegan's Player Manager (Europe) (Sample)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Kevin Keegan's Player Manager is a soccer/simulation game developed by Anco Software and published by Imagineer for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. It is based on Dino Dini's Player Manager though developed without his input. The player can manage the team from the sidelines, and they can also participate in soccer matches by assuming control of the player-coach. The goal is to lead the player's team to victory in the UK's Division 1 (the Premier League had not yet been introduced). The game is endorsed by Kevin Keegan, a former England striker and then-manager of English league team Newcastle United.The game was released in Germany as K.H. Rummenigge's Player Manager. Karl-Heinz Rummenigge is a former Bayern Munich striker and participated in two World Cups on the side of West Germany.	</plot>
	<releasedate>30/11/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Imagineer Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>1773</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/943947-kevin-keegans-player-manager</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/kevin-keegans-player-manager</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kevin-keegans-player-manager/3030-29480/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/UvfsffE.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/s3ke9tJ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/0njmdGB.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/NrzdppF.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Bv56qlV.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/lPRyksX.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/tDaIO2m.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CWC9dC6.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/4I2IXdQ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/1h6RsHk.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2bRi5u9.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/4vbqyjV.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/FzGLpib.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/bYKBhtI.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>State of the art soccer management simulation and world famous KICK OFF, played independently or interlinked.  KICK OFF - one or two players option. Numerous skill levels, Challenge Cup and practice option. MANAGER - 3 Management skill levels. 3 division league and 2 Cup competitions. Options to play on the pitch or watch or get computer predicted results.  Played in REAL TIME - other 47 Managers are actively managing their clubs under same pressures as you. Lively transfer market due to strict financial controls. Physics, Scouts, promotion and relegation battles are all there and as in real life, create pressure cooker game environment. Player Manager is truly rich in its depth and is highly addictive.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/943240f7-5ef2-47ee-8eb2-8e465493abbe.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4550434c-84d8-4634-ad51-58df576864f4.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/994f4293-c12a-4db1-9e3d-941229a10465.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/85c2e1c0-f64a-4db6-913a-4db553551b7b.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Imagineer</Publisher>
</game>