<Game>
	<Name>Kid Klown in Crazy Chase (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Kid Klown in Crazy Chase is an isometric endless runner from Kemco. The player, as Kid Klown, must run down a path while avoiding obstacles to reach a bomb before its fuse runs out. The game was originally released for the Super Nintendo in 1994 and was later ported to the Game Boy Advance in 2002.Kid Klown, despite (or because?) being the most accident-prone clown on the planet, is tasked by the King to rescue Princess Klown from the interstellar space pirate Blackjack. Kid Klown's starfighter fails to take down Blackjack's spaceship and hurtles back down to the planet, where he must stop Blackjack from bombing various locations.Kemco originally created the Kid Klown character for the US version of a Mickey Mouse NES game that couldn't use the Disney license in that territory: Kid Klown in Night Mayor World. He would return for the PlayStation sequels Kid Klown in Crazy Chase 2 and The Bombing Islands.Gameplay:Collision with one of the many hazards and blockades will cause Kid Klown to lose some health and slow down/stop for a few seconds. He must reach the end before the fuse on a bomb beats him there, which the player can see throughout the course as well as by a gauge in the top left that compares Kid's progress to that of the bomb's fuse.As well as getting to the end before the bomb fuse, Kid Klown must also find four card suit icons by opening balloons. The balloons can be opened by jumping up and grabbing their string as they pass overhead. As well as the four icons, the balloons provide bonuses such as extra coins and health recovery items. If Kid Klown doesn't manage to grab all four icons, he must restart the stage (though his icon progress is saved - he'll only need to find the ones he missed).Cheat: Stage SelectReset the game, and on the title screen, hold L and R on both controllers, and then hit on BOTH controllers, at the same time:</plot>
	<releasedate>10/9/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Kotobuki System Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>2ZjW7p5PEBg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3825</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588264-kid-klown-in-crazy-chase</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/kid-klown-in-crazy-chase</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kid-klown-in-crazy-chase/3030-14982/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/6FjtpMj.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/J3M7xAf.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/grPx8lg.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/vrlB0x3.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/LXGmEGa.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/KzMm5Xh.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/o732C1L.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/GiEkLx2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/FmyTILp.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/bp3lLKO.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/wBhkd3R.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/byTuHvk.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/vQHNin9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/jq9XIiP.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/JLn4W42.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/rhFqnhM.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>"Hey, kid! Help me out! I've got to run for my life from evil space pirate Blackjack. He wants to conquer the planet with bombs, banana peels and booby traps; and I need all kinds of balloons and klown coins to escape! It's the spookiest, kookiest race you can run, with new diagonal scrolling for pie-in-your-face action! Plus hidden zones, power ups and bonus stages that make it a riot to play every time. So get off your butt! Let's go klown around!"</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5594e46c-d5f9-434e-9077-7891cfab39d5.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2123215b-bd62-47d1-857e-d0d6e5147715.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3f88e895-f75a-4692-aa08-fb06458da3b7.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40f39656-2db4-458d-aae4-4361bc89f5f1.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Kemco</Publisher>
</game>