<Game>
	<Name>Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>This is an RPG that was only released on the SNES, which also shares its name with several other titles across different systems, due to them all being based on the same Anime series "Patlabor".In this RPG, you control the two main pilots from the series/films, Noa Izumi and Isao Ota, as you complete your typical duties each day, helping to deal with rogue Labors (Mecha) and other such incidents. The game, only having been released in Japan, is only really advisable to play if you understand Japanese, as it really is a text-heavy game.The gameplay consists of three screens - a map of Japan, showing where your asignments are located, the "main" screen, where you control your Labor from a top-down viewpoint and maneuver it around the area of the crime. Finally, there's the combat screen, for when you press the action button to attack a rogue Labor. From here you can select one of various attacks; naturally, as the game goes on your pilots can learn new attacks, though unusually for an RPG there's also the option to just talk with the rogue Labor's pilot and try to convince them to back down - as a policeman, sometimes this is the only way forward.This is a fairly typical Eastern RPG with a fairly unique setting. Just don't forget your Kanji-English dictionary!</plot>
	<releasedate>22/4/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Interbec</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/564347-kidou-keisatsu-patlabor</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/kidou-keisatsu-patlabor</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kidou-keisatsu-patlabor/3030-19782/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/QoaxvaR.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/H8kZyTi.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/OPXUx9G.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/x1jSWoS.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/2D1w9E9.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Z8k0R5Q.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/hkLjfxc.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/RluEdD9.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/mqEUa40.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/htOdHHt.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/BRQ9Q89.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/klz1UBM.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/kYj6J2l.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/aEpfI4M.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/wlPmf2z.jpg</fanart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/9OglFOz.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>One of the several games based on the anime and manga Patlabor. In this role-playing game the player controls two main pilots from the series, Noa Izumi and Isao Ota, as they complete their typical duties each day, helping to deal with rogue Labors (Mecha) and other such incidents. The gameplay consists of three modes - a map of Japan, showing where assignments are located, the "main" screen, where the player controls the Labor from a top-down viewpoint and maneuvers it around the area of the crime, and the combat screen, for when you press the action button to attack a rogue Labor. From here it is possible to select one of various attacks; naturally, as the game goes on the pilots can learn new attacks. Unusually for an RPG there is also the option to just talk with the rogue Labor's pilot and try to convince them to back down - as a policeman, sometimes this is the only way forward.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/76d084f7-76e1-4e18-82b6-512b60be6fb2.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fdc7a2f0-b159-4934-84cc-5f05ccf5bbb8.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aa0620fb-a442-413a-8519-c9d2a34d6f57.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/64e7262f-6430-4c25-906e-f487b2007cd8.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e7fbf214-f5e2-498f-b104-3c9c06cd67ae.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/932edc95-d0e3-41bf-a22f-74e1fab8caf9.jpg</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Interbec</Publisher>
</game>