<Game>
	<Name>Kidou Senshi Gundam F91 - Formula Senki 0122 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Kidou Senshi Gundam ("Mobile Suit Gundam") F91: Formula Senki 0122 is a strategy game based in the Gundam universe. Specifically, it follows the F91 series that chronologically takes place 30 years after the original. The F91 series began as a feature-length movie which summarized what would've been the first thirteen episodes of a longer TV show, and was released in March of 1991 - four months before this game.The aim of the game is to direct the player's Gundam and intercept enemy unit formations, and then line up individual targets in a space sim-like mode. After selecting a target in this mode, the player then selects between their Gundam's weapons (certain weapons do better depending on the player character's distance from the enemy) and watch the combat round unfurl. Upon destroying all nearby enemies, the player returns to the strategic mode to head towards the next set of units.</plot>
	<releasedate>6/7/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Nova Games Ltd.</Developer>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>332AiSNieKI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>24837</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/565621-kidou-senshi-gundam-f91-formula-senki-0122</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kidou-senshi-gundam-f91-formula-senki-0122/3030-28266/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/kdQGVOU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/pSx6bFC.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ZOwtLNY.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/csFtQ7K.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/UjAZoLg.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/MmuD3yk.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/OpgdR4L.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ixDJl1o.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DAYmAM1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ER6Mdm9.jpg</snapshot8>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/2qejPFT.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In U.C. 0122, the detached corps of the Mars Zeon, led by Charles Rochester, invades Earth with assistance from the Crossbone Vanguard. The Earth Federation Space Force deploys the Gundam F90 and the F91 Gundam F91 to repel them. Also known as Mobile Suit Gundam F91: Formula Wars 0122.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/faed857b-ddca-4c23-9c9d-e8c9461a69f2.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b7bde2c7-9e83-4f08-965a-c1859e2abbce.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c59db830-856d-40f7-94b5-efc0e16134a4.png</snapshot9>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>