<Game>
	<Name>Kirby Super Star (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Kirby Super Star is a side-scrolling platformer developed by HAL Laboratory and originally published by Nintendo in 1996 for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. The fourth platforming-focused game in the Kirby series, Super Star is actually a collection of seven main game modes and two smaller minigames. All of the modes star eponymous protagonist Kirby, a pink puffball who can inhale his enemies and swallow them to copy their special abilities. New to the franchise is the ability for Kirby to convert his current Ability into a "Helper" AI partner which can optionally be controlled by a second player.Super Star was remade for the Nintendo DS in 2008 as Kirby Super Star Ultra, featuring enhanced graphics and sound effects, rearranged music, 3D cutscenes, four new main game modes and three new minigames. The original title was digitally re-released for the Wii and the Wii U via Virtual Console, and it also appears in the Kirby Dream Collection disc-based compilation.Gameplay:As with previous Kirby titles, most of the game modes in Super Star consist of platforming through a series of levels that gradually increase in difficulty, nearly all of which contain several standard enemies and a stage boss. Kirby's basic move set allows players to walk, run, jump and fly, and Super Star introduces two new core abilities: the slide tackle and guarding to reduce damage. Besides his new slide tackle, Kirby can also inhale enemies or objects before spitting them out as his standard method of attack. However, some enemies can be swallowed to grant Kirby a special Copy ability based on the type of enemy consumed.Although the Copy mechanic was originally introduced in Kirby's Adventure, Super Star features a new set of twenty-four Copy powers for players to discover throughout the game, some of which make a return from Adventure. This is the first Kirby game that displays full in-game move lists for each of Kirby's Copy abilities, and the first to have unique hats associated with each power-up. Kirby can sacrifice his equipped Copy ability at any time in order to summon a CPU-controlled helper character corresponding to that ability. Helpers have many of the same abilities as Kirby and occasionally possess special techniques, and they all employ a unique color scheme to differentiate the helper from its enemy counterpart. A second player can play as the helper character by connecting a second controller.Ability &amp; Helper ListAbilityHelperMove List / NotesNormalN/AInhale/Spit Enemy: YNo Ability equippedBeamWaddle DooBeam Whip: YCycle Beam: Dash + YBeam Machine Gun: Dash + Y (in air)Capture Beam: Forward + Y (near enemy)Wave Beam: Hold YBombPoppy Bros. Jr.Hold/Throw Bomb: YSet Bomb: Y (near enemy)Drop Bomb: Down + Y (near enemy)Straight Throw: Dash + YCookN/ACook: YOne-time useCopyT.A.C.Analyze Beam (Kirby only): YSneaky Hand (T.A.C. only): Dash + YUseful for obtaining Abilities in Milky Way WishesT.A.C. Helper can steal Abilities from enemiesCrashN/ACrash Fire Ball: YOne-time useCutterSir KibbleCutter Boomerang: YCutter Dash Attack: Dash + YCutter Drop Attack: Y repeatedly (in air)High-Speed Cutter Drop: Down + Y (in air)Non-Stop Cutter Attack: Y repeatedly (near enemy)Cuts ropes and extinguishes flamesFighterKnuckle JoeVulcan Jab: YSmash Punch: Hold YLeg Sweep: Dash + YSpin Kick: Dash + Hold YDown Kick: Y (in air)Double Kick: Hold Y (in air)Rising Break: Up + YGrab Enemy: Forward + Y (near enemy)Arm Throw: Y (while holding enemy)Tomoe Throw (Kirby only): Back + Y (while holding enemy)FireBurnin' LeoFire Blow: YFire Ball: Hold Y + BackBurning Attack: Dash + YFire Ball Spin: Y (while jumping)Fire Ball Roll: Y (in air before landing)Lights cannon fusesHammerBonkersHammer Nail: YHammer Swing: Dash + YGiant Swing: Y (in air)Ultragiant Swing: Dash + Y (in air)Hammer Flip: Up + YHammer Throw (Kirby only): Dash + A (destroys Hammer)Can be used underwaterHammers down wooden postsIceChillyFreezer Breath: YFreezer Blizard: Dash + Y or Y repeatedlyFreezer Sprinkle: Y (in air)Freezer Suction: Forward + Y (near enemy)Freezer Ejection: Y (while holding enemy)Ice Kick: Touching iceJetCapsule-JStore Power: Hold YSave Stored Power: B or L or R (after storing power)Jet Kick: Y or release YJet Heading: Y or release Y (in air)Jet Dash: Y (with full power)Jet Cracker: Y (during Jet Dash)Jet Blow: Y or release Y (near enemy)Diving Rocket: Y (with full power near enemy)Hover: B (in air)Ultra-Jet Jump: B (with full power in air)Lights cannon fusesMikeN/AMegaphone: Y (first use)Desk Mike: Y (second use)Stand Mike: Y (third use)Three-time use; damages increases with each useMirrorSimirrorMirror Cut: YReflect Force: Hold YMirror Body: Dash + YReflect Guard: L or RNinjaBiosparkKnife Throw: YQuado-Shock Attack: Hold YDash Attack: Dash + YNinja Kick: Down + Y (in air)Air Drop: Forward + Y (near enemy)Hide Defense: Y (while taking damage)Stick to Wall: Press against wall while in airTriangle Jump: B (while stuck to wall)Cuts ropes and extinguishes flamesPaintN/APaint: YOne-time useObtainable only from Chameleo Arm or Heavy LobsterBlinds Heavy Lobster and forces cloaked Chameleo Arm to become visibleParasolParasol Waddle DeeParasol Swing: YParasol Shield: Hold YParasol Drill: Dash + YParasol Dive: Down + Y (in air)Parasol Roll: Forward + Y (near enemy)Parasol Chute: Up (in air)PlasmaPlasma WispStore Power: Press any directionPlasma Needle: Y (with no power)Plasma Arrow: Y (with low power)Plasma Spark: Y (with medium power)Plasma Laser: Y (with high power)Plasma Wave Cannon: Y (with full power)Creates a damage shield at full powerSleepN/ANo moves; puts Kirby to sleep for several seconds and then disappearsStoneRockyStone: YStone Smash: Y (in air)Turbo Stone: Dash + YInvincible while in Stone formSuplexBugzzyDash Capture Lifting Up: YTurbo Dash Capture Lifting Up: Dash + YBack Breaker: Up (while lifting enemy)Body Slam: Down (while lifting enemy)Pile Driver: Forward (while lifting enemy)German Suplex: Backward (while lifting enemy)Air Body Slam: Forward or Up or Backward (while lifting enemy in air)Air Body Down Slam: Down (while lifting enemy in air)Pin Point Kick: Down + Y (in air)Quick Stamping: Y repeatedly or Dash + Y repeatedly (near enemy)SwordBlade KnightChop: YChop &amp; Beam: Y (with full health)Multi-Sword Attack: Y repeatedlySword Stab: Dash + YSword Spin: Dash + Y (in air)Down Air Stab: Down + Y (in air)Can be used underwaterCuts ropes and extinguishes flamesWheelWheelieTurn: Left or RightBrake: BDash/Dash Release: YDash across surface of waterVulnerable while turning and brakingKirby can ride Wheelie helperWingBirdonFeather Gun: YCondor Heading: Dash + YBomber Heading: Down + Y (in air)Toss: Forward + Y (near enemy)Shuttle Loop: Y (after tossing enemy)Fluttering: B (in air)Yo-YoGimYo-Yo Throw: YBreak Spin: Dash + YUp Throw Attack: Up + YDown Throw Attack: Down + YGrab Enemy: Forward + Y (near enemy)Hammer Drop: Y or Forward + Y or Back + Y (while holding enemy)Gazer Spiral: Down, Up + YModes:A variety of game modes can be selected from Super Star's bulletin board-style menu, although only four of the main modes (Spring Breeze, Dyna Blade, Gourmet Race and The Great Cave Offensive) and both minigames are initially available. Revenge of Meta Knight is unlocked by finishing Spring Breeze and Dyna Blade, as well as placing first in Gourmet Race. Milky Way Wishes requires completion of all four of these modes, and The Arena is only accessible after clearing Milky Way Wishes. While each game mode only allows for a single save file, three separate player profiles can be accessed from Super Star's main title screen that track players' overall progress across each of the sub-games. Earning 100% completion on a single profile unlocks the game's Sound Test.Spring BreezeKing Dedede and his minions have stolen all of the food in Dream Land, and it's up to Kirby to recover it before the inhabitants starve. The easiest and shortest of the seven main game modes, Spring Breeze is essentially a remake of the original Kirby's Dream Land with four stages and the inclusion of Copy abilities, which were not present in the original game, as well as altered stage layouts. However, Spring Breeze omits the "Castle Lololo" stage and Kabula boss from Kirby's Dream Land. It also removes the boss rush mini-stages that originally occurred prior to fighting the game's final boss, King Dedede.Stage 1 - Green Greens: A short, grassy level that gently introduces players to Kirby and a handful of his Copy abilities. Mid-Boss: Poppy Bros. Sr. | Boss: Whispy WoodsStage 2 - Float Islands: Kirby takes a swim and discovers the powerful Invincibility Candy capable of defeating even mid-bosses in one hit. Mid-Boss: Mr. Frosty | Boss: Lololo &amp; LalalaStage 3 - Bubbly Clouds: Danger appears in the skies above Dream Land in the form of Kracko, a persistent cloud-like enemy with powerful lightning attacks. Mid-Boss: Kracko Jr. | Boss: KrackoFinal Stage - Mt. Dedede: Kirby reaches the mountain fortress for a final showdown with Dedede to decide the fate of Dream Land. Boss: King DededeDyna BladeWhen Kirby is violently awoken one day by a gigantic bird named Dyna Blade, he sets out towards its nest to discover the reason behind its sudden aggression. This game features a simple world map containing four main stages, as well as two hidden stages that serve as power-up caches for several of Kirby's various Copy abilities. Although somewhat lengthier than Spring Breeze, this mode is only slightly more difficult in comparison and continues to introduce new Copy powers to the player, some of which can be used to open new areas or discover secret items.Stage 1 - Peanut Plains: A breezy area that hosts only a few enemies, but the terrain is rugged enough to keep new players on their toes. Boss: Chef KawasakiStage 2 - Mallow Castle: Kirby explores a large castle containing several secret areas and an auto-scrolling section. A hidden switch located here opens the path to Trial Room 1. Boss: BonkersStage 3 - Cocoa Cave: A mysterious cave system filled with dangerous traps and a few new enemies. Boss: BugzzyStage 4 - Candy Mountain: The final stretch leads straight up the side of a treacherous mountain brimming with lava. A secret switch here unlocks the path to Trial Room 2. Mid-Boss: Mr. Frosty &amp; Bonkers | Boss: Poppy Bros. Sr. (x2)Final Stage - Dyna Blade's Nest: At the mountain's peak, Kirby battles against the ferocious bird and makes an unexpected discovery after their fight. Boss: Dyna BladeTrial Rooms 1 &amp; 2: Together these small secret stages contain twenty Copy abilities and only a few easy enemies, allowing players to practice the use of these power-ups freely. Unlocking both Trial Rooms is required for 100% completion.Gourmet RaceA game mode that takes place in "Gourmet World" where Kirby races against King Dedede while also competing to eat the most food along the way. Players can practice any of the three courses in a solitary time trial, but Kirby must win the full three-course Grand Prix to complete this mode.Course 1 - Pumpkin Grand: A short course with gentle rolling hills and few real obstacles.Course 2 - Corn Hall: The difficulty increases in this course featuring multiple paths across much more rugged terrain.Course 3 - Onion Garden: The final maze-like course begins with five Copy pedestals that Kirby can use to keep up the pace against the insatiable Dedede.The Great Cave OffensiveThe lengthiest mode to fully complete, The Great Cave Offensive is a non-linear treasure hunt in which Kirby must collect hidden treasure chests while navigating an expansive cave system. There are a total of sixty unique treasures to discover; each one collected increases the player's overall completion rate. This game does not feature strictly-linear level design and instead shares similarities with the structure of a "Metroidvania"-style platformer, allowing for backtracking which is usually necessary for perfect completion. Collecting all of the game's treasure also requires extensive knowledge of Kirby's various Copy abilities.Sub-Tree Area: Kirby falls into an underground forest teeming with enemies. A few scattered treasures are easily found, but one inside a maze of switches requires clever timing. Boss: Fatty WhaleCrystal Area: A mine cart takes Kirby into a series of larger caves encrusted with shimmering crystal. Boss: Computer VirusOld Tower: This optional area holds many treasures, but locating them all demands patience and the assistance of Helpers. Boss: Chameleo ArmGarden Area: The path winds slowly back up through stone rooms and puffy clouds that hide some of the most valuable treasure. Boss: Wham Bam RockList of TreasuresIcon#NameValueAreaNotes1Gold Medal10,000GSub-Tree 2Gold Coin1,000GSub-TreeA koban, an Edo-period Japanese oval coin3Whip6,800GSub-TreeResembles the Vampire Killer from Castlevania4Crystal Ball200,000GSub-Tree 5Lucky Cat5,000GSub-TreeManeki-neko, a Japanese luck talisman6Seiryu Sword142,000GSub-TreeSeiry&#363; (the Japanese name for Qing Long) is a mythological Chinese dragon7Screw Ball80,000GSub-TreeScrew Attack power-up from Metroid8Echigo Candy8,000GSub-TreeEchigo was an old province in Japan now located in Niigata Prefecture9Zebra Mask278,000GSub-TreeResembles Phanto from Super Mario10Star Stone82,100GSub-Tree 11Beast's Fang7,300GSub-Tree 12Bandanna1,990GSub-TreeSimilar to the bandanna worn by Fighter Kirby13Springtime250,000GSub-Tree 14Dime10GCrystal 15Glass Slippers120,000GCrystalCinderella's famous footwear16Goblet800GCrystal 17Saucepan10GCrystal 18Brass Knuckle20,000GCrystal 19Amber Rose22,100GCrystal 20Fish Fossil8,250GCrystal 21Beast Fossil24,220GCrystal 22Nunchuks55,480GCrystal 23Bucket200GCrystalBucket worn by Mario in Mario &amp; Wario24Summertime250,000GCrystal 25100 Dollar Coin10,000GCrystal 26Ancient Gem68,000GCrystalA magatama, a Japanese ceremonial jewel27Falcon Helmet41,000GCrystalCaptain Falcon's helmet in F-Zero28Dud30GCrystal 29Truth Mirror500,000GCrystal 30Star Tiara408,200GOld Tower 31Turtle Shell800GOld TowerGreen Koopa Troopa shell from Super Mario32Sword325,000GOld TowerMarth's Falchion in Fire Emblem33Warrior Shield50,000GOld Tower 34Unicorn's Horn80,300GOld Tower 35Autumntime250,000GOld Tower 36Rice Bowl50GOld Tower 37Tut's Mask160,000GOld TowerGolden burial mask of Egyptian pharaoh Tutankhamun38Mr. Saturn120,000GOld TowerMascot character from EarthBound39Armor212,000GOld TowerResembles Sir Arthur's armor from Ghosts 'N Goblins40Treasure Box100,000GOld Tower 41Mannequin3,000GOld Tower 42Gold Crown528,000GOld Tower 43King's Cape508,000GOld Tower 44Model Ship800,000GOld Tower 45Sun Ring800,000GOld Tower 46Wintertime250,000GGarden 47Katana990,000GGardenHighest value of all treasures48Charm8,000GGardenAnkh necklace49Xmas Tree40,000GGarden 50Kong's Barrel1,500GGardenBarrel from Donkey Kong51Ramia's Scale12,800GGardenMistranslation of Lamia, a creature from Greek mythology52Shiny Bamboo600,000GGarden 53Tire1,100GGarden 54Spirit Charm78,500GGarden 55Pegasus Wing42,800GGardenOne of the Three Sacred Treasures in Kid Icarus56Raccoon Doll8,150GGardenJapanese tanuki doll57Shell Whistle82,000GGarden 58Orihalcon512,000GGardenMistranslation of orichalcum, a mythical substance found in Atlantis59Platinum Ring40,000GGarden 60Triforce800,000GGardenPowerful artifact from The Legend of ZeldaRevenge of Meta KnightAs Meta Knight launches the flying warship Halberd in his latest bid to conquer Dream Land, Kirby races against time to stop him. Revenge of Meta Knight is the only mode to feature a time limit for each level, as well as NPC commentary during gameplay in the form of dialogue boxes at the bottom of the screen, lending Revenge a more frantic tone than Super Star's previous games. Meta Knight appears near the end for a climactic sword duel and continues to harass Kirby during the final escape sequence from the destroyed Halberd.Stage 1 - Halberd Deck: Kirby begins his assault on the main deck of Meta Knight's warship, but he is distracted by Heavy Lobster before being blown away from the ship by one of its main thrusters.Stage 2 - Orange Ocean: After landing in the ocean, Kirby quickly makes his way to shore and finds a Warp Star, but he is shot down by the Halberd's cannon and falls into a forest. Mid-Boss: Iron Mam | Boss: Whispy Woods &amp; Twin WoodsStage 3 - Forest: His second detour takes Kirby through a thick forest and up a familiar mountain; after reaching the summit, Dyna Blade gives Kirby a ride back to the Halberd. Boss: Bonkers (x2)Stage 4 - Halberd Cannon: Dyna Blade is injured by cannon-fire, but Kirby manages to board the Halberd once more and quickly destroys its Main Cannon No. 2. Mid-Boss: Meta-Knights, Jukid &amp; Poppy Bros. Sr. | Boss: Combo CannonStage 5 - Halberd Port Section: Kirby descends across the port-side hull and locates another Warp Star, which he uses to deal serious damage to the Halberd's left wing. Boss: Mr. FrostyStage 6 - Halberd Interior: Jumping into a hull breach, Kirby fights through the Halberd's maintenance ducts and is again ambushed by Heavy Lobster. This time Kirby destroys it and takes out the Halberd's right wing. Boss: Heavy LobsterStage 7 - Halberd Lower Hull: Clouds swirl beneath the belly of the Halberd, giving Kirby some much-needed cover as he infiltrates the underside of the ship and destroys its main reactor. Boss: Halberd's ReactorStage 8 - Halberd Bridge: Kirby makes his final approach towards the bridge as the crippled Halberd rapidly loses altitude, where Meta Knight awaits him for one last duel. Mid-Boss: Meta-Knights | Boss: Meta KnightStage 9 - Evacuation: Though defeated, Meta Knight relentlessly pursues Kirby as he frantically races to escape the Halberd before it crashes into the ocean.Milky Way WishesOne day the Sun and Moon began fighting ceaselessly above Kirby's home planet of Popstar, throwing the heavens into utter chaos. A jester-like resident of Popstar named Marx asks Kirby to make peace between the Sun and Moon by gathering power from each of Popstar's seven neighboring planets. This power can be used to summon Nova, a gigantic mechanical "comet" capable of granting a single wish.Milky Way Wishes sports an increased difficulty with tougher enemies and more challenging stages than those in previous modes. Kirby navigates between planets on an overworld map, allowing players to visit stages in any order. This mode also features a twist on the standard Copy mechanic in that Kirby can no longer swallow enemies to Copy their powers; instead, players must locate Copy abilities as unique pedestals hidden throughout the game's stages. Once a particular Copy ability has been acquired, Kirby can manually activate that ability at any time without the need to swallow its corresponding enemy first.After gathering all of the planets' power and summoning Nova, Marx suddenly reappears and shoves Kirby aside before making his own selfish wish to rule over Popstar. Nova complies and grants Marx incredible power, and Nova then begins to descend upon Popstar. Fortunately the comet is temporarily held back by the combined strength of the Sun and Moon, allowing Kirby to fly into Nova on a Warp Star. He destroys its mechanical core from the inside, halting Nova's advance long enough for Kirby to confront the powered-up Marx in an all-out final battle. Once defeated, Marx flies out of control toward the heavens and crashes straight into Nova, destroying them both in a massive explosion and ending the crisis on Popstar.Floria: Popstar's closest neighbor, its climate can be altered simply by entering a door, and Kirby can use these seasonal changes to open new paths. Abilities: Ice, Fighter, Cutter | Boss: Twin WoodsAqualiss: A watery planet featuring yet another tricky maze for Kirby to conquer. Abilities: Parasol, Sword, Beam | Mid-Boss: Jukid | Boss: Fatty WhaleSkyhigh: A sky-themed area resembling the Bubbly Clouds stage in Spring Breeze. Abilities: Jet, Wheel, Wing | Mid-Boss: Poppy Bros. Sr. | Boss: KrackoHotbeat: Things heat up in this lava-filled stage, but Kirby can take refuge in some mine carts later on for a quick breather. Abilities: Fire, Suplex | Mid-Boss: Bugzzy | Boss: Chameleo ArmCavios: Kirby begins this area on a mountainside and descends into the caverns of the planet, where he must fight through a series of mini-bosses. Abilities: Bomb, Hammer, Stone | Mid-Boss: Poppy Bros. Sr., Jukid, Mr. Frosty, Iron Mam, Bonkers, Chef Kawasaki, Bugzzy | Boss: Wham Bam RockMecheye: This high-tech world is actually one gigantic city packed with nasty traps and windy skies. Abilities: Yo-Yo, Plasma | Mid-Boss: Mr. Frosty, Jukid, Chef Kawasaki, Bugzzy, Poppy Bros. Sr., Bonkers, Iron Mam | Boss: Heavy LobsterHalfmoon: Nighttime eternally covers Halfmoon, which more closely resembles a loose collection of stardust than an actual planet. Abilities: Mirror, Ninja | Mid-Boss: Chef Kawasaki, Iron Mam | Boss: Computer VirusNova: Following Marx's betrayal, Kirby infiltrates the approaching Nova in this unique side-scrolling shoot-'em-up stage. Boss: Heart of Nova, Marx???: Hidden among the larger planets, this tiny area contains a few TAC enemies and one power-up. Abilities: CopyThe ArenaThe Arena is a hidden boss rush endurance mode similar to Super Smash Bros.' "All-Star Mode." Players can select from any of Kirby's standard Copy abilities before fighting through a series of nineteen randomly-ordered battles featuring every boss previously encountered in Super Star. Two of the battles are groups of mini-bosses, and one battle contains only the common enemy Waddle Dee (albeit with increased health). The Arena's final boss is always Marx. Between bouts, players may recover health using a total allotment of five Maxim Tomatoes, and they can acquire new Copy abilities from two randomly-selected Copy pedestals. A player's total completion time is displayed following a successful run.List of BossesChameleo ArmCombo CannonComputer VirusDyna BladeFatty WhaleHalberd's ReactorHeart of NovaHeavy LobsterKing DededeKrackoLololo &amp; LalalaMeta KnightMid-Boss Set #1 (Chef Kawasaki, Bonkers &amp; Bugzzy)Mid-Boss Set #2 (Poppy Bros. Sr., Mr. Frosty, Iron Mam &amp; Jukid)Twin WoodsWaddle DeeWham Bam RockWhispy WoodsMarx (Final Boss)Samurai KirbyThis feudal Japan-themed minigame is a test of reflexes between Kirby and one of several opponents. When the game begins, both characters appear on opposite sides of the screen. Players must react to a sudden on-screen "!" prompt by pressing any button, with the winner being whoever strikes first without a false start. Against the CPU, Kirby's opponents will gradually react more quickly, with Meta Knight being the fastest CPU opponent. This minigame features three levels of CPU difficulty and a two-player mode.Megaton PunchThe second timing-based minigame takes place in a martial arts competition between Kirby and three separate opponents where the goal is to cause the most damage to a stack of bricks in a single strike. Three different meters must be activated in succession to build up striking power, with their strength determined by the player's timing accuracy. The competitor who deals the most damage (measured in megatons) in a single round will be declared the winner. Like Samurai Kirby, Megaton Punch also features three levels of CPU difficulty and a two-player mode.Cheat: CameosIf you use the Stone ability enough, you may turn into a statue of Samus, or a golden statue of Mario.Cheat: CameosIn Megaton Punch, if you look in the background, you'll see Mario, Luigi, and a few other people from the older mario games.Cheat: Secret Level in Milky Way WishesOn the level select screen in Milky Way Wishes, move kirby to the green star between Cavios and Skyhigh, and then enter the level. Here you can find the Copy ability.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/9/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>GMjG70AHm00</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1315</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588425-kirby-super-star</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/kirby-super-star</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kirby-super-star/3030-9233/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kirby_Super_Star</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/t95qEVQ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/T18PmM7.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Gysoaw7.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/4IYaptY.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/cadXKfL.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/Mehimd3.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/WIXnuwP.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/ArPRfJF.jpg</boxart8>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/WzcpOhz.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/xJ89pxu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/3UTlKHb.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/zimGcOs.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/kt6azw5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7iJEsA6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/6Wgnkjq.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/LdJ3xvw.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/nX0u7zG.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/OipB4eG.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/1ORnc16.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/yRQaJg0.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/C9aXFzM.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/vc0xxcZ.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/3JA9SNn.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/wncknMP.jpg</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/lwfMYRd.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>Dream Land is under siege again! Our hero, Kirby, returns to instigate a rescue. King Dedede is snatching up Dream Land's food supply, but he's not the only one! Dyna Blade, Meta Knight and a slew of other evil baddies are on the loose and wreaking havoc throughout the land. Use any of Kirby's amazing powers to create a "helper" to assist you in battle. Or have a friend join you for some two-player action by taking control of Kirby's helper. Help Kirby work through EIGHT challenging games filled with action and adventure. Enter the fray in Spring Breeze, enter a foot race against King Dedede in Gourmet Race and tackle a winged warrior in Dyna Blade. Hone your reaction skills in Megaton Punch and Samurai Kirby, then battle your way through the Great Cave Offensive, Revenge of Meta Knight and Milky Way Wishes. Each game is different AND some extra-special surprises are in store for you!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>neXqXnkl8Jc</VideoURL1>
	<boxart9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/58a230d0-87ae-4d1f-abb6-0af436d3639b.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/685ff8c2-af76-41b4-99c4-fd020328d9b5.jpg</boxart10>
	<boxart11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/651e0e55-f5c5-4e62-8dd1-e177fe45d3e6.png</boxart11>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/978bf3ea-e42b-428f-84c9-9ed176cdb973.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/929acaf5-0394-4e3c-9953-a9400521463d.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e956c0b9-dcb0-4b63-ac2d-b67585b95bc8.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67f899aa-2b51-4660-8ee9-fffb14014113.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1ab7b6f5-5c54-461b-8df9-91d4a17ae0b7.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0e8fa1b6-0eb6-48d6-9da6-ee39972eede9.png</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>