<Game>
	<Name>Kirby's Fun Pak (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Dream Land is under siege again! Our hero, Kirby, returns to instigate a rescue. King Dedede is snatching up Dream Land's food supply, but he's not the only one! Dyna Blade, Meta Knight and a slew of other evil baddies are on the loose and wreaking havoc throughout the land.Use any of Kirby's amazing powers to create a 'helper' to assist you in battle. Or have a friend join you for some two-player action by taking control of Kirby's helper. Help Kirby work through EIGHT challenging games filled with action and adventure. Enter the fray in Spring Breeze, enter a foot race against King Dedede in Gourmet Race and tackle a winged warrior in Dyna Blade. Hone your reaction skills in Megaton Punch and Samurai Kirby, then battle your way through the Great Cave Offensive, Revenge of Meta Knight and Milky Way Wishes. Each game is different AND some extra-special surprises are in store for you!Cheat: CameosIf you use the Stone ability enough, you may turn into a statue of Samus, or a golden statue of Mario.Cheat: CameosIn Megaton Punch, if you look in the background, you'll see Mario, Luigi, and a few other people from the older mario games.Cheat: Secret Level in Milky Way WishesOn the level select screen in Milky Way Wishes, move kirby to the green star between Cavios and Skyhigh, and then enter the level. Here you can find the Copy ability.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Hal</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>9.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>GMjG70AHm00</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1315</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588425-kirby-super-star</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kirby-super-star/3030-9233/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kirby_Super_Star</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/t95qEVQ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/T18PmM7.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/WzcpOhz.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/xJ89pxu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/3UTlKHb.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Ad1pGUZ.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Q0P1Bv7.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/3GXzW5g.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/j6W9yXc.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/q7yGion.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/m43zP9i.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/cQaKKva.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/1ORnc16.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/yRQaJg0.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/C9aXFzM.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/vc0xxcZ.jpg</fanart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/wncknMP.jpg</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/lwfMYRd.png</clearlogo2>
</game>