<Game>
	<Name>Kirby Bowl (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Scan the course and check out the obstacles ahead. Get ready for the most surprising game play imaginable in Kirby's battle against King Dedede!This checkboard challenge brings outrageous hazards and bizarre surfaces. Warp panels instantly transport you to new and exciting challenges. Conveyer belts provide higher levels of adventure. Turntables take the action in a whole new direction.Gordo, Kracko, Whispy Woods and a cast of zany characters await you. Gain special powers including Fireball, Freeze, Spark and Parasol. Transform your enemies into stars revealing eight hidden cups of each wildly different course. Control the force and angle of your shot and sink Kirby for a hole-in-one!Cheat: Gaining extra livesTo gain an extra life, you must make a Hole in One on any level. It's usually pretty tough to do, but the extra lives come in handy late in the game!Cheat: Gaining extra livesTo change your name without restarting the game, go to the member screen and highlight the file to be changed. Press L, R, and A at the same time to get to the Name Entry Screen.Cheat: Gaining extra livesIf you complete all EXTRA courses with a silver or gold medal (you have to have already completed all regular courses with a silver or gold medal) two new items will appear on the main menu: Sound Room and Dance Select.  Sound Room gives you a classic sound test screen where you can hear all 125 effects and 31 music tracks.  Dance Select lets you view any of the kirby dances that happen at the end of each single and 2-player round. </plot>
	<releasedate>20/2/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Arcade</genre>
	<Developer>Hal</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>THcSlrx4wxU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1774</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588427-kirbys-dream-course</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kirbys-dream-course/3030-9316/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kirby%27s_Dream_Course</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/dC3WLyl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/7eiDSyV.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/HDhp5HA.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ixk6Jns.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/PThslLT.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/MlYv0B0.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/3CK4s8H.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/v0C5tKG.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/AO6XVAq.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/vpyJinn.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/M6qh133.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/3UkoN2C.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/M3wiIaR.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/86S9u8M.png</clearlogo1>
</game>