<Game>
	<Name>Knights of the Round (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Knights of the Round is a  side-scrolling brawler - in the same genre as games like  Final Fight - developed by  Capcom in the early 1990s. The game is very, very loosely based on Arthurian legend. It follows the exploits of the legendary  Arthur and two of his Knights of the Round (Table), Percival and Lancelot, as they attempt to overthrow the fictional King Garibaldi and take his throne.Knights of the Round plays as one would expect. All three characters have an attack button and jump button. Pressing the attack button several times performs powerful combination attacks, while pressing back attack allows the knights to block most incoming attacks. By pressing both attack and jump at the same time, the knights will perform a powerful spinning attack which will knock back nearby enemies, at the expense of some of the hero's lifebar, making the attack useless. The life in that lifebar could be replenished by eating a hearty helping of turkey which could be found in crates and other smashable objects. Additionally, the knights can mount  horses, which vastly increases their combat prowess.Though the characters play very similarly, each knight has strengths and weaknesses.Arthur is the balanced character, with decent speed and strength.Lancelot is a speedy character, with great maneuverability but less strength.Percival is a large, slow character, who has very powerful attacks.Knights of the Round does have a feature rarely seen in brawlers. As the knights dispatch enemies, they gain experience which increases their stats and makes them more effective in combat. As each character levels up, their appearance changes as well. For instance, Percival starts the game with blond hair and a bare chest. As he levels up, he shaves his head, and gains bulky armor.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>0s5W6THYMKg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1316</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588428-knights-of-the-round</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/knights-of-the-round</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/knights-of-the-round/3030-15143/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/tXFT2h6.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/I9wXCpd.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Jp6WS3m.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/Ut119nw.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/zfLNDq3.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/mt0mfc9.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/nbtB3DT.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/qpNk6q7.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vKGF9w3.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/PczVdDc.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/283ha6M.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/McvGJ7m.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/0SlubO7.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/GdheNWi.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/7blBgaF.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/RcGEutD.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/9v7N4LY.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Legend says that the man who pulls the sword, Excalibur, from the stone is destined to be king. But even the power of Excalibur can not release Britain from the chaos into which it has plunged. Years of civil war have taken their toll and now only the power of the legendary grail can bring peace back to the land. Join Arthur, Lancelot and Percival as they begin their quest for the magic grail. Do battle with evil knights, petty tyrants and sinister sorcerers as you fight through the darkest trials that evil can muster. Defeat them all to reclaim the grail and you may assume your rightful place as a Knight of the Round!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/032976cf-d3a6-4d61-8259-78ad03c6e10f.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/66ee3216-e853-4b6d-b60c-fa9e6df979d3.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4f560182-105f-469a-aa9e-a0d71330f1f2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5abb7ddb-db33-4b17-9401-b3f15007bf33.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e4d393f3-83e5-4dd4-aae2-0d26d3ed6ff6.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>