<Game>
	<Name>Kouryuu Densetsu Villgust - Kieta Shoujo (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Kouryuu Densetsu Villgust: Kieta Shoujo ("Radiant/Armed Dragon Legend Villgust: Missing Girl") is a Super Famicom RPG from Winkysoft. The player is a regular schoolkid from modern Japan who has to rescue his girlfriend from a parallel fantasy universe named Villgust. He quickly encounters and befriends several warriors who are part of R.A.G.E. (Resistance Against the God of Evil) who are attempting to take back their world from evil forces.The game was followed up with a spin-off for the Famicom: Kouryuu Densetsu Villgust: Gaiden. It was also adapted into a pair of anime OVAs that came out several months after the game's release.CharactersShun - The main hero. Attempting to rescue his girlfriend. Like many RPG heroes, he's the best fighter in the group and has access to the strongest equipment.Michiko - Shun's girlfriend. She mysteriously appeared in Villgust and was quickly kidnapped. Doesn't fight.Kui - The toughest member of the initial group of RAGE that Shun meets soon after entering Villgust. A powerful front-line attacker.Chris - A skilled swordswoman with an acerbic attitude.Yuta - Another warrior with limited magical ability. A man of few words.Fanna - A female archer and the most powerful magic-user of the initial group.Murobo - A strong wolf-like beastman. Uses a giant axe in combat.Ryukia - A cat-like beastgirl who uses her claws in combat. Has purple hair and an optimistic outlook.Bostov - A dexterous ninja character that can attack whole groups of enemies with his boomerang.Lemi (Remi) - A female elf and a strong magic-user. Fights with a retractable whip staff.				</plot>
	<releasedate>23/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>1yJtH-3RUDQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18806</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581081-kouryu-densetsu-villgust</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/kryu-densetsu-villgust-kieta-shjo</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kouryu-densetsu-villgust-kieta-shoujo/3030-17419/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/K%C5%8Dry%C5%AB_Densetsu_Villgust</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Bq4lAWP.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/YWYiDBZ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/DUyGBkB.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/fMBe5cA.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/05IExlS.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/MXjmfdt.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/eOzHOYY.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/8ED69YK.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/EPHZJcI.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/uTbKAGt.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/FYoNUkf.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/l4VPBfL.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/qtTPh8i.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/hKRxHr6.png</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/mzb0Ali.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/OxnPBUJ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The main hero of this game is Shun, a teenager who lives in modern-day Japan. One day, when he was going back from school with his girlfriend Michiko, Shun noticed a strange red-eyed rabbit. When he tried to follow him, Shun suddenly found himself all alone in a forest clearing. He was immediately approached by a group of four adventurers who said they were members of a group called R.A.G.E. (Resistance Against God of Evil). Apparently, Shun was transported into a parallel medieval world, and an evil organization known as Vile was the one behind Michiko's kidnapping. Shun and his friends will now do anything to help Michiko and to destroy Vile! Kōryu Densetsu Villgust: Kieta Shōjo is a traditional Japanese-style RPG. You travel on the world map, visit towns, buy equipment and items, descend into dungeons, and fight random enemies in turn-based combat viewed from a third-person "over-the-shoulder" perspective. The party can hold up to five characters. The characters level up in a standard way, and also get experience and new levels for their magical spells.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>xdrF5QgIGDc</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3417da9a-ae53-49ec-9771-5ac20f8cbfff.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a9dcdbe2-34a6-4ea0-b952-1db3b45772e8.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/af2809c5-a88d-49cc-948b-9ca0465f98d8.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/108bb755-4566-482b-b6c1-97c076e0d5df.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23d35575-d706-4430-a075-fcc0f3d858cb.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>