<Game>
	<Name>Kunio no Oden (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Another tournament rocks the streets around the Nekketsu High area, and you know Kunio and his gang aren't going to let an opportunity to prove how baddass they are pass them by.The tournament this time is an eating contest, and the game itself plays like a block-lining puzzle game in the grand tradition of Tetris and Puyo Puyo. You must line-up blocks  of the same type as they fall in the classic rectangular play area, clearing them before time runs up or they fill the entire screen. Features a 1P tournament mode, and a 2P competitive Vs mode in which you can chain blocks and send them to your opponent as "attacks" in hopes of causing him/her to lose.Cheat: View Momozonos Hidden *Lover to Friend* Music ConcertTo view the hidden concert version of the BGM "Lover to Friend", select Omake Mode (bottom option) on the title screen. Then, scroll through the list of BGMs until you find Lover to Friend. Once highlighted, hold down Select+L+R, and press A-B-X-Y in that order while still holding down the other buttons. If done correctly, the screen will fade out and you'll be taken to a screen where Momozono will be standing in spotlight with stars in the sky. Now read the Japanese words and sing or hum along to her music.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/5/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Technos Japan Corp.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>26528</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581923-kunio-no-oden</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/kunio-no-oden</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kunio-no-oden/3030-1824/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Sy3Crqa.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/M2WlOzj.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ppIyffa.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wRrG5t9.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/LmTIiKo.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/04v10dt.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/BXO0msG.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Jw7jx5S.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FPP1sJm.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/USM8WJj.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JGlQhbZ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/dJ6s4Wz.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/MHYB48h.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>When Misako realizes her favorite Oden shop is going out of business, she comes to Kunio in helps he can save the business from going bankrupt. Kunio must awaken his appetite to save the Oden shop.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be5cbb2b-4c92-4f70-b24e-5deea4773700.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9df32f12-0871-46ed-93b3-74a8e10cd84d.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Technos Japan</Publisher>
</game>