<Game>
	<Name>Lamborghini American Challenge (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Starting out with just a basic Lamborghini and $6000, your aim is to rise to the top of the 4 divisions of racing through success on 60 racetracks across America. In each division there are 20 rival racers, up to 3 of which compete in each race at a time.The races also feature lots of local drivers (who can take crucial positions away from you and the other championship drivers), Sunday drivers going at normal speed, and police. before each race you will be told of the quality of the locals and the likelihood of police presence.When police are in the area, speeding beyond 110 Km/h could see you branded as an offender, at which point the police will try to ram you off the road, Chase H.Q.-style. You can attempt to reach the end of the race despite this damage (which eventually hampers your speed), or simply pull over and accept a fine and the loss of race points. If the police subsequently stop you, the fine is heavier.Each race costs money to enter, and your earnings can be boosted by betting on the results with the other championship drivers. If one of you wins, each driver gives you either the amount they bet or the amount you bet, whichever is lower; if a local wins you get your stake back.Lots of power-ups can be bought along the way, including tires, radar jammers, engine improvements and nitro boosts. To move up a division you must take the Divisional Challenge, a one-off trek through a tough section within the time limit. You buy a set of 3 passes for this, each allowing one attempt.Cheat: Shooting ModePlug a Super Scope into your Super Nintendo and turn on the game. This will bring you to a new game mode in which you control your car with the Super Scope and can shoot down your opposition while racing.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Titus France SA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>yviNuQPJKqw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3829</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588431-lamborghini-american-challenge</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/lamborghini-american-challenge</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/crazy-cars-iii/3030-2074/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/UfD2mfr.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/N0MOaNY.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/9Ty7Mkx.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/AwNHoO5.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/cVw90BB.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/tp3imfc.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/NajWWtM.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/p22A09q.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/jzIKCYL.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/eUjYQea.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rxpZTFI.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/B8VL7ER.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/3ASL4wf.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/J9xjYUw.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6sGUunu.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/GkcP8CU.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Imagine speeding along endless American highways in the fastest sports car in the world, racing against a multitude of artificially intelligent competitors in a bid to become the world number one. Well now your greatest fantasies can come true as you take the wheel of a Lamborghini Diablo in an attempt to become king of the Saturday Night races, an internal tournament in which eighteen drivers battle it out to become the world's greatest. Lamborghini American Challenge will test your driving skills but you must also be good at handling money, as each race requires an entrance fee which increases along with the challenge. Money can be gained by placing bets, which in turn can be spent on helpful power-ups and parts to enhance your car's performance. One final word of advice... watch out for those cops! Ready, get set, GO!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cfc5b92a-958b-49ba-b5a7-464a34967c1d.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d37a04b3-51db-46bc-8009-b9881322960b.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b60cf733-b841-4d9d-be41-b7ed2a5e7376.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/92a11012-4c1e-44d1-b9b6-78018a8fd15b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a3e61bf5-7083-4cae-9292-7b6e18a3e1de.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Titus</Publisher>
</game>