<Game>
	<Name>Leading Company (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Leading Company is a corporate strategy simulation game from Koei, and part of their library of modern business "Executive" strategy games that also includes Aerobiz and Winning Post. It's based around 1970s and 1980s corporate culture, with the player assuming control of a corporation that researches and produces VCR and VHS electronics. The player's given a plot of land with which to expand their operation, and must balance income and growth.The game was never released outside of Japan and is very text-heavy, making Japanese fluency a necessity in order to play it. It was originally released on the NEC PC-9801 and Sharp X68000 home computers and eventually ported to the Super Famicom. 	</plot>
	<releasedate>26/2/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Koei</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570914-leading-company</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/leading-company/3030-28302/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/0DlD0xL.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/eHs12Yj.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ENF7Gwt.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/nb4mNcU.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/XTcPoU7.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/S8jfBag.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/8ksKNRg.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ZIo1pej.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Wc24753.jpg</snapshot8>
	<Notes>Leading Company is a corporate strategy simulation game from Koei, and part of their library of modern business "Executive" strategy games that also includes Aerobiz and Winning Post. It's based around 1970s and 1980s corporate culture, with the player assuming control of a corporation that researches and produces VCR and VHS electronics. The player's given a plot of land with which to expand their operation, and must balance income and growth. The game was never released outside of Japan and is very text-heavy, making Japanese fluency a necessity in order to play it. It was originally released on the NEC PC-9801 and Sharp X68000 home computers and eventually ported to the Super Famicom.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/669edcec-b57b-48eb-bf10-7f50106844d2.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1745cd58-1ec3-4124-a51d-cc32e53ba59e.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b17eed61-f47b-4076-b150-63f7286abb92.png</snapshot10>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0f4b4007-f021-4990-87a0-1776e70aa112.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Koei Tecmo Europe Ltd.</Publisher>
</game>