<Game>
	<Name>Legend (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Legend is a SNES game developed by Arcade Zone. The game is a side-scrolling brawler in the same vein as  Golden Axe and the  Final Fight game series. It was published in the US by Seika Corporation and in Europe by Sony Imagesoft.Legend is played through the eyes of a character seeking to depose the leader of the nation of Sellech. The country is lead by Clovious, who is an incompetent and corrupt leader. In order to do this the player character must harness the power of Beldor's spirit. Beldor was a previous leader of Sellech, and ruled as a despot.In order to complete this quest to rid Sellech of Clovius the player is expected to fight against waves of hostiles. The protagonist is able to perform many different kicks and slashes in order to dispose of foes, but also has access to magic and special, ranged, attacks. When an enemy is defeated, they will drop different items. These items can include food (for replenishing health), and 'magic bags', which replenish magic and allow devastating, screen-clearing spells. In the spirit of all good brawlers, a stronger boss lurks in wait at the end of each stage.			</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Seika Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>pxJpOA36-4g</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3248</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588434-legend</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/legend-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/legend/3030-14402/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/EAu1f2O.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/UUa9eTJ.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/eGESviv.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/KudIPl5.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/0OVPCTh.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/MYt033x.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/m5EARSV.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/tASiH2l.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/DE9Nxam.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/a29gVoX.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/a7JLccL.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nEaSQiS.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/qiWV4ed.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/KW1epPM.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Egm0n1X.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/98UTKnH.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The action is non-stop, the villains gruesome, the weapons are wicked and the graphics are sensational. Travel back into a medieval time when your sword was the only law. Where the rich and powerful reigned over the land with an iron fist of terror. Only you can free the people of Sellech, and keep Clovis from resurrecting the evil power and curses of Beldor. Enter the Black Temple and battle through worlds of wizards and fire breathing dragons. Conquer the baddest boss monsters ever seen and fight your way through the uncharted world of Legend.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9436c726-2211-4efd-894a-c0aa3529d0a8.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/36e86fd6-1792-45f3-a51e-01535340f091.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f1860277-1785-4172-9d23-09412c86bc94.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/abf3e848-dd5a-4f57-a20a-18da22934271.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a82536f-ebd5-46c7-83e8-2feaafe3aa27.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Seika</Publisher>
</game>