<Game>
	<Name>Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past (France)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Originally released in Japan in 1991, The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past was released in North America and Europe in 1992 on the Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES). This game featured the series trademark hero, Link, on a quest to save the Princess of Hyrule, Zelda, who had been kidnapped by the evil wizard Agahnim. The game marked a return to the series' 2D overhead roots, which Zelda II: The Adventure of Link departed from. It is considered by many to be the best game in the series, though it is not quite as popular as Ocarina of Time.Story:Link battling Agahnim.The story of Link to the Past follows a young boy named Link who is contacted by a princess named Zelda. After rescuing her from a wizard named Agahnim, Link sets out upon a quest to retrieve the Master Sword and three mystical pendants. With the Master Sword eventually in-hand, Link defeats Agahnim, but is subsequently teleported into the Dark World version of Hyrule. Once there, Link sets off to find and defeat Agahnim yet again, but must first find the seven descendants of the Seven Sages throughout temples in the Dark World. After freeing the descendants throughout the Dark World, Link does battle with the Agahnim, and upon defeating him finds Ganon where Agahnim's remains lie. The final battle against Ganon ensues.Gameplay:World map of the Dark World.A major concept in Link to the Past is that a dark version of everything in Hyrule exists in a realm known as the "Dark World". This world was once a Sacred Realm until Ganon arrived and used the Triforce to bend the realm to his will, covering the land with darkness and despair. Throughout the course of the game, Link must travel between the Light World and the Dark World in order to complete certain puzzles and progress through the game's story. Some areas of the Light and Dark worlds are identical, but others have minute differences that alter Link's ability to travel through them. At first, Link is transformed into a reflection of his inner self whenever entering the Dark World, which leaves him unable to use items or wield a sword and shield, but eventually he collects an item that allows him to maintain his form while traveling through the Dark World (much to the surprise of the world's natural inhabitants).World Map of the Light World.About half of the game takes place in the Light World. Link must win three pendants in order to obtain the Master Sword, as well as defeat Agahnim at the top of Hyrule Castle. Most of the second half of the game takes place in the Dark World, where Link must revisit the seven temples which differ from their Light World counterparts significantly. While traversing the Dark World dungeons, it is sometimes necessary to travel to the Light World to manipulate an object, and then return to the Dark World where a consequence of that manipulation will allow Link to progress further. An example of this can be found when traversing the Dark World's water temple, as Link must first open two flood switches in the Light World's counterpart in order to allow him to venture further.While this " parallel world" mechanic made its first appearance in Link to the Past, it certainly wasn't the last Zelda game to use it. Ocarina of Time and Twilight Princess both included the ability to travel between parallel worlds, and many believe that this mechanic played a significant role in the success of each of these Zelda games.The structure of the game adheres to the formula of the series, of which this game is the prime example. Exploration of the towns and overworld is broken up by dungeon exploration, which involves solving puzzles and facing enemies, including a boss and a miniboss. In each dungeon, Link will find a new item that will allow him to solve puzzles or reach new areas, while also providing a key role in besting that dugeon's boss.EquipmentSwordsFighters SwordMaster SwordTempered SwordGolden SwordShieldsLink's tunicThe Blue Shield protects against arrows and rocks. It can be eaten by Like Likes/Pickit Plants.The Red Shield is an upgrade of the Blue Shield and protects against fireballs. It can also be eaten by monsters.The Mirror Shield is the final upgrade to the shield. It can protect against lasers, and is unable to be eaten by monsters.ArmorThe Green Tunic is Link's initial armor and provides no extra protection.The Blue Mail reduces damage taken by 25%.The Red Mail reduces damage taken by 50%.Pegasus ShoesThese shoes (renamed boots in the GBA version) allow Link to perform a dash. He will continue to run in a straight line until the player stops him or he crashes into an obstacle. The resulting crash can be used to break down certain walls or cause items to appear.GlovesThe Power Glove allows Link to lift light-colored rocks.The Titan's Mitt allows Link to lift dark-colored rocks.Zora's FlippersThese flippers allow Link to swim. His purchase of these flippers also allows him to use whirlpools as warp points.Moon PearlPossession of this mystical artifact allows the owner to keep his true form in the Dark World. If Link does not possess this item when entering the Dark World, he will become a pink bunny.ItemsFire RodLanternBoomerangBombBottleBug Collecting NetThe Book of MudoraBowMushroomsMagical PowderMagical MirrorMagic HammerHook ShotShovelFlute (Ocarina in GBA version)Ice RodFire RodEtherBombosQuakeStaff of SomariaStaff of ByrnaMagic CapeCheat: Death Mountain DescentDeath Mountain Descent will allow you to explore all of Dark World without obtaining the third pendant, the Master Sword, or defeating Agahnim. First, you'll want to get the Moon Pearl out of the Tower of Hera. That's necessary unless you want to stay as a bunny the entire time. Once you've acquired it, exit the dungeon. Now hop in the teleporter just outside the Tower of Hera and go to Dark World. Hop down the cliff, and make your way to the right. Go to where the broken bridge used to be in Light World. Now stand right under the top statue, as far against the wall and statue as you can get. Mirror to Light World. This is the tricky part, you must move ONE PIXEL to the right. No more, no less. If you don't do it correctly, you have to start all over. After you've moved, wait until you get teleported back to Dark World. You should be ONE PIXEL closer to the ledge now. Now DON'T MOVE! If you move, you will have to start over again. Mirror back to Light World. Now walk to the right until you're stopped by the bridge post. Wait until you stop flashing, and hold down the B button until your sword charges up, while still facing right. SLOWLY move backwards into the sparkly teleporter. If you don't do this slow enough, the trick won't work. When you teleport, if you don't get teleported back to Light World, you did the trick correctly. Now press right to jump off the cliff into the black stuff. Make your way around the black stuff and to the bottom of the screen. Go down one screen and you'll be on top of a cliff in Dark World. Hop off the cliff and you're now allowed to explore Dark World! If everything is glitchy, enter a cave, then exit and things will be normal looking.Cheat: Death Mountain DescentAnytime you have the Hookshot equipped, if any enemy or projectile comes to attack you, use the Hookshot, and while the Hookshot is extended, the attack will go right through you, and you will take no damage.Cheat: Death Mountain DescentIn the Dark World, go and stand EXACTLY where the mushroom is in the Light world(Somewhere in the Skull Dungeon). When you use the Magic Mirror to go back to the Light World,not only will you get the Mushroom but the trees will be glitched and you'll be able to fight some of the monsters that are only in the Dark World! When you leave the forest, everything will go back to normal.Cheat: Chris Houlihan roomStart at the Sanctuary and run south with the Pegasus Shoes until you are outside. Then, run south and stop before you hit the barrier. Proceed to run west until you are able to run south. When you run south, you should be in a wooded area with guards. Navigate this area and find the entrance to the castle grounds. While still running, go around the castle grounds to the hole where you fall into at the beginning of the game. If you did it right, you should be in a room with 45 blue rupees and a Saharasla sign that says: ''My name is Chris Houlihan'' and ''Let's keep this between you and me.'' Sometimes when you are fighting Gannon, you may fall into a hole and this may happen.Cheat: Aquire Invisibility Cape EarlyThere is a way to get the Magic Cape right after you get the Hammer in the Palace of Darkness(Dark World's 1st dungeon). In the graveyard in the Light World you'll notice there are dark colored rocks with the number 8 on the them surrounding a tombstone, but if you go to the same place in the dark world you can cut down a flower and dash into a pile of rocks that usually reveals a red ruby(worth 20 rubies). In this place you need to use your Magic Mirror north of the rock pile. If you've done this right you can circumvent the dark colored rocks in the Light World. Cheat: Aquire Invisibility Cape EarlyNote: You need to use the Magic Transprter between the Kakariko Village and the Lost Woods to reach this location.Cheat: Aquire Invisibility Cape EarlyThrow an empty bottle into the fountain at the Waterfall of Wishing. The faerie who appears will give you a free green potion.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/4/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>a6DpoeuJ4ww</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1318</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588436-the-legend-of-zelda-a-link-to-the-past</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/legend-of-zelda-a-link-to-the-past</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-legend-of-zelda-a-link-to-the-past/3030-10276/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Legend_of_Zelda:_A_Link_to_the_Past</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/RAaIooy.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/uoojg0h.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/JlwE5L6.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/mANiPUg.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/0cEkh1W.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/ZWWzwyj.png</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/CQqsT74.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/mXCANpw.png</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://i.imgur.com/GbOIRvR.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://i.imgur.com/c01zFpH.jpg</boxart10>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JrS39ut.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/BjH5vl8.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/g9dQoD4.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/mkwXuyg.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/cgqmxgW.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CgHZiBA.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/JDRjcai.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6PeWUx8.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/I4froTK.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/XNGz0aN.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/uOkvwVG.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/MHDg3jl.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/GntfxlM.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/89uhLgm.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/Ty4w0C8.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/dnquy6C.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>http://i.imgur.com/EvRgxg9.jpg</fanart7>
	<fanart8>http://i.imgur.com/XzXPm2Y.jpg</fanart8>
	<fanart9>http://i.imgur.com/WCVe339.jpg</fanart9>
	<fanart10>http://i.imgur.com/ZY4RarX.jpg</fanart10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Yto76Ei.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/IrQtrMQ.png</clearlogo1>
</game>