<Game>
	<Name>Legend of the Mystical Ninja, The (Germany)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Legend of the Mystical Ninja is the fifth game in the Ganbare Goemon series. It is the first game in the series to appear on the SNES, and the first to be localized for and published in America.PlotOkay, so the plot is a bit strange.The game takes place in a cartoonish representation of feudal Japan. The story follows Goemon and Ebisumaru's ( Kid Ying and Dr Yang in the non-Japanese releases) journey across Japan to rescue Princess Yuki, who had been kidnapped by the Otafu Army. Along the way, they fight past all manner of ninjas, monsters, ghosts, quiz-show hosts, villiagers, and robots.GameplayThe game is divided into multiple Warlock Zones, each one representing a different area around Japan. Each zone is split into two sections:The first section is a pseudo-3D villiage area where the protagonists fight against the various locals while  shopping for health items and powerups. These sections also host the game's  minigames, where players can take a break from the main game and earn extra cash and bonus items. The second section is a 2D side-scrolling platforming level. These levels contain the majority of the combat, and end with a climactic  boss fight.MinigamesGame Center, hosted by Konami GirlThe Legend of the Mystical Ninja has numerous minigames within the villiage areas in each stage. Some are within the Game Center area, while others are located in various homes and shopping centers in the level. Most of the games have a fee or opening wager to play, but usually have a way for the player to win cash or special prizes.GradiusLocated in the Game Center. This is the first level of Konami's classic side-scrolling shooter, Gradius.Tear Down The WallLocated in the Game Center. Tear Down The Wall is a Breakout-style game where the player bounces a ball on a paddle to destroy bricks at the top of the screen.HockeyLocated in the Game Center. An air hockey game for two players.MoleLocated in the employment office. This is a Whack-A-Mole game played with the SNES controller. Moles pop up from eight holes on the play field, where each hole corresponds to a button or direction on the SNES D-pad. Players get more money for each mole struck.PaintLocated in the employment office. In this game, the player controls the direction of a constantly-moving paint roller. The task is to paint as much of the canvas as possible without hitting a wall or overpainting any area. One dollar is awarded for every space that the player paints. One or two players, $80 entry fee.GoblinLocated in the employment office. In Goblin, the player must toss a ball into a basket that constantly moves from side to side. The force of the throw is controlled by how long the throw button is held down. Players get money for the balls they get in the basket. Sixty-dollar entry fee.QuizIn the Quiz Show game, players are asked trivia questions about the game by Quiz Master Shimopy. There is an entry fee of $100, with the chance to win $300.DiceRoll the bonesIn some houses around the game, there is a woman who will offer to play a game of dice. In the game, three dice are rolled, and the player guesses whether the outcome will be 10 or lower, or 11 or higher. The player places a bet which they can double if they guess correctly, or lose if they guess wrong.Fortune-TellingThe fortune-teller offers to read Goemon's future for a $50 fee. He will tell the player that something good, something bad, or nothing will happen. Based on his vision of the future, immediately upon exiting his house the player will encounter five Geishas (which can be collected for $50 each), five spear-toting villagers, or nothing at all.MazeOne of the many game-house barkersUp to two players can pay a $100 entry fee to explore a first-person labyrinth. Prizes hidden in the depths of the maze include bombs, scrolls, and cash that if found, are worth more than the fee taken at the door.LotteryBuy a ticket and participate in the game lottery. If the symbols that appear in the lottery match the symbols on the ticket, the player can win a cash prize.MemoryFor two players or play against the computer. Flip over two matching cards and win cash prizes. Increase the purse by matching a random special card.Horse RacesThe horse race track appears in the carnival area of the game in the third Warlock Zone. Players may bet as much as they like on different horses, and winnings are dependent on the odds of the fastest horse.Codes and TriviaThe Konami CodeIn one of the houses in the game, the man living there will advise the player that if they "use the command Up Up Down Down L R L R B A...nothing will happen." True to his word, the famous Konami Code has no effect in Legend of the Mystical NinjaInfinite HamburgersThis code uses the game's password save system to activate. By entering the password vxZ lh:@Y nn3 1 $T KK hG:!&lt; ! X@ r the player will start on the third stage with an infinite supply of hamburgers, essentially granting infinite health. Konami ManThe character with the winged hat who appears above the entrance to the Maze minigame is Konami Man. He was Konami's official mascot at the time The Legend of the Mystical Ninja was created. Konami Man was the star of a Japan-only Nintendo Famicom game called Wai Wai World. Deleted SceneThe Japanese version of The Legend of the Mystical Ninja contained a storefront in the Amusement Park zone that was not present in the American release. Even though it is mentioned in the instruction manual as "Sammy Rye's Circus Side Show," it does not appear in the actual game. For a fee, Goemon can enter the side show and see four clones of Ebisumaru do a short dance. TakosukeOn the bridge leading away from the Amusement Park zone on Awaji Island, the player encounters Takosuke. This huge red octopus is another of Konami's characters, who appears in the Parodius series. In the vignette that follows this level, Takosuke can be seen in the background, climbing the Konami headquarters building on Awaji.Cheat: Last Level +From the menu select "Continue" and then "From Logbook Entry" and enter this as your logbook to start on the last level with full health, a weapon at level three, all items, and all jutsus.  From here, simply keep heading up and left through the hallways until you get to a cell with a white wall.  Hit different parts of the wall until you hear a sound like you're making contact.  Keep hitting that spot and a door will open up.  Enter and you're on the last side-scrolling mission stocked to the gills.Cheat: Last Level +From the menu select "Continue" and then "From Logbook Entry" and enter this as your logbook to start on the second to last level with full health, a weapon at level three, all items, and all jutsus. From here, keep heading up and go through the doors to the castle. You'll meet the king who will tell you to go find the secret passage.  Exit, go down one screen, go left until you see three statues.  Beat the middle one until it breaks.  Enter and you're on the second to last side-scrolling mission stocked to the gills.  (Because there's no 'heart' nor 'triangle' character on my keyboard, I've used  to mean 'heart' and  to mean 'triangle'.  Make the appropriate substitutions when entering the code.)</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>tmv19VzLfW0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3211</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588435-the-legend-of-the-mystical-ninja</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/legend-of-the-mystical-ninja</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-legend-of-the-mystical-ninja/3030-9522/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ePbIODR.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ppWAF4r.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Y0eGLH8.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/ZUL4zLk.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/dHqerXu.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/uJeXPPH.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/sJeBAlX.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/i6ng3rm.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/3CV3Xls.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/yOt0PSE.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/nPxKP0S.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/eJMjftt.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/RTWiDOd.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/6VORpTr.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/9lzHSoy.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Bc2RZrP.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/64rjWFH.png</clearlogo2>
</game>