<Game>
	<Name>Lennus II - Fuuin no Shito (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Lennus II: Fuuin no Shito is the second and final entry in the Lennus series of JRPGs, known as Paladin's Quest in the United States, developed by Copya System for the Super Famicom. Asmik Ace Entertainment published Lennus II in Japan on July 26, 1996 and the it was never not released overseas by Enix like the previous title. An English fan translation patch was created by a group named Magic Destiny, currently known as Dynamic Designs, which was released on October 15, 2008.		</plot>
	<releasedate>26/7/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Copya Systems</Developer>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>14818</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563031-lennus-ii-fuuin-no-shito</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/lennus-ii-fin-no-shito</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/lennus-ii-fuuin-no-shito/3030-1135/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lennus_II</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/YZH7CMD.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/LicpkoN.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/HSUFqqY.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/5xD3bBP.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/LeqLPGu.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/5MaQAzE.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/hCufThx.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/hA38ufy.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/U0lET4u.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/MSmLOUF.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nLqPFAl.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/bOR0sQU.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JT3OmCI.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CrfY4mb.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/4idhIYq.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>This is a follow-up to the game "Lennus", which is known outside of Japan as Paladin's Quest. The game is set in a world of Andell - a floating continent where ancient prophecies and highly advanced technology co-exist. A curse has fallen onto Andell - its four island, once united, are now separated, and are floating away from the heart of the continent, the temple of Andell. The sages of the temple summon a great hero named Farse, who must find a special magic orb for each one of the islands, which is the only way to re-unite them. Farse embarks on his journey, aided by three Terranos, the big-eared inhabitants of Andell. This is a Japanese-style RPG where you control a party containing the main hero Farse and three Terranos you select out of the available five. You encounter random enemies and bosses and fight them in turn-based combat viewed from first-person perspective. You can use special attacks and magical spells, which don't consume magic points, but take away a certain amount of your hit points. Instead of healing items, you have mini-bottles you can refill with potions in special places in towns. You can equip various magical artifacts which will allow you to use magic spells belonging to eight different elements.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be468245-23cb-4f56-9f58-3f6b6545c1a0.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fb64d3fb-6b62-4a55-88e4-24669b7f82a5.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7e2f005f-cf58-4b37-b052-9200802a6b0b.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99cfa5c3-1ec7-4e85-a658-de82b5bdfe25.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6b0d7735-1c9a-4a9f-b424-19fabdfeda39.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Asmik Ace</Publisher>
</game>