<Game>
	<Name>Lester the Unlikely (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Lester the Unlikely is a side-scrolling platformer that uses a similar rotoscoping animation format seen in platformers such as Another World or Prince of Persia. Lester moves awkwardly and must carefully climb up high ledges and take small drops in order to avoid injury. He gradually becomes more confident in himself as the game progresses and becomes more effective at the platforming elements. He'll also stop being scared of creatures he encounters, walking past them or fighting them instead of screaming and running away.Lester the Unlikely was released exclusively on the Super Nintendo in 1994.Story:The "kind of geeky" and "kind of sleepy" hero Lester recently acquired the latest issue of his favorite comic book "Super Duper Hero Squad". While reading his new comic and walking along the docks, Lester soon falls asleep next to a cargo crate next to a nearby cargo ship. While asleep, Lester is loaded onto the ship with the the cargo by a crane and the ship sets sail along with Lester aboard. While on the sea, the cargo ship is hijacked by pirates, and in the chaos, begins to sink. Luckily our hero discovers a life jacket and swims to shore on an adjacent island. Now lost and stranded on an unknown island, Lester must search for someone or something that can help him survive and find his way home.						</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>DTMC, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>6qssl3qKwvQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3830</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588439-lester-the-unlikely</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/lester-the-unlikely</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/lester-the-unlikely/3030-2657/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/LZmz2Yj.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/attk5qL.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/riAmolp.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/RQdFT3s.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Nt9KHON.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/IKFC2ys.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/GawwFFM.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/2lw3lqg.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/9UwVYpQ.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/NnNI5pA.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/1anyRRR.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/gurqTTO.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UgQFzZi.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/V5HNKLH.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Marooned on a tropical island far from home, Lester faces it all with the courage of a small frightened rodent. Our unlikely hero has as much trouble walking as he does facing treacherous obstacles. It's the ultimate "geek to greatness" adventures as you guide Lester through his rite of passage. Help him face the terrors of the beach, the haunting chills of the underworld and the dreaded pirates of the south seas. Do all of this and Lester just might make it home, maybe even a little cooler than when he started. There's just one catch though, Lester can be slightly opinionated when it comes to his safety.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/873ca6a3-f76d-4596-ae1d-1caa4aa8b05e.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d2b47ca-9928-4989-b621-28d1ae34246b.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0949116b-2dca-480a-a787-57902146837f.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/92002149-3189-40c3-9588-c77bc8e001e3.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1ff75b9d-16ef-4640-ade3-5781ffbd36c3.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>DTMC</Publisher>
</game>