<Game>
	<Name>Libble Rabble (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Libble Rabble is a 1983 Namco Arcade game, created by the same Namco developer (Tohru Iwatani) that created Pac-Man and Pole Position. It features the characters of Libble and Rabble as they attempt to harvest Mushlins for dinner.The gameplay resembles the once-popular board game where players wrap rubber bands around pegs lined up on a board. The player, as the red (Libble) and blue (Rabble) arrows, must maneuver their attaching string around the pegs on the board and touch in order to create a closed loop. Anything within the loop is either collected (Mushlins, and other bonuses) or temporarily thwarted (Hoodlins, other enemies). Once all the Mushlins on the board are collected, the player moves onto the next stage. If nothing is collected inside a loop, it may spawn an additional enemy on the board.The game was eventually converted to the Sharp X68000, FM Towns and Super Famicom in 1993/94. While keeping most of the basic in-game art of the original Arcade game, it also featured 16-bit cutscenes that described the story.Cheat: Miracle ModeUsing controller 1, input this code at the title screen; a fanfare will play after you've entered this code correctly. After pressing Start, the MIRACLE MODE option will appear below SOUND TEST.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/9/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<VideoURL>mAJ2ADR0n_I</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571135-libble-rabble</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/libble-rabble</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/libble-rabble/3030-28305/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Libble_Rabble</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/q92psdY.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/dbdE0fB.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/tO361cN.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/bHSyogx.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ze3LKPc.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/uCW1Z9k.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/jRrVESL.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/YWu4Ngh.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/3VzbSJ5.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/V9CuemW.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5Ojneyg.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/UgW7Cxe.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/HAn9zYq.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Libble Rabble (?????? Riburu Raburu) is an arcade game that was originally released by Namco in October 1983. It was designed by Toru Iwatani, who had also designed the Gee Bee series, Pac-Man, and Pole Position. It is a curious but challenging game, where the player tries to harvest little mushrooms (Mushlins) while avoiding various enemies. It was ported to the Super Famicom in 1994. At first glance, the gameplay resembles Taito's Qix. The player controls two "arrows", one red (Libble) and one blue (Rabble) with a line strung between them. The object is to wrap the line around poles and surround Mushlins and enemies with it. The player can either close the loops themselves (worth more points for the Mushlins) or move both arrows to the same edge of the screen. The player clears a "season" when he or she harvests all the Mushlins.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>tltiiHB4bNU</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/94478571-defa-4a0d-af6b-d4c589440536.png</boxart4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/13d70430-7590-4aa4-8637-35073b48373a.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e5cc07b-9a7d-45c6-8563-d2c4dd70e64d.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>