<Game>
	<Name>Lock On (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Lock On is a jet fighter game that has the classic one man vs. the forces of evil formula.  After a vicious warlord threatens the nations of the world, the United Nations have recruited a hot shot ace pilot by the name of Jake Steel to go after the madman and bring peace back to the world.The player will partake in a variety of missions against both air and ground forces and can fly in four different aircraft (the British made Tornado, the Japanese FSX, the A-10 Warthog and the F-14 Tomcat).  The player can use each jets strengths to their advantage along with their powerful weaponry such as Vulcan cannons and heat seeking missiles against enemy jet fighters, tanks and other various enemies scattered throughout each mission.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Vic Tokai, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>2.83335</rating>
	<VideoURL>R87R9ldB6Lc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3212</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588446-lock-on</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/lock-on_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/lock-on/3030-37892/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ALKCygc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/1Rx7Jv5.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/FMxh3p0.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/WOm7kY0.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/cR2wTmw.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/MvtbNmV.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/NsKTWKY.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Bpa4LZg.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/bhBEya9.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/c5yy62O.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/sj5cVzZ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/e6vrkes.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/3zF6ZJK.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/55Jg5GG.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/0wjARwN.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Wreak havoc in the air when you lock on target and blast your enemies out of the skies. You are Jake Steel and it's up to you to stop a crazed madman from blowing up the United Nations. It's a tough job, but someone's got to do it. To make your job a little easier, you get to choose your weapon of attack. You can choose from four different aircraft: the F14 Tomcat, the A10 Warthog, the British Tornado, or the Japanese FSX. Lock On delivers realistic air to air combat and you'll be pulling G's that you never even knew existed. The enemy forces on the ground are not immune to your fire power either. You can defeat enemies in the air and on the ground.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/14be2c48-9691-4a9f-bac1-35062ae15f5d.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/145d3c63-67de-425e-a333-32108f28dfec.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/42de1469-380c-4170-8253-d649b1112b13.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a6e9aede-d250-4477-aaa6-afcf7bfbd7b0.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3124eb94-30ce-4f9d-bb0f-66a3a803f6a4.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a2d8d23f-fad8-44a3-8e69-e0afa227b017.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c6d9e6a2-511f-4941-8ef4-b9270a2abcd6.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Vic Tokai</Publisher>
</game>