<Game>
	<Name>Looney Tunes Basketball (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Story:Oneday Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck finish acting out an episode of Looney Tunes on a stage. Daffy calmly says "Another day, another artistic triumph."Bugs Bunny decides to challenge Daffy Duck with "Not bad. Think you can keep up in a game o' hoops?""Surely you jest!" Daffy responds, "Lead the way, rabbit. I've got more dunks than a donut shop."Just then, a basketball that was sitting to the side of the stage turns into a dog and runs away. In astonishment and awe, Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck pursue this dog basketball.Characters:There is a total of eight playable characters within this each either with those own statistics in the categories of shooting, 3 pointers, defense, speed, and stamina. Games are played as 2 vs. 2 only.Bugs BunnyDaffy DuckElmer FuddWile E. CoyoteTasmanian DevilYosemite SamSylvesterMarvin the MartianPowerupsPowerups can be used by spending money collected through gems that appear randomly on the court.Cream pie (10 cents) - The character throws a cream pie at the opponent, stunning him for a few seconds. If the pie misses the opponent, the player must duck to avoid getting hit with the pie himself.Long Range (10 cents) - The player launches the ball from far away for a high percentage 3 point shot. Each Looney Tune has a unique animation for doing soTime Bomb (15 cents) - The ball transforms into a time bomb. The players then pass it back and forth with their opponents. Whoever is holding the bomb when it explodes is stunned.Defense (15 cents) - Each Looney Tune has a unique animation that stuns one or both of the opposing playersEclipse (20 cents) - The entire screen turns pitch blackBack Door/Teleport (30 cents) - The players not holding the ball is teleported to directly under the rim on the opposite side of the court.Forcefield (50 cents) - The players glows and is impervious to stealsVegas (50 cents) - The score board turns into slot machine reels. When the player makes a shot, the reels stop. The number of gems on the reels correspond to a multiplier applied to the shot. If the reels stop on 3 bomb, the shot is worth 0 points. Dunking negates this powerupCheat: Action CodesEach code costs money and performs some action that aids your team. T is turbo, UDLR are directions on d-pad. ABXY are their respective buttons. All codes assume you are using default controler configuartion. Costs are given in brackets.Cheat: Action CodesType all codes during gameplay. Each code assumes that you are ussing the default controller configuration. No codes require holding of buttons but some are easier to accomplish if the second last key is held. T is turbo, UDLR are the directions on the d-pad and ABXY are their respective keys.Cheat: Action CodesHere are all the transform codes in the game. Each lasts about 10 seconds. T is turbo, UDLR are directions on d-pad. ABXY are their respective buttons. All codes assume you are using default controler configuartion.Cheat: Action CodesAll of these codes can be entered any time during gameplay.Cheat: Dunkus MaximusWhile choosing a character for a VS match, flip around Wile E Coyote for a while and his name will change to (Dunkus Maximus)</plot>
	<releasedate>20/2/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Arcade</genre>
	<Developer>Sculptured Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>p-COcGA_ncA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3213</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588447-looney-tunes-b-ball</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/oTIqErj.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Kodt8PM.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/5delj4R.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/1ehsuS4.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wOzGzT7.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/2ieUv7o.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/T88ATdk.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/71zda7a.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FodRiEm.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/IEJNWVf.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/52WTXPA.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/hrVGrtf.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/EQBKMki.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/fOfB4x5.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/z7XZ95Y.png</clearlogo1>
</game>