<Game>
	<Name>Lucky Luke (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Based on the famous comics series about good cowboy Lucky Luke.In the game you as Lucky Luke have to arrest four Dalton brothers  Averell, William, Jack, and Joe. On your mission you will progress from level to level shooting bad cowboys, jail-breakers, and bad Indians with your revolver; collecting bullets, dynamites, sheriff stars, and other useful items; running, jumping, ducking, and climbing. The locations vary from Forts, Towns, and Jails to Mines, Train, and Saloon with Ghosts. On every level you have to complete different submissions to progress  either to free a Bank Director, or to collect Three Nuggets for Miner to obtain a Nitroglycerine, or to build a Totem for Apaches, etc. At the end of some levels you confront the big boss, it is often the one of Daltons.Different arcade sequences between levels allow you to chase the Dalton brothers or train riding your faithful horse Jolly; to run away from Tornado; and to ride on the raft. Bonus level arcade sequences represent your wrestling challenge with Jolly, bottles shooting, or revolver's barrel roulette.To access the one of the three certain parts of the game you may enter password.The game was made in French/English/German/Spanish.Cheat: Cheat ModeAt the first screen that appears after booting, enter the code.  As you press each button, it must be held down until the entire code is entered.  The words CHEAT MODE and the number will appear if entered correctly.  For Cheat Mode 02, during gameplay press Select to open the debug menu.  You can hold R to freeze action, too.  An extra option, SNES, is also added to the options screenCheat: Level PasswordsAt the start screen go to Options then Password</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1997</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Infogrames Multimedia SA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>BQV-U-64UKw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1779</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/924623-lucky-luke</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/lucky-luke</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/1HiDjrP.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/wOXGShT.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/BoU0FNG.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/8NtGDL9.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Qxffpvq.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/qzFHDOF.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/njAgwqg.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/WNArapT.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/E4Hnbjg.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/jetRtaC.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/i0dSlPR.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/QvTs21W.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/HlpOR2g.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/NesyVzW.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/T8MRHJo.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/xnZp54w.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/zPIkBes.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/2PGJmNO.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Based on the famous comics series about good cowboy Lucky Luke. In the game you as Lucky Luke have to arrest four Dalton brothers – Averell, William, Jack, and Joe. On your mission you will progress from level to level shooting bad cowboys, jail-breakers, and bad Indians with your revolver; collecting bullets, dynamites, sheriff stars, and other useful items; running, jumping, ducking, and climbing. The locations vary from Forts, Towns, and Jails to Mines, Train, and Saloon with Ghosts. On every level you have to complete different submissions to progress – either to free a Bank Director, or to collect Three Nuggets for Miner to obtain a Nitroglycerine, or to build a Totem for Apaches, etc. At the end of some levels you confront the big boss, it is often the one of Daltons.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9a4f79ea-a2f0-42d3-9d02-55da9ff41212.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/060e16d6-a347-4379-8d72-106a265c4de6.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5313860f-83ce-4ee0-a3de-204b11b19015.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/611ea890-06f0-4044-ab52-97146152a939.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Infogrames</Publisher>
</game>