<Game>
	<Name>Lupin Sansei - Densetsu no Hihou o Oe! (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Lupin III: Densetsu No Hihou wo Oe! ("Lupin the 3rd: Hunt for the Treasure of Legend!") is a Super Famicom exclusive platformer featuring Monkey Punch's gentleman thief Lupin III. Though based on the anime adaptation of the manga, the game has an original plot and puts Lupin III up against his old nemesis Inspector Zenigata as he climbs through a skyscraper to look for the kidnapped Fujiko Mine.The game was one of the few to use Epoch's Barcode Battler II adapter peripheral, which was used to unlock additional content in the game by scanning the right cards into the device while it was connected. Cheat: Level PasswordsEnter Goemon, Jigen, Lupin, Fujiko as a password.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>SAS Sakata</Developer>
	<VideoURL>4tS9fjNFwoA</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588453-lupin-iii-densetsu-no-hihou-o-oe</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/lupin-iii-densetsu-no-hihou-wo-oe/3030-23288/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/S5WhioJ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mldBj0S.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Cw21BXM.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/EmHiaRa.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/HHRJCsC.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/bifs8PK.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/POGSkj8.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/i0EU02N.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/0zPJ881.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/8N3MjxI.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/uPeenTA.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/DgTNx2i.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Lupin, Jigen, and Goemon are at their Manhattan hideout plotting their next caper, when suddenly a large masked man bursts in. The man is escorted by a woman who proceeds to tell Lupin and the others that Fujiko has been kidnapped and is being held prisoner at one of the skyscrapers downtown. In order to get her back they must find the fountain of youth. When the two leave, Lupin decides to go and rescue Fujiko himself and sets off to save her. When arrives he discovers that the building is crawling with police, all under the command of Zenigata... so Lupin must enter through the building's ventilation to find Fujiko.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL1>jwuFbEB4ESY</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3ce85b07-c4ea-4ef1-8b5a-2dfca8f191a8.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7cacb0ad-03f5-4b7f-b5cf-3f994390ee05.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Epoch</Publisher>
</game>