<Game>
	<Name>Madden NFL 96 (USA) (Sample)</Name>
	<plot>John Madden returns for the '96 season of Madden NFL.Play exhibition, Super Bowl, playoffs or full season with any of the 1995 teams or all Madden teams.While you can still select weather and there are over 100 injuries, this version adds voice-overs and the ability to draft and create players and see if they get drafted.Still includes windowless passing, all new Madden-designed strategies and team match-up that shows how your players stack up to the other team in their position.Cheat: Codes to get teamsHighlight the All-Madden team and press B, A, L, L, Select.Cheat: Codes to get teamsOn the team selection screen Highlight the Panthers and press: L,Y,B,R,A,R,YCheat: Codes to get teamsHighlight the Panthers and press L, Y, B, R, A, Right, Y.  Cheat: Codes to get teamsAt the Game Setup screen, highlight the Quarter Length option and put in the following code to get 15 second long quarters. Y, A, Y, A, R ButtonCheat: Codes to get teamsTo get the Super Bowl Win screen, enter the following code at the Game Setup screen: A, Y, A, Y, L ButtonCheat: Codes to get teamsOn the team selection screen Highlight the Jaguars and press: A,Y,B,A,B,YCheat: Codes to get teamsAt the Setup Menu, press A, Y, A, Y, L.  Cheat: Debug Screen As you turn on the system hold the start,select,L,R, and A buttons on the second controller.Cheat: Debug ScreenHold START,SELECT,L,R,A on Controller 2 while turning the game on. Once at the hidden ''Gamepak Stats'' screen, you can clear the battery backed memory by simultaneously pressing DOWN,B,Y,L,R. This will erase all the stats.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>290</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588458-madden-nfl-96</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/madden-nfl-96</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/madden-nfl-96/3030-12957/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/g8c2wm6.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/k2CrsVH.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/0xq7hM1.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/KDuX0nZ.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/W8dzX12.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/aKvibNB.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RxrKAXs.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/t4eUBlB.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/FXYsCUA.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/KZpYprL.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/usRFE0V.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/6JCmxKg.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/bVBk63W.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/hevRRiS.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CPE95lj.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/mm0W1IZ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The Ultimate Madden!  - Scouting Combine - Game within the Game - Create Players at any Position, Compete in 14 different events, Results determine player ratings and draft position. - General Manager - Trade players and sign free agents - NFL Player Portraits - Pat Summerall and Lesely Visser join the EA Sports Broadcast Team - All 30 NFL Teams - Hidden codes reveal secret teams</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8f6032be-a248-407b-96b6-83895ce462e9.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8163074c-a249-40ed-887f-1faf82b52190.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/69af5eb0-0e58-4649-95a4-1026aaeec91e.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b510ed8a-7a51-403a-ba38-e8e7791e40fb.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>EA Sports</Publisher>
</game>