<Game>
	<Name>Madden NFL '94 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Madden NFL '94 is the third in the Madden series of football games for the SNES. It features 80 teams -- 28 teams from the 1993 season, 38 Super Bowl teams from 1966-1991, 12 All Star franchise teams since 1950, and two "All-Madden" teams: one for the 1993 season and one from a 20-year time span. You can play these teams in a regular exhibition game or sudden death overtime game, or take the 1993 teams through an entire season. You can also enter the playoffs with the 1993 teams, the Super Bowl champions, or the All Star franchise teams. Unlike many other sports games, saving a season is done by password rather than by storing the data into a saved game.Cheat: Easily block field goalsWhen on defense against a field goal or extra point, take control of your fastest player. In most cases, this will be the player all the way on the right.Cheat: Easily block field goalsLine him up between the long snapper and the guard to his right, but just a hair above where they are standing. In Madden 94, the line of scrimmage is not the ball, but the feet of whoever is snapping the ball. This is how you'll be able to line a man up so close to the offensive line in the first place.Cheat: Easily block field goalsWhen the ball is snapped, you'll easily be able to shoot your man through the line and block the kick thanks to this lovely little glitch.Cheat: Easily block field goalsWhen the computer is forced to punt, take your fastest player and line him up on the left side of the field, just outside the leftmost offensive lineman. When the ball is snapped, you'll easily be able to use your superior speed to charge in and block the punt due to the running back in the punt formation never moving over to assist in the blocking scheme.Cheat: Easily block field goalsTake control of your fastest defender and line him up directly in between the offense's guard and center, but a hair above where they are standing. If done correctly, you will not be called offsides when the play begins. The line of scrimmage in Madden 94 is parallel to the feet of the offensive lineman as opposed to the ball, which is why you're able to line up so close to the offense in the first place.Cheat: Easily block field goalsWhen the ball is snapped, you'll have plenty of time to blast your defender through the line untouched, and you'll be able to stop virtually every play in the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-5 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3219</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/930709-madden-nfl-94</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/madden-nfl-94</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/madden-nfl-94/3030-7106/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/zlOac9n.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/TxBMGnG.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7cwLJk2.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Y7WOIMV.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/yIJscj8.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/nSQ5oPY.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/N9Pw5hq.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/rV8rFbt.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/mzzPJqR.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/AKSoCUw.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/F6AgSJE.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ayno4IR.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ERvNuYL.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/XClH8Nr.png</clearlogo1>
</game>