<Game>
	<Name>Madden NFL 95 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Madden NFL '95 is a football game for the 94/95 season of American Football presented by John Madden's virtual doppelganger. It is the The game takes the advancements of the prior games in the series and continues to tweak the rules, animations and graphics. The game features the NFL license and contains all 28 teams in the NFL at the time. The Genesis version also has the NFLPA license, allowing the use of real names for the athletes as well.The game would be followed by Madden NFL '96.							Cheat: Expansion TeamsBefore beginning a new game, go to the Game Setup Screen and highlight either the Home or Visiting Team Options. Press L,R,L,R,A to play as the Jaguars or press L,R,L,R,Y to play as the PanthersCheat: Expansion TeamsIn exhibition mode, go to game length, and hit L, R, L, R, X. You should get one minute game time. Cheat: 69 BearsTo Play with the 69 Bears and little Walter press YYXY at the team slectCheat: Easily block puntsWhen the computer is forced to punt, select the "Punt Rush" formation, then take control of your fastest player and line him up on the left side of the field, just outside the leftmost offensive lineman. Remember to use the line of scrimmage glitch to your advantage and move him down a little bit.Cheat: Easily block puntsWhen the ball is snapped, you'll easily be able to use your superior speed to charge in and block the punt due to the running back in the punt formation never moving over to assist in the blocking scheme. It should be noted that while this glitch is practically identical to the glitch seen in Madden '94, you need to be much faster this time around to pull it off correctly.Cheat: Easily block puntsTake control of your fastest defender and line him up directly in between the offense's guard and center, but a hair above where they are standing. If done correctly, you will not be called offsides when the play begins. The line of scrimmage in Madden 95 is parallel to the feet of the offensive lineman as opposed to the ball, which is why you're able to line up so close to the offense in the first place.Cheat: Easily block puntsWhen the ball is snapped, you'll have plenty of time to blast your defender through the line untouched, and you'll be able to stop virtually every play in the game.Cheat: Easily block puntsAfter scoring a touchdown, you can use a very simple glitch to guarantee yourself an extra two points. Select Goal Line Halfback Lead Left.Cheat: Easily block puntsThe AI will always come out with their Field Goal block team and call an audible. Snap the ball while they're running around like idiots changing their defense around and you'll have a free path to the end zone every single time.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-5 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.7</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3834</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588457-madden-nfl-95</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/madden-nfl-95</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/madden-nfl-95/3030-7715/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/SidQOU3.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/h9qZ3yE.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/jEBjM3b.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/jEig65Y.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/72C4Y7M.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Gpt3L9O.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Zm2ySrb.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/aCVFgYy.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/0zIRveM.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DxqdJ9f.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/FTV8CZc.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/L4vLJQB.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/EaTo6HW.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/MJs4v1j.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/2dHtCIk.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/gckDfyw.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1DCy8bh.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/6bNAgHJ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Last week our #1 wideout was lost for the season. This week our all world rookie steps in-with off the planet speed but no hands. Under a minute &amp; down by seven from our own 45, we go with the no huddle against the Bears' Grizzly Attack. With the boys up front in gap protection, and passing windows off, I check the tight end. He's blanketed by the zone, but I see the rookie down the sideline. I make the read, fire a bullet and the kid actually hauls it in, straight arms the corner and high steps down the sideline for six. Sweet. I peel myself off the turf in time to catch him cabbage patching through the paint. Then I look to the sidelines and the man says go for two - and the win. - Any Madden 95 QB</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/394790d3-4d71-4564-87df-02cc9041a371.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9b33d456-41b9-4b15-97f5-e498b08fcc09.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f383d33a-de6a-46d3-95e8-b0243a838630.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e53a57e4-ad03-40bb-83a2-8be718722ab7.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>