<Game>
	<Name>Madou Monogatari - Hanamaru Daiyouchienji (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The game is set in the same universe and shares characters and storyline with  Puyo Puyo puzzle games. Unlike Puyo Puyo, Mado Monogatari is a Japanese-style RPG. You play Arle, a five-year old apprentice magician. She is attending a special kindergarten, and it is time for the Final Exam. At the same time, Arle receives a mysterious letter that tells her that if she finds eight magical gems and takes them to the Wizard Mountain, she'll be granted one wish. Arle decides to search for the gems which are scattered all over the world, and to overcome all the obstacles with her great magic power!The game features random enemy encounters and turn-based combat, which takes place on a platform (Arle to the left, the enemies to the right). You can't perform physical attacks at all, and your only way of harming enemies is through magic. During the game, you learn a variety of magic spells, which can be upgraded later. In battles you can't see your own and the enemies' hit points, and have to act according to your intuition.Cheat: Automatically win easy battlesWhen the screen goes black after encountering a weak enemy, hold down L or R and you will skip the battle but you will receive experience and cookies as if you have fought the battle normally.Cheat: Automatically win easy battlesBehind the Devil's Door, in Bazaar, talk to Sasori man (a guy that looks like a scorpion) and take a ride to the ancient town. Travel slowly and listen to the Dark Concert to be able to listen any music from the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/1/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Tokuma Shoten Publishing Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>LLCuxXlB8h8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>23377</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581924-madou-monogatari-hanamaru-daiyouchi-enji</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mad-monogatari-hanamaru-daiychienji</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/madou-monogatari-hanamaru-daiyouchienji/3030-11513/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mad%C5%8D_Monogatari:_Hanamaru_Daiy%C5%8Dchienji</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/LxiQHK8.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/biYts4U.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/S5H2fML.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/jeDxVfH.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lLzsAYT.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/K9seifk.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/AXKCokj.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/lExXTlO.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/3q7kEu2.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/rpn1Qc9.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/u7l9OUh.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/AI2y32v.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/IuKfxoH.gif</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ICOjAd7.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Arle Nadja is 5 years old and is attending kindergarten, and it´s final exam time. But in order to take her final exam, she needs to locate a Final Exam Certificate... In the meantime, a letter arrives which speaks of eight magical gems. Find all eight and take them to the Wizard´s Mountain, and you will be granted one wish. Arle decides to search for the gems and wish for her final exam certificate, and along the way she´ll have to fight off a gang of local bullies and other various characters you may recognize from the Puyo Puyo series of games!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5a0f1cbc-48da-4777-b8fd-bfb085acabb4.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9c0c5906-296b-4897-8b0b-28dd57a36c10.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/946d7ed6-4342-427d-b2a0-0434dc15c7a9.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Compile</Publisher>
</game>