<Game>
	<Name>Magical Drop 2 (Japan) (Bunka Housou Special Version)</Name>
	<plot>In Magical Drop II, you control a clown that can grab and throw balloons. You have to match three balloons of the same colour or more vertically to pop them and clear the screen. You can hold multiple balloons of the same colour at once and cause consecutive collisions. There are special balloons that cannot be removed that easily and power-ups that clear entire rows or provide additional help.Depending of the originating country, there are different game modes:1. Survival: Play as long as you can - an endless flow of balloons appears at a rapidly increasing speed while you move up levels.2. Puzzle: You have a limited time to clear a fixed set of balloons before time runs out.3. VS Mode: Fight the CPU or a fellow player in a direct split-screen duel. Each character has specific item balloons during gameplay.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Data East Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>oGI5C5X032g</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>21138</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575220-magical-drop-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/magical-drop-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/magical-drop-ii/3030-7667/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ODwItHS.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/NAXKayv.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/lIJfS8c.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ghUeUbQ.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/MHWGq3J.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/DyN8aqf.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/30OsPcg.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/UECJaZS.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Ook80r0.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/BNWHepr.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/RjGy5UH.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NpNFHGF.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/hjGiL9J.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Magical Drop is played in a style and gameplay similar to Compile's (now Sega's) Puyo Puyo and Taito's Puzzle Bobble franchises; a "stack" of random colored bubbles descend from the top, and a player is defeated when a bubble hits the bottom. Bubbles can be picked up and dropped by the player's "clown" at the bottom, and are destroyed when three or more of the same color are put together on a single column. "Chains" are formed either when a single drop caused a chain reaction, or when more than one group of bubbles is destroyed in quick succession. The game is normally played with two players (one may be a computer opponent), and chains cause the opponent's stack to descend faster. There are 24 characters, all but the Black Pierrot being named after a tarot card (although the Strength card has been represented by two characters throughout the series). Different characters have different attack patterns. The columns of the opponent's stack will descend at different rates relative to each other depending on the character chosen. This causes a disjunction of colors that may make it more difficult for the other player to clear their stack. For example, with the character Devil, all the columns will descend at the same rate, whereas with Sun, the middle columns will descend faster than the others.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/151c7d84-5a4e-4060-84f4-17bf5e74711b.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d5ec9a54-81d0-48b7-afdd-c900d6e40d01.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Data East</Publisher>
</game>