<Game>
	<Name>Majin Tensei (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Majin Tensei is a Japanese-exclusive Super Famicom turn-based SRPG developed by Atlus and released in 1994. The first of several SRPG games in the Megami Tensei franchise, Majin Tensei tasks the player with fighting an onslaught of demons that suddenly appears in the world and, when possible, negotiating with them so that the demons will join their cause. Although in terms of presentation and gameplay mechanics the game greatly resembles other SRPG series such as Nintendo's Fire Emblem with regards to how battles are conducted and the player roams the map, Majin Tensei still contains a number of a features that are common to Megami Tensei games specifically, including the aforementioned demon recruitment/negotiation, fusion, and lunar cycles that affect demon strength and behavior, among other things.Majin Tensei would later go on to spawn another Japan-only sequel for the SNES titled Majin Tensei 2: Spiral Nemesis, as well as two spin-offs, Ronde for the Sega Saturn and a cell phone side story that picks up where the first game ends.Plot:In the late 1990s, the world explodes with ethnic conflicts, resulting in massive death and the closing off of much of the world. Several decades later, in the year 202X, a boy living in area D-03 of Nieder Tokyo suddenly receives a strange demon summoning program on his personal COMP, with demons suddenly appearing in the world immediately afterwards.							</plot>
	<releasedate>28/1/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>UsUMpiOo_uA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>31478</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581302-majin-tensei</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/majin-tensei</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/majin-tensei/3030-17102/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Q4tAZBT.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/YgckxuP.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Hs4VBgY.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/D8fvafV.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/iI0B37d.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/E7CCrEX.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/gosxnF9.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/KRAsmKV.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/vzR2IXG.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vFdH2F8.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/XUAsr0G.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2YRu9jU.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/qEKarEy.gif</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/qq56hDC.png</clearlogo1>
</game>