<Game>
	<Name>Mario Paint (Japan, USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Mario Paint is a paint program and minigame collection, with games that range from reflex-based fly swatting to music compilation. The game included the SNES Mouse peripheral and a plastic mouse pad. The mouse itself consisted of a roller-sensor and left and right-click buttons.Game Modes:Drawing BoardText Music CompositionAnimationColoring BookGnat Attack Drawing BoardThe Drawing Board is the game's standard paint program. Here, the player is given tools such as pencils, fills, and stamps to draw and color whatever they wish.Text Music CompositionWhen on the drawing board hit the Text Stamp Icon to open up text. Mario Paint has upper and lower case English letters, numbers, and three types of Japanese (Hiragana, Katakana, and Kanji).Music CompositionThis mode allows players to place various icons representing sounds on a note-chart to create music. The sounds vary from from traditional twings and twangs, to the beeps of a Game Boy and Yoshi sound effects.AnimationMario Paint offers a simplistic tool to create animated sequences. Using a limited number of frames, the player can draw a sequence of images that can then be played as an animated short.Coloring Book Coloring BookIn the game's coloring book, there is a collection of pre-drawn images featuring Nintendo characters and other items. In this mode, the player is free to color the images using fill and drawing tools. Gnat AttackGnat Attack is a training game. The mouse is used to control a flyswatter, and the player must swat incoming insects before they sting the player's hand. Hands representing extra lives can be collected over the course of play. The goal is to swat 100 insects to reach King Watinga. When King Watinga is defeated, hands will appear on the screen and applaud the player.										</plot>
	<releasedate>1/8/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>qwyxaiIYv7Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1781</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588465-mario-paint</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mario-paint</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mario-paint/3030-8791/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Y7pcyde.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/K7Deygm.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/skA2NUp.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/F8s6WNu.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/ZyZHlhF.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/Q9oPqQB.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/mVywiEt.jpg</boxart7>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/inNnFr4.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/kbH813p.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FHffcNO.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RJ6hNvF.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Xu5rfGG.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/UUrjAWu.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/MwXJOoN.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/VggiXTO.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/aQj7z6U.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NRgfjXk.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/lJShDBg.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1re44Qy.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/OtA99PX.png</clearlogo1>
</game>