<Game>
	<Name>Mario's Early Years - Preschool Fun (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Ah, the easy life. For Mario, that is. And that also describes the game. Too easy. Even for a preschool child it's too easy. I wouldn't even dig this game as a 3 or 4 year old. Although the animations are really catchy. Bottom line: Nintendo made a grave mistake making this game. Children of course love playing as the mustached Plumber, but they'd rather see him stomping on goombas rather than bumping his head on a red square.Directions:You are Mario, Peach, or Yoshi and you're playing games that have no end and no reward. The games are to challenge youngsters about numbers, letters, shapes, sizes and the like.Controls:A Button - Pick things on certain gamesB button - Pick thingsX Button - Pick things on certain gamesY Button - Pick things on certain gamesStart Button - Start gameSelect Button - NothingReviewer: Bloody_rivenhttp://www.consoleclassix.com/snes/marios_early_years_preschool_fun.html</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Educational</genre>
	<Developer>The Software Toolworks</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>dIUpPXDQb80</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3839</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588468-marios-early-years-preschool-fun</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/marios-early-years-preschool-fun</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/marios-early-years-preschool-fun/3030-26024/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/a6UP2U1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/A5I7x8l.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/7P6tF4i.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/QbTZHa5.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/R0BYvGA.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/0XX30df.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/8bRoPFL.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/AV0fzk3.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ObV8ICo.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/kS4jRV9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/EmVWzbP.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/eZp3HIf.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/MlyoN6Q.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In PRESCHOOL FUN, children develop concepts through the exploration of shapes, colors, sounds, opposites, and numbers. With Mario’s help, your child learns to define and identify these subjects without pressure. Your child simply guides Mario, selecting objects on the screen which Mario bonks and bounces through, frequently affirming your child's correct choice. With Mario, Luigi, Princess Toadstool and all their friends as classmates, your child just may make the biggest stride since learning to walk. That's because MARIO'S EARLY YEARS is all about learning to think in a way that doesn’t seem like learning, but much more like playing. Moms and Dads get to interact and play, too. Mario invites them to join in the fun and observe their kids as they become totally involved in the learning process.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/34aa31ac-5c50-4913-85df-f91ae5f3d1d8.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0f401ea-47cd-40f7-8f3e-fba5e4c663dc.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dec9ad05-9e90-49d6-a04d-ebe7e8c40eed.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/536385a0-b948-41cf-af26-bd313f284678.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Software Toolworks</Publisher>
</game>