<Game>
	<Name>Mario Paint (Japan, USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Mario Paint is a paint program and minigame collection, with games that range from reflex-based fly swatting to music compilation. The game included the SNES Mouse peripheral and a plastic mouse pad. The mouse itself consisted of a roller-sensor and left and right-click buttons.Game Modes:Drawing BoardText Music CompositionAnimationColoring BookGnat Attack Drawing BoardThe Drawing Board is the game's standard paint program. Here, the player is given tools such as pencils, fills, and stamps to draw and color whatever they wish.Text Music CompositionWhen on the drawing board hit the Text Stamp Icon to open up text. Mario Paint has upper and lower case English letters, numbers, and three types of Japanese (Hiragana, Katakana, and Kanji).Music CompositionThis mode allows players to place various icons representing sounds on a note-chart to create music. The sounds vary from from traditional twings and twangs, to the beeps of a Game Boy and Yoshi sound effects.AnimationMario Paint offers a simplistic tool to create animated sequences. Using a limited number of frames, the player can draw a sequence of images that can then be played as an animated short.Coloring Book Coloring BookIn the game's coloring book, there is a collection of pre-drawn images featuring Nintendo characters and other items. In this mode, the player is free to color the images using fill and drawing tools. Gnat AttackGnat Attack is a training game. The mouse is used to control a flyswatter, and the player must swat incoming insects before they sting the player's hand. Hands representing extra lives can be collected over the course of play. The goal is to swat 100 insects to reach King Watinga. When King Watinga is defeated, hands will appear on the screen and applaud the player.Cheat: 90 degree rotation options for stampsOn the title screen, click on the "N" in "MARIO PAINT" and the credits will start rolling.  When "PROGRAMMER: NORIAKI TERAMOTO" (the second credit) appears, hold down the right-click button and left-click on the "N" to stop the credits.  Now, click on Mario to start the game as usual.Now, four 90 degree rotation options for stamps are available in addition to the regular flip options.  You can cycle through them by clicking the flip/rotate command in the bottom left.Cheat: 90 degree rotation options for stampsView the credits by clicking on the N in Mario Paint on the title screen. While viewing the credits, when Programmer Noriaki Teramoto appears, hold the right-mouse button and click on the N again with the left mouse button to unlock use of the right-mouse button until you reboot.Cheat: Messed up scenery.When you click the letter that makes the grass appear along with several things such as fire flowers trains and animals, every so often a star will shoot down, if you manage to click it (which can be difficult) the music will change and everything will mess up by raining all sorts of objects.Cheat: Alternate MusicClick on the letter I or O in the word Mario.Cheat: Alternate MusicClick on the letter M in the word Mario Paint.Cheat: Alternate MusicClick on the letter T in the word PaintCheat: Alternate MusicClick on the letter P in the word Mario Paint.Cheat: Alternate MusicClick on the letter A in the word Mario Paint.Cheat: Alternate MusicClick on the grid iconand wait.After a while,the undo icon will come to life and will walk around.If you move the mouse,it will run back and turn into an icon.Cheat: Alternate MusicWhen Mario turns and faces away from the screen on the title screen, quickly click on him (he turns away fast). If you do this correctly there'll be a chanting song as you enter the game.Cheat: Alternate MusicClick on the letter I in the word Paint.Cheat: Alternate MusicClick on the letter N in the word Paint.Cheat: Alternate MusicClick on the letter R in the word Mario Paint.Cheat: Alternate MusicClick on the letter A in the word Paint.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/8/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>qwyxaiIYv7Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1781</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588465-mario-paint</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mario-paint</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mario-paint/3030-8791/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/JsHdUBL.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/K7Deygm.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/skA2NUp.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/F8s6WNu.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/ZyZHlhF.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/Q9oPqQB.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/mVywiEt.jpg</boxart7>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/inNnFr4.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/kbH813p.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FHffcNO.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RJ6hNvF.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Xu5rfGG.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/UUrjAWu.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/MwXJOoN.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/VggiXTO.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/aQj7z6U.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NRgfjXk.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/lJShDBg.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1re44Qy.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/OtA99PX.png</clearlogo1>
</game>