<Game>
	<Name>Mario's Early Years - Fun with Letters (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Mario's Early Years: Fun With Letters is a collection of letter-related activities for kids ages 3 to 6 hosted by Mario and Co. Playing with either Mario or Princess Toadstool, you select from 10 different activity "worlds" each filled with different activities that range from letter recognition to sentence fill-in, letter-sound recognition, vowel recognition, etc. Each activity can be played in either Discovery mode, where you are free to do what you wish, or in Learning mode, where Luigi guides you through the activities.The game also includes a Parent's Information Center, which explains what each of the activities does and how to complement them. Options to configure the activities to each parent's wishes are also provided.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Educational</genre>
	<Developer>Software Toolworks, Inc., The</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>H7e-EmDh_KM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3837</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588466-marios-early-years-fun-with-letters</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/marios-early-years-fun-with-letters</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/marios-early-years-fun-with-letters/3030-10943/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/T88IxBH.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nbKxQPH.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/VBZjbNi.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/sTTb4td.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/KZB1pzj.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/nqAVPVK.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/HmdhmxI.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/dzPd1Lw.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FuQqQtZ.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/yzBdkzr.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/oHMzwaV.jpg</snapshot9>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/wHb8qfs.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/0jClUQp.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In FUN WITH LETTERS, children are introduced to the fundamentals of letters and sounds by way of numerous learning worlds: Alphabet, Vowel, First letter, Lost letter, Building, Sound, Sentence, and more. Your child simply guides Mario, selecting objects on the screen which Mario bonks and bounces through, frequently affirming your child’s correct choice. Moms and Dads get to interact and play, too. Mario invites them to join in the fun and observe their children as they become totally involved in the learning process. Through the MARIO'S EARLY YEARS Series children will discover the world around them by exploring the elements of that world. The MARIO'S EARLY YEARS Series covers a multitude of subjects, helping children to acquire valuable skills and develop a rich and active imagination.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b6e85f56-8afa-44b0-a34c-033f143d27de.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b2bc53d7-7ede-4b96-ac33-9f334b47aed2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fa9dc959-024d-49f1-9386-d798d030ec83.png</snapshot10>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/189b6eff-34d9-4fc5-9dcd-ecacfc5c9e06.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>