<Game>
	<Name>Mario no Super Picross (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Mario no Super Picross is a Miscellaneous game, developed by Jupiter Multimedia and published by Nintendo,which was released in Japan in 1995.Cheat: Erase a Saved GameTo erase a saved game file, highlight the file you wish to delete and press the following:Cheat: Extra normal LevelsTo unlock extra normal levels, do this:Cheat: EX Puzzle ModeOnce you beat the puzzles in the Ultra puzzle mode you will see what looks like a final puzzle.  When you select this final item you are taken to the game's title screen.  Now you can select any of the 12 EX puzzles that border the screen.Cheat: EX Puzzle ModeAfter you beat all 13 (be sure to play the puzzle in the middle of the screen) of Mario's EX Mode Puzzles, this mode opens up.Cheat: EX Puzzle ModeBeat Wario's Special puzzles to unlock the Ultra puzzle difficulty.  (It is not yet clear whether or not you need to beat Mario's Special puzzles first as well to unlock this new mode.)</plot>
	<releasedate>14/9/2007</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Puzzle, Logic</genre>
	<Developer>Jupiter Multimedia</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>VoQXGZRM7AY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>21356</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/576709-mario-no-super-picross</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/marios-super-picross</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/marios-super-picross/3030-6944/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Sy0N1e8.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/aXl6U4G.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/w2kCkin.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/0gOv8y6.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/z92jwWY.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ulTqWfU.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/M7R4BHJ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ESRtg8x.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/rgwOCF2.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/hjNZGIu.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/eHUEndA.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/6YWsXDp.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/NLlV7Hq.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5Dimt3m.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/LBssrPj.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Gameplay remains the same as in Mario's Picross, where the player must decipher the picture in each level, progressing to harder and harder puzzles. However, the player may also play "as" Wario, who presents a different challenge due to changes in the gameplay. Each game is played against the clock. Opposing the picross tradition of black and white squares, the puzzles are set in stone and are picked out by Mario with a pick-axe type tool. The initial levels are smaller and a lot easier and are mainly Japanese symbols and Greek letters. When the player solves a puzzle correctly, the black-and-white representation becomes colored and animated, and the game shows the player the title of the puzzle. When the player finishes a section, Mario will congratulate them on their progress and either bow (in the first and last levels) or give a thumbs up (in all other levels).</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1ae0a1a3-9583-42c4-b659-adaf52034490.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f80e3a7e-efbb-4e4d-8210-1caad6087daf.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>