<Game>
	<Name>Mark Davis' The Fishing Master (USA)</Name>
	<plot>In Mark Davis' The Fishing Master, the player can take control of fishing legend Mark Davis and fish in five different lakes and even compete in a fishing tournament to win a trophy.The gameplay is reminiscent of Super Black Bass.  The player picks a location to fish using an overhead map where the player is then taken to a behind the person perspective to cast their reel.  Once the player casts their line, the view will change to a split screen with the original view on the top with a underwater view on the bottom to view the bait and an approaching fish.Each lake has a different criteria to meet such as a weight limit, time limit, etc., to advance to the next lake and ultimately compete in the major tournament.  Players can also assemble their own set of authentic fishing gear including rods, reels, bait and various equipment.  The game also boasts that the fish in the game act realistically to their real-life counterparts.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/4/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Natsume, Inc.</Developer>
	<VideoURL>apSG6Mlqd8A</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3841</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588470-mark-davis-the-fishing-master</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mark-davis-the-fishing-master</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mark-davis-the-fishing-master/3030-30217/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/z2uHgVQ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/FUgEfke.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/uJkljf6.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6op3BSv.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/9v40rpC.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/vYbgMh0.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/FBGz7cb.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/RqInI4E.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/q4IH7hg.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/THrpaYA.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/g7nYrJY.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/WsuLEEZ.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/wd5PUSi.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Iji3gHk.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/n1390UM.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Reel in the most realistic Bass Fishing game ever! In 1995, Mark Davis became the only angler ever to win both the BASS Angler of the Year and the BASS Masters Classic titles in the same year. Join Mark now, as he leads you through the tournament of a lifetime. Unlike other fishing games, the fish in this game are crafty and reclusive. You won't see them until they bite! With an impressive selection of rods, reels, lures and the finest in marine transportation, you may choose the appropriate gear for all of the 5 stages and the final Grand Championship Tournament. It will take patience and time, but the big ones are waiting deep down below, and it's your job to find them. It's time to cast off...good luck!</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL1>B_yD9Di52ds</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/95d02167-e4e6-46be-aa91-e3d1b07c07ef.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab25c980-ae19-4cb3-92d7-436ea275c8ad.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4e5c1a5c-ab46-44a5-9e2a-392906d85068.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7b1d61ac-2a10-4655-b21b-5a68e77e9f52.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Natsume</Publisher>
</game>