<Game>
	<Name>Marko's Magic Football (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Colonel Brown, the evil owner of a toy factory, has created a substance that can turn people and animals into mutant sludge monsters. When Marko's football comes in touch with the substance it gets magical powers, giving Marko the power to stop Colonel Brown.Now Marko has to find his way through numerous platform levels filled with enemies and obstacles. Using his magic football, he can perform various moves and attacks. He can kill his enemies with different kicks, header shots or even bicycle kicks and also use his ball as a trampoline.The SNES version features two additional moves for Marko (the ability to balance on the ball and a different method of returning it to him), but they do not have a great impact on gameplay.http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/marko_</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>3842</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/944528-markos-magic-football</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/markos-magic-football/3030-5077/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/vwMtqvW.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/M73R6fB.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/yGEkxiW.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/OFsGKnL.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/cBMvtn7.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/tQJ0GeJ.jpg</snapshot4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/S05fQ4z.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/yhB6Ixr.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Welcome to the world of Marko, a world of cartoon madness. Experience the addictive blend of football skills and platform action that combine to make a superb gameplaying experience. Add the most incredible graphics ever to be seen and the result is Marko's Magic Football. It's just like playing a cartoon.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fbe07a52-48bf-4189-bbea-faed74e2eae6.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/913ff261-9485-49a6-b022-70d5ef31d907.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e05ad35b-a754-4ddf-80c8-a5a2733b3bcd.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fe63d0cc-4f21-4bac-8031-4d40c2490fe3.png</snapshot6>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>