<Game>
	<Name>Marvel Super Heroes in War of the Gems (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Marvel Super Heroes in War of the Gems is a side-scrolling platformer/beat 'em up based on the Infinity Gauntlet storyline from the comics.  Adam Warlock calls on the heroes to recover the 6 Infinity Gems before they are used for evil.You may choose ones of five heroes: Spider-Man, Hulk, Captain America, Iron Man and Wolverine.  Each one has different stats and abilities.  (i.e. Spider-Man is agile. Hulk is strong, Iron Man can double-jump with his rocket boots, etc.)  Initially you can choose a training area in Avenger headquarters or four levels.  As you complete levels, most open up.  Each hero can be equipped with gems to boost their abilities in each section.  These must be obtained by finding them in the levels.Gameplay: is fairly similar to X-Men-Mutant Apocalypse.  Combat is all on a 2D plane.  Each hero has basic jumps and attacks and special moves that can be executed with button combinations like quarter-rolls.  Enemies include various villains from the Marvel Universe and evil doubles of various Marvel heroes.</plot>
	<releasedate>17/10/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>cFcFQOjSraU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3225</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588471-marvel-super-heroes-in-war-of-the-gems</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/marvel-super-heroes-in-war-of-the-gems</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/marvel-super-heroes-in-war-of-the-gems/3030-8899/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/xC8fmp5.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/LjEkqlh.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/lQjBul6.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/1ItS6dy.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JDjMviW.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/kWdHpYB.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/NU0kIWH.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/S1nb7KB.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/KMjlHEW.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7eg69EE.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vYaD0xq.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/dOzlnsF.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/uDKQ4Cp.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/efkVHGv.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/ajBykOa.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/gaCwliU.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/acMcHTH.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/BwHcqOx.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The most powerful collection of MARVEL SUPER HEROES now unite to battle treacherous mobs of Super-Villians! A mysterious foe has kicked off his plan to rule the world by collecting the Infinity Gems. While each gem controls one force of nature, combined they command limitless power. The fate of the entire world depends on your ability to defeat this sinister scheme before the gems are combined. Master the brute strength of your favorite hero to take on this life and death challenge. You choose the hero best suited to each mission and control all the action, like breaking barriers with the Incredible Hulk or tackling challenges with Spider-Man's webs and climbing ability. It's an incredible action-adventure demanding skill, cunning and reflexes to defeat a diabolical plot and the most amazing assortment of corrupt Super-Villains ever assembled.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c42248fc-492d-49f5-8a6a-15dbf5d9c9cb.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/43bb8aa0-d5e6-4450-bb9c-04ffaf35c4e5.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bcc245bc-4df9-46e2-9716-daa56cebab29.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8c3ba792-ebde-4b6f-a11e-7ad85b610b8c.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b7b8da07-60eb-4abd-9ff5-943c28a258f8.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f5cd56fc-b424-401b-ae6f-38069912951e.png</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/12d5d7ab-02e3-4e8a-838b-6026bda42b5f.png</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e997970-c099-45e8-98a0-830880e32acc.png</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5936170c-4526-4ab9-b09b-1effa6c0913c.png</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/43066959-07ca-4290-a85f-78aa5cd49cf7.png</snapshot18>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>