<Game>
	<Name>Mary Shelley's Frankenstein (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Based of the 1994 movie remake of Frankenstein, the player is the artificial man created by Victor Frankenstein. After Victor rejects his creation due to its hideous appearance, the creation flees from Victor and swears revenge on him.The player goes through a number of levels, battling anything that attacks with a wooden stick. It's possible to set the tip of the stick on fire, by swinging it at the fire torches located on the walls. The player can also use a special attack: a blue ball coming out of the hands of the creation, which takes some of the player's life away. There are also some simple puzzles to be solved in order to get through the levels.Cheat: Level change and cheat passwordsSelect the password option on the title screen to enter the password menu.Cheat: Level change and cheat passwordsAt the password enter the following codes.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>5wphDoG1AzY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3843</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588345-mary-shelleys-frankenstein</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mary-shelleys-frankenstein</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mary-shelleys-frankenstein/3030-7903/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mary_Shelley%27s_Frankenstein_(video_game)</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/dG4JCBB.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/vcAOT4T.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/wUXHmzl.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/DCT1Q0F.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/MUb2ibt.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/1OOeg70.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/K7c80r2.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/dmcODzY.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/JvyRwvp.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/kJms6bh.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ziDBCUU.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/1OuVnuL.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vKb9R7c.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ap4GYaD.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/X0y8Ulx.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>From the pages of Mary Shelley's classic novel and the blockbuster film comes your own living nightmare - Mary Shelley's Frankenstein! Brought to life by Dr. Frankenstein, you're plunged into six huge levels of intense action. Dramatically unfolding through a unique "storyteller" feature, Mary Shelley's Frankenstein demands that you use both brains and brute strength to defeat a fearsome array of enemies, ranging from leeches and giant spiders to wolves and mounted soldiers. This fantastic world of Gothic horror is brought to life through stunningly realistic graphics and an eerie soundtrack, creating an atmosphere of unrelenting suspense.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>5wphDoG1AzY</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f17e50d1-be98-40d7-8bc7-fe5ba39370ed.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/93147abb-c319-4bd4-b174-45f1704abf6a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/73a2495b-be9c-41bc-b909-55bf24ed6016.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a9339b8c-0335-4709-8b08-de328059c378.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sony</Publisher>
</game>