<Game>
	<Name>Maui Mallard in Cold Shadow (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Disney's Donald Duck takes the starring role in this sidescrolling platform game.  As the detective Maui Mallard, he's on the trail of a long lost Idol, which has recently vanished.  Early on, Maui can also switch between his normal self and Ninja Maui, and with all the creepy voodoo enemies he'll encounter throughout his adventure, he's going to need all the help he can get.As previously mentioned, there are two personalities to Maui, and as a result, two different sets of controls.  Normal Maui carries a bug gun, which can fire a variety of different insect ammo, from basic bugs, to the more powerful lightning and fire bugs.  It's also possible for Maui to combine bugs to pack a more powerful blast at his enemies.Once Maui starts to find Yin-Yang coins, he'll be able to transform into Ninja Maui.  Ninja Maui has lightning-quick reflexes, and wields a bo staff.  In addition to being handy for whacking enemies, Ninja Maui can also climb between walls by jumping and propping the staff between the walls at the height of his jump.  He can also hook onto duck heads and swing from them to reach areas he normally couldn't.  You'll need to constantly find Yin-Yang coins to fuel your Ninja persona, otherwise you'll run out and transform back to Maui Mallard.Cheat: Level PasswordsEnter the passwords at the password screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Disney Interactive, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>CAvzZ824XOY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3845</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588473-maui-mallard-in-cold-shadow</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/maui-mallard-in-cold-shadow</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/maui-mallard-in-cold-shadow/3030-19990/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ScvXUK2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/r1tzs9l.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/NSGd3z4.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/rWOckNn.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/bh4LD5K.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/vcRaVAX.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/X9Pfbyc.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/sk6Azpw.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/qfsI2j9.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/MP9Q5N3.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/QtDKBC0.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/i11Qa7E.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Vi15zaJ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/RxBcW4y.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/fSHqtel.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7r8J89C.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/PXgLB7j.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>When he morphs into a ninja, you better duck! Play as Maui. Play as the Ninja. Play as Maui. Play as the Ninja. Try not to get dizzy. Find the missing Shabuhm Shabuhm idol before your island paradise goes kaboom kaboom! 40 hours of intense gameplay. So pack plenty of attitude. And your bug gun. Come beak to beak with MudDrakes, Rotting Pirates, Duck Zombies, Amazon Warriors. And a bunch of fowl-tempered hangers-on. Laugh in the face of danger from the top of a volcano, the bottom of the sea, the Realm of the Dead, and Ninja Training Grounds. Then get the heck out! Live every level like it's your last - 'cuz it may be!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>9s-Dt1qb9EY</VideoURL1>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d4ced3bd-8eec-4447-ac16-6c78eae748c6.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2d061879-5c31-4c4a-aabc-1cbc93c0f8df.png</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/db1cf242-7250-422a-8e03-25c433c6ae70.png</boxart7>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9e5e6a62-1afc-45b4-ad04-5eb75b3efe05.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f1177fa8-5ce7-4858-8bbd-47d4be99fdcc.png</clearlogo3>
	<Publisher>Disney Interactive</Publisher>
</game>