<Game>
	<Name>Mazinger Z (Japan) (Putative Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Dr. Hell's robot army has destroyed Tokyo, and now only Kouji Kabuto, and the giant robot Mazinger Z, can stop them from taking over the entire world. Animated cutscenes between levels tell the story of the game.The Mazinger Z comes with a full armory of anti-robot weaponry, from super-powered karate moves to missiles, Breast Fire, and its signature Rocket Punch. Special moves deplete a regenerating energy meter, while Rocket Punches can be preformed at any time, although Mazinger will be unable to punch until its arms return. Each level contains several varieties of enemies, all of them from the show and unique to each level, that must be defeated to progress. Some enemy robots will fire projectiles from a distance while others will rush in attempt to grapple the Mazinger, and sometimes more than one enemy must be fought at once. Enemies will drop healing items and occasionally an item that upgrades Mazinger's Rocket Punch to the Iron Cutter for a limited time. At the end of each level is a fight with a stronger boss robot with more dangerous attacks.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/6/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>FzuUCYLKUgk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18798</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570942-mazinger-z</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mazinger-z</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mazinger-z/3030-28340/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/xBqiw7T.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Vy1wjZl.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JusgszB.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/12X0yyB.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/GuAYiaR.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/NyqeAMA.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VKYdPEr.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/1mrNgd5.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/7KImAWR.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/LBUSed7.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/IbCWL8a.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JQHDVCr.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jmADj7C.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/eVavX3Q.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dr. Hell's robot army has destroyed Tokyo, and now only Kouji Kabuto, and the giant robot Mazinger Z, can stop them from taking over the entire world. Animated cutscenes between levels tell the story of the game. The Mazinger Z comes with a full armory of anti-robot weaponry, from super-powered karate moves to missiles, Breast Fire, and its signature Rocket Punch. Special moves deplete a regenerating energy meter, while Rocket Punches can be preformed at any time, although Mazinger will be unable to punch until its arms return. Each level contains several varieties of enemies, all of them from the show and unique to each level, that must be defeated to progress. Some enemy robots will fire projectiles from a distance while others will rush in attempt to grapple the Mazinger, and sometimes more than one enemy must be fought at once. Enemies will drop healing items and occasionally an item that upgrades Mazinger's Rocket Punch to the Iron Cutter for a limited time. At the end of each level is a fight with a stronger boss robot with more dangerous attacks.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c1b94f1c-dec1-4685-b05b-5018d7bda712.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7d3fd643-4ddf-4ccd-8e7d-c1fc36154843.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/671cf282-6100-4986-ac21-da02ad379580.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/daac41be-f0d2-45fe-9caa-e8204d2eeb36.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b0cb626-e6f1-4240-813f-0489441c76d4.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>