<Game>
	<Name>MechWarrior 3050 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:MechWarrior 3050 is the second game in the MechWarrior franchise released for the SNES. Unlike the original MechWarrior, this title changed its cockpit perspective to an isometric view similar to contemporary titles like Desert Strike and its sequels, leading to the graphics being completely overhauled from the previous title on the system. It was released on the Sega Genesis as Battletech: A Game of Armored Combat.Gameplay:The game has the player control a Mech outfitted with an arsenal of missiles and energy weapons in missions that take place on a large map. Like the titles in the Strike series, the player can freely roam around and explore the mission's map before tackling the objectives of the stage. The main single player mode in the came is a campaign that tasks them with several objectives spanning various missions. These can be getting to objective points, clearing out enemies, or escorting convoys across the map. One of the major changes to the game is the introduction of a cooperative two player mode where one player controls the bottom half of the Mech to navigate it around the battlefield while the other player controls the top half of the Mech and its arsenal independently.Cheat: Cheat CodePress Down, A, X on the Tiburon screen,  and enter XTRM3K as a password, to play as the enemy mech.Cheat: InvincibilityIn order to gain invincibility, you must do the following. Choose "Options" from the main screen, then go down to the Password entry screen and enter all of these codes in the following order. Once you have done this, you will be invincible with unlimited ammo.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Isometric</genre>
	<Developer>Activision</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>E3d8aqP8uio</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3847</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588476-mechwarrior-3050</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/battletech-a-game-of-armored-combat</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mechwarrior-3050/3030-21690/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/V4gQxdJ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/dijEoF1.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/gwLID3C.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/oCaYTPM.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/GJgCARC.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/gkIMcHF.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/og7nsg2.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/AaeHtSo.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YCZMrA4.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/fHJhOpn.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/rlGJar6.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Ozz1OVT.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/jfZRFdz.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/IeDLuBu.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/jKkGKQz.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>It is the year 3050. The universe is a brutal and violent place. The galaxy is racked by a devastating war waged by massive 75-ton BattleMechs with the most ruinous weapons systems of the 31st century. It's up to MechWarriors like you to pilot the MadCat Heavy OmniTech on desperate missions against enemy installations. Alone against the relentless onslaught of enemy defenders, you'll need skill and cunning to knock out your objectives! Steer your lethal 'Mech into the savage fury of metal-shredding attackers - and lay waste to all before you with the MadCat's incredible firepower! Fight to the last for a victory that will bring you honor and glory. But if honor isn't motivation enough, remember that the enemy takes no prisoners... - Employ nine devastating weapons systems to obliterate enemy resistance! - Battle the ground defenses of the inner sphere on give different planets! - Take on the enemy in 2-player cooperative mode - one player steers while the other controls the MadCat's weapons systems!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/88130cfc-8428-41fd-99dd-786ecbe0bb30.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7b738939-93e3-4698-9223-19f7ca613224.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fcaf98f1-8c4c-4c08-a01e-39739d817a4d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/095bbbe4-8e39-469a-8c1f-9c3596e011b9.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Tiburon Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>