<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man Soccer (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Mega Man Soccer (known in Japan as Rockman's Soccer, also known as Mega Man's Soccer) is a sidescrolling soccer game developed and published by Capcom for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System in April 1994. There was no European release.A spin-off of the original Mega Man series, players control a variety of robots (including hero Mega Man, ally Proto Man, and 19 of Mega Man's previously-defeated Robot Masters and other adversaries), each with their own special ability, as they face off in games of soccer.Up to two players can play simultaneously (either competitively or co-operatively) in one of four modes (including the game's main campaign, Capcom Championship Mode, where players start with a team of only Mega Man and must gain new teammates by defeating their teams).Characters:Mega ManProto ManCut Man (Mega Man)Elec Man (Mega Man)Bomb Man (Mega Man)Ice Man (Mega Man)Fire Man (Mega Man)Bubble Man (Mega Man 2)Flash Man (Mega Man 2)Air Man (Mega Man 2)Wood Man (Mega Man 2)Needle Man (Mega Man 3)Top Man (Mega Man 3)Snake Man (Mega Man 3)Gemini Man (Mega Man 3)Skull Man (Mega Man 4)Toad Man (Mega Man 4)Dust Man (Mega Man 4)Pharaoh Man (Mega Man 4)Enker (Mega Man: Dr. Wily's Revenge)Dr. Wily (only playable via certain League Mode teams)Teams:Capcom Championship ModeThe playable team in this mode consists of only eight multiples of Mega Man. As players defeat teams (which consists of multiples of a certain character), they gain teammates that can be used to replace teammates.Both the mode's progression and the way players "earn" something from enemies is similar to the traditional Mega Man platformers. First, the player team defeats each Robot Master team in any order they choose:Cut ManDust ManElec ManFire ManNeedle ManPharaoh ManSkull ManWood ManThen, they enter Dr. Wily's castle and face off against:EnkerProto ManDr. WilyTournament ModePlayers can pick one of the following teams:Mega Man (8x Mega Man)Cut Man (3x Cut Man, Bubble Man, Flash Man, Ice Man, Snake Man, Toad Man)Dust Man (3x Dust Man, Air Man, Bomb Man, Gemini Man, Toad Man, Top Man)Elec Man (3x Elec Man, Air Man, Bomb Man, Bubble Man, Flash Man, Ice Man)Fire Man (3x Fire Man, Air Man, Bomb Man, Gemini Man, Ice Man, Top Man)Needle Man (3x Needle Man, Air Man, Gemini Man, Snake Man, Toad Man, Top Man)Pharaoh Man (3x Pharaoh Man, Bomb Man, Bubble Man, Flash Man, Ice Man, Snake Man)Skull Man (3x Skull Man, Air Man, Bomb Man, Bubble Man, Gemini Man, Ice Man)Wood Man (3x Wood Man, Flash Man, Gemini Man, Snake Man, Toad Man, Top Man)After they progress through the eight-team single-elimination tournament, they must face off against the Enker team (consisting of 3x Enker, Bubble Man, Flash Man, Gemini Man, Snake Man, and Top Man) and then either the Proto Man team (consisting of 3x Proto Man, Air Man, Bubble Man, Ice Man, Snake Man, and Top Man) or the Dr. Wily team (consisting of 3x Dr. Wily, Bomb Man, Flash Man, Gemini Man, Ice Man, and Toad Man).League ModePlayers can pick one of the following teams:Mega Man (3x Mega Man, 2x Ice Man, 2x Bubble Man, Proto Man)Cut Man (3x Cut Man, 2x Ice Man, 2x Bubble Man, Enker)Dust Man (3x Dust Man, 2x Air Man, 2x Snake Man, Dr. Wily)Elec Man (3x Elec Man, 2x Gemini Man, 2x Snake Man, Dr. Wily)Fire Man (3x Fire Man, 2x Bomb Man, 2x Flash Man, Enker)Needle Man (3x Needle Man, 2x Toad Man, 2x Top Man, Proto Man)Pharaoh Man (3x Pharaoh Man, 2x Gemini Man, 2x Top Man, Enker)Skull Man (3x Skull Man, 2x Bomb Man, 2x Flash Man, Proto Man)Wood Man (3x Wood Man, 2x Air Man, 2x Gemini Man, Enker)Cheat: All bosses on teamLast level: _ _ _ o _ o _ _ o o o o o o o _ o o o o o _ o _ o o o _ _ o o _ o _ o o _ o o o _ o _ _ _ o _ _ _ o _ _ o _ o _ o o _ _ _ _ _ _</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ghVv0Dxb6Tc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2494</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588478-mega-man-soccer</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mega-man-soccer</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-man-soccer/3030-11496/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mega_Man_Soccer</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/xcqmnMV.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/AXXc3NP.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/bWhleid.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/7xijrD3.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wMGqN9T.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/PPdILRJ.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/A3fOINJ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/hVJrRl5.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YdGVIfk.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/fTIiWOb.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/RloPzBf.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/a96Utdk.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/4Q2Yeqa.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/gHcBBlg.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/MDsP6gr.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dr. Wily will stop at nothing to control the world and who would have thought his next move would be to attack the world's most popular sport? Dr. Light is ready and he's preparing Mega Man for a new type of battle. As the two best soccer teams in the nation took the field for the championship, suddenly the stadium was pelted with blasts of fire and the field was engulfed in smoke. The smoke cleared and some very familiar robots replaced the players on the field. Dr. Wily had sent his greatest robot creations like Skull Man, Cut Man, Wood Man, Needle Man and Pharaoh Man to rule the soccer world. But Dr. Light was prepared for this new tactic. Almost instantly a reserve of Mega Man robots appeared to take on the evil forces in the strangest game of soccer ever seen. No matter where evil appears, Mega Man will be there to kick one past Dr. Wily and hist robot master.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6466d83f-f6a7-4156-bf60-6fed2b6bc290.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f61c3c96-08ac-4a5b-9fa4-94c8197b4dd6.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ba50a1d3-5167-4680-af27-6b31e9e06da1.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea7afae0-cff2-4f84-9256-0ee57c9277d2.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>