<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man 7 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Mega Man 7 (also known as Mega Man VII, and known in Japan as Rockman 7: The Confrontation of Fate!!) is a side-scrolling action platformer developed and published by Capcom for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System on September 1995.It is the seventh installment of the original Mega Man series (and the sequel to Mega Man 6). The only installment of the series for the SNES (with the exception of spin-offs Mega Man Soccer and the Japan-exclusive Rockman &amp; Forte), Mega Man 7 introduces the series to "bolts", a collectible currency (dropped by enemies and found scattered throughout levels) that can be used in a store (Big Eddie's Cybernetic Support Shop) to purchase items and upgrades. It also introduces Dr. Light's mechanic/assistant Auto and Mega Man's robotic rival Bass (along with his robotic wolf Treble). Mega Man's robotic bird, Beat, is also given new functionality as he can carry Mega Man out of fatal pitfalls.Set in the year 20XX, the game takes place a half a year after the events of Mega Man 6 (in which the humanoid robot hero Mega Man defeats the evil roboticist Dr. Wily a sixth time, sending him to prison for his crimes). Despite being imprisoned, Dr. Wily triggers a fail-safe in this lab (by not being in contact with it for six months) which awakens four Robot Masters sent to rescue him. When Mega Man fails to apprehend Dr. Wily (encountering the mysterious robot Bass, along with his dog Treble, who claims to be after Dr. Wily as well), he must venture out to defeat the new Robot Masters and find Dr. Wily.The game was later released (in North America only) as part of the Mega Man Anniversary Collection compilation for the PlayStation 2 and GameCube on June 23, 2004 and the Xbox on March 15, 2005. An unofficial 8-bit "demake" of Mega Man 7 was finished in 2008, coinciding with the release of the deliberately-retro Mega Man 9. More information can be found here.Gameplay:BeatMega Man 7 is very similar to the previous six titles in the Mega Man franchise, except for several refinements to gameplay. Mega Man 7 was the third Mega Man game to have a store with wares such as items and powerups available for a set amount of "bolts," the currency of the game which can be collected during levels. To access the store, the player must press the select button on the stage select screen. Later games, such as Mega Man IV (Game Boy version), Mega Man V (Game Boy version), Mega Man 8, Mega Man &amp; Bass, and Mega Man 9 also featured the store.In Slash Man's stage, the character Beat is unlockable upon being rescued. Beat's job, unlike in Mega Man 5 and Mega Man 6 where he attacks enemies, is to rescue Mega Man when he falls into a pit. The player can hold up to four of Beat's whistles, summoning Beat. Beat can also carry Mega Man for a short period of time, but when it runs out, Beat drops him. If Beat drops Mega Man in a pit by accident, or if the player runs out of whistles, then Mega Man loses a life.BassCapcom, being the creators of the Street Fighter franchise, slipped in an extra two player versus mode. It is two rounds long and can be accessed by typing a password while holding L and R. When the password is inputted without L and R, it takes the player (fully powered Mega Man) to the very last Wily Level.The weapons that Mega Man earns from the eight bosses of the game play more of a role in Mega Man 7. For example, the weapons can be use to alter the environment to discover hidden areas for secret items. In Slash Man's stage, the scorch wheel weapon can be use to burn some of the trees that are in the level.Mega Man 7 also introduces the game with a level, making it the first game in the series to have an introductory level. This level serves as the introduction of the story, and shows new characters Bass and Treble, who serve as Mega Man and Rush's rivals.Levels:     Slash Man's StageHeavily based off the film Jurassic Park, Slash Man's stage contains robotic dinosaurs--some can shoot razor sharp propellers, and others can help Mega Man get across spiked plains. Mega Man will also go though waterfall sequence with logs coming down the waterfall's stream--the logs are used as platforms for Mega Man to get through. Eventually Mega Man will encounter a large dinosaur as a mid-boss fight.     Shade Man's StageThis stage has areas of robotic zombies that will regenerate. They come out of a coffin that rise up out of the ground. Robotic crows will appear to give Mega Man a hard time - the stand in the way and shoot out a pellet. Enemies will sneak up on Mega Man from the background. Mega Man will also encounter a mid boss fight in this stage as well--a giant pumpkin that bounces around as one of its attack, then the top and bottom sides will open up and shoot out pellets at Mega Man. This level also houses a secret battle with Proto Man. In order to meet him here, you must have met him twice before.     Junk Man's StageA factory that has robotic bugs coming out of hives that's made out of junk. Other section contain gaps that's filled with molten lava that Mega Man has to cross. One touch of the lava and Mega Man is done for. Another area is an elevator section with enemies coming down while the elevator is taking Mega Man to the next part of the level.     Freeze Man's StageFreeze Man's stage is a snowy level that has robotic polar bears that can breath out spiked balls and throw them at Mega Man, bob sliders that will throw three bombs once destroyed, and enemies that hang on the ceiling and shoot glaciers that can be use as platforms to get through gaps filled with spikes. Sections of the stage have platforms that are covered with slippery ice - if not careful, Mega Man could accidentally fall off.     Burst Man's StageThis stage has platforms that are ticking time bombs. A large portion of the stage is done underwater - the water can increase the height that Mega Man can jump, but it can be dangerous for Mega Man because some areas in the stage have spikes hanging on the ceiling. In other sections, the water level will rise up and down, Mega Man will float on top when the water level is up - which will help Mega Man get through sections with gaps that are filled with spikes.     Turbo Man's StageMost of this stage is made out of tires. Right at the beginning, Mega Man will be attacked by a robot on a bulldozer with spikes on the front. Other sections have tires that are attached to chains. They can get in the way of Mega Man jumping across spiked gaps. Another has Mega Man going dropping down avoiding fiery beams that will destroy Mega Man with one hit (This section is reminiscent of Quick Man's level from Mega Man 2).     Spring Man's StageThis stage contains springs attached on walls, floors, and ceilings- they can launch Mega Man up in the air. Two of the enemies are robotic springs; one jumps around the stage and attacks Mega Man, and the other is similar to a Slinky. Sections in the level have jack-in-the-boxes suspended in mid air; they launch out a metal boxing glove. Mega Man can jump on them and change the direction where the metal boxing will aim.    Cloud Man's StageVery reminiscence of Air Man's stage from Mega Man 2, Cloud Man's stage takes place up in the air. Some sections have robots that can change the weather depending which weapon is used on it. For example, If Freeze Man's weapon is use, the entire level will be covered in snow.Robot MastersFreeze ManFreeze ManEnemy Alignment: IceEnemy Weakness: Junk ShieldWeapon Gained: Freeze CrackerJunk ManJunk ManEnemy Alignment: TrashEnemy Weakness: Thunder Bolt Weapon Gained: Junk ShieldBurst ManBurst ManEnemy Alignment: Water Enemy Weakness: Scorch Wheel Weapon Gained: Danger WrapCloud ManCloud ManEnemy Alignment: Air Enemy Weakness: Danger Wrap Weapon Gained: Thunder BoltSpring ManSpring ManEnemy Alignment: Coils Enemy Weakness: Slash Claw Weapon Gained: Wild CoilSlash ManSlash ManEnemy Alignment: Claws Enemy Weakness: Freeze Cracker Weapon Gained: Slash ClawShade ManShade ManEnemy Alignment: Sound Enemy Weakness: Wild Coil Weapon Gained: Noise CrushTurbo ManTurbo ManEnemy Alignment: Fire Enemy Weakness: Noise Crush Weapon Gained: Scorch WheelCheat: Different Shade Man MusicFor different music for the Shade Man level highlight his level, press and hold the B button, and then select his level. You must not have defeated Shade Man for this to work.Cheat: Different Shade Man MusicFirst, go to ProtoMan's room in CloudMan's stage (right before the outdoor part before the boss, there will be a ladder. Use Rush to get to it). ProtoMan will comment about using weapons to find areas. Then go to ProtoMan's room in TurboMan's stage (this one is at the very top of the area with the traffic light platforms; go through the wall just before you reach the top of the ladder). He will mention something about the Super Adaptor.Cheat: Different Shade Man MusicAfter you go to these two rooms (doesn't matter with order you go to those), go to ShadeMan's stage. Continue like normal until you reach the Pumpkin mini-boss. Shoot the small orange core of the Pumpkin (NOT the eyes on the outside). After you defeat it, it will open a hole on the bottom. Go down until you reach the room with a lone green Sniper Joe. Defeat the Sniper Joe, and instead of going down the ladder, go right through a secret passage and enter the gate you find. If you did everything correctly, ProtoMan will challenge you to a duel.Cheat: Different Shade Man MusicOnce you defeat ProtoMan, he will give you the ProtoShield. This can be used at the same time as the MegaBuster (don't forget to select it), and it will block many enemy shots (like those birds that hatch from the egg; let all of them run into the shield and they will die).Cheat: Different Shade Man MusicEnter the following password: 1415 5585 7823 6251 Then press and hold R &amp; L, and push the start button. After doing so you'll be taken to the [I]Versus Mode[/I] character select screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>el3VjUkffME</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>292</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588477-mega-man-7</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mega-man-7</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-man-7/3030-7391/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mega_Man_7</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4xoKPkH.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/l9h4vYk.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/yAXy9DU.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/2xV0yPo.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/Y8gK4th.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/5KU9gLO.png</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/9wI08pn.png</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/xkrNQ9A.jpg</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://i.imgur.com/nkkA3hM.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://i.imgur.com/pO5AvQ1.jpg</boxart10>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/73rm6Nd.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Pk5Vpz5.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/xwyQYPL.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Rj7xY2X.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/k4C2gk1.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/8OCzZfD.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/EBpcUPU.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Trru3LJ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/K6GzmMQ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/S5mza56.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/l3uMpRR.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/BDPRoEq.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/XSNmPRX.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/j7FBUuw.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/ROL9aUP.png</clearlogo2>
</game>