<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man X3 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Mega Man X3 (known in Japan as Rockman X3) is a side-scrolling action platformer developed and published by Capcom for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System on January 1996.The third game in the Mega Man X series (and the sequel to the Mega Man X2), players control android Mega Man X and, for the first time, his Reploid ally Zero (who can be called in to deal with tough situations thanks to his energy sword). It is the last game in the franchise to feature the original art and gameplay style of Mega Man X (as well as the password system).Set sometime after the events of Mega Man X2 (where X and the rebuilt Zero defeat the Maverick Sigma for the second time), the Maverick rebellion becomes neutralized due to the technology of Reploid scientist Dr. Doppler. Reformed Mavericks form an utopia near the scientist (named Dopple Town) and lived peacefully before they suddenly go berserk and cause mayhem. Believing Doppler to be responsible, X and Zero must defeat the eight Maverick leaders of Dopple Town and foil the mad scientist's plans (while surviving his henchmen, Bit and Byte, and a mysterious Maverick).An enhanced version of the game was released for the Sega Saturn and PlayStation in Japan (on April 26, 1996) and Europe (published by Virgin Interactive on March 1997). While the core game remains the same, it includes animated full-motion video cutscenes, a rearranged soundtrack, and new sound effects. This version was later released for the PC in Japan (on March 28, 1997) and North America (on October 5, 1998) and is included in the Mega Man X Collection compilation for the PlayStation 2 and GameCube (released on January 10, 2006).Gameplay:The gameplay has only somewhat differed from Mega Man X2 by making the wall jumping slightly easier to preform while reploids become tougher. The gameplay compared to the Mega Man series is much more fast paced with more tricky and more powerful mavericks than ever giving rise to more difficult battles. As a side point, their battles can be completed faster than other bosses in previous games, as they are more susceptible to their weakness, and take more damage from their attacks.Boss Robots(Mavericks)At the end of every level X must fight a boss to proceed, and after fighting all 8 bosses he goes to the final fight against Doppler and his army. Here is a list of the boss robots in order to exploit all of their weaknesses.Boss selectionBoss- Blizzard BuffaloWeapon: Frost shieldPower-9200rpSpeed-3200rpWeakness-Parasitic BombBoss- Toxic SeahorseWeapon: Acid BurstPower-5800rpSpeed-4300rpWeakness-Frost ShieldBoss- Tunnel RhinoWeapon: Tornado FangPower-4200rpSpeed-8000rpWeakness-Acid BurstBoss- Volt CatfishWeapon: Triad ThunderPower-8200rpSpeed-1600rpWeakness-Tornado FangBoss- Crush CrawfishWeapon: Spinning BladePower-4000rpSpeed-7600rpWeakness-Triad ThunderBoss- Neon TigerWeapon: Ray SplasherPower-3600rpSpeed-9900rpWeakness-Spinning BladeBoss- Gravity BeetleWeapon: Gravity WellPower-6200rpSpeed-3600rpWeakness-Ray SplasherBoss- Blast HornetWeapon: Parasitic BombPower-3400rpSpeed-8600rpWeakness-Gravity WellUpgrades:Armor CapsulesDr. Light has once again hidden some secret capsules that will enhance Mega Man X's abilities. When Mega Man X steps into one of these capsules, it will come to life and change the appearance of Mega Man X. Here are descriptions of some of the Capsules:Boots(Nothing required)Gives X the ability to dash again while in the airLocation-Blizzard Buffalo's lairGun(Boots and T.Fang)Allows X to charge up one level and fire two powerful shots; also X can charge special weapons.Location-Neon Tiger's lairHelmet(Gun and Triad T.)A map will appear at the beginning of the level to show X where hidden items are located.Location-Drill Rhino's lairArmor(Boots, G. Well and Gun)Automatically creates a defense shield on Mega Man X's chassis that reduces damage by 50%. After getting hurt a shield will automatically form around X to lessen damage by 1/2Location-Volt Catfish's lairRobot Ride ArmorIn addition to the armor capsules, Dr. Light has set out 4 different armors known as robot ride armor. Mega Man X and Zero must find these 4 armors, each with different capabilities and functions. The armor looks like a giant robot that they can activate by jumping into it. Once X finds an armor, he may use the armor in any stage where he may find the Robot Ride platforms.If X has found an armor, the platform will activate. A menu will appear just to the left of the platform, so use the game pad or the arrow keys to select which armor X would like to use. While in the robot ride armor, Mega Man X and Zero will not be damaged. The armor can be damaged, but can be healed by returning to the platform. If the armor is destroyed, X cannot use it again until he enters a new stage. He can also jump out if need be by jumping while holding up on the D-pad.Robot Ride ArmorsChimeraHawkFrogKangarooSoundtrack:Cover ArtIn 2005 Capcom released a 5-disc box set called Capcom Music Generation Rockman X1~6. It contains the original music of Mega Man X through Mega Man X6 as well as some unused tracks. Mega Man X3 tracks span the entire second disc containing both the SNES (tracks 1-29) and Saturn/Playstation (tracks 30-69) arranged tracks. The track listing is as follows:Track #TitleLength1.OPENING0:542.TITLE0:123.PASS WORD0:414.OPENING STAGE0:445.ZERO1:136.STAGE SELECT0:217.STAGE START0:148.EXPLOSE HORNECK STAGE1:429.FROZEN BUFFALIO STAGE1:3510.GRAVITY BEETBOOD STAGE1:5711.ACID SEAFORCE STAGE1:4912.ELECTRO NAMAZUROS STAGE1:5213.SCISSORS SHRIMPER STAGE1:3314.SCREW MASAIDER STAGE1:5815.SHINING TIGERD STAGE2:1016.VAVA STAGE1:2717.BOSS 10:2418.BOSS 20:3419.STAGE CLEAR0:0620.STAGE SELECT 20:3121.DOPPLER STAGE 11:1722.DOPPLER STAGE 22:3123.DOPPLER STAGE BOSS0:4024.SIGMA 1st0:4725.SIGMA 2nd1:1426.DOPPLER DEMO1:0927.Dr.RIGHT0:4928.ENDING1:2829.CAST ROLL2:3130.OPENING1:1831.TITLE0:1432.PASS WORD0:4133.OPENING STAGE DEMO0:2834.OPENING STAGE2:0035.ZERO0:5236.STAGE SELECT 10:1937.EXPLOSE HORNECK DEMO0:2538.EXPLOSE HORNECK STAGE1:5239.FROZEN BUFFALIO DEMO0:2940.FROZEN BUFFALIO STAGE1:4941.GRAVITY BEETBOOD DEMO0:2642.GRAVITY BEETBOOD STAGE1:5843.ACID SEAFORCE DEMO0:2544.ACID SEAFORCE STAGE1:5345.ELECTRO NAMAZUROS DEMO0:2346.ELECTRO NAMAZUROS STAGE1:5247.SCISSORS SHRIMPER DEMO0:2348.SCISSORS SHRIMPER STAGE1:3649.SCREW MASAIDER DEMO0:2250.SCREW MASAIDER STAGE1:4851.SHINING TIGERD DEMO0:2352.SHINING TIGERD STAGE1:3653.VAVA STAGE1:3054.BOSS 10:4555.BOSS 20:3656.STAGE CLEAR0:1057.DEMO0:2158.STAGE SELECT 20:2859.DOPPLER STAGE 11:3760.DOPPLER STAGE 22:2061.DOPPLER STAGE BOSS0:3662.SIGMA 1st0:5063.SIGMA 2nd0:5964.DOPPLER DEMO1:1365.Dr.KEIN DEMO0:3266.Dr.RIGHT DEMO0:4867.ENDING 12:0068.ENDING 20:2269.CAST ROLL2:41Cheat: Code or Password for Megaman X3All armor parts,all enemy skills,all sub-tanks,all heart tanks,all ride armors and no enhance chip aquire, so you can still have the change to obtain the gold armor in doppler stage.The stage start at where Doppler stage just shown out at the MAP selection screenCheat: Code or Password for Megaman X3Depending on Zero's status in the game, you can have different endings and a different charge on your Buster.Cheat: Cx4 testHold B on controller 2, then turn on the power of the Super Nintendo to view the stats of the game's Cx4 chip.Cheat: Cx4 test1) After defeating the first two mavericks, you will now be able to access Vile's mini stage through the funny looking teleporter in the Volt Catfish, Crush Crawfish, or Blizzard Buffalo stages. Go there. You MUST defeat Vile with either Crush Crawfish's or Neon Tiger's weapon, and then quickly make your way out of the stage before the timer reaches zero. This trick will not work if you do not follow this step.Cheat: Cx4 test2) Complete the rest of the stages. Although it is not required, you should find all of the Upgrades, E-Tanks, Heart Tanks, and Robot Armor pieces. Make it all the way to Doppler Fortress Level 2. If you completed Step 1 correctly, this level should be alot harder now, as the stage will be filled with water and different enemies.Cheat: Cx4 test3) Right before the first sub-boss door, switch to Zero. Go inside, and defeat the bug robot. He's not too difficult...stay toward the center, then when he comes towards you, dash under him, and he should land on the ground behind you, then shoot him. After you defeat the bug robot, it will land on Zero, damaging him badly. At this point, he will give Mega Man his Z-Sabre to use for the rest of the game. Use the Z-Sabre by charging the Y button all the way up to the fifth energy level(green) and then firing.Cheat: Cx4 testNote: For this to work, you need all power-ups BESIDES the chips, and have full health. Go to the First stage of Dr.Doppler's Lab. Near the end, you should see a bunch of spiked balls falling into a pit. Jump and cling onto the left side of the pit and you should slide into a secret room, which contains the upgrade capsule for the golden chip. This chip gives you all the benefits from all the chips, and turns Mega Man's suit into a golden color.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>lUlHBc_t94c</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1016</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588481-mega-man-x3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mega-man-x3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-man-x3/3030-16948/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/wlFZ6IM.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/GpdhaiE.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/dOcuytg.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/BA2ey0B.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/G2Klajp.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/erq13Vb.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Hkjy1fD.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/eyIpqy2.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/lAQOhgI.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/6tQ3pG8.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/p7BNhY1.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/cymGN1L.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/7zdPSqO.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/lH12Tvy.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JhAijzs.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/6sFa89p.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/dWB4NQ4.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/njraKrT.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/iJfNkMb.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Mega Man X and his trusty partner Zero have a new force to reckon with. Who or what has caused a riot of Mavericks to break out in the experimental utopia known as Doppler Town? Named after the scientist reploid, Doppler Town was supposed to be a place where humans and reploids could live in harmony. After discovering a virus that was turning reploids to Mavericks, Doppler's anti-virus was a big success. But Doppler itself became infected with the virus and assembled a team to take out the Maverick Hunter Units. The Doppler Effect is about to unfold, with Mega Man X and Zero the only cure for the deadly virus!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>lUlHBc_t94c</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/af103947-7c56-42a7-80a1-574b746dea35.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7e97c1a1-79a2-4a72-b948-c5509c3dce1c.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0d6a1c6c-f888-41ed-8718-549a83a340cd.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ead2f4a6-2328-4ebe-b107-3c3d9337779a.png</boxart8>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f42ab260-abab-4add-af00-27ad33be2af2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/11e5f0b3-8306-4225-a2e9-db8311da3f24.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1724f8e8-b359-43e3-bd0e-9db8e970e60d.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49d7711b-fe9e-4a93-94db-d743095541a0.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/26ee9a0f-be95-4016-ae32-b70b4416f4f7.png</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>