<Game>
	<Name>Metal Max Returns (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>This is a remake of the game Metal Max, originally for NES. You are a little boy who lives with his father in a town in a futuristic world dominated by machines. Your wish is to become a "hunter" - to kill monsters that roam the world and to receive rewards for that. The storyline and the gameplay basics remained unchanged in this remake. You fight enemies in turn-based combat, and use vehicles, such as your own personal tank Mosquito, to transport yourself through different areas, and to participate in battles. You can also buy equipment and upgrade your vehicles.The remake features enhanced graphics and sound, background pictures for battles (they were black in the original), slightly different locations (more houses in towns, sometimes different layout of the towns and of the world map), and reduced difficulty level.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/9/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Data East Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>fkNhWAGnOv8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14821</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581815-metal-max-returns</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/metal-max-returns</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/metal-max-returns/3030-6911/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/vud9jKk.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/8MHBa2x.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xcBirMM.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/xtdTK69.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/iJdBHeJ.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/72mDX4c.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/7koUj60.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/3MWGWjm.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/xSeHJYg.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ykX2t2b.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/j42EWyH.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/RYNQmQn.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/bh1crON.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7MjgSgT.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/jSF7MwX.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Metal Max Returns is a post-apocalyptic turn-based RPG with a heavy emphasis on open-world, non-linear gameplay and vehicle customization. It is the remake of the original 1991 Famicom game, and the third game in the series overall after the 1993 sequel Metal Max 2. The protagonist is a player-named hero who is disowned by his mechanic father after he insists on pursuing his dream to be a monster hunter, a dangerous profession. The player can acquire new party members and create tanks to ride around in, as well as customize the load-out of those tanks. It plays fundamentally the same as the original Famicom game.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a81ec8fc-16ad-468a-8e86-8cd0d30edbcb.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/92eeec18-0a0c-4a68-983b-d43cb7bcf7b6.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Data East</Publisher>
</game>