<Game>
	<Name>Metal Slader Glory - Director's Cut (Japan) (NP)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Metal Slader Glory: Director's Cut is an enhanced port of an adventure game from 1991 called Metal Slader Glory. The port features redrawn graphics by Yoshimiru Hoshi (the game's original creator and character designer), a new soundtrack, and additional scenes that had to be cut from Metal Slader's original release on the Famicom. Hal Laboratory developed the Director's Cut for the Super Famicom and Nintendo published the title on November 29, 2000. Metal Slader Glory: Director's Cut holds the honor of being the very last officially released Super Famicom game to come out for the system.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/11/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Hal</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>QNMlY6oKIdc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>30790</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/579658-metal-slader-glory-directors-cut</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/metal-slader-glory-directors-cut/3030-28342/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metal_Slader_Glory</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ZzI43o8.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/1gTVBiz.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/p9z1q16.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/5PGC9SL.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/VN024tE.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/smGbg90.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/KIpXkAF.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ppfoVuq.jpg</snapshot6>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/nNU02NC.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/Xxe1W6D.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/D7s5iuJ.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/r4bJTRi.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/NFITteS.jpg</fanart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/hJfuq7f.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Metal Slader Glory is a graphic adventure game where the player interacts with the protagonist's surrounding via a menu-based commands. The commands the player can choose varies between context, which usually ranges from talking to supporting characters to investigating the surrounding. The player must explore every possible option in order for new choices to appear. However, if the player makes a wrong selection, the game will end and the player must restart the game from where they left off. The player can quit at any point of the game and continue later via a password feature.This game was also the final official Super Famicom release by Nintendo. After that, the Super Famicom was retired as a viable gaming platform. The Super Famicom release features improved graphics and audio over the original Family Computer release, including redrawn graphics by Yoshimiru Hoshi himself, additional scenes that were excluded from the original Family Computer release due to the lack of cartridge space, different background music (due to copyrights issues), and new artwork added to the ending</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>QNMlY6oKIdc</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7e64bf25-edaf-41e4-ae6c-813a498aef1c.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7035f2f7-a2c7-480e-b2c6-0f183516cfc8.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/96631c2f-31f2-46b4-8cbf-2d95d8a9cb84.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6f3f0ddc-2ff9-46dc-84df-ff6e50d446be.jpg</snapshot8>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>