<Game>
	<Name>Mickey to Minnie - Magical Adventure 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Mickey and Minnie plan to spend a fun-filled day at the circus but to their dismay all the performers have disappeared. Some unknown force has replaced them with crazy characters who are out to make Mickey and Minnie's day an unpleasant one. And on top of that, Donald Duck and Pluto are nowhere to be seen.As Mickey and Minnie search for clue, the trail leads them beyond the circus. Travel along with our hero and heroine as they explore 6 hostile levels like the Haunted House, Frozen Plains and the Jungle. Use special Safari or Western outfits to fend off the enemy and climb through treacherous terrain looking for Donald and Pluto. Hopefully along the way the happenings at the circus will beging to make sense.Cheat: Hidden 2-UpsWhen in Stage One, the Haunted Circus, you will start the game on the fairgrounds. Just ahead is a small pond with an enemy fish swimming in it. At about halfway through the water, there is a wooden support beam in the background. Swim past this and you will receive a 2-Up. In Stage Two, the Jungle, there is another opportunity for a hidden 2-Up. After beating the halfway boss (the giant turtle), you'll go a couple more screens and come to a section where you'll use the Safari outfit to slide down a number of vines. After reaching the bottom vine, swim in the water beneath, all the way to the left.  The word ''2-Up'' will appear when you have found it.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<rating>8.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>_7Iu_GOxsE0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2786</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588363-the-great-circus-mystery-starring-mickey-and</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/rhZMsua.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OqKe4Er.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7SqRKVJ.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/jTtUiLz.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/AHWBfNt.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/OanbmEE.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Un2Ho6W.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/fs6AtJA.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/PX1UK9r.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/HY0zPzn.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/v8AO0dP.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JaRiaXn.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/ofPdgUq.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/RF20KBt.png</clearlogo1>
</game>