<Game>
	<Name>Mighty Morphin Power Rangers - The Fighting Edition (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:Power Rangers: The Fighting Edition is a two dimensional fighting game, where the objective is deplete the other character's vitality in order to win the round. Players must win two out of three rounds in order to advance in Story Mode. Power Rangers: The Fighting Edition is a four button game; each character has two punches (light and heavy) and two weapons (light and heavy). In conjunction with the D-pad, players can execute throws and special moves. The game also has a Power Meter that periodically fills up. If a player executes a special move when the meter is full, they will gain a power level, eventually gaining the ability to do their character's super move when the gauge displays a thunderbolt.Natsume would go on to use an improved version of this engine in New Mobile Report Gundam Wing: Endless Duel for the Super Famicom.Characters:Top RowThunder MegazordNinja MegazordShogun MegazordMega TigerzordBottom RowLipsyncherGoldarLord ZeddSilver HornsHiddenIvan OozeUnlock Ivan Ooze by holding down X + Y and pressing Start. This only works in Fighting Mode.Modes:Story ModeIn Story Mode you get to choose between playing as the Thunder Megazord or the Mega Tigerzord. You then battle against every character in the game, including a copy of yourself, until you face off against Ivan Ooze.Fighting ModeIn Fighting Mode you can either fight against the CPU or another player, or watch two CPU controlled characters duke it out. To use CPU characters in Fighting Mode, players need to hit the select button on the respective controller.Trial ModeIn Trial Mode you face an infinite number of enemies, regaining a small amount of vitality between rounds.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Bandai America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>2.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>lFTI2KdUhcc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5612</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588494-mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-fighting-edition</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-fighting-edition</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mighty-morphin-power-rangers-the-fighting-edition/3030-11585/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/TATQEw5.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/JfK47hM.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/nUVg1eQ.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xai1Hml.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/2ipdpWz.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/B7runHI.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/GofDlUl.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/3SjKL2k.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/1j8cgk7.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/HDDueak.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MBGhNvv.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/3LAmFBC.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/7739iIN.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/tfKfw1Y.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/tLYRovF.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/67RmNRi.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Y5A6uNZ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Get ready to rock your world with the Mighty Morphin Power Rangers Fighting Edition, a three mode, smashing, bashing, monster trashing no-holds barred slugfest. This one-on-one two player simultaneous fighting game features your favorite Power Zords and a host of evil meanies. The Thunder Megazord, the Shogun Megazord, the Ninja Megazord, Lord Zedd, Goldar, and many more compete for total galactic supremacy in the mother of all battles. When the dust clears, only one will remain standing. Who will be crowned the mightiest, morphiest warrior in the universe? Only you can control the ultimate outcome.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>lFTI2KdUhcc</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3179d8c9-8116-46ab-9d1e-5798b00802ee.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a44bdb7f-ceff-462f-81d3-e1de111c20ae.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eb4b1c57-3585-4b23-aeda-3a640bfa840a.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d4e5d9b1-088f-40cf-9326-6737ca5f194b.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>