<Game>
	<Name>MLBPA Baseball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The strategy of baseball is merged with a fast-paced arcade game in MLBPA Baseball from Electronic Arts. Details designed to appeal to the die-hard fan include: real players with statistics based on the 1993 season; a full 162 game season mode; stadium music; animated scoreboards; defensive alignments; cut-off plays; run-downs; and even the double switch. Features meant to appeal to the casual fan include: large colorful arcade graphics; one stadium with animated crowds; a simplified pitching interface allowing players to steer the ball; and a batting interface that relies on timing instead of aiming cursors. Secret power-up play modes await so step up to the plate and take some hacks! Season play can be continued using passwords provided at the end of each game.Cheat: Cheat PasswordsEnter these cheat passwords by selecting restore season option:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3227</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588496-mlbpa-baseball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mlbpa-baseball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mlbpa-baseball/3030-2315/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/8g4QPuP.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/TVu3nEs.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/5ivovEl.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ncPyIQW.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6kwX7zb.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8Zqc7T1.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/lltwtLv.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/PIRWtjg.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/XsK17J4.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/h0wUyGP.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/pFgNTkR.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/cYVavjb.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/0TIQIas.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/zAc2top.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/cnrcNpD.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Never before has a baseball game been created that captures the details of the sport like MLBPA Baseball. Realistic run-downs, accurate cut-off plays, the double switch, multiple defensive alignments, snap throws, even bad hops and booted balls. Throw in every player from Alamar to Zeile and you've got the only baseball game worth playing for the Super NES.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/21f9b77f-7542-4db7-a2b0-7e5f714ee63b.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/224e5569-2530-4e8a-819d-10c39dc627e8.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9fe1a743-8e8e-46c8-852a-95d4888dde2d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d1ed7533-390d-4451-9e6b-c115c6490a25.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>