<Game>
	<Name>Mohawk & Headphone Jack (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The aim of each level is to collect enough CDs in order to open the exit to the next level. The CD number in the top left-hand corner will sound an alert and begin flashing when the required number has been reached. The exit appears on the map as a flashing X (not to be confused with the player's current location) after the required number of CDs has been reached. There are different coloured CDs worth a different amount of points, as well as large CDs that can be collected that unlock different audio tracks (the final one being Elephant Funk). Every second level ends with a boss, and will lead to a different world upon completion.Mohawk's health is represented by yellow triangles and each time he is hit by an enemy, the number will go down (maximum of five). However, spikes bring instant death like in most classic video games. He can also collect floating balls (maximum of 3) which allow him to explode, killing all enemies on screen. There are also a variety of forms Mohawk can become including wheelie, springs, angel and mer-hawk.Tips:Level Passwords:508917 Level 10049389 Level 2095649 Level 3111592 Level 4037090 Level 5028113 Level 6689992 Level 7987009 Level 8685497 Level 9http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mohawk_%26_Headphone_JackCheat: Level PasswordsEnter one of the following passwords to see the desired secret message:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Multi-Directional</genre>
	<Developer>THQ</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>5613</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588497-mohawk-and-headphone-jack</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/mo-hawk-headphone-jack</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mohawk-headphone-jack/3030-7939/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/7rLLcr3.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/TRNY0Jw.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/RwqUXNn.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/z86ouCB.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/GCGvAzD.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/54HHGJY.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/RRf4Ybe.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/9V4vELB.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/83XjYkV.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/DRcVkce.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Sjd7xTJ.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/8KzBbVM.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/JKkodrL.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ciHU2k4.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Go With The Flow! Mohawk &amp; Headphone Jack are funky, flexible life forms who can morf and completely change their shape. Normally laid back, these gelatinous guys are forced into a battle to protect their party lifestyle from the militant forces of General Headslot. Grab some tunes and get busy! - Sprout wings, burn rubber, stick to walls, transform into a sea creature and more! You can even reconstruct yourself if you explode. - Pick up tons of cool music CDs and cruise through ooze tubz to find the hidden vortexes throughout the game. - Use the special zoom-out map feature to keep from getting lost in 14 huge levels! - Forget up and down! Leap onto a surface and make it a floor. But better hang on - the whole level rotates around you!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/701d5ff3-fc27-4644-88df-5070b368a400.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2229f125-b770-41aa-8d9f-f10434f912b8.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f6af7f43-900d-4189-b6dc-de68ec62b47c.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d79cf404-f7db-4aec-8d22-fcc20b7482d7.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5958dcd5-b598-4f77-b449-e7a20d2752cf.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>