<Game>
	<Name>Multi Play Volleyball (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Multi Play Volleyball is a four-player volleyball game for the Super Famicom. The sixteen featured international teams are exclusively female and play the indoors version of the sport, rather than beach volleyball. Two, three or four players can play as two-person teams or competitively against one another. The game has a "free battle" mode for single exhibition matches and a "World Cup '94" mode that puts all sixteen teams in an elimination tournament.It features the following countries: Cuba, the Commonwealth of Independent States (the former Soviet Union; the game uses the Russian flag), United States, Brazil, Japan, Netherlands, China, Spain, Italy, South Korea, Canada, France, Algeria (the game uses the flag of Peru, however), West Germany (referred to as FRG, or the Federal Republic of Germany), Australia and Argentina.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Mebio Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>Glv-2cTcMSk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>29041</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571158-multi-play-volleyball</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/multi-play-volleyball/3030-28365/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/05tsSM7.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OirHKmk.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/OcKiX1E.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/f5lDw3y.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/F0MsubK.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/SXOOIcC.jpg</snapshot4>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/FE4v8iE.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The player controls a national volleyball squad (i.e., Cuba, USA, Canada, Brazil) as the play controls the entire team using an overhead view. Since indoor volleyball is simulated instead of beach volleyball, all matches take place on hardwood.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cbbb2466-548c-4429-9ca9-71cc44ebd130.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d97ce09c-c452-42ec-a538-8688997d20ea.png</clearlogo2>
	<rating>1.5</rating>
	<Publisher>Pack-In-Video Co</Publisher>
</game>