<Game>
	<Name>Muscle Bomber - The Body Explosion (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>It's Saturday night and the Slam Masters have arrived! Ten of the biggest and beefiest wrestlers ever to step into the ring have gathered for one bone-crushing, back-breaking tournament where there are NO RULES!Step into the ring and get ready for no-holds barred wrestling as you bounce your opponents off the ropes and clothesline the fools! Or dare them to take the fight outside the ring where brawls with tables, chairs and bottles are all part of the action. And just when you think you've got enough muscle, grab a multi-player adaptor and try out the four player Battle Royal where only the ultimate Slam Master will survive.Cheat: Easy Way to get to New YorkStart Single Match and lose. When you continue choose the person who you purposefully lost to and you will go to the next arena. Keep doing this until you face Jumbo Jack. It will not work when you face The Scorpion or Jumbo Jack because they are not selectable on the select character screen.Cheat: Easy Way to get to New YorkWhile fighting, go on the top ropes and press the Pin button. Your character should turn red. Now, you will deal more damage when you attack or slam someone.Cheat: Easy Way to get to New YorkPause the game right as your move lands, doing this will add to the amount of damage it inflicts.Cheat: Easy Way to get to New YorkIn single match get out of ring pick up weapon go in to left or right far side corner while out of the ring push B then Y to throw the weapon in the ring.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/6/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>vjBaLrg-ZH0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3247</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588642-saturday-night-slam-masters</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/saturday-night-slam-masters/3030-16684/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/x6IvbVU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/jAkF75H.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/0nbNNs8.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/cmGNbWI.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Cb4cj1u.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/WkefrGW.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/IFojTxF.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Z9zBfy9.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/wGjYhjf.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/QUAFcLL.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/MShvYaJ.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/BWhaKF0.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CbCEmpW.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Qvc7efo.png</clearlogo1>
</game>