<Game>
	<Name>Musya - The Classic Japanese Tale of Horror (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Shizuka holds a talisman that has locked away the Evil One in the Abyss. Recently, a guard of the Evil One has taken Shizuka away from her village along with her talisman. Now it is up to the pikeman, Imoto, to save her and seal away the Evil One.Gameplay: has Imoto going through various stages defeating enemies and stage bosses with his spear. Imoto can both thrust and spin his spear to attack enemies. He can also use 5 different magic spells, such as Thunder and Flame, which kill all the enemies on the screen.  Imoto may hold up to four scrolls of each of the five spells. Used spells can be replenished by finding items throughout each stage.The stages included are Tengumura Cavern, Catacombs, Palace of Hate, Cave of Darkness, Catacombs of Akuma, Cursed Palace, and the Watery Prison.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SETA U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>5620</thegamesdb_id>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/musya-the-classic-japanese-tale-of-horror</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ETm4qAy.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/dl8v66Z.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/znnEPna.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/beEqJvB.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/AdcLvHy.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/UAO1CSK.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8UGnUuX.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/hFKCsAW.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ZcTC9l4.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/dX7pkA2.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/gDy4Iyl.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/kqyhx4g.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/4O2NvIy.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/UriZKsg.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/bYgqq2s.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Plunge into a world of ancient Japanese horror. As Imoto, a spear wielding Samurai, it's your duty to descend deep into the Abyss to save the world from the horrors of the Evil One. Fight through hordes of hideous monsters to save Shizuka, the keeper of the Talisman that seals the Evil One in his prison. It's up to you to save her. Use your fierce spear spin attack to weave a web of destruction. Call on magical farces to blast your way through the legions leprous beasts.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b5b7e0e-d192-4616-8742-521158d08e71.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eeaddd56-06b3-4b0b-b44f-71aa0925ec7c.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/84fc7ead-32f7-4816-ab2f-27fcd39bde80.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ee6826a3-9de2-4193-8f4e-209da46a3f9f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/28b7227c-add4-4eed-9ef5-da270308eeff.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>SETA</Publisher>
</game>