<Game>
	<Name>Mystic Quest Legend (Germany)</Name>
	<plot>The planet is dying. Cold winds blow. Fires rage. Trees are withering. In other words, it's brutal out there. Only you can stop the Dark King from consuming the light from the Crystals of Earth. But don't think it'll be a walk in the park. You're up against the sleaziest of slimebags, the evilest of ecto-scum -- we're talking serious monsters here. This isn't your basic shoot-'em-into-smithereens kiddy game, either. You'll have to think your way out of some tough spots. Think you can handle that?Cheat: Battlefield ResetWhen fighting in a battlefield against an enemy that can selfdestruct, make sure all but that one enemy is dead. Also, make sure your hp is low enough for the selfdestruct to kill you as well. Wait for the enemy to selfdestruct and kill both of you. The battle will end, you will gain all the experience, gp, and even the battle count will decrease, and then it will ask you to try again. Do so and repeat the previous steps until you see that you have won the prize for defeating all the enemies. Win the next battle and exit. The battlefield icon will look like one that has been cleared out and the battlefield will now say: Battlefield Round 255 of 10.Cheat: Battlefield ResetIn the menu screen, press START and SELECT at the same time.  You should then get a box telling you which version number all the chips in your SNES are.  Afterwards, the text in the menu screens might act a bit wacky.  Just exit the menu and enter it again to fix it. Weird little trick for Square to put in the game, eh?Cheat: Battlefield ResetUsable with any battlefield that gives Experience points as a reward.Cheat: Battlefield ResetFight in the battlefield until you have one battle left. Then, go anywhere else, and fight enemies until your experience needed for the next level is within the range that the battlefield gives. (i.e. If the battlefield gives around 200 exp. per battle, get your needed exp. to within 200.)Cheat: Battlefield ResetThen, go back and finish the battlefield. You will gain the level with the exp. gain from the enemies, get the exp. reward, then gain another level.Cheat: Battlefield ResetThis glitch will completely skip getting the fire crystal and/or getting Reuben for the first time.To start, you need your items to be in this order for consumables, Seeds, Cure Potion, Refresher and Heal Potion last. Best way to get this order set up is to get the Seed in Bone Dungeon, getting the Cure Potion right after killing the Flamerus Rex. Get the Refresher in the Ice Pyramid's first room, waiting to get the Heal Potion in the room where you get the second chest armor (It's the right chest of the bottom two.) Okay, now once you beat the Ice Golem, get the coin and make way to Fireburg and go into the Hotel.Use up the last of your seeds so none are left and talk to the npc behind the counter on the right, they sell seeds, set it to buy 0 (ZERO) seeds and accept, open your menu and you'll see the zero seeds, use one and you'll see your Cure Potions turn into the Sun Coin, the final coin to get through Doom Castle.Okay, next thing we'll want to do is talk to the person sitting at the table just to the left and up a bit, they're selling Cure Potions, you want to buy 19 and then open your menu again, actually look at your items, you'll see you've lost both coins you've collected at this point from the first two dungeons, but now, where they were, you now have the last two coins.All you have to do from here is leave fireburg, go back to the focus tower, and enter the next area.Reuben will still pop out of your ass for the little scene at the bridge, but...eh, broken game is broken.Cheat: Battlefield ResetOn American versions of Final Fantasy: Mystic Quest, there is a particular glitch regarding the Life spell. Like in most Final Fantasies (and the EU/JP versions of this game), it is intended to be able to do extreme damage to undead enemies. However, a few flags got mixed up in the US versions of the game: in this version, you can use Life to kill non-undead enemies, although you can't damage undead enemies at all with this spell.Cheat: Battlefield ResetWhen you lose a partner and gain a new one, the new partner will retain resistances from your previous partner if you never turned off the game in between.  Stats are also affected, but do not remain exactly like the previous partner.The new partner will continue to have the incorrect stats and resistances until you restart the game.Cheat: Defeating Doom King EasilyOnce the battle with Doom King has begun, cast Cure on him, and you'll do massive damage to the boss. You'll do about  10,000+ to him. That's an easy win against the final boss, dont you think?Cheat: Defeating Doom King EasilyGo to any town, and if you find a treasure box, open it. Go out of town, then go back in. Open the box again and the item will be available. This can be of great help when you are stocking 99 of each item. </plot>
	<releasedate>5/10/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>SquareSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>AyVxBfFc6-c</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1602</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/532476-final-fantasy-mystic-quest</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/final-fantasy-mystic-quest/3030-3638/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/RXki03f.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nSNLDoV.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/4RrOGyb.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/MN80O01.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Z9XKzkL.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/WEAByFD.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/M4WwPP4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/KGM4uUM.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/P26VaNV.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/B77qoDC.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ar6Fv0L.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/1hPp8XO.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/jboldUH.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/k3hgTq5.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/60IrvEG.png</clearlogo1>
</game>