<Game>
	<Name>Nangoku Shounen Papuwa-kun (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Nangoku Shounen Papuwa-kun ("Southern Boy Papuwa") is a manga and anime about a young boy and his unusual friends on a tropical island. The player character is Shintaro, a member of the Genma army, as he runs across the island to find out where a bunch of invading monsters came from.The game is a mix of brawling and platforming. Shintaro has a quick punch move and a charged-up beam attack, and fights various sub-bosses as he makes his way through levels. He'll occasionally meet characters from the manga as well, including Tanno and Itou, who are a transvestite fish and an effeminate pink snail respectively.Both the Game Boy and Super Famicom versions were released on the same day by Enix Corporation, which also published the manga.	</plot>
	<releasedate>25/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Daft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>p4CyZ6-bDQY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14782</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571056-nangoku-shounen-papuwa-kun</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nangoku-shounen-papuwa-kun/3030-28373/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/LXus52l.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/SuwJZB4.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/x7I8Foj.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/yjCezw6.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zSVP2K1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Ft3YpFV.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/4duN1dw.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ILN4sfQ.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Z1FLtDl.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/iWwsWdY.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/XHbDtbI.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/jisfbMT.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/R2IrYQh.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/j5wL4Nl.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The game is a mix of brawling and platforming based on the manga of same title about a young boy and his unusual friends on a tropical island. The player character is Shintaro, a member of the Genma army, as he runs across the island to find out where a bunch of invading monsters came from. Shintaro has a quick punch move and a charged-up beam attack, and fights various sub-bosses as he makes his way through levels. He'll occasionally meet characters from the manga as well, including Tanno and Itou, who are a transvestite fish and an effeminate pink snail respectively.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ff323919-9685-4b06-a235-0f154f406066.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/35297bfb-e37a-42ef-bf10-182dafc2b84e.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Enix</Publisher>
</game>