<Game>
	<Name>NBA Jam - Tournament Edition (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:NBA Jam Tournament Edition is the second game in Midway&#8217;s basketball arcade series, featuring two-on-two fast paced matches with NBA players from the 1993-94 season (1994-95 on consoles). In total, the game featured over 120 NBA athletes and over 40 hidden characters. Improvements include additional power-ups, more detailed player attributes, player substitutions after each quarter, and a new soundtrack. The namesake "Tournament Mode" turns off all cheats and powerups, and rewards players with expanded rosters for nearly all teams if the player beats all 27 teams.In addition to these features, console releases added practice and &#8220;juice&#8221; modes, optional game toggles like "hotspots" and powerup icons, and an "injury" stat that lowers a character's stats. Later console releases ( Jaguar, Saturn, PlayStation) also featured larger character sprites and scaling effects to match those of the arcade version.Gameplay:The core gameplay is largely unchanged from the original NBA Jam. Players still have the ability to do all the crazy dunks from the original, and all actions (running, passing, shooting) can be enhanced by holding down the "Turbo" button. Turbo drains while active, and replenishes quickly when not in use. Players also have the series-staple ability to go on fire after making 3 unanswered scores in a row - giving the player temporary unlimited sprint and the ability to goal tend without being penalized. Small, but significant changes in the T.E. include slightly improved A.I., game speed, new dunks, and court changes matching the color of the home team. Up to four players can play at once, with the A.I. filling in any empty slots.More stats in the T.E.The most significant changes in the Tournament Edition are expanding each player's stats, and expanding each team's roster to three players (with some exceptions due to trades or retirement, such as Dallas, which only has two players). Players are graded from 0 to 9 in eight categories: Speed, Dunk, 3-Point, Block, Power, Clutch, and Pass. Stats directly affect a player's success for each particular action, and players can be substituted out at halftime to respond to the changing needs of the game. For example, the player would send in a player with high Power and Pass ratings if ahead, to minimize getting shoved or picked and secure your lead. If trailing in the 4th, send in players with a high Clutch rating. These changes bring an added level of strategy somewhat missing from the original.Every version of the game also contains the Tournament Mode, where all cheats, powerups, and special characters are disabled. Players are challenged to beat all 27 NBA teams, with progress stored to their initials (inputted at the start of the game). If a player beats all challenging teams, they unlock new characters and challenges. In the Arcade version, this unlocked the "???" team for play, consisting of NBA All-Stars and secret characters. These characters would also populate opposing teams, and always come with the "Quick Hands" and "Max Power" powerups (except in Tournament Mode). On consoles, beating Tournament Mode unlocked 2 new players for almost every team's roster, plus a new difficulty level.All versions of the game also included "Powerup" codes input at the Tonight's Matchup screen. These were secret combinations of button presses and stick moves that granted abilities akin to cheats (such as infinite turbo and power dunks). Playing in Tournament Mode disables these.An owner dipswitch option in the arcade allowed the winning team out of a game of four players to continue playing for free, adding extra incentive to beat any challengers lined up.ConsolesHotspots enabledSome additional modes were added for console releases, and could be individually toggled in the options screen off the main menu. "Hot Spots" place marked circles randomly around the court and reward the player with extra points (up to a 9-point shot) for sinking a basket while standing inside them. Each spot clearly displays its value within the circle. "Power-up" icons add randomly-appearing icons around the court that bestow an effect when touched (such as enhanced accuracy, instant "on fire," or an earthquake knocking down all other players). Finally, some releases included a "Juice" mode that increased the game's speed by a factor of four. Once again, playing in Tournament Mode disables all of these.The console releases also added an "Injury" stat for each player. This stat would increase as the player was repeatedly shoved to the ground, and decrease all his other stats proportionally. Substitutions were also increased to each quarter, encouraging injured players to be swapped out for a quarter and come back refreshed. It also added a further layer of possible tactics, as a strong player could be shut down with repeated shoving.Console releases also include an optional "Tag Mode" where you always control the player holding the ball. Passing to a player switches control to that player as soon as the ball connects. This mode can be helpful for anyone not content with the A.I. teammate's handling and decisions.Computer AI AnalysisThe computer artificial intelligence seems to have two different modes. In one mode (mostly seen in early tournament matches) the computer adopts a more passive defensive strategy. They will rarely ever try to push the player over, and the player can often simply run the length of the court and put up a three, or go for an easy dunk without ever worrying about passing. On offense, they tend to often go for three pointers, and will almost always make them if the player doesn't steal or block the ball first (especially if the player is ahead in score). The AI will rarely ever go inside the paint for a lay up or a dunk in this mode.In the second mode (mostly seen in later tournament matches) the computer is much more aggressive. They will often try to push the player over, making it almost impossible to progress the ball up the length of the court without passing the ball to the other player frequently. Also, if the player tries to put up a three, they will almost always get shoved by the opposing computer controlled AI player if he is nearby. This makes it hard to get three pointers up, and the player can end up getting pummeled if they do not pass frequently. On offense, the AI will frequently go for dunks and attack the paint. However, if the player leaves them wide open on the perimeter they will pull up a three and make it almost all the time.In general, AI in the first mode is much easier to deal with than the aggressive second mode. The one advantage the first mode has to the second mode is on the offensive side because they will often go for three pointers and will make them almost all the time meaning they can come back quickly if the player is sloppy on the offensive end. However, because of the second modes extremely aggressive defensive, it is more often than not much harder to deal with. Though if the player can manage to get a huge lead on them, it is a lot harder for this mode to make a come back because they often don't put up three pointers.Always going for dunks is a good strategy when in the leadHowever, it is hard to get a big lead on either types of AI because of the Rubber Band AI effect. As the player's lead grows, the probability of making shots becomes progressively lower, while the AI's probability of success progressively increases. One strategy to deal with this is to always go for dunks when you start to get a lead bigger than two possessions (4 points), because dunks have a very high probability of going in. Likewise, never go for three pointers because the probability of a three pointer going in is very small when you have a lead. Also increasing your defense on the perimeter is recommended because the computer's probability of making a three pointer when you have a big lead is nearly 100%. This is why the second computer AI mode is easier to get a big lead on because they tend to not go for three pointers and have tougher defense on the perimeter than they do in the paint.It is interesting to note that if, in the last seconds before half-time or the end of the match, the computer has the ball and they throw up a full court shot it will always go in (a 100% probability) regardless of the score, but if they advance the ball to half court and shoot it from there their probability of making the shot is significantly reduced. For the player, the probability of making a full court shot is very small, giving the computer a competitive edge at the end of the game. Also in the last ten seconds before halftime or the end of the game the computer will become extremely aggressive (even more so than the second AI mode) regardless of the type of AI the player may be facing. If the player has the ball the computer will sprint full speed towards him/her and try to steal the ball and take a quick shot. So if the player is not careful, the computer can score 4 or 6 points in the final 10 seconds using quick steals and shots.Teams and PlayersNBA Team RostersKevin WillisAtlanta Hawks: Stacey Augmon, Mookie Blaylock, Kevin WillisBoston Celtics: Dee Brown, Dino Radja, Dominique Wilkins ( Xavier McDaniel, Eric Montross)Charlotte Hornets: Muggsy Bogues, Larry Johnson, Alonzo Mourning ( Dell Curry, Hersey Hawkins)Chicago Bulls: B.J. Armstrong, Toni Kukoc, Scottie Pippen ( Luc Longley)Cleveland Cavaliers: Brad Daugherty, Mark Price, Gerald Wilkins ( John Williams)Dallas Mavericks: Terry Davis, Jim Jackson, Jamal Mashburn ( Tony Dumas, Jason Kidd)Denver Nuggets: Mahmoud Abdul-Rauf, LaPhonso Ellis, Dikembe Mutombo ( Robert Pack, Jalen Rose)Detroit Pistons: Joe Dumars, Oliver Miller, Terry Mills ( Bill Curley, Grant Hill)Golden State Warriors: Tom Gugliotta, Rony Seikaly, Latrell Sprewell ( Tim Hardaway, Chris Mullin)Houston Rockets: Robert Horry, Hakeem Olajuwon, Otis Thorpe ( Sam Cassell, Vernon Maxwell)Indiana Pacers: Derrick McKey, Reggie Miller, Rik Smits ( Antonio Davis)Los Angeles Clippers: Pooh Richardson, Stanley Roberts, Malik Sealy ( Loy Vaught)Los Angeles Lakers: Vlade Divac, Anthony Peeler, Nick Van Exel ( Eddie Jones, James Worthy)Miami Heat: Harold Miner, Glen Rice, Steve Smith ( Billy Owens, Khalid Reeves)Milwaukee Bucks: Vin Baker, Todd Day, Eric Murdock ( Eric Mobley, Glenn Robinson)Minnesota Timberwolves: Christian Laettner, Isaiah Rider, Doug West ( Donyell Marshall, Sean Rooks)Penny HardawayNew Jersey Nets: Kenny Anderson, Derrick Coleman, Kevin Edwards ( Armen Gilliam, Yinka Dare)New York Knicks: Patrick Ewing, Charles Oakley, John Starks ( Derek Harper, Anthony Mason)Orlando Magic: Nick Anderson, Horace Grant, Penny Hardaway ( Dennis Scott)Philadelphia 76ers: Shawn Bradley, Jeff Malone, Clarence Weatherspoon ( Dana Barros, Sharone Wright)Phoenix Suns: Kevin Johnson, Danny Manning, Dan Majerle ( Wayman Tisdale, A.C. Green)Portland Trail Blazers: Clyde Drexler, Terry Porter, Clifford Robinson ( Aaron McKie, Rod Strickland)Sacramento Kings: Mitch Richmond, Lionel Simmons, Spud Webb ( Bobby Hurley)San Antonio Spurs: Sean Elliott, David Robinson, Dennis Rodman ( Terry Cummings, Wesley Person)Seattle SuperSonics: Shawn Kemp, Gary Payton, Detlef Schrempf ( Kendall Gill)Utah Jazz: Jeff Hornacek, Karl Malone, John Stockton ( David Benoit)Washington Bullets: Calbert Cheaney, Scott Skiles, Chris Webber ( Rex Chapman)(players in brackets are unlocked after beating all 27 teams in tournament mode)New PlayersThe Following players are new to the franchise (They did not appear in the original NBA Jam):Jason KiddDoug WestDennis ScottBill CurleyYinka DareTony DumasGrant HillEddie JonesJason KiddDonyell MarshallAaron McKieEric MobleyWesley PersonKhalid ReevesGlenn RobinsonJalen RoseBrooks ThompsonMonty WIlliams (Tavares Montgomery Williams)Sharone WrightGary PaytonTerry DavisRobert PackSam CassellRobert HorryOtis ThorpeStanley RobertsMalik SealyLoy VaughtAnthony PeelerSean RooksDoug WestA.C. GreenRod StricklandBobby HurleyLionel SimmonsTerry CummingsDennis RodmanDavid BenoitKevin WillisXavier McDanielEric MontrossMuggsy Bogues (Tyrone Curtis Bogues)Dell CurryToni KukocLuc LongleyGerald WilkinsJohn "Hot Rod" WilliamsOliver MillerAntonio DavisBilly OwensSteve SmithTodd DayKevin EdwardsArmen GilliamAnthony MasonDennis ScottDana BarrosShawn BradleyJeff MaloneRex ChapmanHidden Players (Varies Depending on Version)Former U.S. President Bill Clinton, one of the hidden playersAir DogEd BoonBrutahJohn CarltonChow-ChowSal DaVitaFacimeFalcusDan FordenTony GoskieHillKabukiKid SilkKirbyShawn LiptakJay MoonMoosekaMuskettJamie RivettScooter PieSnakeMark TurmellWeaselRandall CunninghamFrank ThomasLarry BirdCarol Blazejowski/BlazeFresh PrinceDJ Jazzy JeffMike D. (Beastie Boys)ADROCK (Beastie Boys)MCA (Beastie Boys)Heavy DBill ClintonHillary ClintonAl GorePrince CharlesBenny (Chicago Bulls Mascot)Crunch (Minnesota Timberwolves Mascot)Hugo (Charlotte Hornets Mascot)Suns Gorilla (Phoenix Suns Mascot)Sub-Zero ( Mortal Kombat. Removed due to video game violence controversy)Raiden (Mortal Kombat. Removed due to video game violence controversy)Reptile (Mortal Kombat. Removed due to video game violence controversy)Tony Goskie from MidwayCheat: CodesEnter the following codes at the Tonights Match-Up screen:Cheat: CodesAt the title screen, press Start, Y, Up, Down, B, Left, A, Right, Down, Start, then enter JAM as initials. NOTE: JAM must be entered as initials whenever you want to use the extended rosters.Cheat: Play as Stud MuffinThis secret player requires a special extra step before he can be used. No other secret players require such a thing. At the first "Licensed by ..." screen, (this will be the very first screen displayed on SNES, and the first screen after the Sega logo on Genesis) push and hold the following button combination: Left + L + R (SNES) Left + Start + C (Genesis) You will NOT receive any confirmation that the cheat has been activated. So press and release the buttons a few times if you have to, just to get it right. With this done, go to the "enter initials" screen and enter the following: Highlight "G", hold Start, press A. Highlight space, hold Start, press A. Highlight "F", hold Start, press Y (SNES) or C (Genesis). If all steps where done properly, you will get the standard "Secret Player" message. And you will see it is "Stud Muffin" once you get to the team select.Cheat: Goaltend the final shotAfter the buzzer rings to end [I]any[/I] quarter of play, you can goaltend the final shot.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>2813</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588512-nba-jam-tournament-edition</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/nba-jam-tournament-edition</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nba-jam-tournament-edition/3030-14792/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/pLNepPn.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/23l97xe.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/0BNG4vh.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/s09ipIa.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/hgYOeO2.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/anwQuOw.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/MsmnA5R.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/36HS0vo.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/6v810Yb.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/WMzqWhC.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/4vKOBAI.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/w2PhRP6.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JU23LtI.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/kfmE9Ep.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/FvcY9CY.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/LccL9jz.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/BNds3L1.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/VgqcTnS.png</clearlogo2>
</game>