<Game>
	<Name>NBA Give 'n Go (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>NBA Give 'N Go is a port of the arcade version basketball game. The game is different from usual basketball games of the era because it is played in a vertical view. Most basketball games previously had a side scrolling or isometric view. Building upon this technique, the game features large player sprites and graphics. The game features the NBA roster from 1995 complete with player ratings. Gameplay consists of true 5 on 5 basketball but in a more arcade like style with alley-oops and high flying dunks. The audio includes action oriented commentary, in the style of NBA Jam.</plot>
	<releasedate>5/7/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Konami (America), Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>5624</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588509-nba-give-n-go</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/nba-give-n-go</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nba-give-n-go/3030-11202/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XvAULaD.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/b78y31c.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/cm6Y9bp.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ZB38OTu.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/eABLIy7.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/8CLa43x.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ZUXRP44.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Qr6ARge.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/y4ZH4n4.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/M3OKmPY.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/GHesLeT.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QSYzd5v.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/e78QQUS.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/2LKCxzW.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>No Quarters Required... We took all the action from our arcade classic and stuffed it with new features. Then we added some more. And more. - Official NBA license (What's a game of hoops without the biggest names on the court?) - Play one game, a whole, or just the Playoffs. And set the teams up the way YOU want. - Up to four people an play. Hey, it's a team sport. - You liked the arcade version cuz there were no rules. Cool, now you can play the arcade game at home. - You didn't like the arcade version cuz there were no rules. Cool, we added realistic play for the home.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0c5e6111-a39c-48f7-bfdb-5cbf7ce7e287.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3d9a473d-e493-462b-8204-70c2a96a3e00.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0f0ab1dd-e0ad-425e-93a8-df19712f09d4.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ac65675d-80a0-471f-9e2d-d3a4463947d9.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>