<Game>
	<Name>NBA Live 96 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Game Boy Version The Game Boy version of NBA Live 96 was developed by    Tiertex Design Studios and published by   Black Pearl Software.  Modes   In NBA Live 96 on the Game Boy there are not only a few different modes  of play, but also a simulation or arcade style modifier for each one.  In addition to the game modes there is also the option to change the  difficulty and period length for each mode. The different modes of play  are:      Season Mode Screen Exhibition - Exhibition is a simple one on one game against the AI. Season - In season mode a team is first chosen. At that point the schedule window will come up and allows the player to play the current game, simulate the current game, make trades, or exit the season mode. Season mode plays much like it's console counterparts and features a password save system.Playoffs - Playoffs mode is basically a tournament mode where a team is chosen and the goal is to win the tournament.Enter Password - A password can be entered to continue progress made in the season mode.Cheat: Hidden CharactersOn the Edit Player Screen, highlight a player and enter the player's name from the list below (last name only for those listed with a full first name). The hidden player will get that player's statistics. You can now trade this player to your team with the Trade Players option:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>5626</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588514-nba-live-96</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/nba-live-96</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nba-live-96/3030-20257/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/INX2sfv.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Utz9ISi.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/HvdBpB3.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/suBuc0M.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/DP010r7.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/rOo4VTB.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/f9vcyBF.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/EWcfW01.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/9U4cBaH.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/hAnAW1z.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/MR9jJLY.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/bkB4gqG.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/xs6Khin.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/efrBosG.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/f4ucBRF.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/IkOYBCs.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Back to Back Champion! NBA Live 96 returns for another CHAMPIONSHIP season. NEW player animations and REALISTIC strategy make it the COOLEST hoops game ever created on the Super NES.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3cd35b26-0af5-4b95-a688-3d114241ec00.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/30b096a4-14c3-4499-b62a-d1dc4323747a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b023f224-9195-4465-95ef-091c617f4b8f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f475c8d4-a158-4df3-9f4c-52c1642a9b93.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>