<Game>
	<Name>NBA Showdown (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:NBA Showdown is an NBA licensed basketball game from EA Sports. It is the fifth and final game in EA Sports's NBA Playoffs series, before EA's NBA franchise was relaunched as NBA Live. The game was released in Japan as NBA Pro Basketball '94: Bulls vs Suns. The game was originally released on the Super Nintendo in October of 1993, and was ported to the Sega Genesis the following year with the title NBA Showdown '94.Officially licensed by the NBA, it was one of the few early basketball games to feature every NBA team of the '93-'94 season. It also allows for a full 82 game season. Its successor was the first NBA Live game, NBA Live 95.Critical ReceptionIn reviewing the SNES version electronic Gaming Monthly gave a review score of 7 out of 10. Mike Weigand wrote, "may have been really somthing if it wasn't for the choppiness during game play -- it totally interrupts the game play at times and can be rather frustrating. However the ability to switch between players during the game, and other actions, are simple to execute".					</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>5629</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588516-nba-showdown</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/nba-showdown</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nba-showdown/3030-20242/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/KEZbohI.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/kBfVsph.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ZCeAKB2.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/gw01lwL.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/M5zgdgN.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/a9WhIdw.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/5gkgCuU.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/plbnbab.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Eb5Yc6O.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/gW4RG7u.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DTyK0vr.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/QgEEhD0.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/XCy1Vsn.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/SPWpJVk.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/f498Dob.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/xzGwFzQ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>AMERICA'S ROUGHEST NEIGHBORHOOD Features: - NEW! All 27 1993 NBA teams, plus the All-Stars - NEW! Single games, full season, and Playoffs - NEW! Battery back-up, tracks team standings and league leader stats - NEW! Trade players - NEW! Create dream teams - NEW! Sig moves for rad rookies Zo, Jackson, Laettner and 27 more pros - NEW! Injuries. Subs and Fatigue - NEW! Twice as fast as the original version - T-meter control over free throws - EA SPORTS instant reply If it's in the game, it's in the game.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/534fc735-5397-481c-9880-aa02b6ffc7ba.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/90b11d65-a2c4-44a6-8114-ef71cc13cc4a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/941f43ba-6419-426f-9d3b-282a4ec82f21.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8e65cf8d-e947-4d7a-b780-98a59ed344ad.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>