<Game>
	<Name>NCAA Football (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:NCAA Football is an American football game developed by The Software Toolworks and published by Mindscape for Genesis and SNES. It features multiple real teams from the NCAA (National Collegiate Athletic Association) competing via a horizontally-oriented perspective. NCAA Football was released several years before EA Sports would procure the name and license for their NCAA Football series: at the time, EA Sports's college football games were known as Bill Walsh's College Football.Gameplay:NCAA Football uses American college football rules and contains two game modes. The two play modes are tournament and exhibition.The game features sixteen college football teams, all of which are used as part of the games tournament mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Mindscape, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>XD2jJUxKSao</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5702</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588519-ncaa-football</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ncaa-football</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ncaa-football/3030-15972/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/tyo0Dmh.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/RgXZaYO.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/YXXW7Hd.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/brSQnHS.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/iry3s7B.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/rotstr8.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SIPIx8z.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/SEfFJUm.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ubIbRKy.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/BchSZ4s.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/U456dOe.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/10FKWf5.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8ShcG1d.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/LOPxDaM.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>NCAA FOOTBALL puts you right in the thick of it. This game plays like your team plays! Now you can play your favorite teams in the fantasy NCAA Championship. 40 top Division 1-A gridiron powerhouses - with real team colors and logos. This is REAL NCAA Football. Pit the greatest teams of the 60s, 70s, 80s, and 90s against each other in an all-out fight to be number ONE! Over 60 plays including all-time college favorites like the Wishbone and Suicide Blitz! State-of-the-art digitized sound effects, pulse-pounding music and battery back-up features! Intuitive controls make NCAA Football the game any fan can play. Choose quarter length, weather conditions, instant replay and more!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a85b6f2-e124-463c-8ac4-d21c57f37a9f.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/89fbde13-b10a-481d-8483-a50c0b0eb1e6.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a9d2f8fd-af6e-4c6f-a1ff-90714a47e1a7.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bc986128-7800-4bc9-a067-b7adbbdb77f5.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Mindscape, Inc.</Publisher>
</game>