<Game>
	<Name>New Horizons (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Imagine a time when mighty navies controlled the seven seas, ruthless pirates searched for hidden treasures and scholars argued that the Earth was round. Now, picture yourself as a young explorer on a mission that will carry you to the four corners of the globe.Play the son of a Portuguese Duke out to discover the legendary land of Atlantis, a Spanish female navy lieutenant turned pirate, a British privateer commissioned by Henry VIII to destroy the Spanish fleet, an Italian adventurer in debt from his father or a Turkish orphan starting his own trading business.Your adventure will take you to over 130 exotic destinations. Along the way, you will discover exotic monuments, long sought treasures and valuable merchandise to trade. As captain of your fleet, keep a careful eye on the horizon for pirates eager to steal your valued cargo or an enemy navy at war with the flag your ship flies. Once in port, remember to recruit mates, purchase new ships and gunnery, gather useful information and settle disputes with your enemied by challenging them to a duel.Get ready for the adventure of a lifetime!Cheat: Almost Never Get AttackedEnter Black Beard as your name, and no pirates will attack you.Cheat: Almost Never Get AttackedTo gain some easy gold at the beginning of the game, take the COLLECT DEBT job at the guild in Venice. When you collect the 5 gold ingots, deposit it in a bank. Then go back to venice and the banker will say you failed the job. You still get to keep the gold. Do this only when you have no fame or else you will lose some of your fame.Cheat: Almost Never Get AttackedHold the button ''Y'' when it is not your turn to speed up the battle.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Koei</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>j9eZIpuAzGo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6321</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588823-new-horizons</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/new-horizons</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4kW37wR.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/yEmP0jG.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/SHcTf6X.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/xYLYJCO.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/2r55WOJ.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/pL5Z00Y.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/EUChrq2.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/qFVYeHC.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/M9jZFiO.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7Ep0MGx.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/sU6ukKj.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/PFrLNob.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/tiIntRO.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/yAwGcQ3.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/PE2eTC9.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/o9WeytX.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Imagine a time when mighty navies controlled the seven seas, ruthless pirates searched for hidden treasures and scholars argued that the Earth was round. Now, picture yourself as a young explorer on a mission that will carry you to the four corners of the globe. Play the son of a Portuguese Duke out to discover the legendary land of Atlantis, a Spanish female navy lieutenant turned pirate, a British privateer commissioned by Henry VIII to destroy the Spanish fleet, an Italian adventurer in debt from his father or a Turkish orphan starting his own trading business. Your adventure will take you to over 130 exotic destinations. Along the way, you will discover exotic monuments, long sought treasures and valuable merchandise to trade. As captain of your fleet, keep a careful eye on the horizon for pirates eager to steal your valued cargo or an enemy navy at war with the flag your ship flies. Once in port, remember to recruit mates, purchase new ships and gunnery, gather useful information and settle disputes with your enemies by challenging them to a duel. Get ready for the adventure of a lifetime!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/37a8505b-e081-415f-b254-30ab79d8fd03.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d7c763c2-9a91-4479-8376-b328a8b6ee41.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/70517e28-f046-402c-8b82-ca2349acc380.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6fae2bbd-3461-49d6-9f92-a7adb85453e4.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
</game>