<Game>
	<Name>NHL '94 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:NHL 94 is a vertically oriented ice hockey simulation based on the game engine behind NHLPA 93. NHL 94 makes playable all NHL teams (active at the end of the 1993 season), complete with robust (though incomplete) player rosters, in addition to the East and West conference All-Star teams. Various players attributes (e.g. speed, aggression, shot) are ranked based on a 100 point system and affect the way players perform in the game.New Features IntroducedThese features were added from EA Sports previous game NHLPA 93:Goalie ControlShootout GamePenalty ShotsBench and Board Checks3 or 4 Player Compatible with Adapter (5 players on SNES)1992-93 Player Ratings &amp; RostersVariable Player Ratings when on Hot/Cold StreaksSave Player Records for each playerSave User Standings and RecordsOne-times and Special Moves by Selected PlayersNew Player StatsFlip PassesReverse-Angle ReplayClear the zone while killing penaltiesAutomatic Line Changes (can manually change lines at play stoppage)Tougher Computer DefenseTougher GoaliesComputer Shooting Scoring MovesPlayer and Team CardsPlayer Profiles with 144 Player PicturesLogan Organ Music matches Home ArenaTeam logos at center iceNew crowd animationsNo fighting or bloodPeriod StatsMore kinds of game statsTwo expansion teams (Anaheim and Florida)InnovationNHL 94 has been lauded as one of the best sports games ever made. It improved on the innovative NHLPA 93 engine, adding smoother sprite animation and a host of new gameplay mechanics. Perhaps the most important of the newly introduced gameplay features was the ability to perform a one-timer. (For non-initiated, a one-timer is when you pass the puck to a player and the intended recipient shoots the puck immediately, without pause.) The one-timer proved to be one of the most accessible scoring options in the game. Scoring was also made easier by the inclusion of a more robust deke mechanic with NHL 94 (at least in the SNES version of the game). In addition, gamers were also able to save their user records.NHL 94 also evolved from its predecessor by reducing the frequency of slap-shot goals scored through the goalie&#8217;s five-hole and stopping the ability to run into the goalie and have the puck your player was carrying drift into the net. Perhaps the most conspicuous feature included in NHLPA 93 and omitted from NHL 94 was the ability to fight your opponents. Fighting returned with NHL 95.Game Modes:Regular SeasonPlayoffsBest of Seven PlayoffsShootoutExhibitionNHL Teams &amp; RankingsThe following is a chart of the 26 NHL teams featured in NHL 94 and their rankings, strengths and weakness. These stats appear in the manual and the Team Selection screen. For the All Star East and West teams their home arena is Madison Square Garden.TeamOverall RatingHome AdvAway DisadvPower PlayPenalty KillingAnaheim Mighty Ducks51LowLowInsignificantWeakBoston Bruins76HighAverageStrongAverageBuffalo Sabres73HighAverageNormalStrongCalgary Flames75LowLowInsignificantStrongChicago Blackhawks78HighAverageNormalStrongDallas Stars67LowLowNormalStrongDetroit Red Wings75LowLowStrongAverageEdmonton Oilers67AverageHighInsignificantWeakFlorida Panthers52LowLowInsignificantWeakHartford Whalers66LowLowInsignificantWeakLos Angeles Kings74AverageAverageNormalWeakMontreal Canadiens73HighAverageNormalAverageNew Jersey Devils68AverageHighNormalAverageNew York Islanders66LowLowStrongAverageNew York Rangers74AverageAverageNormalAverageOttawa Senators55LowLowInsignificantWeakPhiladelphia Flyers69HighHighInsignificantWeakPittsburgh Penguins75HighAverageStrongStrongQuebec Nordiques71LowLowStrongAverageSan Jose Sharks56AverageHighInsignificantWeakSt. Louis Blues69HighAverageStrongStrongTampa Bay Lightning56LowLowInsignificantWeakToronto Maple Leafs72AverageAverageStrongStrongVancouver Canucks71AverageAverageInsignificantWeakWashington Capitals70AverageAverageStrongStrongWinnipeg Jets72AverageAverageNormalAverageTop Rated PlayersOnly 10 players had an overall rating of 90 or higher in NHL 94, they were the following:PlayerOverall RatingPositionTeamMario Lemieux100ForwardPittsburgh PenguinsRay Bourque99DefenseBoston BruinsEd Belfour98GoaltenderChicago BlackhawksAlexander Mogilny96ForwardBuffalo SabresSteve Yzerman95ForwardDetroit Red WingsPatrick Roy94GoaltenderMontreal CanadiensAdam Oates93ForwardBoston BruinsPat Lafontaine91ForwardBuffalo SabresPavel Bure90ForwardVancouver CanucksTeemu Selanne90ForwardWinnipeg JetsSkater AttributesThe skaters (defensemen, forwards) have an overall rating that is comprised from the average of the following attributes:EnergyAgilitySpeedOffensive AwarenessDefense AwarenessShot PowerShot AccuracyPass AccuracyStick HandlingEnduranceAggressivenessCheckingGoaltender AttributesLike the skater attributes, the goaltenders have an overall rating comprised of the average of the following attributes:AgilitySpeedGlove HandDefensive AwarenessPuck ControlStick RightStick LeftGlove RightGlove LeftPenalties in NHL 94Holding - Illegally grabbing or pinning a player so he can't move.Roughing - Unnecessary roughness or causing an injury.Slashing - Deliberately hitting an opponent with your stick in an attempt to obstruct or intimidate him.Cross Check - Lifting the stick off the ice with both hands and using it to check an opponent.Tripping - Tripping the puck carrier, the referee has to believe there was no attempt to capture the puck.Hooking - One player's attempt to "hold up" the other player with his stick.Charging - Slamming into a player after two or more deliberate strides in his direction.Interference - Called when a player interferes with the opposing goalie in the crease or on his way to the crease.Game Bugs in Genesis/SNES VersionsGame freezes and error message appears, most likely occurs if you bump into the console while playing.Skater can get a "boost of speed" after being checked into the boards.Skater "freezes" on a one timer and gets stuck in the shooting position.A player can pull off a "double shot" when missing the initial shot but then will shoot it on the second attempt, although no animation will occur for the 2nd shot.When passing a puck directly at the goal it can occasionally go in as a goal and slide "underneath" the goalie.Puck is shot out of the rink and floats from the crowd back into the rink.You can cancel an opponents penalty shot if you change goalies before his skater can take the shot.Occasionally on a one-timer goal, the person who passed on the one timer gets 2 assists for the goal.In the Saturn CD Version the goalie can "fall apart into pieces" after being scored on.Differences Between SNES and Genesis VersionsThe Genesis and SNES versions of the game are mostly similar but differ in some ways. The main menu looks rather different from one version to the next, the SNES version adopting a much more basic design. There are also slight graphical differences during gameplay. Possibly the most significant difference is that the SNES version will not track players' statistics from one game to the next (for example, to see which player on your team is leading in goals scored during playoff mode).Ron Barr's QuotesWelcome to a sold out {insert arena], home of the [insert home team]Hi I'm Ron Barr for EA Sports... and in goal tonight [goalie name] for [team] and [goalie name] for [opposing team]For [team name], [player name] is on a hot streak, but [player name] is on a cold streak.The [arena] crowd record is [number] db.Hit the Start button to begin, Use the A and C to cycle through menus.Lately [team name] has been playing well ... [team name] has been playing extremely well.SpecialA version of NHL 94 was released on the PlayStation 2 version of NHL 06. It was based on the Sega Genesis version. However do to copyright, lacked the official NHL rosters of the time. There was also a European version of the game released as NHL Hockey 91.Cover AthletesTomas Sandstrom of the Los Angeles Kings shooting against Andy Moog of the Boston Bruins.Cheats for Sega Genesis Release30 Second Periods: Hold A C when you turn on your Sega Genesis and do so until you get to the Edit Lines Screen, you should see a :30 time on your periods.Instant Healing: If a player gets injured, pause the game and then take a time out. The injured player will return to the game with full health.Edit Other Teams: If you are the home team, you can edit the other players lines.PC Release System RequirementsMinimum CPU Class Required: 80396Minimum OS Class Required: DOS 4.0 to 6.22Minimum RAM Required: 2 MBMedia Type: 3.5 " Floppy Disk, CD-RomMinimum CD-Rom Speed Required: 1XVideo Modes Supported: VGASound Devices Supported: Adlib, PC Speaker, Roland MT-32, Sound BlasterInput Devices Supported: Gravis Gamepad, Joystick (Analog), Keyboard, MouseCritical ReceptionElectronic Gaming Monthly gave the game scores of 9,8,8,8. Ed Semrad wrote, "... a must for any sports fan. EA is getting closer to making the ultimate hockey game". Mike Weigand wrote, "...Loads of new features have been added to NHL '94. Now there are four players with 2-on-2, or any combination you may like. Other new features include real players' stats from the previous season, including faces and streaks. They also have the new logos and each team's rink music. The level of detail, from the crowd scenes to the control is great".Cheat: Mighty Ducks of Anaheim Playoff PasswordsNHL 94 (Super Nintendo) - Mighty Ducks of AnaheimBest of 7shttp://youtu.be/B39AOG00thwCheat: PasswordsAt the "Cont. Playoffs" screen, you will be prompted to enter a password.Cheat: PasswordsCodes can be entered from the Continue Playoffs option</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-5 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3228</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588524-nhl-94</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/nhl-94</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nhl-94/3030-20166/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/fXgG1yQ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/rHEW8Hc.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/H87DF7A.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/9ORDmZM.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ZHUAzUb.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/QJPBAYo.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/AGkYpMX.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/PqkOda0.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/K9wgMPm.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/uVCEdcE.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/B1kE7lC.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/yHuudAh.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/couYU56.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/G4AK7K8.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/7vYOdHp.png</clearlogo1>
</game>