<Game>
	<Name>NHL 95 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The SNES and Genesis releases of the game feature significantly improved graphics from years past.Also introduced in NHL 95 is the ability to play through a complete NHL season controlling a team. The user has the freedom to trade and sign players. They can also create their own hockey players. The user is given "300 Points" that can be allocated to various categories.Categories for create a player include...AgilityDefensive AwarenessPuck ControlStick RightStick LeftGlove RightGlove LeftThe game also introduces fake shots, drop passes, and the ability to go down to the ice to block a shot. Line Changes and Instant Replay are also available in NHL 95.Game Modes:Exhibition - Team 1 vs Team 2Season - Players pick a team and play an entire 84 game season (season is now 82 games). Following an NHL Season the game also shows screens of which player won which award, including the Vezina Trophy, Hart Trophy, and Conn Smythe for playoffs.Playoffs - Players pick a team and the game randomizes a playoff bracket. The player also has the option to make it single elimination or the traditional best of 7 games for each series.Practice - Pick a team and practice passing, shooting, and skating around.Game with Trades - Whenever someone makes trades, signings, etc, the player can pick this mode in order to have access to them. The game features an internal General Manager that approves or denies trades depending on how even they were.Shootout - Each team takes turns in the shootout with 5 various players. It is one on one with the shooter and goalie.CoverThe cover of the game features New York Ranger Alexei Kovalev scoring on Vancouver Canucks goalie Kirk McLean in the 1994 NHL Stanley Cup Finals. This would be the second to last time that the cover of the game featured two athletes. NHL 96 would be the last to do this.Team RatingsThis is a list of each team and their corresponding rating out of 100 in the game.TeamRatingMighty Ducks of Anaheim58Boston Bruins77Buffalo Sabres78Calgary Flames77Chicago Blackhawks83Dallas Stars71Detroit Red Wings79Edmonton Oilers69Florida Panthers65Hartford Whalers64Los Angeles Kings73Montreal Canadians76New Jersey Devils73New York Islanders66New York Rangers79Ottawa Senators58Philadelphia Flyers71Pittsburgh Penguins78Quebec Nordiques69San Jose Sharks70St. Louis Blues79Tampa Bay Lightning64Toronto Maple Leafs75Vancouver Canucks75Washington Capitals70Winnipeg Jets70The game also features teams for the Eastern and Western All Stars.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>5708</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588525-nhl-95</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/nhl-95</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nhl-95/3030-15126/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/G1m5opW.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/vLlxlnt.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/rizbEFi.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/nDbnEjs.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ijEpIfh.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SPYibOR.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/llyoP7j.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/bD2DYaO.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Nk3doSM.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/3xRGu6O.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nYb4HJn.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/qF4biBo.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/BUgJWXf.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jKOl267.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/29StvY2.png</clearlogo1>
</game>