<Game>
	<Name>NHL 98 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This is EA's yearly NHL franchised hockey game.   Improvements For the first time, EA's NHL series included National Teams.  Although they could not get the official Nagano Olympic license, they were able to have national teams with corresponding rosters. EA introduced for the first time in their NHL series 3Dfx Glide support which dramatically changed their graphics from previous years (although the SNES and Genesis versions of the game continued to look like the previous 2D games) Game Modes:Exhibition - single game, pick your team and your opponent and face against the computer or friend.Season - You can play all 82 games of the 1997-98 NHL season, trade players, sign free agents and go through the ups and down of a full season.Practice - Try situations like penalty kills, power plays, odd man rushes.  Select how many players you want versus how many players the opposing teams have.Skill Challenge - Try some of the challenges that have been made popular with the NHL's All Star game, such as faster skater, accuracy shooting, skating around cones and 2 on 0 goalie scenarios.Shoot Out - One on One, goalie versus a skater on a breakaway.Teams &amp; Rankings In addition to the then 26 NHL Teams (before Atlanta Thrashers, Nashville Predators, Columbus Blue Jackets and Minnesota Wild), two All Star Teams and only 3 National Teams (United States, Canada, Europe).  Here are the default NHL Team Rankings: TeamEven StrengthPower PlayPenalty KillingGoaltending Anahiem Mighty Ducks9th 6th 22nd 11th  Boston Bruins26th 16th 21st 26th  Buffalo Sabres6th 26th 13th 6th  Calgary Flames21st 8th 17th 13th  Carolina Hurricanes19th 4th 10th 19th  Chicago Blackhawks14th 17th 11th 7th  Colorado Avalanche1st 3rd 2nd 5th  Dallas Stars2nd 19th 16th 3rd  Detroit Red Wings5th 7th 4th 2nd  Edmonton Oilers13th 6th 18th 16th  Florida Panthers7th 21st 7th 4th  Los Angeles Kings24th 25th 3rd 20th  Montreal Canadians17th 13th 26th 23rd  New Jersey Devils3rd 23rd 1st 1st  New York Islanders22nd 22nd 15th 18th  New York Rangers8th 1st 25th 1th  Ottawa Senators16th 11th 20th 12th  Philadelphia Flyers4th 18th 6th 8th  Phoenix Coyotes11th 5th 5th 15th  Pittsburgh Penguins10th 2nd 23rd 25th  San Jose Sharks25th 20th 12th 24th  St. Louis Blues12th 15th 14th 14th  Tampa Bay Lightning20th 24th 8th 17th  Toronto Maple Leafs23rd 14th 19th 22nd  Vancouver Canucks15th 10th 24th 21st  Washington Capitals18th 12th 9th 9th   Players with 100 Rating There are several players in the game that are by default rated 100, they are:   CenterNameTeamPosition Paul KariyaAnahiem Mighty Ducks Left Wing  Dominik HasekBuffalo Sabres Goaltender  Peter ForsbergColorado Avalanche Center  Sergei FedorovDetroit Red Wings Center  Rod Brind'AmourPhildelphia FlyersLeft Wing  Eric LindrosPhiladelphia Flyers   Jaromir JagrPittsburgh Penguins Right Wing  Keith TkachukPhoenix Coyotes Left Wing  Paul CoffeyPhiladelphia FlyersRight Defense Ray BourqueBoston Bruins Left Defense Cover Athlete Peter Forsberg of the Colorado Avalanche   Trivia: Mario Lemiuex was in the Saturn version of the game, although he had retired at the end of the 1996-97 NHL Season.  Cheat: Easy GoalsDuring gameplay,   pause the game and select "Controllers" on the menu.  Switch your controller to the opposing team.  Get out of that screen and select "Change Goalie" option.  Switch goalie to "none" and then go back in the "Controllers" option and change back to your original team.   Your opponent now has an open net for easy goals!</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1997</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>5711</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575221-nhl-98</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/nhl-98</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nhl-98/3030-18845/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/5dBqD1L.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/oF1dMXN.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/fEgd9hA.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qsKtgoG.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/CdXyfXv.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/iVyENoD.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/pIJ9TKn.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/j9CO8tI.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ixaks2l.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Fj2jPmc.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/P5AGMUn.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/fcsgWUQ.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1JO0KAe.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ABfq0Yp.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The ultimate judge! Run the ice with the world's best hockey players, execute give-and-go plays, shake the boards with brutal hip checks, fire off blistering one-timers, and vault the wall to change lines on the fly. In the sports gaming world, NHL 98 is the only competition on ice.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6aed171a-747c-46c7-b64c-ad003cd2e211.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/70b21136-cd6c-47c9-a63b-837a6ad78d35.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/722f0ad0-3730-4c07-b071-80c5fc346e34.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a270086e-9c0e-48b7-a737-c0735d6f5e99.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>