<Game>
	<Name>No Escape (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Based on the 1994 movie of the same name starring Ray Liotta, the player takes control of Liotta's character, Capt. J.T. Robbins, whose only objective of the game is to escape an island. After shooting his commanding officer, Robbins is imprisoned and eventually sent to the island Absolom as a war criminal, from where there is no escape possible. To do this still, the player must explore the island with side-scrolling platform gameplay for clues, finding items and combining them to make weapons and traps.  Robbins can talk to some prisoners to help him in his quest, but he must also avoid violent prisoners, either by attacking them with punches or kicks or using traps and stealth to bypass them. The graphics are based off of rotoscopes of the actual actors from the movie.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>I3LQhfKNaKM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5714</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588534-no-escape</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/no-escape_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/no-escape/3030-50395/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Jv4xdTH.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/veYftg2.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/yFgrKkj.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/hpwYDDi.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/KWiLK6a.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/8bptd6F.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/W6Eocwo.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/i1ltSeb.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/rsEj63S.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/8zfXywn.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/VCK4Ny9.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/7qUDTDW.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/DmE3BkY.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/eHI9ilm.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/gFCVvPc.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Based on the Hollywood action-thriller, NO ESCAPE puts you in the shoes of Robbins, an inmate on the island penal colony of Absolom. Free to travel anywhere on the island - except off! - you'll come face-to-face with ultra-realistic characters rotoscoped from real actors and confront countless deadly traps. You'll be forced to fight or outsmart gangs of savage Outsiders. Only the Insider's Camp gives you a place to rest, exchange information and trade items necessary for your escape. A detailed warden's overhead map lets the player choose which part of the island to explore next. If you gather together the right pieces as you proceed, you'll ultimately confront a final choice... to boldly break free in the prison helicopter or slip quietly away in a specially designed stealth boat. Unlike in the movie, the ending to this story is up to you.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49f00dc4-f93f-494c-a98d-276b1e0997c8.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/04c41837-5c9e-484e-a0b3-366445fa3b8b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/924f45a6-42d0-414b-84df-0c7d41b8f20b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0824d935-6a76-4a38-872a-5d6559393a7c.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sony Imagesoft</Publisher>
</game>