<Game>
	<Name>Nosferatu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Nosferatu is a horror-themed action-adventure game based on the legend of Nosferatu (an adaptation of Bram Stoker's Dracula). The player, as Kyle, must recover his girlfriend Erin from the vampire Nosferatu after the undead creature spirits her away in the middle of the night and takes her back to his castle.The game takes elements from both Konami's Castlevania franchise and Prince of Persia. Kyle moves through the castle using his fists, acrobatics and wits to avoid traps and fight Nosferatu's minions, most of which are classic horror archetypes like Frankenstein's Monster. Like Prince of Persia, the player has a hard time limit to get to Erin and Nosferatu in a far tower, but this time limit can be extended by finding special hourglass power-ups. Kyle can also find crystals that increase his power (red), restore health (green) or increase the length of his health bar (blue).								</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SETA U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>nlJ8rNjBENA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5717</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588539-nosferatu</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/nosferatu</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nosferatu/3030-6408/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/dUtYuuV.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/0PoyzM2.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/GsV9tA1.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/h8SZgVR.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/JEp2IBq.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/U771ST3.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/mm4Jdez.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/lTqsT99.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RqWkIfY.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/FY3ALgh.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/T1zBL4u.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/8ZLJOcL.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ZbKUJVA.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/8iJuLsr.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/5lUksKi.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/yCpB75Q.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/gr0KjJy.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/rNbKRNK.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>It's a race of time. Kyle must save his fair maiden Erin before the evil clutches of Nosferatu can sway her fate forever! Dungeons and graveyards are only a few obstacles in his path, littered with traps and beasts of unspeakable nature. Join Kyle's journey into darkness to return his love before her soul is lost for eternity! - 16 megs of dramatic action and adventure at its best! -With 6 master stages, 14 sub-levels, and countless hidden rooms, Nosferatu will challenge you with fun and adventure! - Discover treasures and hidden secrets of every level! - Fluid play control for speed and maneuvering! - Multiple hit combinations including flying reverse kicks, roundhouse kicks, spinning back fists and many more! - Awesome movie like graphics, including more than 350 frames of character animation! Realistic arcade style action! - Battle creatures like Werewolves, Beholder Eyes, Stone Golems, Gargoyles, and Vlad the Impaler (Nosferatu) himself! - Superb sound track and quality sound effects!</Notes>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4228095a-aa78-47e8-8c15-21b56e9c5c72.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0881ecca-f0b3-4d3d-8684-51026c0f8c5d.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a854758c-346b-453e-957f-c190342a752c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2139f0ff-a661-4a58-88a7-e75c8fb5a698.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>SETA</Publisher>
</game>