<Game>
	<Name>Obitus (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Wil Mason has been transported to the fantasy world of Middlemere, which is ruled by four rival brothers. Wils aim is to find the secret to how he was transported here and discover a way back.The gameplay consists of a combination of arcade elements and first person view much like Eye of the Beholder and Dungeon Master.  One of the more remarkable features is in the first person mode, rather than having just 4 directs to face and flicking between them there are 8 directions and the view scrolls smoothly as you turn. This smooth scrolling continues when you move forward, giving the game more of a 3D feel.The arcade elements consist of horizontal scrolling areas where you fight enemies with your bow while avoiding their attacks.  Later you encounter a similar type of gameplay that involves exploring castles and adds 4 directional movement.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Psygnosis Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>RR0VePS_DBc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5718</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588540-obitus</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/obitus</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/obitus/3030-16358/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/TEE9KWn.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/tWSD3Qs.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/hpJSFhF.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/IaSdYMG.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/VQQpYa4.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/AvcbbuS.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/NH3mBsH.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/iEJfBm0.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CE66Muy.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/6Lkfij1.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/bMBML0b.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ROCw2v1.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/0Wrtayc.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/IVw4Htr.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/OS4YGX4.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Adventure in a Land of Ruin. Old King Cullen warned his sons that the kingdom of Obitus would fall into evil hands if the Gems of Tranquillity were removed from the tower in the center of the land. Not long after his passing, the king's prophecy came true. Now Obitus is a dark maze riddled with mean creatures and sinister secrets. It's up to you to venture to the corners of the kingdom and recover the Gems so that peace is restored to the land. Your adventure takes place in both first person perspective and side view stages so that you always have the ultimate outlook on the action. Go forth and bring peace to the land. - Battery-backed to save your progress. - First person perspective and side view stages. - More than 12 adventurous areas to explore. - Dozens of weapons and magical items.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23121c55-17ce-47fb-9d67-cde90b2179ed.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9a024421-0329-4be8-8ec6-d50d10fc2368.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dae86189-7d2f-46bb-9ee9-7d75effbc87f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1bf88fe1-9503-4a6b-8010-7e4026335a86.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Bullet Proof Software</Publisher>
</game>