<Game>
	<Name>On the Ball (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>There's a kind of knick-knack you may find in dusty games rooms, a maze through which you navigate a marble by subtly tilting the board, dancing with gravity and momentum, deftly rolling your sphere out of dead ends and around the obstacles posed by holes in the board. Marble Madness explores this theme in a fudged 3-D perspective, Cloud Kingdoms in a flat 2-D one -- both by directly influencing the actions of the ball.  The game takes a different approach toward a similar end; instead of moving the ball around the board, you move the board around the ball.That's right; from the get-go, gravity pulls ever down, down, down on your ball toward the bottom of your screen regardless of board orientation; the task of the player is to rotate the board now clockwise, now counter-clockwise, to further a timely and unobstructed path beneath the ball in its progress toward each level's goal before the timer ticks down to zero.  The game might as well have been named "inertia."  Many obstacles can be avoided, but some must be engaged head-on: a certain momentum, if not terminal velocity, must be achieved to break through crumbling brick barriers; other obstacles toggle on and off like traffic lights, demanding not only speed but timing.  Some influence the ball's direction, and in addition to merely delaying the ball's progress, touching some impediments incurs an additional time penalty -- conversely, some blocks bestow time bonuses, if you can afford the ever-diminishing time needed to take the scenic detour and collect them.It may seem like a transparent attempt to cobble together a game around a technical demo of the SNES' Mode 7 on-the-fly graphics-rotation capabilities, but Taito actually cooked up this kooky game interface two years earlier for an arcade release of this game.(Now if only someone could explain the "Camel" part - referencing the Japanese title.)</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>fbudpdhIjUE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5720</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588543-on-the-ball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/on-the-ball-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/on-the-ball/3030-35800/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/v6r9Nqz.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/EuIcLrj.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/t9af8m6.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/1BYW2RU.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/0kuv3Lz.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/iSg5yxB.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/txZY7KL.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/CyBF6Y2.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/HmKZIVJ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/j8Ltg51.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Vovcs0N.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/CrCT8yR.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/1ckJZgo.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/SDrcF32.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7EHIGEj.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/PKTfaRK.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Time to Rock and Roll! On The Ball brings you fast-paced arcade action like never before! Cascade through multiple levels of intense, brain busting rounds that feature tricks, traps and killer dead ends! Gravity takes a whole new spin as you manipulate the 3-D fields to guide the ball to the final hidden Goals. Build up enough momentum and you'll blast through bricks that protect short-cuts and valuable bonuses! But Beware! Time is the ultimate enemy as you race the clock to defeat the puzzles! Danger lurks in every course as you navigate past Timer Drains. Power Bumpers and Rock-hard Bricks. Follow the guide arrows to safety and prove to everyone that you're really On the Ball! - Share the excitement in the awesome 2 Payer Mode! - Control 3 levels of speed: Fast, Really Fast and Watch Out! - Password feature saves you from starting from scratch. - Dozens of mind-bending Courses that will challenge the toughest players!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ee9f71bf-a5b6-41b8-b4ac-3d3d8eb14bd8.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a20c1e7c-11b9-4e1a-967c-b6994084f2b3.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ff101eb4-2845-48bb-87fe-8c2b6fcbf78c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c8c80728-dd36-4514-a2a9-ddeb2a16324d.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Taito</Publisher>
</game>