<Game>
	<Name>Oonita Atsushi FMW (Japan) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Onita Atsushi FMV is a one-on-one fighting game licensed by and featuring Onita Atsushi and his Frontier Martial-arts Wrestling organization. The player can select between Onita Atsushi himself or various real-life fighters involved in his organization, like Tarzan Goto and Ricky Fuji. The game has a fictional antagonist in the Shadow King, who acts as the final boss of the one-player mode.The combat is a mix of wrestling moves and standard fighter game moves a la Street Fighter II. There are a total of four playable characters, though there is also a secret fifth fighter that can be unlocked: Megumi Kudo, the only female fighter in the game.Cheat: Unlock Megumi Kudo and the Womans Single Player modeDefeat K.Shadow in his final form in Single Player mode using any character. After the credits have finished, a third mode will now be selectable from the main menu screen featuring a special single player Death Match between two hidden characters: Megumi Kudo and Combat Toyoda.</plot>
	<releasedate>6/8/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Marionette</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>31605</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581885-onita-atsushi-fmw</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/onita-atsushi-fmw/3030-30213/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/KusyjO4.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/wPb9EK4.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/bhwyPHW.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/9bm1fH3.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/w3foQQe.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/y3rLDfa.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SlONyco.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/YbGMrGA.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ukbiQWf.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/YUzS62P.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/zBPi0vB.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/gxO84zm.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Player have to fight their way through a fictionalised version of the Frontier Martial-Arts Wrestling organization; the wrestling promotion Onita owned, booked and was the star of throughout the nineties, portrayed in this game to be more of a tournament of the Street Fighter variety than a realistic wrestling company. According to the official slogan of the game, it was considered to incorporate an entire batch of innovative ideas. The instruction manual for the game talked about the virtual pursuit of achieving the total potential of each wrestler.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/45ad991c-b8a8-400a-8b16-2d8612372e7e.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9f2ecce9-5e19-42a4-aec0-46124b363598.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Pony Canyon</Publisher>
</game>