<Game>
	<Name>Operation Europe - Path to Victory 1939-45 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Operation Europe: Path to Victory 1939-45, or Europa Sensen ("European Front") as it's known in Japan, is a Koei turn-based war strategy game based on conflicts taking place during World War II.The game is the WW2 equivalent to Koei's earlier Nobunaga's Ambition and Romance of the Three Kingdoms series. As with those games, emphasis is placed on individual commanders and their abilities, and the game prioritizes tactics and numbers over graphical prowess. The player has a number of different WW2 commanders to choose from while playing either side, some of which are real but most are fictional.				</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Simulation, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>KOEI Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>2.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>t2m2SzZMNuc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5721</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570898-operation-europe-path-to-victory-1939-45</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/operation-europe-path-to-victory-1939-45</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/operation-europe-path-to-victory-1939-45/3030-6667/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/oW3j1g1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/uLkSV2a.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/8T5DBII.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/UL0xW3l.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/vae5pfU.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/DaNDo3M.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/TCAWbUB.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ZlV2HuB.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/NcpSS5A.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/9RU0rq6.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/I8uCFec.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/tBm60NY.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/267DV9f.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/YEE9ai0.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/dwcFISt.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The World's About To Change! The year is 1939 and Hitler's war machine is rumbling across Europe. Here's your chance to plot the strategies that will either stop the Axis in its tracks or carry it to victory. Take part in the war in Africa, the famous tank battles at Kursk, Battle of the Bulge, Battle for Normandy and the fight for Berlin. Give orders to your generals in the field: Patton, McAuliffe and Montgomery. Assassinate enemy commanders with special forces, have engineers lay mines and drop paratroop units into occupied cities. The Axis is a ruthless adversary with commanders such as Rommel, Rundstedt and Manstein leading the charge. With their advanced weaponry and strong footing it won't be easy to drive them back to Berlin. Leave diplomacy to the politicians. Now is the time for military men to take actions into their own hands!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/46f62ddf-7741-4738-93fa-9b0a5c567414.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/38e825f7-9088-4190-83ea-f497cd5391c4.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5b55f8f1-a4f6-4526-99db-14fe5237c1dc.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6210c6b7-cd46-4a5a-93db-484a4d1fac55.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
</game>