<Game>
	<Name>Oscar (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Your name is Oscar. You have to run and jump through 7 Levels in Hollywood-style (Science Fiction, Western, Horror, Cartoons, Dino, Detective and Gameshow) to find Oscars (yes  the Academy Award!). If you have enough Oscars you solve the level. You can choose the levels in every order you want. In the levels you must jump on platforms to discover the level. You kill the enemies by jumping on them. Some of them lose a power up like invulnerable or a superjump. You can also find a JoJo to break down walls or using as ladder. Two creatures are no opponents. First the white rabbit. He gives you a extra continue. Second a red elephant. Touch him for using as save point in level.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Titus France SA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>TRTxRlhYCC0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5723</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588547-oscar</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/oscar</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/oscar/3030-4920/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/zlZ1uyv.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/srG6aGl.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/LnSisKz.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ymZ5ihf.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Uxtqcgj.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xBeEOz6.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/kTAl8Vn.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ZHdF7We.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/JbXPTBT.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/tIjRX41.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/UTmqQWR.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QyeVMF1.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/cpbRBDA.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/GHnDXEM.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Lights! Camera! Action! It's time to meet Oscar, the newest legend of the silver screen, ready to take Tinseltown by storm... once he's used his star-power to escape the theater he's trapped in, that is! Star in the role of a lifetime as you help Oscar navigate 4 different levels full of fun and adventure in search of a way to escape the fantasy film world he's trapped in. Will our hero be able to turn in an award-winning performance and escape from the theater, or will he be stuck on-screen forever?</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/15e73440-f583-4ded-82a7-1d07a4d91c15.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/135b6d63-f6aa-4c0b-99cf-be7bc1e4d08e.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ecd436e-ea21-42a4-96db-d6f0798b7c4f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4779b343-dae2-45b4-9db4-408cfe16a540.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Titus</Publisher>
</game>