<Game>
	<Name>Out of this World (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Story:Lester's Lab.The player takes on the role of  Lester Knight Chaykin, a young physicist who  accidentally manages to destroy his lab and gets himself somehow  teleported onto another world. After a quick exploration of the local area, he is quickly captured by the sentient inhabitants of the planet, a race of bulky, humanoid creatures. Lester then wakes up in a cage with another one of the creatures, looking over what appears to be a mining complex.He quickly escapes, eliminating his guard and freeing his companion who proceeds to help Lester leave the complex and get to the surface. It is immediately apparent that the alien race was using their own as slaves, and that they operated as a Roman-esque society, albeit with lasers, complete with a Colosseum and a harem. Lester is eventually caught and nearly killed by one of the creatures, but he manages to defeat his attacker and is saved by the very companion he freed at the start. Lester and his companion then ride an enormous bird-like creature off into the distance.Gameplay:The laser in use.Out of This World uses 2D  side-scrolling mechanics, similar to most platformers released at the time. As such, the player could move both left and right, run, jump, crouch, and at some points use a  laser gun. The gun allows the player to both create charged shots and shields. Because Lester can only survive one hit before dying, and in early parts of the game it is entirely possible for the gun to run out of ammo, precision and care are needed when attacking enemies. Although inefficient, the game includes a password system, which affords the player the ability to continue on from previous  checkpoint.There are many points where the player must solve complex  puzzles in order to proceed, often involving trial and error. Notable is the  lack of a HUD; there is no  score, no lives system, no map, no  ammunition count, no  inventory.The Game-worldAs there are no explanatory  cutscenes or dialogue, players must figure out for themselves what the nature of the place is, and its true location. There is a clue toward the end which suggests that the world where the player character was transported to may not be what it first appears, although that interpretation is left up to the player.From the outset, the region of the world where the game takes place seems to be arid and largely desolate. Animals and plants tend to be brutal and predatory, and the sentient life forms conduct gladiatorial games and what appears to be forced labor, as noted earlier. These traits may be evident of a Roman Empire level of culture in terms of art and architecture, although the architecture may be more comparable to medieval Muslim architecture in the  middle-east. Although their culture may be primitive by human standards, their technology is certainly not. They possess a greater understanding of energy and how to harness it, evident in  power nodes which are dotted around the city, but also in their weaponry, which can  stun on the lowest setting and is otherwise lethal. They also possess flying vehicles that supersede technologically anything humanity has built so far.Original ProductionRotoscoping models used by Eric Chahi.Animation of the principle characters was performed through a process called  rotoscoping, whereby real objects were used as models for animation work, lending a life-like and quirky feel to the movement that might seem flat and predictable if animated through simple physics models. Allegedly, Lester's appearance is based on  Eric Chahi. However, because Chahi found it disturbing to see himself in the game, he decided to change Lester to a Redhead.The game was originally, officially released for  PC (DOS),  Amiga,  Atari,  Macintosh,  3DO,  SNES,  Genesis and the Sega CD. The Atari and Amiga versions were developed first. They are relatively shorter compared to later versions, and have a higher  difficulty level due to more precise timing required of the player. The PC version was the first to introduce a whole new level in the middle to latter third of the game to help lengthen the game and strengthen the narrative.Further obstacles were added for the Genesis and SNES console ports, as  Interplay purportedly wanted players to get as much gameplay as possible for their dollar.  Nintendo also had demands about certain scenes which were considered to be inappropriate for minors (which amounted to a few pixels worth of deletions during a bathhouse scene; as well as changing reddish ichor, which might be interpreted as blood, to green).The Sega CD version of the game included a game set in the same world, dubbed  Out of this World 2: Heart of the Alien, which took place from the point of view of the aliens. Eric Chahi has stated, however, that this in-house Interplay project suffers in terms of animation quality and its value as a game, as he was not involved in the project.Eric Chahi has stated that the problem with some of the early enhanced versions was that the backgrounds were a lot easier to improve than the characters themselves. In order to enhance the characters, new rotoscoping or detailed, frame-by-frame enhancement of the animations would have to be done, while the backdrops could be repainted with relative ease. Doing the latter without the former, though, would result in the characters in the foreground looking flat. For the 3DO version, Chahi says, this is especially apparent.The enhancement of the animations themselves could probably not be done because processors of the time could not handle so many frames of animation being very detailed, although currently such restrictions are negligible.In addition to the listed versions, there were also unofficial ports to both the  GBA and GP32 systems.SequelThough fans have been hoping for a true sequel, Chahi has stated that he wishes for the game to have no continuation as he wants the ending of the original to remain ambiguous and fans could make their own conclusion to the franchise."I think the story is complete. It has a lot of mystery, so doing a sequel would be very tricky. It could break the magic it has."- Eric Chahi(Retro Gamer issue #96, 2011)Despite this, a sequel was made for the Sega CD in 1994 called  Heart of The Alien, which placed Buddy as the main protagonist. Chahi was not involved with the development and dismissed the "sequel" to be non-canon.AvailabilityThe original game is not easy to find, but a new, high resolution version is available as a demo, or a full version for 7 Euros (at the time of this writing) from the creator Eric Chahi on  his website. The new version has more detailed backgrounds, multiple graphics modes, more save points and Windows XP and Vista compatible.Telco Games also distributes a mobile phone version of the game.15th Anniversary EditionThe 15th Anniversary Edition is also available from GOG.com and comes with a selection of extra content, including:manual (17 pages)2 HD wallpapersdevelopment diarytechnical handbooksoundtrack"making of" video20th Anniversary EditionIn 2011, in commemoration of its 20th anniversary, Out of This World was made available for the iOS (iPhone and iPad) and later Android. The game also arrived on Steam for the first time in 2013. These versions were created by DotEmu and distributed by Bulky Pix.Included are:The ability to switch to the original and HD graphics at any timeNew intuitive touch controls3 difficulty modes - Normal (easier than original game), Difficult (equal to original game) and Very Hard (more difficult than original game)100% remastered sounds and FXGame Center support with 13 achievements5 languages support (English, French, Italian, German, Spanish)Cheat: SkippingYou hold the run button and hold the jump button at the same time, Lester will do this goofy little jump-run that looks like he's skipping like a kindergarden student. This is actually a little faster than just running, so this is helpful if you're stuck at the part when running from the beast in the first stage. But doing this, for some reason, makes you more likely to get hit by laser fire from the enemy.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Interplay Productions, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>Gm9lgIzjlK8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>296</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588548-out-of-this-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/out-of-this-world</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/out-of-this-world/3030-17483/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Another_World_(video_game)</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/wzg37qd.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/jDtPRm0.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/qNGbfx3.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/GopKPM3.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/zDfV1Qg.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/hwdczAN.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FwnWhqH.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/yZqFD5U.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/CuKUEIF.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/NWIz81U.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/PAaXIMz.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/K7qq9p1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/1FHGelj.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ufvKMHQ.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/hqtg3Fx.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/2XQ7r3P.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/Sd3Z8fv.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Dhnbma6.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/XYGJeSP.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/Wboe5tP.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>You'll think you're actually on a movie set when you star in the cinematic action/adventure Out Of This World. Out Of This World is like no other game on the Super NES. Using a completely new graphic system of cinematic zooms, pans, close-ups, and cuts, Out Of This World gets you involved in a breathtaking story of inter-dimensional travel.  You'll duck as lasers blast, boulders crash, and monsters roar. The complete musical score and realistic, digitized sound effects will make you feel like you're on a movie sound stage. Being a hero is hard work, and you'll experience it first-hand as you run, jump, dodge, and shoot your way across a hostile world of deadly earthquakes and alien monsters. So, grab your hat and whip, charge up your blasters, and get ready to star in your own movie that'll take you Out Of This World!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>Gm9lgIzjlK8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c07a0043-2466-4994-9a10-4b309b83c6c7.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ec239dc-0ed9-47ea-972f-1ff0d452c29d.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5cf4e486-be77-42bf-b256-ca16b782c729.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0174e70d-ada6-4f5f-b7ed-63996788b3f5.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/af64e8dc-47c6-4a56-8ec0-41f4ba5e2126.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a5d83c48-3cbb-4258-9fda-3173d536bb97.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c719e42d-df82-4167-85d3-a77fb839474d.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e2537fa4-c3da-4ebd-8e77-4fd8b2103a39.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/997ad82e-ac75-4d07-8c88-d735084d1169.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/16cbb3c1-8bcb-4813-9613-2fd7d77bdaab.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/747210a8-cb95-47d5-9b60-7f109ed49f68.jpg</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/285817d1-ce20-48bb-a386-1b5841fa082b.png</snapshot18>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Interplay</Publisher>
</game>