<Game>
	<Name>P.T.O. - Pacific Theater of Operations (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:PTO: Pacific Theater of Operations, or Teitoku no Ketsudan, is a very in-depth strategy game in which the player takes control of the US Allied forces or Japanese Axis forces during naval battles set across the Pacific Ocean. As well as directing the various ships in the player's fleet during battles, the player is also responsible for maintaining their fleet, their supply lines and their good relations with allies and potential allies.PTO: Pacific Theater of Operations was followed up with a sequel, PTO 2. Although the third game (Teitoku no Ketsudan III) did not receive a localization, the fourth game (PTO IV) was released in the US and Europe for the PS2.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>KOEI Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>YymnxfGp11g</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3239</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588551-pto-pacific-theater-of-operations</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/pto-pacific-theater-of-operations</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pto-pacific-theater-of-operations/3030-5174/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Lt6QIgH.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/6FsFkTM.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/odzyjLH.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/zsd4BUO.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ZcKW6m5.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ycRkiVK.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/icKRHkW.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/3cowgU6.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/sQEijkX.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/7pJeMwm.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/aNGIXRd.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/1Jf1PPf.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/MQZw3aC.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/i5hfoC9.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Relive the entire Pacific campaign of WWII. You have the incredible opportunity to command either the Allied or Japanese forces. Challenge history and change the outcome of the great sea and air battles of the day, such as Pearl Harbor, the Battle at Midway and Okinawa! Assemble warships into fleets and forge a comprehensive battle strategy with land forces. Launch air attacks, dispatch ambitious forces or fire warship artillery to fulfill military objectives. A huge arsenal of warships, planes and new developments such as rockets hold the key to victory. Experience the complexities and excitement of war operations on the pacific. Will victory be in your future? Go for it in P.T.O!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b03c697c-19bc-4c6e-99e9-27597166e0e9.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/35fc625e-0c60-4c5d-833f-272770fc29b2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8719c2e7-eccc-4789-9269-b0c4609926e1.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2792b490-62e2-4316-b51d-e28cdb8b69ec.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
</game>