<Game>
	<Name>Pac-Man 2 - The New Adventures (Germany)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pac-Man 2: The New Adventures is a puzzle/adventure game spinoff of the Pac-Man series. It takes elements from Pac-Land, the Pac-Man themed side-scrolling platformer that is thought to be one of the earliest examples of the genre, as well as elements from the official TV show such as Pac-Man's family.The game was released for both the Super Nintendo and Genesis in 1994. In Japan, the game is known as "Hello! Pac-Man", due to how the player has to communicate directions to Pac-Man to solve puzzles.Gameplay:The player is equipped with a sling shot and can shoot at points of interest to bring them to Pac-Man's attention. The player may also tell Pac-Man which way he should go. Pac-Man, however, has a mind of his own and will grow increasingly frustrated if the player leads him into harm's way too many times, and he might just completely ignore the player if he gets too angry. The game also contains super pellets which can be given to Pac-Man at any point to have him transform into Super Pac-Man. In fact, when the ghosts appear throughout random points in the game, Pac-Man is left in paralyzing fear. If the player has run out of super pallets before eliminating all the ghosts, Pac-Man faints.In the first stage of the game, Pac-Man is tasked with stopping by the farm and picking up milk for Baby Pac. The next section of the game leads Pac-Man to the mountains in search of a flower for Lucy. This section also contains a hand-gliding section in which the player guides Pac-Man in the proper direction. In the third section, Pac-Man must retrive Pac Jr.'s stolen guitar which leads Pac-Man to the city and eventually to a mine cart section that controls much like the hand gliding section. The final stage begins with a broadcast of the ghosts stealing all the ABC gum in the city followed by a message from the Ghost Witch of Netor who goes onto warn Pac-Man of her near completed Gum Monster. Pac-Man must search for the abandoned factory which houses the Gum-Monster and turn into Super Pac-Man to defeat it and all the ghosts. Upon defeating the Gum Monster Pac-Man is congratulated by his friends, family, and the citizens town, but then scolded for not being able to save their ABC gum.Hidden Arcade ClassicsPac-Man 2: The New Adventures also contains two in game video arcades where a NES based version of the original Pac-Man can be played. The player can also participate and complete in an optional side-quest in search of three cartridge pieces which together unlock either Ms. Pac-Man in the SNES version, or Pac-Jr in the Mega Drive/Genesis version.		</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Hometek Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>-kKtpRjkGuU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3234</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588556-pac-man-2-the-new-adventures</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/pac-man-2-the-new-adventures</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pac-man-2-the-new-adventures/3030-12294/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/23VqJPy.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/hcp0nGG.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ZncDF9E.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/IP1xMpg.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/vGi10qA.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FLxiT9U.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Y9IcdSQ.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/4S6GjcD.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/OsjByJN.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/nNbGUrp.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/We1ZdJ5.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/tXh747H.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/1PidTsp.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/TGKLviN.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7ssPWax.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Erit3B2.png</clearlogo1>
</game>