<Game>
	<Name>Pac-In-Time (Europe) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pac-in-Time is a platformer game for the Super Nintendo, Game Boy and PC featuring Namco's spherical ghost-eating hero. It is a re-branded version of 1993's  Fury of the Furries which didn't feature Pac-Man, but four different furry, ball-like creatures, called Tinies. The developer of Fury of the Furries, French company Atreid Concept (later Kalisto Entertainment), was also the developer of Pac-in-Time.Frustrated at Pac-Man's repeated victories over her spectral minions, the Ghost Witch warps Pac-Man through time to prevent him from interfering with her plans. Pac-Man has to make his way back through a series of worlds to stop her from taking over.Gameplay:Pac-Man can only complete a stage after collecting all the pellets on the level. To reach them, he has to find some or all of the power-ups: each increases his ability to move around the level or unlocks more of it to explore. These include:Rope: The rope lets Pac-Man swing across any ceiling, but Pac-Man has to be within a certain range for the rope to attach. It cannot be used horizontally: only vertically.Fireball: Pac's best weapon against the non-ghost enemies. Without it, Pac-Man won't be able to get around enemies without getting hurt, and he can only take so many hits before losing a life.Hammer: The hammer allows Pac-Man to break through certain barriers and open chests.Bubble: The bubble allows Pac-Man to swim through underwater sections, collecting whatever is under the surface. Without it, Pac-Man simply bobs on top of any body of water.In addition, Pac-Man also has to find a way to eliminate ghosts on the stage, as they will continue to hound him until he has been defeated. Ghosts can be eaten whenever Pac-Man finds a Power Pellet, but these are rare and Pac-Man must chase down the now fleeing ghosts before its effects wear off.					</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Hometek Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>WSvCiL9oJJg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5773</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588554-pac-in-time</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/pac-in-time</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pac-in-time/3030-11100/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Np00hAg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/GJvwCP9.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/eYtNV4H.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/zQ5F2cY.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ZulFrIg.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FArmYxT.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/JtHKegx.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Fkt5EqZ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IQx2T1I.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/o0Y6xC6.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Q6DFaJV.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Dl4py3M.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/kIp8Oej.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/rO8ukue.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/peAFd0t.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/YjkMfz6.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The evil Ghost Witch has cast a vicious spell on Pac-Man and thrown him back in time to when he was a Pac-Boy. Only you can save him now. Down some Pac-Pellets and get ready to battle your way through a totally supersonic side-scrolling adventure. Journey through snowy mountains and forests, collect fireballs and bubbles, crunch Pac-Bats and ghosts, swim like a fish and swing like a monkey... and ultimately get Pac-Man back to the real world!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/489a89aa-4714-451d-b0c5-8448edd88585.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/37b7a18d-59ee-4666-8ed3-449e0e438ae5.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/81b3cd79-356c-4b58-90ba-57f0ef87bf63.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e084d61b-a9a9-448e-a5d3-a99c46172c39.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>