<Game>
	<Name>Pachinko Maruhi Hisshouhou (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pachinko Maruhi Hisshouhou ("Pachinko Top Secret Winning Strategy") is a 1994 pachinko game from Jorudan and Vap for the Super Famicom. It features four practice pachinko tables as well as plenty of tips to help the player maximize their pachinko wins. There is a single-player with its own story, but the player can choose to go straight to the tables and practice them. As well as virtual representations of real pachinko tables, the game also includes a virtual representation of a pachinko tips magazine that the player can peruse.Like all pachinko games it was never localized or released outside of Japan.	</plot>
	<releasedate>18/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Card</genre>
	<Developer>Jorudan</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571172-pachinko-hi-hisshouhou</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pachinko-maruhi-hisshouhou/3030-30440/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/PQXp147.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/usKbQU9.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/YzfsYK7.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8A9kexq.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/MGjiQcH.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Notes>Pachinko Maruhi Hisshouhou ("Pachinko Top Secret Winning Strategy") is a 1994 pachinko game from Jorudan and Vap for the Super Famicom. It features four practice pachinko tables as well as plenty of tips to help the player maximize their pachinko wins. There is a single-player with its own story, but the player can choose to go straight to the tables and practice them. As well as virtual representations of real pachinko tables, the game also includes a virtual representation of a pachinko tips magazine that the player can peruse. Like all pachinko games it was never localized or released outside of Japan.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f48a96d7-e132-419b-8dbb-342bd012107b.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b7106b39-9c8b-4338-bc60-524877a4ec7c.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7c484257-ddf5-4b6b-a791-d10e3b40a5d4.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/994107ae-45a3-4362-9cb3-825d2fa7e3a1.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/21b15a45-8fc8-44b6-93e1-da04c54c0de4.png</snapshot8>
	<Publisher>Vap Inc.</Publisher>
</game>