<Game>
	<Name>Pachi-Slot Land - Pachipachi Coin no Densetsu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pachi-Slot Land: Pachi Pachi Coin no Densetsu is a pachi-slot game for the Super Famicom developed by ISC (their final game) and published by Carrozzeria (their first game). The player moves around pachi-slots parlors via a first-person dungeon crawling type of perspective, and each of the pachi-slot machines has a distinctive theme. The player character is attempting to raise money for either a new bike or a video game console (the Super Nintendo).The title is a pun: "pachi pachi" is Japanese onomatopoeia for popping (like popcorn), crackling or clapping.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/2/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Card</genre>
	<Developer>I.S.C.</Developer>
	<VideoURL>cslLXYL4M9s</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571039-pachi-slot-land</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pachi-slot-land-pachi-pachi-coin-no-densetsu/3030-30433/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/GO6yRIN.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Q2lgKZU.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Y216F9q.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ohC3f1z.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ssvJqmp.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Notes>Pachi-Slot Land: Pachi Pachi Coin no Densetsu is a pachi-slot game for the Super Famicom developed by ISC (their final game) and published by Carrozzeria (their first game). The player moves around pachi-slots parlors via a first-person dungeon crawling type of perspective, and each of the pachi-slot machines has a distinctive theme. The player character is attempting to raise money for either a new bike or a video game console (the Super Nintendo). The title is a pun: "pachi pachi" is Japanese onomatopoeia for popping (like popcorn), crackling or clapping.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/06087247-2429-48d0-80de-a8aaa82f660e.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e2122cf0-22b5-43b8-993b-95d20cad8051.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4f77fb8b-a4ca-48d0-8b09-4c84a88ab6b2.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/96ba6034-4da9-4f23-bb30-3ffe82b6438b.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/732c639f-e300-48aa-86bf-ecc29ee345df.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/52e4edf3-003d-4b2a-800d-a59a2af42d76.png</snapshot9>
	<Publisher>Carrozzeria</Publisher>
</game>