<Game>
	<Name>Panel de Pon (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Peace in the world of Popples is being threatened by the devil king Thanatos, who has cast a spell over the world. Lip, the Fairy of Flowers, escaped the grasp of this spell, and must free her friends, the other fairies, and defeat the evil king to restore peace to the land.Panel de Pon is a fact-paced action puzzler that belies its cute exterior with extremely fast-paced matches. A stack of blocks continually rises from the bottom of the screen, and the player controls a cursor which can swap any two blocks horizontally. Make a row or column of three or more and they'll clear, potentially creating combos from new blocks falling to take their place. Combos will send large garbage blocks to your opponent, which must be eliminated by clearing a piece that is touching it, turning it into normal blocks.The game offers a story mode against the computer, as well as a 2-player versus mode, an endless mode, a timed mode where a certain number of blocks must be cleared, and a puzzle mode where a set arrangement of blocks must be cleared in a specific number of moves. A reworked version of the game, which changes all the characters to ones from Super Mario World 2: Yoshi's Island, was released internationally as Tetris Attack.Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsGo to 'vs' in the menu selection, then go to the 'password' menu. Input one of these codes:Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsCheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsCheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsCheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsGo to the 1P menu, then 'stage clear' and then to the password section. Enter one of the following to go to the corresponding level:Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsAfter the title screen select 1 player game, then the fourth selection, then the second and enter the following chain.Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsAfter the title screen select 1 player game, then the fourth selection, then the second and enter the following chain.Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsAfter the title screen select 1 player game, then the third selection, then the second and enter the following chain.Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsEnter these at the 1P vs. password screen. When it says ERROR! keep pressing the B button to backup to the menu that says new game and password and select new game. Choose a difficulty level and start the game. Now when you loose it will say you have 43 or 90 continues.Cheat: Guaranteed Victory vs CPUIf you have a controller with a "turbo" option for buttons A or B, you can use the following exploit against the CPU so that you [I]always[/I] win! Cheat: Guaranteed Victory vs CPUFirst, when you turn on the game and Yoshi appears in front of a blue screen and says "Nintendo," press B, A, L, L. You should hear a confirmation code when you input the cheat correctly. This will remove the "freeze" that occurs when you or your opponent makes a combo or a chain. In other words, the blocks never stop rising. After entering the cheat, activate turbo for either A or B. Once you are competing against your CPU opponent in splitscreen, place your cursor over any two blocks or one block and an empty panel, and hold down turbo. The panels will switch back and forth so quickly that your blocks will not rise, nor will garbage blocks fall on you! Eventually, the speed of the rising blocks will surpass the CPU's ability to get rid of them and you will win! Cheat: Guaranteed Victory vs CPUAlthough it takes a while in later stages, you can use this exploit to beat every difficulty in VS Mode.Cheat: Guaranteed Victory vs CPUIn any of the sessions hold down the "R" button.  You can now control the cursor and try out the chains, combos, and skill chains on your own.Cheat: Guaranteed Victory vs CPUIn Time Trial, you get progressively more and more points for larger chains until the 13x chain. However, if you keep a chain going any longer than the 13th link (x?), you don't get any chain-link bonus points. For this reason, you should never let a chain go past the 13th link in time trial.Cheat: Secret CharacterGo to the Player vs. Player character select screen, then hold L + R on both controllers for a few seconds. If you did it right, the question marks (?) at the bottom of the screen will be replaced by bosses.Cheat: All EndingsGood Ending: Beat the game using no continues.Cheat: All EndingsBad Ending: Beat the game with at least one continue.Cheat: All EndingsAfter you've beaten the game on Medium difficulty or higher and the credits are rolling, hold SELECT and you can use the Control Pad to move Yoshi around in the background.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/10/1995</releasedate>
	<Developer>Nintendo Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>W-kXJa_5R4Y</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>23944</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588787-tetris-attack</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/panel-de-pon</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tetris-attack/3030-13130/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/HvpR9Fl.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/NlnCjKS.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/2KG4GLW.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/y9DL8TT.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/sUWxZKu.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zMpiwtr.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/lZCO5xZ.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/LHO5CRv.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/dRLPpt4.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/9PNTreo.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/IpPyfbj.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/188oxkK.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JSsmeeY.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/wtDqKxj.png</banner1>
</game>