<Game>
	<Name>Paperboy 2 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Paperboy 2 is the follow up to Atari's minor Arcade hit Paperboy and features identical gameplay. The goal is to deliver papers to all the houses specified by the player's route, while occasionally scoring bonuses by "shooting" excess papers at various targets along the way. The player must also avoid all the obstacles along the street, which range from traffic to dogs to RC cars to the Grim Reaper. The game was developed specifically for early 1990s computers and consoles; unlike the first, it never began life as an Arcade game.Unlike the original Paperboy, Paperboy 2 also features a girl who delivers papers. The player must also deliver papers to houses on either side of the street, whereas in the first the player simply had the one side to consider. Achieving certain objectives during the run, like foiling a criminal mid-robbery, will put the Paperboy on the front page of the newspaper that appears at the end of the stage.						</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Mindscape, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>NmgYktKxNfU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2916</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588559-paperboy-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/paperboy-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/paperboy-2/3030-17563/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/N5BmUOY.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/MCeEVhY.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/yKME1RG.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/bmYv91O.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xvE2hpH.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/AF1nLTN.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/h3XWqHz.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/TjLIRoy.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/bCd2WRv.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/I4h5Opj.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/0mGgjk9.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/4AbWsN5.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/WMHN462.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/BCGQiNz.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/tZTtN2r.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/IvKiPp8.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Look out! He's back, with an all new route. No window is safe. No fence is too high. The paperboy is determined to deliver the paper to his subscribers...any way he can. Tossing papers left and right, riding in 3 directions, jumping anything that'll give air...This free-wheeling carrier visits more neighborhoods and houses, faces more targets and obstacles, in more vivid colors than ever before. Plus, rad stuntriding and BMX tracks in bonus rounds. Choose to ride as either Paperboy or Papergirl, too!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/90e4e9b5-c177-4e70-a5e5-d8425c139f28.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c4df2c99-3e70-4e5e-a1ef-ab539aef5ea0.png</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f8c0c7a6-c3c8-4ad0-a581-994b90bb6014.jpg</boxart7>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0a86c21e-b885-4a2d-9bc0-e848631ab1b6.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c57947b3-fc56-4d5b-b953-7361829220f7.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7f1e6627-67e7-4fc6-a797-765df91f7860.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Mindscape</Publisher>
</game>