<Game>
	<Name>Parodius (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Following the popularity of their own Gradius franchise, Konami took the basic concepts from those games, but added a healthy dose of weird to the characters, environments, and enemies. Parodius is a side-scrolling shooter at its heart. Players use their ships to blast wave after wave of enemies, collecting powerups that range from shields to missles to, in the case of Parodius, heat-seaking octopi. A lot of characters in the game come from various Konami franchises, as well as popular characters in Japanese culture and history. It is a very deliberate send-up of Gradius, with menu options including "One Player", "Two Player" and "Lollipop", but is a very accomplished version of the series at its heart which, despite the candy-coated visuals, zany characters and far out enemies, is a great game in its own right.Characters:While the only playable character in the Gradius series is the Vic Viper fighter, Parodius' selectable characters offer a bit more variety.TwinbeeTwinbeeA small blue plane with two big fists on the front, Twinbee is the eponymous main character in its own series of games, the first of which was ported to the US and renamed as Stinger. In its games, Twinbee's powerups were granted by shooting bells that appear on the screen. The bells also appear in Parodius, supplying the player with a limited set of power-ups that work independently from the standard weapon powerups gained from blowing up enemy ships. Twinbee's powerups include rocket fists, which fly across the screen and slowly return to the plane, a forwards and backwards shot, a three-way shot, shadowed out copies of twinbee that fire and cannot be damaged, and a radial shield that offers a wide area of protection.Vic ViperVic ViperThe Vic Viper is just about the only normal thing about Parodius. Its powerups match those found in Gradius. Included are missles that travel along the ground and ceiling, a double-shot, a laser beam, small glowing options which absorb bullets and fire when the Vic Viper fires, and a shield which blocks shots in front.TakosukeTakosukeTakosuke is a space-faring, headband-wearing octopus. He was created specifically for this game, and in a weird way fits into the game better because of it. His powerups include missles that fire straight up and down, a forwards and backwards shot, a wide-area ripple laser, little octopi that follow Takosuke around and fire when he does, and a jellyfish-shaped shield.PentarouPentarouPentarou is a penguin, a penguin that travels through space and shoots out of his mouth and other places. His upgrades are missles that travel along the ground and ceiling, a double-shot, an exploding shot, small penguins that travel close to Pentarou and shoot when he does, and a bubble shield.Cheat: Option CheatsIn the options screen, press the following buttons:Cheat: Debug menuHighlight Octopus on the character selection screen, and hold Up+L+X for around 30 seconds. A menu will then be displayed allowing you to select your starting stage, scene, and ''Mutek'' (set it to 01 for a fully powered up, invincible ship)</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>Flf3lQSuB5E</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2200</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588560-parodius-da</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/parodius</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/parodius/3030-810/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/et2vSHi.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/JfkWMie.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Fz1gIbs.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/wbmwkgU.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/nqgilmO.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wxM22KE.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/9gM3WS3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RLWCJD5.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/v1qv7L6.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/mPek3Jp.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/RVMxcaO.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/15ZjlMd.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Mo52U5g.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vtmC5Su.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7bhDXr7.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/UjaUNQj.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>What A Wonderful World! The year is 1993, and the changes in world history have been astonishing, with only seven years left before the beginning of the 21st century. Earth's people have lost everything, their hopes, their dreams, their works and their money. Revolutionary things are about to happen: Young boys hide amongst the fantasy world of their computers, ignoring the rest of families. There is only Sushi or Curry to eat, the computerized refrigerator is often on strike and rumour has it that the Great Octopus is soon to arrive on Earth. This can only mean trouble. In a world, war!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a41df698-c5c0-4233-976c-795573fbd0a8.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67f01c05-aae9-4473-b2c1-87d7a2271921.png</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1058b534-9615-4b1d-a63d-cbf566f57290.png</boxart7>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/679aa916-7b0e-40f0-a5ec-0dc8d68fce0f.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/71f2ad35-ed34-4234-b398-b85c2ca2069c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9f43e469-f7af-423d-8fda-268c9e19192d.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>