<Game>
	<Name>Peace Keepers, The (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Released in Japan as Rushing Beat Shura (&#12521;&#12483;&#12471;&#12531;&#12464;&#12539;&#12499;&#12540;&#12488; &#20462;&#32645;), The Peace Keepers is the third title in the Rushing Beat series of brawlers, following Rival Turf! and Brawl Brothers. Like its previous US localizations, the story is rewritten and unrelated from those of the previous games. It was released in Japan on the 17th of December 1993 and later in the US in March 1994.Gameplay:The game plays a lot like contemporary brawlers such as Final Fight. The player can move horizontally and vertically along a two-dimensional field where they have to fight off waves of enemies with kicks, punches, throws and life bar consuming special attacks. The game features several branching paths with their own stages, cut scenes and boss fights as well as multiple endings. The game features six playable characters and allows for co-op play with up to four players using the SNES multitap accessory. A two player versus mode is also available in the game, allowing players to fight each other with the game's selectable characters.Story:After the damage caused by the economic wars of 2011 left the world in turmoil, the Deutchland Moldavia Corporation led by a man named Trip Iago rose to power and acquired most of the world's land and resources. By 2015, they have nearly conquered the entire world. With their power unchecked, the DM corporation sets out to fuse their bio-genetic and nanotechnology research to create a super being to further the vision of their corrupt leader. It's now up to four people affected by the ill deeds of the DM Corporation and its genetic experiments to seek revenge on the corporation for its crimes against humanity.								Cheat: Secret CharacterIf you go up to the door at the end of the first stage without going in, then return to the beginning, you will find a secret character: Douglas Bild / Oozie Nelson from an earlier Jaleco title, "Rushing Beat" (the other character, Rick Norton / Jack Flack, is playable in this game). Douglas will apologize for not being able to help fight the Deutchland Moldavia (DM) corporation.Cheat: Secret CharacterIf you go up to the door at the end of the Roy D Tutto Hospital stage without going in, then return to the manhole you passed in the street, you will find it is open. It is a shorcut to the Stalag 17 stageCheat: Secret CharacterIf you play as Prokop up to the Ozymandias stage, then play as any other character on that stage, Prokop will be killed when you go down the flight of stairs.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>Vas8iJv5NZo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2591</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588561-the-peace-keepers</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/peace-keepers</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-peace-keepers/3030-7950/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/bMiMPxe.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/M2j90qQ.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/4lkN10P.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/pgH0P8K.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/jzpzXmm.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/DMX49Yu.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/XTq9nkP.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/edxHT5J.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/hEqEZHS.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/LmF0Oqy.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/3sThnxS.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/588rcN6.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/oRedhOW.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/TTEzifu.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/z3rYOWm.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/GUc5Y2V.png</clearlogo1>
</game>