<Game>
	<Name>Phalanx (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Phalanx is a side-scrolling shoot 'em up from Kemco. Its full title, as shown in the title screen of every version, is Phalanx: The Enforce Fighter A-144. A fairly standard example of the genre, the game is best known for its unusual North American SNES box art which depicts an elderly banjo player with the spaceship far in the background.The game was originally released on the Japanese home computer the Sharp X68000 in 1991, this version was developed by Zoom Inc. It was followed by the SNES version the following year, which was released in the US, Japan and Europe. The 2001 GBA version was also released in those three territories. A WiiWare remake was added to the digital store in 2009 in Japan.Gameplay:The first stage in the game. The background is comprised of seven layers of parallax scrolling.Phalanx is a side-scrolling space shooter. The ship which the player controls has the ability to switch between three different movement speeds, allowing for greater dexterity when avoiding enemy threats. Also unlike most space-shooters, the player's ship can take up to three hit points worth of damage, and an item existed which would restore this health. There are three different difficulty levels available at the start, a fourth can be accessed by entering a cheat code.The player's ship has three slots for weapons, which can be switched between at will. When the player grabs a fourth weapon, the one which they are currently equipped with will be switched out with it. Dropping a weapon will create a "smart bomb" effect which differs depending on the weapon which was dropped.Box ArtThe Game Boy Advance version features more representative cover art.The gameplay of this title has been significantly overshadowed by its SNES box art, which, instead of depicting a space ship fighting, features an old man playing a banjo with a spaceship zooming past in the background. The words "The Hyper-Speed Shoot-Out In Space" are displayed to the right of the man.The publisher has stated that the decision was made due to wanting to do something different.The box art for other platforms omitted the banjo-playing man and focused on the player's spaceship.Cheat: Extra Lives and ContinuesAt the Execute Mission, press the R buttons, then enter "System Configuration." Press L and R Simultaneously on controller 2 and will able to change the number of credits and live that you have in reserve when start the game.Cheat: Extra Lives and ContinuesAt the Execute Mission, press the R button, then enter "System Configuration." Hold R and press B on controller 1 and enter the System Configuration option, then simultaneously press the L and R buttons on controller 2. Now press A+B+X+Y simultaneously on controller 2 and stage select will appear.Cheat: Extra Lives and ContinuesAfter unlocking the 3 Special Environments (Lives, Continues, and Stage Select), Press Start and Select on Controller 2. This allows you to have more lives (up to 30), more continues (up to 99), and select any stage (instead of just the first 5).Cheat: Secret AreaOn Level 2 the Underwater Area, when you see a red box on either the top or bottow screen, enter it and you will go into a secret area. Their are two secret Areas in the Underwater Area. The first one's on the top. And the second one's on the bottom. 1st- When you have to move and either destroy or dodge the poles that come at you, at the last one, where it stays and you have to be careful not to get hurt because it's a thick area and you have to move slowly, go up to the top and quickly into the  red box  . 2nd- After you go pass the revolving circle of bones that don't connect together, go through it. To know which one it is, its the one where inside the circle of bones have a P power up there. After that, look towards the bottom of the screen and look out for it.Cheat: Secret AreaIn the last stage- Final Mission, there are 2 secret areas in this place. The secret place looks like a yellow circle with some gadgets around it. 1st- When you have to slowly go through a series of bars, make sure you just don't take damage or if you do, just quickly cross it to the top to the  Yellow circle . 2nd- Can't excactly remember but its after the sub-boss you have to fight. The sub-boss is thi wierd looking ship where it spits a gravity whole in nowhere between the middle of the screen and then his two projectile users try to slam into you. I just know this one's on the bottom and its right before you go to these wierd monsters where they look like cubes and some digusting cube worms that drip acid water, which damages you so just dodge it.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Kotobuki System Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>Na59pQz7-wQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3235</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588567-phalanx</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/phalanx</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/phalanx/3030-18519/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/1licOeB.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ErlE4ml.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/GpKOJ6g.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/Bfnq19H.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/bFaFwBa.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/WiOQT1b.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/xhpz7DC.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/auAgSyN.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/nfKbFYt.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/EkEK6XG.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/0tT7zuu.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/5gesqAf.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/gUwZ1et.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/jkTRtV8.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/sTNvL6p.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/iOP4WKz.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/JChLkw4.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/U74YZYP.png</clearlogo1>
</game>