<Game>
	<Name>Picross NP Vol. 1 (Japan) (NP)</Name>
	<plot>Picross NP Vol. 1 is a Miscellaneous game, developed by Jupiter Multimedia and published by Nintendo,which was released in Japan in 1999.Cheat: Access the Extra LevelTo open up the extremely difficult Extra Level, complete all the puzzles in all the other levels in the game (this includes the Beginner, Regular, Professional, Character, and Special levels).</plot>
	<releasedate>1/4/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Puzzle, Logic</genre>
	<Developer>Jupiter Multimedia</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>jWHLUth5FyU</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/577449-picross-np-vol-1</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/picross-np-vol1</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/hVKPNEV.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/86M3lQI.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ZZSaXoE.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/NyVdUCP.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/qxEUdz3.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/g13x5UP.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VirHPDn.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/qMFotef.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/bPFsO7X.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/PIiAVTA.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/16FNluq.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/TIYvQA6.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Fgl7USx.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/pLdc4BM.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Following the success of Mario no Super Picross on the Super Famicom, Nintendo decided to reuse the basic engine from that game to develop a series of Nintendo Power branded Picross titles for distribution over their Satellaview system in Japan. There were a total of eight volumes in the series released on a bi-monthly basis from April 1999 to June 2000. Each volume includes a substantial number of puzzles of varying sizes and difficulty. A large number of these puzzles would later be rereleased as downloadable content for Picross DS. The puzzle solving gameplay of the titles is nearly identical to that of their direct predecessor Mario no Super Picross just with minor changes in the presentation. Notably, Mario and Wario are no longer featured as guides through the game modes. Also, the stone chiseling archeologist motif that was present in the previous titles has been dropped in favor of a simple pen-on-paper style.</Notes>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c5a3158d-9a82-48c3-8d2f-de427d140f03.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7f14df0a-e7c8-4ba0-b751-d45e8ad9d517.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9e58888a-5da8-4bfa-80e8-4b2c7616d2dd.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>