<Game>
	<Name>Pinball Fantasies (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pinball Fantasies is a pinball game with four different themed tables. Sequel to the game Pinball Dreams and the predecessor of Pinball Illusions. It was created by Digital Illustions CE in 1992 for the Commodore Amiga, and was eventually ported to many other home computers and consoles. It also appeared in a number of pinball-related compilations and was later adapted for mobile phones and iOS by Cowboy Rodeo.The four featured tables include:Billion Dollar Gameshow: A board that is based around showy gameshows where the player must earn prizes by taking the ramps in specific orders.Party Land: An amusement park themed board. Filling up the words CRAZY or PARTY allows the player to enter a high score event.Speed Devils: This board is based on high-speed car racing. The player is in a race and must overtake other cars with the pinball.Stones 'N Bones: A haunted house-themed board featuring various modes to progress through.		</plot>
	<releasedate>20/2/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>GameTek, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>0.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>mvVcaBgCI3U</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5780</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588572-pinball-fantasies</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/pinball-fantasies</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pinball-fantasies/3030-12347/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/yu5z283.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/HoOFapf.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/s03S2l1.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/gNmKKIh.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/24RrRKw.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/dxfFEzX.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/mmdeFFv.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4AVptlh.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/odOtFSM.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/zFj7gkB.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/X5LcMSK.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/EfOl3hc.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1Gzp2Bh.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/DPltsD3.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>After the success of Pinball Dreams on several systems, a sequel featuring four new tables was created. The gameplay is much the same as the first game, with realistic physics, multi-player options and a high score table to aim for. The tables are Partyland, Speed Devils, Billion Dollar Gameshow and Stones 'n' Bones, taking in a funfair, racing cars, a tacky game-show, and a graveyard. Each one has a range of ramps, combos, light sequences and targets to shoot, as well as general themes which are less influenced by real tables than those in Pinball Dreams.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d7062474-0b70-48dc-9cc8-6b8e00a48c63.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5a1efa61-11f8-4973-b64d-2f33bbdc01b6.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>GameTek</Publisher>
</game>