<Game>
	<Name>Pocky & Rocky 2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pocky &amp; Rocky 2 is a top-down shoot 'em up from Natsume and part of their Kiki Kaikai series of shmups with a cartoonish youkai twist. In Japan the game is known as Kiki Kaikai: Tsukiyozoushi (roughly, "Mysterious Ghost World: Tome of Moonlit Night"). Like the original Pocky &amp; Rocky (a.k.a. Kiki Kaikai: Nazo no Kuro Mantle), Pocky &amp; Rocky 2 was released in Japan, the US and Europe. Natsume published the game in the US and Japan, and the European release was handled by Ocean Software.The game's plot revolves around a kidnapped princess, abducted by demons led by a character named Impy. Pocky (Sayo in the Japanese version) can now be joined with various partners beyond just Rocky (Manuke). These include Bomber Bob (Takuan) and Little Ninja (Shinobi) from the offset, with the additional characters Tengy, Scarecrow, Digger and Ottobot unlocked as the game progresses. All partner characters can temporarily combine with Pocky when she casts her magic, each providing a different benefit.Cheat: Level PasswordsIf you're unfamiliar with Japanese characters, consult a hiragana chart while entering a password. Enter any of the following passwords after selecting the middle option (password) on the main menu:Cheat: Level PasswordsGo to password screen (middle option on start screen)Enter password in JapaneseOnly works on Japanese version</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Natsume, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>l9FTLQCypjI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>11002</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588580-pocky-and-rocky-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/pocky-rocky-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pocky-rocky-2/3030-13678/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/aPaVooc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/JtNzKoY.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/jG2KonX.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/tK00t5C.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ioDM4E0.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Vb61fSc.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/j25b9HN.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/be3vszI.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/gGzGipN.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/44XfKT7.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/SWAeb6p.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/YG1k2sI.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/IjRgAJw.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/sKjslJl.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/14f6KZl.png</clearlogo1>
</game>