<Game>
	<Name>Pocky & Rocky 2 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pocky &amp; Rocky 2 is a top-down shoot 'em up from Natsume and part of their Kiki Kaikai series of shmups with a cartoonish youkai twist. In Japan the game is known as Kiki Kaikai: Tsukiyozoushi (roughly, "Mysterious Ghost World: Tome of Moonlit Night"). Like the original Pocky &amp; Rocky (a.k.a. Kiki Kaikai: Nazo no Kuro Mantle), Pocky &amp; Rocky 2 was released in Japan, the US and Europe. Natsume published the game in the US and Japan, and the European release was handled by Ocean Software.The game's plot revolves around a kidnapped princess, abducted by demons led by a character named Impy. Pocky (Sayo in the Japanese version) can now be joined with various partners beyond just Rocky (Manuke). These include Bomber Bob (Takuan) and Little Ninja (Shinobi) from the offset, with the additional characters Tengy, Scarecrow, Digger and Ottobot unlocked as the game progresses. All partner characters can temporarily combine with Pocky when she casts her magic, each providing a different benefit.Cheat: Level PasswordsIf you're unfamiliar with Japanese characters, consult a hiragana chart while entering a password. Enter any of the following passwords after selecting the middle option (password) on the main menu:Cheat: Level PasswordsGo to password screen (middle option on start screen)Enter password in JapaneseOnly works on Japanese version</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Natsume, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>l9FTLQCypjI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>11002</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588580-pocky-and-rocky-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/pocky-rocky-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pocky-rocky-2/3030-13678/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/tfd4uJy.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/SKEHYGz.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/jG2KonX.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/tK00t5C.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ioDM4E0.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Vb61fSc.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/j25b9HN.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/be3vszI.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/gGzGipN.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/44XfKT7.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/SWAeb6p.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/YG1k2sI.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/IjRgAJw.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/sKjslJl.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/14f6KZl.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Princess Luna was visiting from the moon for the joyous harvest day celebration. All the villagers were gathered around the festival square, eating, dancing and having a wonderful time. Meanwhile, far away on the Demon Island, Dynagon was plotting his revenge. After the beautiful Proncess Luna refused to marry him, Dynagon went into a frenzy. Dynagon then ordered Impy, his most faithful servant, to go kidnap the princess from the harvest festival, in order to force her to get married to him. "Help! Help!" cried the Princess, but it was too late. In a flash, She disappeared. Pocky stood in amazement as she watched the Princess vanish. As Pocky and her partner, you are about to embark on a fantastic and dangerous adventure to rescue the Princess. You will need to use your wits and bravery to reach the end of your journey. Are you up to the challenge? - Seven different partners to choose from. - Outstanding graphics and music. - Plenty of unique and playful moves. - Action/Adventure game for the entire family.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5147f2be-0fed-4d23-bf41-32e8c39f1126.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea40c9c5-74d8-41ff-8167-2b41ad6f7775.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7550949-26d4-4ed8-af43-2828e18b672f.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b712028f-9125-4f65-9e8c-b87cbc26fe84.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/83cebc88-e121-4c70-88dc-f28238ae6d54.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8239a4f5-72eb-4e23-a205-1597074ac1d2.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d3bcc1c6-75bd-4ec3-a0d3-6b3f2ebfdd03.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Natsume</Publisher>
</game>