<Game>
	<Name>Pop'n TwinBee - Rainbow Bell Adventures (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pop'n TwinBee Rainbow Bell Adventures is an action platformer spin-off to Konami's TwinBee vertical shooter series. In the game the player controls one of three anthropomorphic ships from the shoot 'em up series, including Twinbee, Gwinbee and Winbee. TwinBee: Rainbow Bell Adventure was originally published in Japan for the Super Famicom on January 7, 1994 and was released in the Europe later that year. However the European version removed all of the game's dialogue, the secret endings, and the battery save function among other features. An English fan translation patch for Rainbow Bell Adventures was created by Aeon Genesis on November 14, 2013 which retained all of the game's content.Story:The eponymous Rainbow Bell is what keeps peace in the galaxy. However, Dr. Warmon and his army of Zakobee troopers have invaded the kingdom and stolen the Rainbow Bell for his own nefarious purposes. As a result, the Princess of the bell's protectors, Melora, starts to mysteriously vanish. It's up to Twinbee, Winbee and Gwinbee and their human pilots to stop Dr. Warmon, recover the Rainbow Bell and save Princess Melora.Gameplay:The player must pass through several stages to their end to continue. Along the way, they can explore the stage for cat bell collectibles, the number of which is provided at the bottom of the screen.The player is limited to a punch, but can find weapons by collecting power-ups. Both the attack and jump buttons can be held down to charge them up: A charged-up punch will destroy thin wall tiles and a charged-up jump allows the player to fly a small distance.Power-UpsThe trio can also find the colored bell power-ups from the prior shoot 'em up games, each of which provides a different upgrade. Getting hit will lose a number of power-ups currently held, but because they fly off the player they can be recovered if the player's fast enough (like Sonic's rings).Gold: Gold unlocks the character's special melee weapon, different for each character. These replace the standard rocket punch, and are usually have longer reach or are more powerful. Twinbee's is a hammer, Winbee's is a lasso and Gwinbee's is a rattle.Blue: Blue unlocks a ranged weapon any -bee can use with the ranged attack button.White: White greatly enhances the jumping height of the player who grabs it.Purple: Purple generates a shield around the player that will block the first hit they receive, and then vanish.Green: Green generates an option that follows the player.Pink: Pink makes the player temporarily invincible.Cheat: Cheat CodesPause the game, press A 5 times, B 5 times, X 5 times, Y 5 times, L 5 times, R 5 times and unpause. Now, hold Start to pause the game and while holding, press the directional keys to move anywhere on the stage map. If you wish, press R to remove the map from the screen.Cheat: Game Endings (Japanese Version)After the credits, depending on how many Fairies, Doors and Goals you collected you'll get a percentage score. The percentage score dictates what rank you get and depending on the rank, you'll get one of the following endings:Cheat: Easy bells on most stagesOn most stages, mainly the early stages, do the following: When you begin, simply fly to 9999 km high, staying on the left boundry of the level, right where you began.  When you get to the top, there is a stream of regenerating bells of most colors!</plot>
	<releasedate>7/1/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4</rating>
	<VideoURL>f5-voOCUNf0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5786</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563054-popn-twinbee-rainbow-bell-adventures</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/popn-twinbee-rainbow-bell-adventures</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pop-n-twinbee-rainbow-bell-adventures/3030-5496/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Y9EgpTK.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Fw1BVBn.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/mvr3X0D.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ArNwJA7.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/a2LN1OE.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/0HQOe5W.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/OqSlqnW.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/6FdhZOv.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/LH6tfrj.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/we4nES7.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/xr3cBMX.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/10jQL6K.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/oUUpsIj.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KNbjxPZ.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/90TgWJx.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You play as either Twinbee, Gwinbee or Winbee. Cooperative play is also available. In this mode the second player takes control over one of the two characters left. Either way your task is to find and defeat the evil Dr. Warmon who tries to enslave the islands of Dunburi. To deal with the many villains Dr. Warmon throws at you, you need to collect colored bells. Depending on the color of the bell you can use different attacks like a laser (blue bells) or a lash (orange bells). But even without the bells you're not defenseless. Your standard-attacks include a shock wave and the ability to fly.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/573c8e2b-152e-4137-857c-d2bfcf4155bf.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a61c78d3-772f-417e-952a-dfd5aff43a74.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/78329fdb-524f-48c1-9e4a-34e9f1c2b384.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/05532ba1-f009-4a54-b89f-b81d080586fa.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d01d1337-0c25-41d8-9839-ca93acd6ee5d.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/171fa9da-be24-43ce-934d-f9c7495d5d5f.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>