<Game>
	<Name>Popeye - Ijiwaru Majo Sea Hag no Maki (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Popeye Ijiwaru Majo: Sea Hag no Maki ("Popeye and the Harassing Witch Sea Hag") is a Popeye platformer-action game from Technos Japan. After Popeye trounces his nemesis the Sea Hag, she gets her revenge by separating all of Popeye's friends from their lifeforce, causing them to turn to stone. Popeye has to recover all their life energy (in the form of hearts) from a board game-like grid while avoiding the various heavies that have been sent to deter him, including his rival Bluto who is hoping to win Olive Oyl's heart by rescuing her first.The game was released only in Japan for the Super Famicom.Gameplay:Each stage takes place in a grid, and Popeye moves around by rolling a die and moving one to six spaces around the board. Some tiles allow him to purchase upgrades, recover health, move to other map squares and play through small platforming sequences. Occasionally, Popeye can bump into moving enemies on the map (similar to the overworld enemies in Super Mario Bros. 3) and fight a quick one-on-one battle with them for bonuses. His goal is to land on every square with a heart on it and find the heart in the stage somewhere. By collecting them all, Popeye saves a friend and moves onto the next board.Cheat: Level PasswordsAt the password screen, enter the following character's portraits to go to the desired level. The order of each portrait is as follows: Popeye, Olive Oyl, Swee'pea, Wimpy, Eugene The Jeep, Pappy, Granny, Nana Oyl, Marsman, Emok, Dufus, Alice The Goon, Blozo, Bernard, Bluto, Sea Hag</plot>
	<releasedate>12/8/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>Technos Japan</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2</rating>
	<VideoURL>VtHY7ahoGwg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26531</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571111-popeye-ijiwaru-majo-sea-hag-no-maki</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/popeye-ijiwaru-majo-sea-hag-no-maki/3030-49704/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/T1O87SC.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/EWY1mGG.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/YVVuLvj.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/MH0M9qn.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/BIoM26u.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Rj0GVVh.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/DtH09qV.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/iIJNp2h.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/FzUFcuW.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/tYAn0EC.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/B00ellN.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/OQtcmaQ.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/mLGtumQ.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/XKvncbN.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>After countless defeats at the hands of Popeye, the evil Seahag has devised a fool proof plan for revenge. She turns all of Popeye's friends into stone by removing their hearts and scattering the pieces across the corresponding islands. Now Popeye must search for the hearts within each of five islands in order to revive them. It won't be easy, as General Bunzo and his troops has issued a "100,000,000G" bounty for the hearts. This prompts the likes of Bolo, Ox to try and collect the hearts for the reward. Upon reading this, Brutus decides to quest for the hearts as well in a plan to impress Olive. Thus making this a race against time for Popeye to save his friends and put a stop to Seahag's plan.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eebc3a51-c4d9-43c2-a3c2-34300d88e449.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a61d363-e927-482e-9e60-c3b8a36a7198.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d1d4a31b-3f24-4b17-baee-d21b5d9ed9ff.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fd587c53-c60f-423a-a314-f2d320374b04.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9f695404-75ef-48a4-97fe-f6d2fcc6fdb2.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Technos Japan</Publisher>
</game>