<Game>
	<Name>Porky Pig's Haunted Holiday (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Porky Pig's Haunted Holiday is a sidescrolling platformer, in which the player guides Porky Pig through several of his nightmares. These nightmares include a forest, a western town, Atlantis, a mine, the alps, and a castle. This title was notable for being the only game staring Porky Pig, and its unique weather system, in which the weather cycles through seasons.Cheat: Alternative Options Screen and Joe Booths C.M.S. EditorOn the screen with license text, wait until the screen is about to fade out, then quickly enter the code.  If successful, the Alternative Options Screen will appear afterwards.  Here, you can view various cutscenes and the credits.  During gameplay, press Select to enter a debug menu called Joe Booth's C.M.S. editor.  This screen allows changing gameplay flags and the current level.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SunSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>vRWxNldSl2w</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5788</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588582-porky-pigs-haunted-holiday</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/porky-pigs-haunted-holiday</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/porky-pigs-haunted-holiday/3030-1683/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/JXoTzes.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Up3pgcU.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/asIK6sy.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ttNvR6Q.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/pnDlDbR.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8G6WYUi.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/9jFAf1V.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/uKzpbsb.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Bsm7mdY.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/HpNitqg.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/89Gaen3.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/0swVKSE.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/39o3Tt7.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/gsHtiKj.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/nXW3lnv.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Porky's going on a dream vacation to Dry Gulch Creek Haunted Theme Park. But as he sleeps, the holiday of his dreams turns into a real nightmare... Be brave! Choose your skill level and guide Porky through six scary worlds like the Haunted Woods and Dry Gulch Ghost Town. Be careful! Each world is full of hazards, traps, tons of ghosts, monsters and villains to trash and smash. Be surprised! The amazing Chaos Mapping System actually changes the weather each time the game is played! Snow, rain, fog, sun - you never know what you'll be up against. Be a hero! Is this little piggy just crying wolf, or is it really a dream-come-true? Pack all your game playing skills, because this is a trip you'll want to take over and over again.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b65805c-e158-4c92-8206-c2fa3bdd5a33.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98f0b53e-42db-4ae7-9b24-00aaf0ef4cb9.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/117b8f3c-aa6c-4b2b-8d1f-b0bfebd09978.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/25c7d44a-2645-49a4-a73e-72f32d30184b.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sunsoft</Publisher>
</game>