<Game>
	<Name>Power Piggs of the Dark Age (Europe) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>The player is put in the role of Bruno, an anthropomorphic pig who has the task to defend his land which is currently under siege by wolves. Bruno comes equipped with a sword and the ability to throw donuts that he finds throughout the six levels of the game. Bruno also has the ability to jump and to also butt slam crates. No description of this game would be complete without mentioning the blowholes which are liberally sprinkled throughout each level. These blowholes will lift Bruno in the air so that he will be able to get to higher plateaus that he simply couldn't get to by just jumping normally.Cheat: Level 5 PasswordEnter at the password screen</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Titus Software Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>5791</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588584-power-piggs-of-the-dark-age</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/power-piggs-of-the-dark-age-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/power-piggs-of-the-dark-ages/3030-38920/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/1A8dgZM.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/5qhM8P0.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lwFQkkh.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/fS99iQv.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/49cXyMe.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/rA5uozI.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/OC92fma.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FgFxwKh.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/zqku20O.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/8O7xy8q.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NnvN6MY.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/h9XvmgZ.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/uYhaSFc.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Ready to pig-out on action-packed adventure? Hungry for a dozen magic donuts? Then Power Piggs of the Dark Age is the game for you! You'll take Bruno--a Pigg who's co-owner of a donut shop in the Dark Age--on an incredible sword-swiping adventure through the hilarious Kingdom of Pigg! When the Wizzard of Wolff attacks his peaceful Kingdom, Bruno is forced to use exploding jelly donuts and his mighty sword to defeat the howling intruders. And when he's not floating in air geysers called -blow-holes- he's busting-open prize-filled boxes with his big fat, well, er... hams. Will the Wizzard's wacky wolves win? Can the cunning cruller-cookers conquer? It's all up to you in this non-stop romp through medieval cities, bizarre forests, the Wizzard's castle, and more donut holes than you can shake a sword at. You'll grunt with glee while you wallow-away the hours playing Power Piggs of the Dark Age!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9c5211f-3df8-4ba6-94cf-696c133f3ed6.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d1402ff1-d06d-4b3c-bd89-51158e338015.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63f62640-17d2-4e2e-be74-3a22ad8e7137.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67cf887e-7bca-460c-beda-4106a7485ccd.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Titus</Publisher>
</game>