<Game>
	<Name>Power Moves (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Power Moves (Super Nintendo's version name), or Deadly Moves (Sega Genesis's version name), both versions known in Japan as Power Athlete, is a fighting game created by Kaneko. One of the many fighting games published in the early 90's to capitalize on the success of Capcom's Street Fighter II, it did not achieve the success of its competition, and was largely ignored by most gamers.The gameplay is that of a traditional head-to-head fighting game. But unlike most games of its type, the single-player mode is limited to one character, Joe, who is the protagonist of the game. One of the game's most distinctive aspects is an RPG-like system which enables the player to boost Joe's various attributes, such as strength, speed and endurance. Another gimmick is the use of a two-plane fighting area (similar to that of Fatal Fury).Trivia:- Despite the difference in name for the Genesis and Super Nintendo versions, there was no actual difference in gameplay, content or characters. However, it is widely believed that the game's box cover and title were renamed only to keep up with Nintendo's stringent no-violence policy, as the Genesis cart features a closeup of a character being punched in the face, with a torrent of blood erupting from the impact. The SNES version's box featured the same image, with the red blood re-colored to look like sweat (the same tactic used with Mortal Kombat).- Although the Genesis version known as "Deadly Moves" featured a blood-spattered cover, there was no blood or finishing moves of any kind in the game.- The US magazine ad for the game, while detailing its features, did not feature any actual screenshots from the game, but crudely drawn ones that did not resemble the game at all.Tips:Play as Ranker in versus modeEYV G9DG 2Q7http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Power_MovesCheat: Fight Last BossIn the 1Player Game Input The password below.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Beat-Em-Up</genre>
	<Developer>Kaneko</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>OtmAnHxhRZs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3237</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/580885-power-moves</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/deadly-moves/3030-19025/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/hdRewhi.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/IE36Ajd.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/8gGcwQc.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/lSncCay.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/YoKCes1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/iPdP6I4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/bA3B5ac.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ntUdRFu.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/B8sG6Ur.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/IWalE6u.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2O3bRUQ.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/eHBOfZP.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ayoAebX.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/aSzzEUb.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Move over masters, a new champion is kicking in! This exciting action adventure game recreates the fury and explosiveness of international boxing. You take no prisoners. It‘s a fight for life and the championship in an eight series match. Set against international backdrops, you're pitted against eight of the most powerful Masters of the Martial Arts. Each master fights with their own special weapons and fighting techniques. You must kick, punch and jump to victory. The action is powerful. Make the right move and you advance to the next match. Make the wrong move and you move over. This exciting video battle features three dimensional screens, high quality graphics, special sound and video effects and challenging game play. Enemy masters can be designed for special attacking action. The weather and seasons change during the course of the game for more challenging game action. Make your move now! We challenge you to the fight of your life!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a0bd3838-612b-4d1a-9405-331bf7eced3e.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a78e6392-57c2-4d68-baf7-117a14b52c03.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fe7c1ba3-1536-4a13-ba0c-4d5c8f8c5c90.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/34e5fcd4-3bfa-4709-b1b2-a9bd74146e7a.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Kaneko</Publisher>
</game>