<Game>
	<Name>Prince of Persia (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Prince of Persia 1989Prince of Persia was originally released in 1989 for the  Apple II by  Jordan Mechner. Mechner used film of his younger brother David running, jumping, and performing many of the Prince's actions. Mechner then  rotoscoped the film to create the animations that give the  Prince his fluid movement.Part of the game's appeal was its then unique focus on  environmental puzzle-solving, as well as its one-on-one  sword duels. Mechner has stated that the game was inspired by the first ten minutes of Raiders of the Lost Ark, for the character's  acrobatics in a  dangerous environment.Prince of Persia has since been ported to a number of different platforms, including the  Amiga,  Apple Macintosh, DOS,  NES,  Game Boy,  Sega Genesis,  Game Gear,  SNES,  Sharp X68000,  Atari ST, and SAM Coup&#233;.The music was written by Jordan Mechner's father,  Francis Mechner.Gameplay:Prince of Persia is a platformer with heavy emphasis on careful jumping and environmental puzzle solving. The player controls the Prince as he attempts to  rescue his princess before she  weds  Jaffar, the evil Grand Vizier. Jaffar has trapped the  Princess, and given her an hour to decide whether she wishes to marry him or die. This hour unfolds in  real time, and the only way to lose the game is to fail to reach the Princess within sixty minutes.The player is given only an hour to navigate the game's thirteen levels and rescue her. Scattered throughout each level are hidden  switches, secret  pitfalls and a variety of other hazards standing in the Prince's way of rescuing his beloved. There are also hidden  potions that have a variety of effects on the Prince.The player will have to explore and pay attention to their environment in order to solve the puzzles and make it to the end. The Prince will also have to fight his way past  guards to reach the Princess. Combat exists as a series of sword fights, which were unusual for its time when  projectile weapons were the norm.Plot:The Sultan of Persia, one day, leaves to wage war in a foreign land. His Grand Vizier, Jaffar, steps in to take his  throne while he is away. Shortly thereafter, a street urchin decides to climb the Royal Tower to see the Princess, whom people have claimed to be as beautiful as a new moon. When the young  orphan finally sees the Princess,  they fall in love. The couple intend to marry.The Vizier discovers this and decides that he wants to marry the Princess. He throws the street urchin into the lowest  dungeon and locks the Princess in the highest tower. He then gives the Princess one hour, counted on a magical  hourglass, in which she has to decide to marry the Vizier or die.The street urchin's main goal is to defeat Jaffar and reach the Princess.Legacy:The SNES versionAside from being ported to several different platforms, Prince of Persia has received  two  proper  sequels and a  3D remake.  Ubisoft re-imagined the series with its  Sands of Time  trilogy, and the French publisher again rebooted the series with a new game, titled simply  Prince of Persia. A motion picture based on  Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time is also being developed, Mike Newell directing, and is being produced by  Jerry Bruckheimer. The movie was released in 2010 starring Jake Gyllenhaal, Gemma Arterton, and  Ben Kingsley and was received with average reviews.The game was  ported many times, and version such as the  SNES one which improved on the original. In the SNES game, the graphics were updated, and the game was given 20 levels, and an extra hour to complete the game.The original Prince of Persia has sold over 2 million copies.Critical ReceptionWhen the Game Gear version was released Electronic Gaming Monthly issued the scores of 8,8,7,5 adding, "...very impressed with this version of the game. Not only were all the characters and pitfalls very easy to see on the small screen, but even the very fluid animation found on the other versions of the game was duplicated almost perfectly".					</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>dNc4EadIMl0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3238</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588588-prince-of-persia</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/prince-of-persia</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/prince-of-persia/3030-2561/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/3jopuF9.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/MspVXNR.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/doDsHlU.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/2IYA16f.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/Rk7yoI7.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/3hXai8n.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/uDbmT28.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/854iOqe.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/TM5V0Y9.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ElruuJd.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VNwN1QE.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/iptLn34.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/3n2V5Gi.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Lw9NB4A.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/XbYk7CH.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/9Jy39X9.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/0LK4XX0.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/b0vsbXY.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/n84SoDE.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The award winning computer software adventure that has people everywhere rattling their sabers is here for Super NES. And now the animation is more detailed, and the controls more responsive. There's even a five part training mode for sharpening your running, jumping, climbing and sword fighting skills. But the sands of time are against you. For you must survive 20 perilous stages, rescue the princess from the evil Grand Vizier Jaffar, and claim the royal residency all before the hourglass is empty. Beware the unpredictable floors and ceilings, gut splitting guillotines, hidden spikes, walls of flames and more. Jaffar's spells spell doom if you're not crafty and nimble. And a legion of savage servants, amazing amazons and immortal skeletons will do his barbaric bidding. Even your own alter ego is the enemy. Pass through invisible doors and walk through space portals. Find vessels of magic potions, but partake of them wisely. They may increase your life or just as easily poison you. So take each step with caution, young would-be prince, or the entire kingdom will suffer the darkest Arabian night ever.</Notes>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99c12efe-bff9-4b9c-8322-11223410bbf6.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f7abefdb-ecb7-4353-b6da-effd098544f6.jpg</boxart8>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dbdade48-f1dc-4652-a6b1-62a0bd2a98a1.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2fd02b11-0088-4f69-b48a-b5b636c6d9c9.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ce7a0999-5d11-4bef-b649-2226eb88fee0.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/36a4b885-acaf-4a41-b6c5-9e3639b177e3.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/071349b8-96d8-41b7-b1f0-954c9cbd09a8.png</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23ecd037-3784-4525-9c14-1cf0e085badd.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/09ebf72a-26c9-4827-bcb6-43bdb0d7d7c2.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9e4685d9-6b2c-448d-b6b1-99c3ad9b45fc.jpg</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6e854245-5341-4f25-a3c0-f76f7000bf23.jpg</snapshot18>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>