<Game>
	<Name>Princess Minerva (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Princess Minerva: Hime no Wagamama Daibouken was first created by RED Company and Riverhill Software and released on the PC-98 in 1992.A somewhat different game was developed for the PC Engine CD in 1994. This version sported animated CG cutscenes as well as voice acting. It also had a unique element where 3 parties of 3 would travel together, and one of them would be selected at random to take part in each regular battle, ensuring the need to keep all 9 characters leveled and well-equipped at all times.In 1995, the PCE version was ported by Vic Tokai to the Super Famicom, but because of the space limitations of the cartridge, all of the voice acting and nearly all the CG was cut out. A number of enemy sprites were also removed, and replaced with palette swaps of other regular enemies.CensorshipThe PC Engine CD version of Princess Minerva featured several scenes of nudity, both of Minerva and company, as well as the primary villainess, Dynastar, and her minions. In the Super Famicom port, scenes were modified so that the protagonists remain clothed, and numerous enemy sprites were edited so their nipples were no longer visible.The PC-98 version, in a rare and unusual case, was not as racy as the PC Engine CD entry.	</plot>
	<releasedate>23/6/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Vic Tokai Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/577354-princess-minerva</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/princess-minerva</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/princess-minerva/3030-16246/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Princess_Minerva</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/u77hq2h.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/EtWyTAe.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/aFP1FRp.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8uHTBcp.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xeDqkBX.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/M0BYkFK.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/RDowdAf.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/eCp40im.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/l3fjfMR.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/1HKiHdW.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/u6VevTG.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/azagDzV.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/as2cOqc.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Princess Minerva is based on an anime of the same name. In the kingdom of Whistler, the best fighters are young, beautiful women, proficient in many styles of combat. Princess Minerva is one of them. She participates in a tournament, battles against the best female fighters of the country, and ultimately joins forces with them, building a super-powerful party that is bound to defeat the archenemy of the Queen of Whistler, the evil sorceress Dynastar. The game begins where the girls are already united and are getting ready for the grand quest. Your party contains nine girls, each one with various statistics and magic spells. The large party is divided into three smaller ones, and you switch between them while participating in random battles and fighting bosses. The combat is turn-based, and is viewed from a top-down perspective, like the locations you visit. You travel on the overworld map, visit towns, and descend into dungeons. The three active girls in your party can also unite to perform combo attacks.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9b126920-5567-47c3-9a9e-051c647f6af4.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/298b2274-7190-457a-8cde-6c3c2849a4aa.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fdba161d-df38-4173-8f26-2861bdebe2ea.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/404ce90f-c6ea-443a-929a-6f62fc5998b6.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/def67052-27f4-4a08-a1a3-6674021ab28f.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Vic Tokai</Publisher>
</game>