<Game>
	<Name>Pro Quarterback (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Pro Quarterback is a football game featuring 27 different teams. Since this game doesn't have an NFL or NFLPA license, there aren't any real NFL teams or players here, although the teams included in the game represent the cities of their real life NFL counterparts and also mimic the colors of their team's uniforms.The games options allow the player to choose to play on 6 different field surfaces (grass, mud, dirt, snow, rain and artificial turf) and to choose how long the game will last (2, 5, 10 or 15 minute quarters). There are also no penalties in this game whatsoever. Gameplay: consists of playing on both offense and defense. There are 26 different offensive plays and 18 different defensive plays to choose from. The game has a down the field view when on offense, so the game doesn't have receivers in windows.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Tradewest, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>fRvsy_V3U18</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1729</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588590-pro-quarterback</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/pro-quarterback</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pro-quarterback/3030-35925/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ygPqixv.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/LJXb87U.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/3i4hZ3Z.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/mpmdXms.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/jvoS8wK.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ILOQbO8.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/QFSNNrC.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/lqoc8kX.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/T3sqHgs.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/moqj849.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/HyX0Z3M.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/OicK1w9.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/SnnpZFH.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/bsFC9Gd.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>WARNING: THIS GAME IS TOO REAL PRO QUARTERBACK is guts &amp; glory football played as a professional would! From the kick-off to the final gun, you have to be quick, smart and tough to win. - Break the huddle into a dramatic, 3-D perspective down the field! - 26 Professional teams, stats track each player's performance, 6 different field conditions and realistic sound! For 1 or 2 players! - You select the players from either side of the ball using the playbook's long list of offensive or defensive plays! - Team up with a friend, go head-to-head or play against the computer! IT DOESN'T GET ANY MORE REALISTIC!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e3f614f4-fb57-4cd4-b247-c2cbf3ad05c8.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dde90c27-1471-405e-84f1-a5ac58dd8b94.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3617c887-2988-4c9f-87b3-4017bb0c3da4.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/66ac6b30-bb9f-4703-ab5b-655d9354cdf3.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Tradewest</Publisher>
</game>