<Game>
	<Name>Psycho Dream (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dream Probe is a platformer, originally released in Japan under the title "Psycho Dream". Though the English version called Dream Probe was cancelled, it was advertised and reviewed. The cancellation came shortly after SEGA bought the game's original publisher, Renovation, with some speculating that SEGA did not want to fund any game to be released on the competing SNES.The game itself has the player controlling a prominent U.S. scientist who has invented a dream machine. After a young girl becomes trapped within the machine you follow her into six of her dreams in an attempt to rescue her. Strangely, most of her dreams are about futuristic cities filled with cybernetic enemies.Critical ReceptionElectronic Gaming Monthly issued the scores of 5,6,5,5 adding, "...there is a good variety of levels with plenty of nice scenery to look at, but when you play the game you find the power-ups are rather mild and the bosses slow down the game too much".Cheat: Level SelectUpon starting the game, hold Y, X, R, and Start on Controller 2 until the Riot logo fades out. Select either Start or Continue on the title screen to access the level select screen. Press Up or Down to select your level and Y to start.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Riot</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>iGAdHJ31SCc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>12502</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/580888-psycho-dream</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/psycho-dream</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/psycho-dream/3030-35962/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/LmNbxB1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/HjVuRUh.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/8Glbn4j.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/48lIDBF.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/qewJS3F.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Siyi8sD.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/zICxgqB.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/rEQHpYa.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/MNwRcNT.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/OVm7PnT.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/gSBnnGt.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/lO05pv5.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/pUCxJoV.png</banner1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3b74b200-d908-42ca-a79c-42547e4dc99b.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8826b34d-fbcf-459a-9e5f-d0d211ffc12f.png</clearlogo1>
</game>