<Game>
	<Name>Push-Over (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>THIS GAME IS NO PUSH-OVERG.I. ANT is a soldier ant. He's extremely clever, and highly trained in tactical maneuvers. What's more, he's extraordinarily strong and super smart! His latest mission is to gain access to the crazy world of Captain Rat's Treasure Caves. Very straightforward..... NOT!You see, this particular cave is a tunnel entrance to Domino Domain - a mini- world comprised of nine different continents. G.I. must negotiate many screens of mind-teasing problems. Each level has a door to the next. To open the door, the 'Trigger' domino-block must be felled by causing a chain reaction with all of the other domino-blocks in that level. Pretty easy..... NOT!--From the SNES Push-Over instruction manual.Tips:Passwords:Enter the passwords below to clear the corresponding stages.44543 Go to Stage 10010758 Level 2511782 Level 2611270 Level 2709222 Level 2809734 Level 2908718 Level 3008206 Level 3124590 Level 3225102 Level 3326126 Level 3425614 Level 3527662 Level 3628174 Level 3727150 Level 3826638 Level 3930734 Level 4031246 Level 4132270 Level 4231758 Level 4329726 Level 4430238 Level 4529214 Level 4628702 Level 4720510 Level 4821022 Level 4922046 Level 5021534 Level 5123582 Level 5224094 Level 5323070 Level 5422558 Level 5518494 Level 5619006 Level 5720030 Level 5819518 Level 5917470 Level 6017982 Level 6116958 Level 6216510 Level 6316511 Level 6417023 Level 6518047 Level 6617535 Level 6719583 Level 6820095 Level 6919071 Level 7018559 Level 7122655 Level 7223167 Level 7324191 Level 7423679 Level 7521631 Level 7622143 Level 7721247 Level 7820735 Level 7928927 Level 8029439 Level 8130463 Level 8229951 Level 8331999 Level 8432511 Level 8531487 Level 8630975 Level 8726879 Level 8827647 Level 8928671 Level 9028159 Level 9126111 Level 9226623 Level 9325599 Level 9425087 Level 9508703 Level 9609215 Level 9710239 Level 9809727 Level 9900512 Stage 107680 Stage 1007168 Stage 1105122 Stage 1205634 Stage 1304610 Stage 1404098 Stage 1512290 Stage 1612802 Stage 1713826 Stage 1813314 Stage 1901536 Stage 215362 Stage 2015878 Stage 2114854 Stage 2214342 Stage 2310246 Stage 2410758 Stage 2501024 Stage 303072 Stage 403584 Stage 502560 Stage 602048 Stage 706144 Stage 806656 Stage 9http://www.consoleclassix.com/snes/push_over.htmlCheat: PasswordsEnter the passwords below to clear the corresponding stages.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle, Static</genre>
	<Developer>Ocean Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>5796</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588592-push-over</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/pushover</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pushover/3030-16767/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/eLl14vh.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OgTkoEd.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/5TMfbYc.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/sOWAq0G.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/XPSmKdG.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/AhR4LtF.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ewMhRws.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/JDjUpqs.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Iah4Y1h.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/xqishfF.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/arYy0nE.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/3W8Tgiy.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/eVCcCEZ.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/6ZWEwQC.png</clearlogo1>
</game>