<Game>
	<Name>Putty Squad (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>In this sequel to Putty, the Wizard's peoples have invaded Putty land, and it's up to you to head to the Wizard city of Klud and free your many POWs. The gameplay has less of a puzzle element than the original, and is more of a standard platform game - to whatever extent a game in which you can become an all-conquering Terminator Putty, must face pups throwing grenades at you, and can use Uncle Ted to play a tune to distract enemies can be seen as a 'standard' example of anything.You take control of the same amorphous blob as before, which has the ability to 'stretch' left and right (using this as a weapon which kills on contact) and to stretch upwards to make jumping easier. He can also explode himself and absorb other objects, even becoming them physically to gain an advantage.There are stars littered around the level, and collecting these upgrades Putty's abilities, starting with a super punch for 10 stars, going up to the Terminator ability for 40. The pups from the previous game are no longer on your side, and are out to get you. These have all manner of abilities - shooting mortar bombs at you, paradropping towards you, and even flying a helicopter.Cheat: Level PasswordsAfter the title screen choose select password and enter the following chain.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ocean Software Ltd.</Developer>
	<VideoURL>zM_AYBa4ckM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2664</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/926450-putty-squad</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/putty-squad</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/putty-squad/3030-6587/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/FMAfieU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ok7i1Vy.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/1phagCi.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/bnMrjyv.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ErfUyWM.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/DaAMdIR.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/z1ppeuG.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/qdnA9E4.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/lQ2BH44.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/RCjevYF.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/7n9gZ8t.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QDkZdj5.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/goJ7R3l.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/oLLZMMR.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The C.I.A. has formed a crack covert team to parachute into hostile areas and rescue the Putty M.I.A.s. The team consists of Super Putty and his one time enemy Dweezil the Ginger Cat. They must also terminate the rogue Commander Naplam the Cat who having gone crazy has set himself up as a god to the native population of spotted frogs in the area. This is their mission and they must not fail or the Putty M.I.A.s are doomed.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5a97c4c9-8a65-4e74-93d6-e8e062c3abae.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bff5a02b-f6ec-4815-b2fe-afb6d5f69866.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/354d45ec-f1e8-4c3b-a0b7-0364b3ccaee8.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6eca3eef-9b5b-46b7-8ea8-e043ad73a569.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Ocean</Publisher>
</game>