<Game>
	<Name>Radical Rex (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Radical Rex is a fire-breathing Tyrannosaurus on a skateboard who has to save the dinosaur race under the spell of an evil creature. The game consists of 10 levels set in the prehistoric age. Radical Rex can use a skateboard or glide down hills, jump, kick and breath fire. Tougher enemies need multiple hits and when burnt Rex needs to kick them once more to destroy them or use his scream (hits everything on the screen). While playing Rex collects eggs, health, power-ups for his fire breath and scream refills. Checkpoints are shown as torches that need to be charged with fire. After each level, there is a Bomberman-like sequence to earn an extra continue. Enemies include flies, turtles, toads and all kinds of dinosaurs.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Activision, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>tt_aXsbWlow</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5802</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588595-radical-rex</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/radical-rex</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/radical-rex/3030-10305/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/PvOeQZo.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/bN1mbMg.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/WnmCxQL.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/i3HduFY.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/PS1n39W.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/k24AdF2.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/W6IMsbp.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/iLx8gnm.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/jw0Ojeg.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/lFa0QZ8.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/9AJZxmC.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/oGXIg0v.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/srvn2yW.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ExuuxD1.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/K3d6VJa.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Come hang with Radical Rex. He's the raddest, baddest fire-breathing Tyrannosaurus ever to shred prehistoric pavement! This badboy-on-wheels is out to save the dinosaur race. Check Rex thrashin' on his board, sportin' his flame-breath, bustin' out with killer jump-kicks, swingin' on vines and blastin' out screen-shaking roars. Excellent! Slam through ten wild levels of jammin' jungles, freaked-out forests, haunted dino-graveyards, piranha-infested underwater caverns -- and inside a giant dinosaur! Rex keeps you groovin' while you keep him movin' past twenty of the meanest prehistoric nasties to rock his dino-world. No sweat for Rex -- 'cuz he's too hip to be extinct!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dc1c4465-53c0-4f8c-8e7e-feece1a0f4d0.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a4abd96b-4d0b-4ebd-b6a5-d849a954d4dc.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e7d7ab82-6da1-44cf-825b-c19e10579af7.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e760edf-92a4-4d89-81d2-900f13104326.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>