<Game>
	<Name>Radical Psycho Machine Racing (USA)</Name>
	<plot>RPM was a successful remake of the Commodore 64 program Racing Destruction Set, developed by Electronic Arts in 1985. It claims to be the first American-developed game for the SNES system.RPM was one of the first SNES games developed in 'High Resolution Graphics Mode' which allowed for sharper detail but fewer colors. While the higher resolution gave finer detail, it also severely limited the number of colors and amount of unique graphics that could be displayed from the SNES video memory. Due to this, the sequel to RPM (RPMII which was later renamed Rock N' Roll Racing) was developed in the lower resolution graphics mode allowing for much more vibrant colors and graphic detail.The logic engine and track editor for RPM were ported from an older EA title Racing Destruction Set. The 6502 assembly code was modified for 16 bit but otherwise mostly left intact.There is an easter egg in the game on Track 29 which spells 'Eat Me' very clearly. This surprisingly made it through Nintendo's QA process and wasn't mentioned in any of the post reviews of the game.Gameplay::In the game, players can race in a regular season, a single race, and even get to create their own course. The courses can be straight and oval like NASCAR, curvy and flat like Formula One, or hilly and unpredictable like a monster truck track. The winner gets money and a chance to score his initials for the fastest time.Development:RPM was developed using the 'Sluggo' development system created by Bill Heineman and his partner which allowed uploading of bin files to a device that emulated a cartridge for the SNES. System did not include step through or trace functionality.RPM was programmed in 65816 Assembly Language using a cross compiler on an IBM computer.Development took 5 months and was programmed almost exclusively by Allen Adham with graphics supplied by Interplay.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/RPM_RacingCheat: $45 million dollarsTo start a new game with fourty-five million dollars,  first select an empty file and use the B button to enter the shop screen.  Choose any of the three cars by pressing B.  Then move the red selection box to the bottom center square.  Then press B, Left, B, Left, B, Right, B, Right, B, B, B, Left, B, B, B, Right, B, Right, B, B.  The red box should be one square right of where you put it it and you will have 45 million dollars.Cheat: $45 million dollarsIf you create a custom map with a useless loop, it confuses the computer opponents, and removes them.  This is usefull if you want to race a friend, but you don't want to deal with the pesky computer.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Interplay</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>0.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>OyvecUB5xp4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5818</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588635-rpm-radical-psycho-machine-racing</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/rpm-racing</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/radical-psycho-machine-racing/3030-28137/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/IQqi91e.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/pCcuBka.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/dt4z53o.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/9FipaEa.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ji4KWr1.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RcGlp8K.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/HAIItle.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/6DV5Nk1.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/bRX4tPH.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/G48Dg4o.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ssr8lhN.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/HS4BbsO.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1hkCuuK.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/JCJyuYd.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Get in. Fire it up. And then hang on. You're in for the ride of your life! Engines scream as the monster truck flies into the lead. All four racers spill over the dirt hill and slam onto the asphalt surface. Pushing past the pack in true dune buggy style, the Sandrail hits an ice patch and skids off the track. The Eurocar crashes through the open hole, but not before dropping off a few mines to slow down any slip-streamers. And the race has just begun! Interplay Productions introduces super high resolution graphics in a radical racing action game. Players zoom over asphalt, dirt and ice as they make their way through 24 levels of track difficulty--or they can build and save their own exciting track designs! And racers use their winnings to buy bigger and better equipment, or arm themselves with mines and oil slicks to sabotage the opposition. The challenge is on. It's machine vs. machine in the ultimate race for the checkered flag!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3db925bb-8a76-4047-b34f-69c6f3f4b771.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4a608a49-8c56-4e4c-8a68-b625f36d7cfe.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/85a92261-00f5-4e6f-82de-04f1e01d5365.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/96aba3c0-7bff-4358-97f4-4717406d51c3.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Interplay</Publisher>
</game>