<Game>
	<Name>Raiden Densetsu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The year is 2090 A.D. in reaction to centuries of war and international strife the people of earth, united under a world allied government, established what was thought to be a lasting world peace. They thought wrong. A new enemy has emerged to threaten earth's peace, an enemy from another world...The planet earth has been invaded by the tyrannical and imperialistic forces of Carnass. You have witnessed the populace of the planet earth's decimation, the scorching and ransacking of cities, and the defeat of earth's mightiest defenses. The future of the earth looked dim, that is until the creation of the world's last hope, the innerspace fighter bomber 'Raiden.' You have been selected to pilot this incredible weapon and defend your home world...Take on the alien invaders in the desert, the Suez Canal and the black void of space. You're not facing cute little green men in space suits here, oh no, but the ruthless, mechanical terrors from a war hungry world. The future of earth is in your hands. You and you alone can save the earth and it's remaining population, and and your innerspace fighter bomber 'Raiden!'</plot>
	<releasedate>20/4/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Side Scroller</genre>
	<Developer>Micronics</Developer>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>nPr5P2c6tM0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3240</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588597-raiden-trad</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/raiden-trad/3030-30347/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/cPUNDEO.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/i6sDZKa.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Dqp83OZ.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/DWjfRYH.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/GCAKKGf.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/aIfBdEn.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/CrbutaG.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/OJIeYLN.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YaBrPdK.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/JhzrjVR.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/uy7fo7F.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/hcyAcfV.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ycfwHYE.png</clearlogo1>
</game>