<Game>
	<Name>Ranma 1-2 - Hard Battle (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ranma 1/2: Hard Battle (known in Japan as Ranma 1/2: Bakuretsu Rantou Hen, or "Ranma 1/2: Exploding Brawl") is a one-on-one fighting game featuring the cast of the Rumiko Takahashi manga and anime Ranma 1/2. Originally released on the Super Famicom in 1992, it is the only Ranma 1/2 video game that was officially localized for distribution in North America with the exception of Street Combat; a western version of Ranma 1/2: Chounai Gekitou Hen that was reskinned to remove its relation to Ranma.CharactersRanma 1/2: Hard Battle features ten fighters (technically twelve, as two characters can fight in two separate forms) as well as an unplayable boss character. In the single player, each fighter is taking part in a tournament due to a promise or a suggestion made by Principal Kuno, though most of them have been coerced or tricked into competing.Ranma Saotome - Ranma is the protagonist of the series and, like many Ranma characters, has a "cursed" form due to falling into a cursed spring while training. This cursed form is a female version of himself, who is slightly faster but also physically weaker - their movesets are otherwise identical. The player can choose to fight as either form. Because he's let his studies fall to the wayside to focus on his fighting, he takes part in the tournament for the promise of being given top grades.Genma Saotome - Genma is Ranma's father and taught him martial arts, though Ranma quickly surpassed him in skill. Genma's cursed form is that of a giant panda, and this is the only form that is playable. Genma competes in the tournament to knock some sense into his rebellious son. Ryoga Hibiki - Ryoga is Ranma's self-proclaimed rival, and has a similar moveset. His cursed form is that of a tiny adorable black piglet with zero fighting ability. Ryoga wakes up in the Principal's office with amnesia, and is fighting in order to get his memory back.Akane Tendo - Scion of the powerful Tendo dojo and semi-reluctant arranged fiance&#233; of Ranma, Akane enters the tournament to deter her many admirers from bothering her.Shampoo - Another of Ranma's fiance&#233;s, Shampoo enters the tournament hoping to impress him with her fighting prowess. Her cursed form is that of a cat, an animal Ranma is phobic towards. She's the fastest character in the game and can even double jump.Hikaru Gosunkugi - A student obsessed with voodoo and the occult, who has a crush on Akane. He fights to win her over. He uses occult items like a straw voodoo doll in combat.Ukyo Kuonji - Another of Ranma's brides-to-be and a dedicated okonomiyaki chef, she is convinced to enter the tournament in order to prove her strength as a fighter and businesswoman. She fights with spatulas.Gambling King - A nefarious figure who looks like one of the kings from a deck of playing cards, he enters the tournament to make enough money to build his very own casino. He's one of the slowest and weakest characters, and thus the most challenging to beat the game with.Mousse - Shampoo's childhood friend, his love for her is unrequited and he blames (male) Ranma for catching her eye. He is tricked into fighting in the tournament by the Principal in a fortune teller disguise, who tells him that his happiness is dependent on winning the contest. Despite being nearly blind, he is an adept fighter who flings hidden objects at his opponents.Pantyhose Taro - The unfortunately-named Pantyhose is an antagonist of the series and serves as the final boss for most of the game's characters. His cursed form is that of a mighty chimera or demon, and characters either end up fighting him in his human or his monstrous form. He is unlocked as a playable character for story mode once beaten, though he can be played in Versus mode from the offset.Happosai - Happosai is a very small but indescribably powerful martial artist as well as a perverted old man. Pantyhose must defeat him as the boss of his story mode in order to receive a new name. He is unplayable.Critical ReceptionElectronic Gaming Monthly issued the review scores of 7,8,7,8 and 8. Mike Weigand wrote, "Purists and fans will immediately be repelled by the 'Americanized' voices, but others will find a very good one-on-one fighting game. The fighters are very original, as are their many moves".Cheat: CodesAfter choosing a character, hold R + X + A. The debug menu will appear before the round starts.Cheat: CodesWhen you select Versus Mode, if both players hold L+R, they can select the same character.  If player 1 does this in Team Battle, they can pick a team of characters for the computer to play against them.  This can also be done in standard Versus Mode.Cheat: CodesAt the Game Mode select screen, press Select, X, Up, Left, Down, Right, Up. If done right, the names of the character will appear on top and you can choose to see all their visual scenes.Cheat: Alternate creditsBeat the game on hard to see a different credits sequence featuring the transformed charactersNote that this is only needs to be done on the JP release as it is already the default ending in the other versions.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>DTMC, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>V4a_yXnXvjA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2665</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588600-ranma-1-2-hard-battle</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ranma-12-hard-battle</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ranma-12-hard-battle/3030-7069/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/hiu1dNG.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/1rfrvdZ.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/cnUdxfP.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/0AhLxjT.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/cmULiLa.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/TgU97KY.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wjIsXB5.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/z7GMngi.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/1dXeiF3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IYZiH9y.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/PFvJ0aU.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/qzCtzcE.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/WfU7Jn9.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/UXZoAAy.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Z9vUl4t.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/YWyMVAl.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/LpNvQdz.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/wZ42Bwe.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/OQYXwAx.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>In a remote part of China is the fabled "Training Ground of the Accursed Springs." There are over one hundred springs there, each with its own mysterious legend. It is believed that anyone that falls into one will be transformed into the being haunting the spring. Without realizing the curse, Ranma and his father Genma, begin their martial arts exercises...unaware of the fate to come.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/70b9d38f-34a5-466f-a0d6-9bc19c7d4831.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/768220f3-55b1-4a8a-9c4b-adadb522ad47.png</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0a561147-6524-4f98-94b2-e1aacd42287c.png</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/14429e36-a793-4e35-836c-de1eaab2da69.png</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/679f85eb-68c1-4011-8f3b-183a890902a0.jpg</boxart9>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/06dea74c-4d92-424d-adeb-8d3722c93fb9.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dbc846fe-d25a-4c2f-80de-26a4decd5b79.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6f9c3537-03ae-4012-8634-c723b3bffb18.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9f733901-29ae-404b-8ba4-5d683b427541.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f68aa5b5-73e5-4641-9e44-6197db630fbe.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6c6ccb2a-a3dc-42fd-9866-75873cdaaacb.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0b48e38a-ba70-4b5a-8f3d-ec62b42015f3.jpg</snapshot15>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>DTMC</Publisher>
</game>