<Game>
	<Name>Rap Jam - Volume One (USA) (En,Fr,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Rap Jam Volume One is basketball video game for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System released in 1995. It features various popular rap artists at that time as the basketball players.Gameplay:Rap Jam plays very much like a standard basketball game. When taking shots, a meter quickly appears, and when you release the ball when the meter is full, you have a better chance of making the shot. Games can be played against the computer in one on one, two on two, and three on three style variants. Local multiplayer is also supported.Reception:Since release, this game has been general accepted as a poor game. Critics of this title have cited the lack of music; awkward controls; uncontrollable, random player changing; and quick repetitiveness of gameplay on a whole as reasons for disliking it. Characters:The rappers and rap groups that appear in the game are: CoolioHouse of PainLL Cool JNaughty By NatureOnyxPublic EnemyQueen LatifahWarren GYo-Yo</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Mandingo Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>1.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>uP9XReZBwlc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5805</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588602-rap-jam-volume-one</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/rapjam-volume-one</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rap-jam-volume-one/3030-946/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/IzLAsIg.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/XntPf6v.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/SNLc7Gd.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/J9Vdaa4.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/iwh99OC.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/pxezuP3.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/NhWKopR.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/KJqy6Ea.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/tk365sW.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/idxeE0g.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/WycAL9T.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8yniLO4.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/no31BnU.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>HIT THE COURTS! Play some serious b-ball with America's hottest Rappers -- including Warren G, Public Enemy, Queen Latifah, Naughty by Nature, Yo-Yo, LL Cool J, House of Pain, Coolio and Onyx -- each with a special slammin' move. Mow 'em down with unbelievable Hang Time Jams! Crush the defense with a Helicopter Jam and slice 'em with a Somersault Slam. Forget regulation play -- it's survival of the fittest when you're pushin', shovin' and jammin' in the streets of Chicago, L.A., New York, Houston and Atlanta. No rules. No refs. Lots of fun. - Play basketball with your favorite rap stars! - Toss a wicked Fireball for moves too hot for your opponents to handle. - Wrack up big points with Xtra smashes -- Somersault Dunk, Flip Flop Dunk, Incredible Jam and Corkscrew Jam. - Play with up to 4 other players using a multiplayer adapter (available separately).</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d6f0195d-e771-4733-8724-53e2ccac5198.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/476c3d39-df33-463f-8a4c-d3de5be88744.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/25c22a3f-8b09-4a21-b7dd-f78d378ab8a2.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/16c9b33e-2cb4-40fe-b442-0f7ee3250084.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Motown Games</Publisher>
</game>