<Game>
	<Name>Realm (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Realm is a side-scrolling platforming shooter released near the end of the SNES era. Players control a long haired blond cyborg in his quest to defeat aliens.StoryThe player controls a teenage cyborg only known as Biomech. His task is to push back the invading alien forces threatening a futuristic earth. His quest begins at the last bastion of human resistance nestled in the forest. Fighting endless hordes of aliens with any weapons found, he must infiltrate each of the four "realms" now under alien control. His only hope in saving earth is in defeating the leader of the aliens residing in a battle ship orbiting earth.GameplayThe player has a wide array of weapons that are found within levels however only two weapons can be help at once. All weapons have ammunition except for Biomechs starting pistol. Ammunition can be acquired by either collecting another instance of a weapon or by shooting yellow crystals commonly found throughout the game. The player can collect shield symbols to increase health as well as a power-up providing temporary invulnerability. Any contact with enemy's will result in health loss and falling into canyons or off the level immediately kill the player. Each realm has a preliminary boss then a final boss before moving to the next area.WeaponsWeaponDamageTraitLaser Pistol1Infinite ammoAD3502Heat-seekingVFR7502Rapid-fireNR7501-4Charge-attackLC-30 "Ring"5Large laser streamGSX7504Machine gunSR5003Rocket launcherCBR6003Boomerang missilesTR12Spread-shotAlthough there are many weapon types, players often use the LC-30 and AD350. A common strategy is to acquire the AD350 "heat-seeking" gun and simply shoot straight up, while avoiding enemy fire. This allows the player to focus solely of the platforming aspects of the game. The LC-30 is often saved for boss encounters as it is the highest damage weapon with a constant stream of fire.Cheat: CodesAfter holding Up + X + B + R + Start at the title screen(invinsibility)Cheat: CodesPress Start + Select during game play to jump to the next level</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Titus France SA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>VOj_IrVdjO4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5806</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588604-realm</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/realm_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/realm/3030-38915/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/wmMKXBR.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/qYh5Buc.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/h7rkKOW.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/KgQuYAT.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/brXtoZG.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ncwzqWe.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SvWmSIa.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/a3bp1d9.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/bEtTAZw.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/v7HPVup.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/o8Coi2l.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/f0ntTTR.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/hZYO88N.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/6yWzbra.png</clearlogo1>
</game>