<Game>
	<Name>Redline F-1 Racer (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Redline: F1 Racer is a Formula 1 racing game from Genki. The game was released in Japan on July 14, 1992, more than a year before the North American release. It is known in Japan as Suzuki Aguri no F-1 Super Driving, named for its celebrity tie-in Formula 1 racer Aguri Suzuki. The European version has the similar title of Aguri Suzuki F-1 Super Driving.Aguri Suzuki F-1 Super Driving was also released for the Game Boy in 1993.Cheat: Last RaceSelect continue on the championship mode and enter the following password:L0960 70H0K0 L1113 081L0F 0K090 9211C0 L2245 5517H7</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Absolute Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>ubpm1-aoV3k</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2544</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588605-redline-f-1-racer</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/redline-f1-racer</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/redline-f1-racer/3030-10056/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/lX0d2j7.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/LNVXthW.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/lYAajN2.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/y7QpqOj.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/cgXlCyW.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/a8Rkw0v.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/LH8TwjH.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/v84o40k.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ylR3LbK.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/YbvB4xI.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/5FE0Kho.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NCcKBV4.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Xm2BUC6.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/zWgBQ3n.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/gt775KJ.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>Grab your helmet, strap yourself in and get ready to burn some serious rubber! Redline: F-1 Racer turns your Super NES into a high-performance Formula One race car and hurls you down the track at mind-numbing turbocharged speeds! Pitted against the best drivers in the sport, you..!! compete on 16 of the most perilous and challenging courses on the international brand Prix circuit! But first you..!! have to design your own precision-crafted F-1 racer from the ground up. You'll have your pick of top-of-the-line tires and brakes, high-tech suspension systems and sleek chassis—carefully molding a machine that will give you the best chance to take the coveted checkered flag. All the explosive thrills and gut-wrenching action of motor sports' most unforgiving arena are at your fingertips! Downshift to power into the lead in the tunnel at Monaco! Bump your opponent off the course on the treacherous crossover at Suzuka! In one-player or two player split-screen mode, Redline: F-1 Racer is the most fiery, heart-stopping racing simulation ever!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a1f55267-d199-4b81-b6a2-41a2b5f5fd53.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/53829081-aba8-463e-8d3e-ac344b459f2c.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c0fe2086-80c8-4dc2-87d1-ca792e81387d.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cc8e3de3-f36f-4577-a8c7-8cad972b307d.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0a757df0-2c93-45f5-84d3-2159b9a2478d.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0521e817-8ee0-4d9c-a5c1-6e8d54fd1f96.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9137c097-34b3-4945-a0a8-ba1be2e46012.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e650a967-de03-455d-a80a-0aae43ab9238.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Absolute Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>