<Game>
	<Name>Ren & Stimpy Show, The - Fire Dogs (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Based on the Nickelodeon cartoon, Fire Dogs was one of the episodes in the first season and inspires this game cartridge.  You start as the dimwitted cat Stimpy who has to search through the different levels of a firehouse to find these objects to proceed: a helmet, hose, pair of socks, rope, trampoline, uniform, and a beaver(!).  They all have to be placed on a fire truck before time runs out.  You can jump, climb up stairs and firepoles, and grab items while avoiding or putting out fires with water and eluding a speedy fireman by painting yourself like a dalmatian to avoid getting thrown out. A short 30 second bonus round follows where you must find Ren, the psychotic chihuahua.  This is followed by another 30 second round to bounce as many bags of Gritty Kitty Litter into a bin as you can.The second level has both Ren and Stimpy holding the trampoline to catch objects falling from a burning building.  Again, there is a time limit by which all items must be caught.  If successful, you return to the firehouse again the next day and must survive a week to gain the award of the Sacred Golden Fire Hydrant Helmets.Cheat: Last Stage passwordPress the right and left buttons the correct ammount of times in the password screen to go to the last level.You have to select a hat, hair, eyes, nose and mouth.Red-Yellow-Blue hat, no hair, dark glasses, stimpy's nose and stimpy's mouth is the result you should see.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/6/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.0833250000000003</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6286</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588608-the-ren-and-stimpy-show-fire-dogs</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ren-stimpy-show-fire-dogs</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-ren-stimpy-show-fire-dogs/3030-40455/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/k6MqxqL.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/38Qiog3.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/HY4og6J.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/cn3NgtS.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SDlAZ2L.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/hGzB2bl.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/e8uAXiT.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/HD13CsP.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/iJiDgEQ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/wkcxPUv.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/UE2oEKi.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/sIajJIW.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/loA76fu.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/oaKUCdv.png</clearlogo1>
</game>