<Game>
	<Name>Ren & Stimpy Show, The - Veediots! (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The Ren &amp; Stimpy Show: Veediots! is the first SNES video game based on Nickelodeon's Ren and Stimpy franchise. The game presents several different scenarios, like episodes of the show, featuring either Ren or Stimpy as the playable character and the player proceeds through them, occasionally achieving optional objectives and solving minor puzzles.The four episodes include:The Boy Who Cried Rat! - The player assumes the role of Ren, dressed as a mouse, and must move through a suburban house before being swallowed by Stimpy and travelling through his mouth.In the Army - The player once again controls Ren in military uniform as he makes his way across a boot camp.Stimpy's Invention - The player switches to Stimpy and moves through an underground lab, avoiding mad experiments.Marooned - The player sticks with Stimpy for this final chapter as he travels through the organs of a giant alien.The game was released in late 1993 on the Super Nintendo and Game Boy. It was closely followed by the Genesis exclusive Stimpy's Invention. The second SNES Ren &amp; Stimpy game was Fire Dogs, which is also known as The Ren &amp; Stimpy Show Part II: Fire Dogs.Critical ReceptionElectronic Gaming Monthly gave the SNES version of the game review scores of 6,6,4,5 and 6 out of ten. Mike Weigand, who gave one of the higher scores, wrote, "Ren &amp; Stimpy had great expectations, and it lives up to some of them (very good graphics and voice, plus the clever idea of making each section based on a cartoon episode), yet the control could be improved greatly".Cheat: Hear the Whole Theme SongAt the beginning of the game, the theme song plays for awhile and then fades away once the demos begin.  Press L and R to hear the whole song.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6288</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588610-the-ren-and-stimpy-show-veediots</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ren-stimpy-show-veediots</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-ren-stimpy-show-veediots/3030-21622/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/8JSxyRd.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/zZJAgJN.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/shyGQAr.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/l5Pu5Cx.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Tjrna6K.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/OK2bKVy.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/QT4f0SI.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IkIIjBc.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/zbHwDjB.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/eAUUsd1.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/dSiMHBS.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JquKzA2.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/mpS0Nds.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ePI0Sx8.png</clearlogo1>
</game>