<Game>
	<Name>Rex Ronan - Experimental Surgeon (USA) (En,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Rex Ronan: Experimental Surgeon is an edutainment game published by Raya Systems (now Health Hero Network) to highlight the effects of smoking on the human body. Each stage, in which a miniaturized Rex Ronan moves through the body of smoke company sales rep Jake Westboro, features numerous facts about tobacco smoke inhalation.It was developed by Sculptured Software for the Super Nintendo exclusively. Story:A man named Jake Westboro, a Blackburn Tobacco Company sales rep, is on his death bed from smoking since he was 15. His only hope is Rex Ronan: Experimental Surgeon, who shrinks down to near microscopic size to save Jake. Meanwhile the Blackburn Tobacco company sends in microbots to stop Rex, out of fear that if Jake lives, the world will know the terrible dangers of smoking.Gameplay:The game plays out as a 2D side-scroller. Rex has an energy gun of some kind, which he uses to defeat the Blackburn Robots, and clean tar from the lungs of Jake. The gun shoots in 8 directions. He also has a high and normal kick, and jump. There are also flying tunnel levels that break up the side-scrolling stages. While flying Rex has a gun on the ship which he can use to destroy debris in Jake's lungs. Rex also has to avoid moving walls and go through moving holes.As an edutainment title, it also quizzes the player periodically with what are called smart bombs. When Rex touches one a statement about the effects of smoking and tobacco will appear at the top of the screen. If the statement is true and Rex shoots it, the bomb will destroy all enemies on screen. If it's false it explodes and hurts Rex instead.As the player goes through a level they will see plain-colored areas that signify tar, tooth discoloration, and various carcinogens in Jake's body. If Rex shoots this it will increase the player's score and can reveal power-ups. These power-ups include more powerful blasts with the gun, and spray reduction.									</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Educational</genre>
	<Developer>Health Hero Network, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>FStwqqI7tow</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3241</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588612-rex-ronan-experimental-surgeon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/rex-ronan-experimental-surgeon</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rex-ronan-experimental-surgeon/3030-8948/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Et95ixS.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ksSIwKE.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/LqD3Dm9.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/NKILgH9.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/INAA4fg.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/E7xmoBj.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/83Qgh1g.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/0F7VsEn.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Z0jfUa6.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/2a0RbMi.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/LOCXfv4.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QSO55ja.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/oeK8tpd.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/gNj3hvG.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Embark on an incredible mission, but beware! Join Dr. Rex Ronan as he shrinks to perform high-tech laser surgery on Jake Westboro - who suffers from long-term tobacco use. Use Rex’s laser scalpel to vaporize tar, plaque, phlegm, and pre-cancerous cells. Stop a heart attack and remove nicotine addiction before it’s too late! Defend Rex against Microbots implanted to thwart his mission. using the laser scalpel and martial arts moves. Follow the path of smoke and nicotine. Discover the harmful effects of tobacco use. make headlines with Rex and save Jake‘s life!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/efc93d93-09f2-4c13-a4aa-3762e98c45b4.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1a359cf5-4ddb-4db2-a844-abe95a258702.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/108a8f83-2481-4cb1-9125-c5817f88ba7b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/efac407e-076b-44dd-b81e-ba31bd4ace59.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Raya Systems</Publisher>
</game>