<Game>
	<Name>Riddick Bowe Boxing (Japan) (En)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Riddick Bowe Boxing is a boxing game from Malibu Interactive and is licensed by former heavyweight champion Riddick Bowe. It is based heavily on the 1992 Sega Genesis licensed boxing game Evander Holyfield's "Real Deal Boxing and includes many of the same systems as well as the horizontal perspective that shows both boxers, though the title boxer has been changed and the graphics have become more cartoonish and light.It was published on the Super Nintendo in the US by Extreme Entertainment Group and in Japan by Micronet. There was no European release.The game was released in Mexico by American Softworks with the name Chavez, putting Julio Cesar Chavez in the title role instead of Riddick Bowe. Chavez is largely identical to Riddick Bowe Boxing, except for the title screen, main character and being exclusively in Spanish. There was also a Chavez II, which was originally Boxing Legends of the Ring after it had undergone a similar superficial facelift. Cheat: Hidden CharactersIn Career Mode, create a new boxer by selecting the question mark, then enter RIKKY, IIIAN, or FRIEDA as your character name. Select OK, then press Start to skip all customization options. This will turn your character into Riddick Bowe with all stats maxed out... and odd colored skin.Cheat: Play Invincible Characters (Only for the Chavez Version)At the main menu, go to Career Mode, and select a question mark to create a new character. Enter either AXY or SPOT as the character name (which are two different characters). Skip everything else in the character creation by pressing Start. The character with maximum stats and invincibility will be created.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Extreme Entertainment Group, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>CEGxAzxGRq0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5809</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588613-riddick-bowe-boxing</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/riddick-bowe-boxing</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/riddick-bowe-boxing/3030-17218/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/5rdBYN0.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/5gEEfMU.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/g3r2uF7.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/w4YIueu.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Xjh2dWe.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/hlPim3Y.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/z2ODRwh.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ZUyp6aF.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Dc5AVgc.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/EtCCyaP.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/0iMx0bn.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/uRPsK7w.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UdvmzOu.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/UZkRfJj.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Riddick Bowe Boxing is another one of the many boxing games released at the time, but with subtle differences. The HUD contains damage and energy meters along with a miniature ring up the top of the screen, useful to see the player's position in the ring so as not to get backed into a corner real easily. Players can compete in the standard, 1-Player v. CPU, 1-Player v. 2-Player or even a career mode, where there are four preset fighters to choose from along with an option to create customers boxers. The career starts out at position #25 in the ranking and players slowly work up the ladder, going to the gym in between bouts to build up stats to eventually take on "Big Daddy" himself, Riddick Bowe. The game is practically a copy of Evander Holyfield's Real Deal Boxing, save for the graphics style and the included fighters.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9add6ac-56e6-4726-9585-6897bb24085c.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/88b6b03b-d414-4843-9126-462d17687a91.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8d3c6549-896e-4dc5-94ad-807261a3b60d.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Extreme Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>