<Game>
	<Name>Rise of the Phoenix (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Rise of the Phoenix (JP: Kouryuuki) is a strategy simulation game based on the historical Ancient Chinese event the Chu-Han Contention, which occurred between 206-202 BCE. The player can assume the role of either Xiang Yu or Liu Bang. Unlike Koei's other Ancient Chinese-set strategy game, Romance of the Three Kingdoms (which usually begins around 185 CE, during the Yellow Turban Rebellion), Rise of the Phoenix splits the player's turn between "planning" and "action": the former for determining who to ally and where to bulk up defense, while the latter involves moving units around and triggering battles.Rise of the Phoenix originally came out on the NEC PC-9801 in 1993, followed by releases for the Sharp X68000, FM Towns and PC. The following year saw a Super Famicom version, with a US SNES release following in 1995. An enhanced PlayStation version was released in 1998. The game has also seen a few anniversary releases on PC.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Simulation, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>KOEI Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>JfsBfsDwRuM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3242</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588614-rise-of-the-phoenix</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/rise-of-the-phoenix</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rise-of-the-phoenix/3030-28283/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rise_of_the_Phoenix</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Hh2AJKG.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nqFs3MP.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/adGAi6R.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/D3vsEhK.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/L81e7TL.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/VuTj4oa.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/yEWHTtI.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/UAi0MNL.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/9Nr8GDg.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/hj79KK3.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JBF89Z8.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/55TFLQj.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/6pmBG7A.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Nfx4S73.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/67K31rO.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The year's 206 BC and things in China are heating up. The First Emperor has just died and a weak successor has been appointed. Seeing an opportunity for control of the nation, two of China's greatest warriors, Xiang Yu and Liu Bang are locked in a bitter rivalry for control of the nation. With their armies preparing to clash, it is said the victor has been selected by the heavens to rule all of China. Assuming the rule of either great warrior, it's up to you to plot the strategies that will defeat your counterpart and lead the country into the next dynasty. Are you prepared to fulfill the myth now known as Rise of the Phoenix?</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>cXHKrIe6lms</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3b1771f4-8c7b-4a25-b8c2-677aa6c91222.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e93cf39-963a-4356-ae2f-3fccab092583.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e26ca72b-e36f-4a6a-8305-88b7d1e67854.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6d59e0a0-59a0-4970-bcc4-eabcce87703a.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
</game>