<Game>
	<Name>Road Riot 4WD (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The arcade action of ROAD RIOT 4WD has made its way to the Super Nintendo. Now you can hit the track in your favorite heavily armed off-road vehicles and hit the track for intense 4X4 racing like you've never seen before. You'll race on four continents Europe, Africa, Australia, and North America as you try to take the checkered flag and leave your opponents in the dust. Throughout any race, you can clear a path for yourself by any means necessary whether it's by nudging another car off the track or by firing a missile. While in most racing games you're supposed to avoid obstacles, in ROAD RIOT 4WD it pays to hit the obstacles, which can reveal special bonuses and upgrades. And with the two-player split-screen option, you're in for some crazy racing action as you battle a friend for control of the track. So hop in, fire up your engine, and get ready to race with ROAD RIOT 4WD.http://cheats.gamespy.com/super-nes/road-riot-4wd/</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>THQ</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>0.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>5811</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588617-road-riot-4wd</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/road-riot-4wd</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/road-riot-4wd/3030-38678/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ICdi8su.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/i5KP4tW.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/92AFB5H.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/lcopF2M.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/xFCS2Z7.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/efkCnYc.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/kCAIyhC.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/kJLegxa.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/6xpMVwm.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/UTnAxdQ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/cUNKxvA.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/xFOGfnn.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/qKo0obF.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7Spyfs3.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/5ElQBeN.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The meanest road rally ever to hit the World Circuit is here! Road Riot brings all the fun and intensity of 4WD racing and added a few surprises along the way! Muscle your opponent's cars off the shoulder of the road. Do somersaults and spin-outs as you try to master each course. Let the missiles fly as you tell the other drivers, "Outta My Way!!" All of the excitement from the arcade version is now ready to drive you crazy as you set out to rule the racing world! One or Two Player modes take your auto skills to their limits! So buckle up for the driving challenge of a lifetime with Road Riot from THQ!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0279586e-a45e-4eed-ace1-c0601b2e218b.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eea6e6ac-35a2-4ecb-aa26-ac2f3cf9cc15.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d9e57b59-2243-47d5-94e5-e7aee2d9ba15.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6cc8dded-101c-4834-82d0-91362f15f0ef.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>