<Game>
	<Name>RoboCop versus The Terminator (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:RoboCop Versus the Terminator is a licensed action game that hypothetically pits the two eponymous cyborg movie characters against each other, placing RoboCop in the role of the savior of humanity from Skynet and its legion of T-800s and other robots. It is based on a comic book series with the same premise.In the near future, the worlds of RoboCop and The Terminator merge into a single reality. RoboCop is placed in charge with saving mankind by destroying the Skynet super computer and preventing a possible future where machines reign supreme. The player, as RoboCop, must traverse 10 levels of action, fighting against thugs and machines alike, all while utilizing a combination of pistols, laser guns, bazookas and even the deadly ED-209 Gatling gun. The player can destroy Skynet and save the world. The game was released for Sega Genesis, Super Nintendo, Sega Master System, Game Boy, and Game Gear. An NES version was developed but never officially released.The SNES and Genesis versions have slightly different stages and stories, though are similar games in practice. The NES and Game Boy games are similar to the SNES game, while the Sega Master System and Game Gear versions are similar to the Genesis game.Levels (Sega Genesis version)Level 1 - Trainer LevelLevel 2 - Streets of DetroitLevel 3 - Delta City under ConstructionLevel 4 - The Toxic FarmLevel 5 - OCP office ComplexLevel 6 - Terminator OutpostLevel 7 - Underground ComplexLevel 8 - Underground BunkerLevel 9 - The wall to SkynetLevel 10 - SkynetCheat: Level PasswordsEnter the password "FNSH".Cheat: Climb Into The SkyWhile climbing up a ladder, hold X+A. Oddly enough, Robocop will continue climbing past the ladder and into the sky!Cheat: Climb Into The SkyBy exploiting this glitch you can find many shortcuts throughout the stages, especially Skynet Outer Perimeter.Cheat: Strange CreditsAfter you beat the game, during the credits press B to see a strange credits sequence after the normal one is over, such as ''Thanks to Bill Clinton'' ect. Additionally, press B at the "Final Game Score" screen to see a picture of the staff team.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Virgin Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2614</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588620-robocop-versus-the-terminator</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/robocop-versus-the-terminator</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/robocop-versus-the-terminator/3030-12494/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/0GYdcsO.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/UySIXAV.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/tOuEg6v.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ifeAzWp.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/sZ1gSVH.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/TToR7uX.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/zqlgTxb.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/2KnUte0.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/JWjNaNE.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/qnyrdWj.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rb2MTDZ.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/d2gMu4L.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Q4ugJbB.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/aCtgccP.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/H9pLOf6.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Qg59oH6.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/uihdvy1.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>As Robocop--both the unwitting agent of humankind's destruction and its last possible champion--you must travel across time into a savage future ruled by the mechanical forces of Skynet. From war-torn modern Detroit, to the mean streets of Delta City, and on to the bone-strewn bunkers of post-apocalypse L.A., you'll face attack from every angle, every moment. An unwavering army of Terminators, robotic dogs, spiders, Endoskeletons and a relentless arsenal of automated weapons await you in this veritable nightmare on earth. To destroy this enemy, free its hostages and finally pierce the dark heart of a brutal computer will take something more powerful than plasma rifles and laser guns: the human mind that still burns within you.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1fc519ee-2c96-4bfe-a291-944a17def190.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9bbcbcc6-aa1c-496a-8697-b8cb8dbdcefd.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c2eedc2d-24a0-4418-9482-c78abe4a6266.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d589bc5a-3983-41d3-a69e-20e45c3a2064.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b43fce10-68ec-45d2-be2c-7927c8756202.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Virgin Games</Publisher>
</game>