<Game>
	<Name>Rocko's Modern Life - Spunky's Dangerous Day (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Rocko's Modern Life: Spunky's Dangerous Day is a two-dimensional side-scrolling platform game inspired by the Nickelodeon animated TV show Rocko's Modern Life. Rather than a straightforward licensed platformer, the player (as Rocko) is required to solve puzzles in order to keep Spunky, Rocko's dimwitted canine pet, from coming to harm as he seeks a fire hydrant with which to relieve himself.Viacom New Media developed and published the game exclusively for the Super Nintendo in North America. It is so far the only video game based on the license.Gameplay:In Rocko's Modern Life: Spunky's Dangerous Day there are four stages in which Rocko's dog Spunky must be protectd. These stages are: Sand In Your Navel (set at the beach), Trash O Madness (set at the dump), Ice Scream (set in O-Town, a fictional town in the Rocko's Modern Life universe), and Unbalanced Load (set in a laundromat). Each stage consists of four different levels. In every level the objective is to keep Spunky safe from danger: to do so, the player must use Rocko to activate platforms and switches at specific times, feed Spunky certain items and defeat enemies that attempt to harm Rocko and Spunky.Cheat: Play with BoneAt the screen with the Nickleodeon bone press Y + X to make the bone long and thin, or press A + B to make the bone short and fat.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Viacom New Media</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>As9CW1td9s4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5485</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588625-rockos-modern-life-spunkys-dangerous-day</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/rockos-modern-life-spunkys-dangerous-day</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rockos-modern-life-spunkys-dangerous-day/3030-22711/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/d0MrIE3.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/0Lt7hjv.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/8lleBMp.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/WzQyxYX.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qtmRITU.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/20LrXvP.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/fVZPAzt.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ijbwQk8.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Kniv6Lj.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BM1Aimd.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6xkuN5E.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/hegpv0K.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/AvBQYgo.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Y69Itgb.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/t4qjwKw.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Spunky...Spunky...SPUNKY!!! Look out! You've got to help me with Spunky, mate. He's on the loose in O'Town and he's got a knack for getting into trouble. O'Town can be a dangerous place, filled with tons of puzzling pitfalls. Down at Rock-O-Whey Beach, we'll protect Spunky from one-eyed pelicans, crusty crabs and other dangerous sea creatures. True fun in the sun! Steel-jawed, steam-belching contraptions threaten Spunky over at the Hill-O-Stench garbage dump. I hope you're quick minded! Through the neighborhood, we'll follow Spunky from treacherous treehouses to dingy basements, keeping him out of danger. Are you ready to face the Bigheads? Finally, we'll outsmart wild washing machines, tricky lint traps and grungy gripes to rescue Spunky from the depths of Laundryland. Please help Spunky survive the spin cycle! The only rest we'll get is when Spunky lies down here for a nice, quiet...Spunky? Hey Spunky? What in the blazes?!?! SPUNKY!!!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d0ff45c8-63e7-4e09-a94c-8648af19a03d.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b6f37c34-fb50-471e-b476-b0ffd9807e94.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/74a28a69-a640-49a6-af3f-194945080c9e.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/241e2218-d7db-4545-9daa-26a6b102f944.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Viacom</Publisher>
</game>