<Game>
	<Name>Rockman X3 (Japan) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Mega Man X and his trusty partner Zero have a new force to reckon with. Who or what has caused a riot of Mavericks to break out in the experimental utopia known as Doppler Town?Named after the scientist reploid, Doppler Town was supposed to be a place where humans and reploids could live in harmony. After discovering a virus that was turning reploids to Mavericks, Doppler's anti-virus was a big success. But Doppler itself became infected with the virus and assembled a team to take out the Maverick Hunter Units. The Doppler Effect is about to unfold, with Mega Man X and Zero the only cure for the deadly virus!Cheat: Code or Password for Megaman X3All armor parts,all enemy skills,all sub-tanks,all heart tanks,all ride armors and no enhance chip aquire, so you can still have the change to obtain the gold armor in doppler stage.The stage start at where Doppler stage just shown out at the MAP selection screenCheat: Code or Password for Megaman X3Depending on Zero's status in the game, you can have different endings and a different charge on your Buster.Cheat: Cx4 testHold B on controller 2, then turn on the power of the Super Nintendo to view the stats of the game's Cx4 chip.Cheat: Cx4 test1) After defeating the first two mavericks, you will now be able to access Vile's mini stage through the funny looking teleporter in the Volt Catfish, Crush Crawfish, or Blizzard Buffalo stages. Go there. You MUST defeat Vile with either Crush Crawfish's or Neon Tiger's weapon, and then quickly make your way out of the stage before the timer reaches zero. This trick will not work if you do not follow this step.Cheat: Cx4 test2) Complete the rest of the stages. Although it is not required, you should find all of the Upgrades, E-Tanks, Heart Tanks, and Robot Armor pieces. Make it all the way to Doppler Fortress Level 2. If you completed Step 1 correctly, this level should be alot harder now, as the stage will be filled with water and different enemies.Cheat: Cx4 test3) Right before the first sub-boss door, switch to Zero. Go inside, and defeat the bug robot. He's not too difficult...stay toward the center, then when he comes towards you, dash under him, and he should land on the ground behind you, then shoot him. After you defeat the bug robot, it will land on Zero, damaging him badly. At this point, he will give Mega Man his Z-Sabre to use for the rest of the game. Use the Z-Sabre by charging the Y button all the way up to the fifth energy level(green) and then firing.Cheat: Cx4 testNote: For this to work, you need all power-ups BESIDES the chips, and have full health. Go to the First stage of Dr.Doppler's Lab. Near the end, you should see a bunch of spiked balls falling into a pit. Jump and cling onto the left side of the pit and you should slide into a secret room, which contains the upgrade capsule for the golden chip. This chip gives you all the benefits from all the chips, and turns Mega Man's suit into a golden color.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>lUlHBc_t94c</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1016</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588481-mega-man-x3</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-man-x3/3030-16948/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/wlFZ6IM.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/GpdhaiE.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/erq13Vb.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Hkjy1fD.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/j8N139f.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Hvz72TT.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/p3nxigr.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/X2Mz6Tb.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/8cE4K4j.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nv5E9cX.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ZpUnCs3.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/WuZT8Uo.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/6sFa89p.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/dWB4NQ4.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/03HW1We.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/iJfNkMb.png</clearlogo1>
</game>