<Game>
	<Name>Rockman 7 - Shukumei no Taiketsu! (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Mega Man 7 is an Action game, developed and published by Capcom,which was released in Japan in 1995.Cheat: Different Shade Man MusicFor different music for the Shade Man level highlight his level, press and hold the B button, and then select his level. You must not have defeated Shade Man for this to work.Cheat: Different Shade Man MusicFirst, go to ProtoMan's room in CloudMan's stage (right before the outdoor part before the boss, there will be a ladder. Use Rush to get to it). ProtoMan will comment about using weapons to find areas. Then go to ProtoMan's room in TurboMan's stage (this one is at the very top of the area with the traffic light platforms; go through the wall just before you reach the top of the ladder). He will mention something about the Super Adaptor.Cheat: Different Shade Man MusicAfter you go to these two rooms (doesn't matter with order you go to those), go to ShadeMan's stage. Continue like normal until you reach the Pumpkin mini-boss. Shoot the small orange core of the Pumpkin (NOT the eyes on the outside). After you defeat it, it will open a hole on the bottom. Go down until you reach the room with a lone green Sniper Joe. Defeat the Sniper Joe, and instead of going down the ladder, go right through a secret passage and enter the gate you find. If you did everything correctly, ProtoMan will challenge you to a duel.Cheat: Different Shade Man MusicOnce you defeat ProtoMan, he will give you the ProtoShield. This can be used at the same time as the MegaBuster (don't forget to select it), and it will block many enemy shots (like those birds that hatch from the egg; let all of them run into the shield and they will die).Cheat: Different Shade Man MusicEnter the following password: 1415 5585 7823 6251 Then press and hold R &amp; L, and push the start button. After doing so you'll be taken to the [I]Versus Mode[/I] character select screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>el3VjUkffME</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>19068</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588477-mega-man-7</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/uG6g2nl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/GQCft1q.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ZE96Juz.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/0vDK71s.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/bq3ogbF.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/vr5NdKN.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/JA5Q3sM.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/QRbMQu8.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/gtpzRli.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/fqR04Pn.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/FUvTYLR.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/yE6eCX9.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>