<Game>
	<Name>Rockman & Forte (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The last Megaman game in the "true" Megaman series, this actually came after Megaman 8, and leans towards its slightly more realistic style, instead of the much more cartoony look that MM7 had. I mean seriously, compare the way Megaman looked in both games. Honestly, guys.I haven't gotten into this game much, but my roommate has, and he tells me that Astroman is a total bastard. The cool thing about this game is that you can play as either Megaman or as Bass. Both have different characteristics, which makes playing each character a really different experience. Like, Megaman can charge his blaster, and Bass can fire in all (eight) directions. Pretty neat? Damn right it's neat.Translation Description:Aside from a minor graphic, everything is translated and very enjoyable. Fixing this graphic isn't really an issue, it's just that satsu is L-A-Z-Y. So la.Guys, this is the translation you want to go with. Even the elusive CD Database is completely translated. There's even two different patches in the zip, depending on whether you prefer the Japanese or American naming conventions (ie. Rockman vs. Megaman, Blues vs. Protoman, Forte vs. Bass, etc.) Absolutely beautiful.Speaking of different patches, use RMF-E.IPS if you want the Japanese names. Use MMB-E.IPS if you want the American names. Why Capcom always has to change the names I dunno, I always thought Biohazard was a cool name for a video game.Tips:Erase CDs CodeTo erase the CDs that are in your data base highlight Continue on the start screen and press and hold the L, R, Select, and Start buttons until the screen changes and you hear a chime. You can now either choose to erase your CDs by pressing the Y button or choose to keep them by pressing the B button (you'll hear different chimes for each option).Reviewer: Spinner 8http://www.romhacking.net/trans/621/Cheat: Erase CDs CodeTo erase the CDs that are in your data base highlight Continue on the start screen and press and hold the L, R, Select, and Start buttons until the screen changes and you hear a chime. You can now either choose to erase your CDs by pressing the Y button or choose to keep them by pressing the B button (you'll hear different chimes for each option).</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>zb3PwUPMEh8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5813</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/562644-rockman-and-forte</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-man-bass/3030-13218/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/AdPHs3Z.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/cyUq1KF.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/4Bs5EJP.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Pka6PIK.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/mN3YHBo.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/UxWatSW.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/pGhE91r.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/W76kN1v.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/TuLo4Sc.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rhNbY0h.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/FTcSbKd.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/uCuYoCl.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/OnpDuz5.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jNqy3Bg.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/7290emF.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/ofTibi4.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>Join Rockman and Forte's fight for humankind as you face off with the newest menace in town--Robot King. King's captured all of the data plans for Dr. Wily's creations. They will equip King with all the knowledge he needs to build his own indestructible army of robots. As either Rockman or Forte, you'll set out separate adventures using a variety of battle moves and weapons to defeat robot masters. Hidden bolts and CDs give you extra items to assist in battles.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>zb3PwUPMEh8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/02c8a008-96c3-4309-9bff-ef0805361890.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/495b2825-8de4-4de6-8841-9a98838884f8.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a2b3f50d-c3f2-4b6b-a35a-1a7943494e60.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/45dbe46d-bf83-406f-b634-738b05c6065f.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2b3bffff-bd0b-4223-a93a-d6f7f17db24d.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a8d9da31-f2e5-4e73-b688-47e49558d1c5.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/029e9c22-feb6-4176-8ab2-0ccc8f6a38e1.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/77a44385-8af1-45d5-a74e-95cd83296db1.jpg</snapshot15>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>