<Game>
	<Name>Rockman X2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Just when Mega Man X thought he had brought down all the X-Hunters, several months later an uprising moves from within an abandoned factory. While 8 all-new X-Hunters occupy Mega Man X, a triple threat plots to resurrect a secret weapon that is all too familiar!The good Dr. Light supplies Mega man X with incredible new abilities hidden in capsules buried deep below the surface. And with new vehicles like the mobile attack cycle plus powers he gains from the X-Hunters, Mega Man X will be ready to face his destiny as a Maverick Hunter. Now it's all or Zero for Mega Man X!Cheat: Disappearing EnemiesThis will work with almost any enemy that can be frozen with the Crystal Hunter. Freeze the enemy with a normal shot then pause the game. Now at the pause menu select the X. Buster and hit start. The enemy that was frozen will no longer be there.Cheat: Disappearing EnemiesTo do this trick, you must have all of Zero's parts and the Flaming Dragon Punch. First, go to the last Sigma stage. Right before you enter the room where Sigma drops in, stop. Dragon Punch your way in and try to land where Zero will punch his hole after the dialogue. If done correctly, X will fall through the hole when Zero punches it out. When Zero starts talking, do not let his dialogue disappear. Leave it there until X lands in Sigma's room. When Sigma enters, make Zero's dialogue go away and X should be able to walk over to Sigma. Have X stand right by Sigma, and when Sigma begins to fill up his energy meter, Dragon Punch him.Cheat: Disappearing EnemiesWhen the fight begins, Sigma should not be able to harm you no matter what he does, making it easy for you to conserve you SubTanks and energy for the second battle. Also, this glitch makes your charged shots look a vibrant reddish-pink color.Cheat: Disappearing EnemiesIt will stay this way until the second Sigma battle begins. Also, using the Giga Crush causes your X-Buster shots to go back to their original color.Cheat: Kens Shoryuken!Megaman can use Ken's Shoryuken if you get all of the energy tanks, all of the hearts, and all of X's parts. The capsule for the shoryuken is in the third x-hunter stage (Agile). At one point in his stage, there is a ladder with many bats around.  Use the Crystal Hunter to crystalize a bat to reach the ladder. Follow the path until you reach a downward path. Scroll on the left side of the path until X discovers a passage. You must be at full power for the capsule to appear.  Dr. Light will give you Ken's Shoryuken.Cheat: Diagnostics TestTo see the Mega Man X2 diagnostic test, hold the B button on controller 2, then turn on your system. Keep holding until the test appears on screen. Cheat: Diagnostics TestThere are two hidden features in the ending, which are triggered from different variables. The first and most obvious difference is whether or not all of Zero's parts were collected from the X-Hunters; if the player didn't collect them, Zero will be fought and a black copy of Zero will appear in the ''Thanks for playing!!'' screen, but if they were found then Zero will not be a boss and the real one will take the fake's place. Another difference is whether or not the player collected any upgrades from capsules - if Mega Man X has no additional armor, Zero will appear for a moment when the cast roll transitions to the boss list, otherwise he will be missing (hearts and tanks are not factored).</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>nPZdUm3XxSs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1015</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588480-mega-man-x2</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-man-x2/3030-19801/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/2yYb9CB.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9KnLkwD.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/z92gTTE.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/hMia3ro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/y7kjPNV.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/dQzg2mx.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/P321fcE.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/pJsJAMd.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/CqGD5FY.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/af9AXBW.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/GkYTyI1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/RCexCVl.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/uhmnBzD.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/Ifxr5sq.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/eb8j8o6.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/YJgM3rh.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/nRjkGL2.png</clearlogo1>
</game>