<Game>
	<Name>Romance of the Three Kingdoms III - Dragon of Destiny (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Romance of the Three Kingdoms III, or Sangokushi III to give it its Japanese name, is the third game in the Romance of the Three Kingdoms series of historical strategy/simulation games based on the Three Kingdoms era. Specifically, it is based on the 14th century novelization of the events also known as the Romance of the Three Kingdoms, considered one of China's most important pieces of literature.The SNES and PC versions of the game carry the subtitle "Dragon of Destiny". The game was originally released on the PC-9801 in Japan and eventually saw releases on SNES, Genesis and PC in both the US and Asia. The game also came out on the Sega CD and TurboGrafx-CD, but in Japan only.Gameplay:The goal is to select one of several monarchs of the era and attempt to wrest control of the rest of China from the selected monarch's rivals by choosing commands for their generals to follow. The player has many options available to them, including military maneuvers, diplomacy, organizing and acquiring supplies and espionage. Up to eight players can assume the roles of the available rulers, which can vary depending on the historical scenario being played out. There are six scenarios, each separated by a few years - the initial scenario Cheat: Maximize all exchangesWhenever an opponent comes to you and asks to exchange goods (happens more frequently the more powerful you become), submit new terms for the trade. Use the same two types of goods, maximizing the number of goods your opponent will be giving you, and minimizing the amount you will give your opponent. As long as you and your opponent have a decent relationship (you will know right away that you don't if the opponent's original terms were ridiculously unacceptable) your opponent should present a counteroffer that is greatly in your favor!Cheat: Maximize all exchangesMost of the time when you ask for troops from an allied ruler with an adviser present, they'll flat out reject you and never offer a counter offer. However, this is a nice little exploit if you start in a city that doesn't have a lot of population, and you want to conserve the population so it will expand.  First, check around for rulers that don't have advisers. This is important. You can do this through trade agreements or alliance requests, or just simply spying. When you find a ruler that has no adviser (they almost always ask one for advice during a diplomatic venture if one is present in their city), ally yourself with them. Then, select ''Help'' under the diplomacy menu. Input a small number (usually under 3000 to be safe) of troops to request. Send the messenger. The ruler will not accept your request straight out, but will present you with a counter-offer most times. Accept whatever they counter with. This is a nice and easy way to get some extra troops if you're population makes drafting prohibitive.Cheat: No-penalty demotion, moving officers quickly, achieving high loyalty.     If a general or advisor has 100% loyalty, you can demote the officer to a lower rank without lowering his loyalty.  This may be done either because you are strapped for gold or wish to use the character\'s ability for long-term jobs such as spying or cultivation.  Simply "Hide" the officer in any random enemy city, and immediately "Withdraw" him.  The computer will have you assign rank as if he were a newly recruited officer, except he will maintain his 100% loyalty rating.Cheat: No-penalty demotion, moving officers quickly, achieving high loyalty.     The only drawback of this method is that the officers who "Withdraw" from hiding go directly to the home city.  This may be used to your advantage, however.  For example, you are ruling Cao Cao\'s sprawling empire in one of the later scenarios and wish to quickly move several loyal officers from Chang'An to your capital Runan.  Using this method takes 1 month instead of 4-5 months.Cheat: No-penalty demotion, moving officers quickly, achieving high loyalty.     Achieve high initial loyalty in newly recruited and captured officers by shuttling them in groups to a peripheral city which has only one or two neighbors, both of which you should occupy.  Then, fire them all and rehire them in the neighboring city.  For example, suppose you defeat Ma Teng and occupy Tianshui and Xiliang.  To give a quick loyalty boost to Ma Teng\'s former officers, send them to Xiliang and fire them en masse.  Rehire them the same month in Tianshui.  They will frequently have significantly higher loyalty than previously and, if not, this process can be repeated.  </plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>KOEI Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>1qIvRgTzDUc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5816</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588629-romance-of-the-three-kingdoms-iii-dragon-of</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/romance-of-the-three-kingdoms-iii-dragon-of-destiny</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/romance-of-the-three-kingdoms-iii-dragon-of-destin/3030-16347/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/vSNcZ9U.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Y3Z0DHt.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/8S2fPRz.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/sR9OHF1.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/lUolFib.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/H7lhJTh.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ql0cKRy.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/0P9ZIBX.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YbeUCgg.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/YJuIvb1.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/xEpPDCY.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/7VUXDk3.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/yaSKuPn.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/rDJioYc.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/CfN5CDH.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>Romance of the Three Kingdoms III: Dragon of Destiny is another strategy game by Koei. The concept is the same here as in Koei's other wargames: conquer all you can! In this case the historical setting is ancient China. The country is under the control of one Emperor, but all of the faction leaders want to be the emperor themselves. You begin with one territory and you must conquer more to win the game.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/633832f0-d177-4663-b735-1963d78e2414.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/243616bd-5417-4260-a041-d31ae1016ed4.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/337e695d-a125-4a87-90ec-2ad12e5ebf5a.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e7b3815f-8d64-4596-8601-f32ca9ba37f0.png</clearlogo4>
	<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
</game>