<Game>
	<Name>Romance of the Three Kingdoms IV - Wall of Fire (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Romance of the Three Kingdoms IV: Wall of Fire (JP: Sangokushi IV) is the fourth entry in Koei's long-running strategy game franchise based on the historical novel Romance of the Three Kingdoms. The subtitle "Wall of Fire" is a reference to the Battle of Chibi (Battle of Red Cliff) in which a navy commanded by Cao Cao of Wei was destroyed in a successful fire attack. The loss stunted his conquest's momentum and was partially responsible for allowing two other kingdoms, Wu and Shu, to rise to power.Gameplay:As in other entries of the series, Wall of Fire is a turn-based strategy game in which the player takes control of a ruling officer with the ultimate goal of conquering all of China through warfare and diplomacy. Each in-game turn spans a single month, during which time officers under the player's control can be assigned various domestic, diplomatic and militaristic tasks. These tasks rage from overseeing farmland and attempting to court officers to the player's side to drafting and training new soldiers.When going to battle, the player must first organize the troops under the participating officers by assigning specific numbers of soldiers to each officer, as well as assigning a unit type. In battle, each turn lasts a single day, during which each unit under the player's control is granted one movement action and one attack or special action such as taunting the enemy or proposing a duel.Cheat: Easy WinStart any scenario and instead of choosing one ruler to control, choose them all. Now, while playing, use the Threat command on the other rulers and when prompted to "surrender", say yes. Do this on all the other rulers to easily control all the areas and win the game.Cheat: Easy WinSelect the first scenario (Dong Zhuo Triumphs in Luo Yang), then select Cao Cao as your leader. On your very first turn, move some generals and troops to Xu Chang. A few months later, Cao Cao will call a meeting, asking all the other leaders to form an alliance against Dong Zhuo.  If Yuan Shao joins, he will become leader; otherwise, Cao Cao will become leader. This makes defeating Dong Zhuo a bit easier, depending on who joins you (such as Yuan Shao or Ma Teng). Cheat: Easy WinUse the War command and select a general to go into battle. Assign the maximum number of men to his unit. When they asked for confirmation for going to war select the ''No''option. Remove the general from the list of commanders and reassign him to the post. Return to the troop assignment screen. The number of men available should be multiply  by the number that was assigned earlier. Repeat this process to increase the number of men, but don't go back to the main menu. </plot>
	<releasedate>9/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>KOEI Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3246</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588631-romance-of-the-three-kingdoms-iv-wall-of-fire</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/romance-of-the-three-kingdoms-iv-wall-of-fire</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/romance-of-the-three-kingdoms-iv-wall-of-fire/3030-6057/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/S6Nz2yn.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mco7vDF.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ma0saXm.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/VhHqISp.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/M23fE8i.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/bZV9799.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6MDKNVA.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/YaC6kfS.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/cSSHvnx.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/tNbEY2p.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/qaee7E8.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/sUaSuwG.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/gW4OIxF.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/BBa4B7O.gif</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/xGJVky6.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/MmjCFZo.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>It's the Second Han Dynasty and China is on the verge of collapse. Infighting among the court families and the emergence of powerful warlords dominates the landspace. The struggle for power has brought an era known as the Three Kingdoms, complete with constant warfare among China's most courageous and skillful heroes. As a ruler during these difficult times, it's up to you to unify a country torn apart by rebellion. Expand your kingdom by building a strong military or try outsmarting your rivals during negotiations. With exciting new weapons including automatic firing crossbows and catapults, you can engage your opponents out in the open or from behind castle walls. But don't forget, a ruler's strength is also measured by the economic power of his kingdom and the happiness of its people!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d19b87a7-12e3-4e34-9524-b503ac4b9712.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/927fdd54-cd9d-4467-8e60-02d5d31f4ea2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/76090909-493f-40e7-afb4-b8a71007704a.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be588e73-09df-48f5-9d6c-a96c66debbaf.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Koei</Publisher>
</game>