<Game>
	<Name>Run Saber (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>In the year 2998, the brilliant Dr. Bruford is experimenting with genetic structures and radiation. He hopes to create new functions in nature that will remove the pollution from the Earth before it is too late. Unfortunately Dr. Bruford's experiments go wrong and genetic monsters are unleashed upon the world. The only thing that can stop these creatures are Dr. Bruford's previous achievement: Genetically enhanced warriors known as the Run Sabers. Two of the Run Sabers, Sheena and Allen are ready to activate.Run Saber is a side-scrolling platform game similar in gameplay to Strider. Players assume the role of one or both of the Run Saber characters. Choosing either Sheena with her Ice powers or Allen with his Thunder powers, players must defeat mutant monsters. The Run Sabers can move side to side, jump in the air, attack with a sword, climb along walls or roofs, slide across the ground and drop-kick. Additionally, each character has a special move, which damages everything on the screen with either Ice or Lightning, and which can be activated by collecting orb power-ups. Other power-ups include small health, large health, extra life and a larger sword. Players progress through 5 different levels, often encountering powerful boss and miniboss mutant creatures.Cheat: CodesHold B + Y + Right + Select at the Atlus screen. A level selection option will appear on the main menu when the buttons are released.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>ocbnMvUkJ0U</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5486</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588637-run-saber</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/run-saber</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/run-saber/3030-18064/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/YPHyC7z.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/iBhffFg.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/VXtEW6v.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6ToOqbB.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/JLDCosY.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/v5qrLEW.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/sUkNhFD.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/leNhuyL.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/yCegrX1.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6ueIyT7.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2xOf1RP.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/r5ivPJy.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/bamJeeY.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Lefo2M0.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The year is 2998 and the Earth is hopelessly polluted. Mankind's last chance for a clean planet rests in the hands of Dr. Bruford's plan to use radiation to trigger a change. Only, something goes horribly wrong! Dr. Bruford is mutated and begins an evil quest, for world domination! Enter the Run Sabers. Cybernetically advanced humans with the raw power to level cities! As Allen, use the Thunder Sword to create concussive waves of energy! As Sheena, wield the Ice Sword to slam a blizzard at the mad doctor's forces. Team up for non-stop action that is guaranteed to put your skills to the ultimate test in this futuristic adventure saga!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>ocbnMvUkJ0U</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea993adb-ce44-484a-b41a-22341546ccd1.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/044efb6b-af2a-4461-975f-58ce497dfe10.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5423af3c-0b88-485a-b981-0eb7f5570691.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/39556ce0-8398-470e-9f27-4764745a84c1.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2fab9c9c-12a6-4ac8-a4b2-2384798e8ae5.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/db40f246-7cd4-4a10-a655-2243c99c624d.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/df73c41c-6d8c-4b2a-9f86-7b9df55e9343.png</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
</game>