<Game>
	<Name>Ryuuko no Ken (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>South Town is no place for the weak. Yet into this urban battlezone comes Ryo; braving the mean streets in order to rescure his kidnapped sister.With this friend Robert, the two must use all their strength and skills to battle and defeat the toughest fighters ever assembled. These fighters are big, powerful, strong - each possess special skills that will be hard to counter. Ryo must master the Super Attacks if he is to be victorious.Fight hard, fast and furious.Only the strongest of fighters will survive the streets of South Town.Cheat: Ingame CodesWhile playing, press Select to pause the game and press the following buttons:Cheat: Ingame CodesStart a new game, then select the Story Mode. When the game starts, pause and press: Up, X, Left, Y, Down, B, Right, A, L, Y Cheat: How to beat the computer with no damage takenWhen the fight starts, jump towards the CPU and kick him or her in the knees while you are in the air.Cheat: How to beat the computer with no damage takenFor some reason, the computer never blocks when you kick hiim or her in the knees.Cheat: How to beat the computer with no damage takenThis works against any character, and also works on Difficulty 8.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Monolith (Japan)</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>7.1</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>T0enTAYSczs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1571</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588201-art-of-fighting</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/art-of-fighting/3030-2760/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/lEorqJV.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/GYRGd1X.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/PXFSaTp.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/aOLGorE.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/7XAcTGd.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/L0874sr.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/d6SHvRj.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/oH5hdGo.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/4QniVbV.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ZXLQQtn.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JPOgBXV.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/UA8FHCq.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/EHsP4jo.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/dTEgB5m.jpg</fanart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/mqaIX3P.png</clearlogo1>
</game>