<Game>
	<Name>Ryuuki Heidan Danzarb (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ryuuki Heidan Danzarb ("Dragon Squadron: Danzarb" in English, and is also sometimes called Ryuki Heidan Danzalv) is a sci-fi RPG developed by Pandora Box (with additional input from anime giant Gainax) and published by Yutaka for the Super Famicom in Japan only.The game is mission-based, and each mission has different directives. This also means that the player will be expected to perform different activities to successfully conclude the mission. The game's turn-based combat is depicted similarly to Phantasy Star and Dragon Quest: large enemy icons with the player's party's stats displayed underneath.The game was never released outside of Japan, but it did receive a fan translation from Aeon Genesis.		</plot>
	<releasedate>23/4/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Pandora Box</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>23111</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581872-ryuki-heidan-danzalv</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ryuuki-heidan-danzarb/3030-46446/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/vauU2Gl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/etcBuPr.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/hjK8Bq0.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/JfqTAHE.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/JFbNTjV.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/QeVo6hT.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/JaVJ1lR.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/QDDPLRr.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/2DAgiFo.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/R9oWJlm.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/8Jz30O9.jpg</snapshot9>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/j6ovOJP.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/W5xGRBD.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Danzarb is a quirky sci-fi mecha RPG. It´s segmented into chapters or episodes, each having a minigame or puzzle for you to solve. In one, for example, you´re tasked with locating a bunch of ID card segments then you have to do a little sliding puzzle to put them together. In another, you collect clues to a time bomb defuse sequence from enemy soldiers, and you have to piece them together in a logic puzzle to decode the sequence.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8c02f662-ef76-441e-9310-d49c712563a6.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d078265e-5f94-4739-980d-deb5c2a8d858.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Yutaka</Publisher>
</game>