<Game>
	<Name>Sangokushi IV (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Romance of the Three Kingdoms (JP: Sangokushi) is a strategy game based on the Chinese novel of the same name. The player assumes the role of one of the Chinese generals involved in the conflict, attempting to recover land from their two rival kingdoms and unite China under their kingdom's rule. The game was originally released in December 1985 for the NEC PC-88 platform. Koei would go on to port the game to many other systems, as well as create many sequels with iterative improvements.Super Sangokushi is a revamped version of the original Sangokushi for the Super Famicom that was released in 1994. It was not the first Romance of the Three Kingdoms game for the system: it followed the 1991 Sangokushi II SFC release and 1992 Sangokushi III SFC release.Cheat: Easy WinStart any scenario and instead of choosing one ruler to control, choose them all. Now, while playing, use the Threat command on the other rulers and when prompted to "surrender", say yes. Do this on all the other rulers to easily control all the areas and win the game.Cheat: Easy WinSelect the first scenario (Dong Zhuo Triumphs in Luo Yang), then select Cao Cao as your leader. On your very first turn, move some generals and troops to Xu Chang. A few months later, Cao Cao will call a meeting, asking all the other leaders to form an alliance against Dong Zhuo.  If Yuan Shao joins, he will become leader; otherwise, Cao Cao will become leader. This makes defeating Dong Zhuo a bit easier, depending on who joins you (such as Yuan Shao or Ma Teng). Cheat: Easy WinUse the War command and select a general to go into battle. Assign the maximum number of men to his unit. When they asked for confirmation for going to war select the ''No''option. Remove the general from the list of commanders and reassign him to the post. Return to the troop assignment screen. The number of men available should be multiply  by the number that was assigned earlier. Repeat this process to increase the number of men, but don't go back to the main menu. </plot>
	<releasedate>31/12/1985</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Koei</Developer>
	<rating>9.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3246</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588631-romance-of-the-three-kingdoms-iv-wall-of-fire</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/romance-of-the-three-kingdoms/3030-4490/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ut2bB8R.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mco7vDF.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/jpt5RxD.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/GNsWIOx.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/A85OfPo.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Pai8fCp.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/wzcbnaK.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/abALK2G.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/S75GmYa.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/unXEIS6.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/mePk7gz.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/XX53fXI.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/MmjCFZo.png</clearlogo1>
</game>