<Game>
	<Name>Saturday Night Slam Masters (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Saturday Night Slam Masters (known in Japan as Muscle Bomber: The Body Explosion) is a 2.5D wrestling game developed and released by Capcom for Arcade (via the enhanced CPS-1 hardware) on July 13, 1993. The game plays similar to other Arcade wrestling games of the time (taking place in a standard wrestling ring where the player has three-dimensional movement of their characters). However, the game includes original international (and colorful) characters, including Mike Haggar from the Final Fight franchise, wrestling to climb the ranks of the fictional Capcom Wrestling Federation (CWF).All versions of the arcade game featured a Single Match (featuring traditional one-on-one matches) mode. Arcade cabinets that supported four players featured a Team Battle Royale mode (featuring two-on-two elimination matches). An updated version of the Arcade release (titled Muscle Bomber Duo: Ultimate Team Battle in the international version and Muscle Bomber Duo: Heat Up Warriors in the Japanese version) was released on December 1993, removing Single Match mode (focusing on the Team Battle Royale mode) while refining the grappling mechanics, adding new moves (for all characters) and allowing players to select the same character.Saturday Night Slam Masters was ported to the FM Towns Marty (in Japan only) on November 1993, and then ported to the Super Nintendo Entertainment System and the Sega Genesis in 1994. While the SNES version was the only version to include Team Battle Royale mode (thanks to multitap accessories), the Genesis version includes an exclusive Death Match mode, which grants more weapons to use, covers the ropes with barbed wire and proximity explosives (making it impossible to bounce off the ropes, but allows players to damage their opponents by throwing them at the ropes), and lays land mines outside the arena.On September 2, 1994, the game received a sequel, titled Ring of Destruction: Slam Masters II, which refined it to a traditional fighting game.Gameplay:The game controls not unlike a simplified Capcom 2D fighting game, including a single button for attacks, a jump button and a grapple button. Wrestlers can also run against the ropes of the ring, creating a new set of running attacks. Each wrestler featured has one unique special move as well as a finisher they can perform from the grapple once they had depleted their opponents health bar low enough. Once the opponent's health bar is either completely empty, or close to empty, the wrestler can attempt a pin to win or use a submission move to make their opponent quit. Matches can also end with a 20-count ring out.The game features two play modes: Single Match, which featured traditional one-on-one wrestling matches, and Team Battle Royale, which featured two-on-two elimination style matches. In Team Battle Royale, both members of a team have to be pinned or submit for the other team to win. Players could either form a cooperative team, or a single player could have a CPU controlled partner. If playing Team Battle Royale in single player, the match ends in a " No Contest" if the player character is pinned and his CPU controlled partner is not.The game also features the ability to leave the ring. Various weapons can be found that allow a wrestler to greatly damage their opponent. The game features no disqualifications for using weapons.Characters:CharacterBioAlexander "The Grater"Alexander "The Grater" (known in the Japanese version as Sheep the Royal) is an American wrestler (Australian in the Japanese version) and butcher (from Kentucky, U.S.A.).He is based on the real life wrestler Big Van Vader.Biff SlamkovichBiff Slamkovich (known in the Japanese version as Aleksey Zalazof) is a Russian wrestler (from Kiev, Ukraine) and the main protagonist of the series.Also known as "The Rocking Ruskie", he is an apprentice of Mike Haggar, and considers fellow apprentice Gunloc as his rival. He seems to know a famous Russian street fighter.El StingrayEl Stingray (known in the Japanese version as El Stinger) is a Mexican luchador (from Acapulco, Mexico) noted for his speed and high flying acrobatics.He is based on the real life luchador Lizmark.The Great OniThe Great Oni (known in the Japanese version as Mysterious Budo) is a Japanese wrestler (from Osaka, Japan) who dresses in a kabuki-like theme and uses high theatrics in his matches (including the green "Asian mist" attack).He is based on the real life Japanese wrestler Great Kabuki.GunlocGunloc (known in the Japanese version as Lucky Colt) is an American wrestler hailing from "Slam Town", U.S.A.An apprentice of Mike Haggar, he considers fellow apprentice Biff Slamkovich as his rival. He is also rumored to be related to a famous American street fighter.Jumbo "Flap" JackJumbo "Flap" Jack (known in the Japanese version as Kimala the Bouncer) is a Canadian wrestler (from Yellow Knife, Canada) and the right-hand man of The Scorpion.He is unplayable in the Single Match mode in arcades and serves as the penultimate boss.King Rasta "Mon"King Rasta "Mon" (known in the Japanese version as "Missing IQ" Gomes) is an American wrestler (from Venice Beach, California). A wild ape-like man, he is always accompanied by his pet monkey, Freak.Mike HaggarMike "Macho" Haggar is an American wrestler (from New York, U.S.A.) who trained over Biff and Gunloc.The international version of the game takes place after Haggar retired from being the mayor of Metro City (to return to wrestling). The Japanese version of the game takes place prior to Haggar becoming the mayor of Metro City.The ScorpionThe Scorpion (known in the Japanese version as The Astro) is a myserious masked wrestler and the main antagonist of the series.He is unplayable in the Single Match mode in arcades and serves as the game's final boss.Titanic TimTitanic Tim (known in the Japanese version as Titan the Great) is a gigantic English wrestler (from London, England).He was the former tag-team partner of a certain English street fighter.Cheat: Easy Way to get to New YorkStart Single Match and lose. When you continue choose the person who you purposefully lost to and you will go to the next arena. Keep doing this until you face Jumbo Jack. It will not work when you face The Scorpion or Jumbo Jack because they are not selectable on the select character screen.Cheat: Easy Way to get to New YorkWhile fighting, go on the top ropes and press the Pin button. Your character should turn red. Now, you will deal more damage when you attack or slam someone.Cheat: Easy Way to get to New YorkPause the game right as your move lands, doing this will add to the amount of damage it inflicts.Cheat: Easy Way to get to New YorkIn single match get out of ring pick up weapon go in to left or right far side corner while out of the ring push B then Y to throw the weapon in the ring.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/6/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>vjBaLrg-ZH0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3247</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588642-saturday-night-slam-masters</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/saturday-night-slam-masters</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/saturday-night-slam-masters/3030-16684/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/x6IvbVU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/jAkF75H.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/fWfiIhP.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ndSvrUB.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/CkvyqDj.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/xL3jIsI.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/jlVLp7L.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ZViBAJ4.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/vwhlEEx.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/EecGAIr.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/7vaNeSt.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/5sNr8hl.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/jfpWj3n.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QOkmCCS.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Qvc7efo.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>It's Saturday night and the Slam Masters have arrived! Ten of the biggest and beefiest wrestlers ever to step into the ring have gathered for one bone-crushing, back-breaking tournament where there are NO RULES! Step into the ring and get ready for no-holds barred wrestling as you bounce your opponents off the ropes and clothesline the fools! Or dare them to take the fight outside the ring where brawls with tables, chairs and bottles are all part of the action. And just when you think you've got enough muscle, grab a multi-player adapter and try out the four player Battle Royal where only the ultimate Slam Master will survive.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/65bb96aa-bf3b-416b-a799-aeecb69c371f.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd460e15-7d0d-4c22-9d5e-c3a3c058cb3f.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be480912-8828-40a8-9bf7-48838607a3e4.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4b54cdd5-0d87-4cc3-91b4-fb3bdc172599.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5a9a3c2c-4b5e-4bc6-878c-bcadec6260dd.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>