<Game>
	<Name>Seifuku Densetsu Pretty Fighter (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Seifuku Densetsu: Pretty Fighter ("School Uniform Legend: Pretty Fighter") is a fighter for the Super Famicom originally released in 1994. It features an all-female cast of eight fighters, most of which wear a specific uniform and are associated with a specific color. The game contains various salacious references though nothing overtly pornographic.Seifuku Densetsu: Pretty Fighter received an enhanced remake for the Sega Saturn in 1995 called Seifuku Densetsu: Pretty Fighter X which added new characters and features like anime-style animated cutscenes.CharactersThe original SNES Pretty Fighter has eight playable characters. Their surnames each contain a specific color which is also used to represent them.Marin Aoki: A schoolgirl wearing blue ("Ao"). Considered the main character of the series.Kris Shiratori: A pink-haired nurse that fights with doctor's tools. Her associated color is white ("Shira").Jyuri Akasaka (Juri): Marin's close friend who moonlights as an exotic dancer and often has to deal with unruly customers. Her moveset is similar to Marin's. Juri's color is red ("Aka").Keiko Konno (Kei): A police officer who fights with standard cop gear. Her associated color is navy blue ("Kon").Ryouko Kiori (Oryou): A tall college student who loves wearing traditional Japanese clothes. Her associated color is yellow ("Ki").Minami Midorikawa: A student of an expensive private school who considers herself Marin's rival. Has a mop of hair and a green uniform. Her color is green ("Midori").Ai Momoyama: A blonde gymnast who wears knee- and shoulder-pads and fights using aerobics and exercise moves. Her associated color is pink ("Momo").Yawara Yamabuki: A cat-like judo warrior who fights while crouched and is determined to prove herself as the strongest warrior. Her associated color is golden yellow.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Genki</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>6lbEcalCnLs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>28833</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575536-seifuku-densetsu-pretty-fighter</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/seifuku-densetsu-pretty-fighter</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/seifuku-densetsu-pretty-fighter/3030-38793/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/pE3l17N.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/63vZn7i.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/c29FyPh.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/FZ9Ym3X.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/okh4XCk.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/0mvfNrA.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/RFwIPRz.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/1IeftIV.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/J5aOFdL.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nGOpBbX.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/83FZ2FS.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/SmTMcVA.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/d36LLAS.png</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/VQmEhwS.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>8 beautiful fighters must compete against one another to prove that they are indeed the most beautiful warrior in the world. Do you have what it takes to defeat the challenger?</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1586210f-3658-477c-b626-a71bb74a5add.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/367ffff3-43dd-4cdc-8a1e-7f72c646abc7.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Imagineer</Publisher>
</game>