<Game>
	<Name>Seiken Densetsu 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>There is one force in the universe that keeps good and evil in perfect balance. It is called the tree of Mana. But a magic sword has tricked a young warrior into upsetting the balance, spreading evil throughout the land. Thus the warrior must undertake a dangerous journey to find the seeds of the Mana tree which has been hidden for centuries. Only then can perfect harmony be restored. In this incredible adventure, things are not as they seem. It's a world turned upside down that you must help the warrior make right. And the only way to succeed is to solve the Secret of Mana.Cheat: 9th Sword OrbHere is how to get the "Mana Sword" permanently, and without a cheating device!Cheat: 9th Sword OrbFly to the ice country on Flammie and look for a small circular island off the immediate coast (trial and error are best here, but its NOT those little itty bitty ice chunks everywhere). You'll know its the right island if you are in a frozen grove with Neko surrounded by purple crystals (this looks like the same area you may encounter Neko on the way to the Ice Palace to fight Frost Gigas). Cheat: 9th Sword OrbAfter that, Save the Game with Neko.Immediately after, do a soft reset (L + R + Select + Start).Start a New Game, and get to the Mantis Ant fighting as few (i.e. none) Rabites as possible. When you and Elliot take a dive into the pit, wait for him to say "You've got a sword don't you, use it!" WHILE THIS TEXT IS ON THE SCREEN, perform another soft reset. BE SURE TO HOLD THOSE FOUR BUTTONS FOR 5+ SECONDS.  I don't know why those 5+ seconds are required, but they are. When you get back to the title screen, load the game you saved with Neko in the Ice Country. If you did the trick correctly, all three of your characters will be in the pit fighting the Mantis Ant! (If you did it wrong, you'll stare at a blank black screen and the game will freeze) Kill the weak boss (took me one hit...), and collect your "1st" sword orb again. Jema will pull you out and Timmy will call you to the elders house. Rather than risk a crash, call Flammie and high tail it to the nearest Watts location.Cheat: 9th Sword OrbYou now have the most broken weapon in Secret of Mana at your disposal, without needing to cast Mana Magic ever again.Cheat: 9th Sword Orb*Final Note: This trick can be repeated if you wish, but do NOT forge your sword past level 9. The game will glitch and/or crash. You may get your Rusty Sword back, or you may corrupt your save file beyond repair.Cheat: 9th Sword OrbWhenever an enemy character casts an attack spell on you or an ally  use the pygmy hammer / moogle belt    on the  character being attacked ,  do this twice  before the  spell animation ends and if done correctly the character will completly avoid taking any damage.  This trick  is especially useful when you are fighting the Mana beast.Cheat: 9th Sword OrbCheat: 9th Sword OrbMost likely a glitch, but after acquiring Sylphid and the spell Analyzer, any chest you scan will be safe from traps, regardless whether or not the chest had a trap before that. This has only been confirmed to be the case in the English PAL version though.Cheat: 9th Sword OrbIf you want to get back inside the village you were banished from, you must have all 3 characters.  Then walk up to the man blocking the entrance, and rapidly push the SELECT button while holding the UP button against the man.  Eventually you would will push your way through him, and be back into Potos Village.  Note that this trick might not work in escaping from Potos Village, so make sure you have the Flammie Drum before you attempt this.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>SquareSoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>_TVU4al3Apc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1253</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588646-secret-of-mana</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/seiken-densetsu-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/seiken-densetsu-3/3030-1296/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/QoKDxQl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/UC2h7rt.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/DUcbqpH.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/e4aylDH.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/eBaTZo3.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SyjOjbC.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xtQZOKp.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/FYyjUh0.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/5Puw3nC.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/1yXrCAF.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/s1UDLkw.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ElsmCLx.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/zT8XzyC.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/RszFLxW.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/IbqcubW.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/2jyvCL7.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/dRdr1M6.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/z1OqvJ8.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/siXzfUV.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>http://i.imgur.com/CztIVFI.jpg</fanart7>
	<fanart8>http://i.imgur.com/KJpDjfR.jpg</fanart8>
	<fanart9>http://i.imgur.com/FFr8ss0.jpg</fanart9>
	<fanart10>http://i.imgur.com/H0PxdZI.jpg</fanart10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/JuJSjG0.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/0D9dwy2.png</clearlogo1>
</game>