<Game>
	<Name>Seiken Densetsu 3 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Seiken Densetsu 3 is the third game in Square Enix's Mana series, following Final Fantasy Adventure and Secret of Mana. The game was released on September 30, 1995 for the Super Famicom in Japan, but was not released in the west. An unofficial English patch was made available on July 27, 1999.Gameplay:At the start of the game, the player is given the choice of whom he wants to have in his party: one protagonist and two allies, out of six total choosable characters. The story plays out differently depending on whom is in your party. Each character has his and her own set of abilities to use in battle. As the character levels up, you are prompted to invest points in one of the six different stats (strength, agility, vitality, intelligence, spirit, and luck). When the character reaches level 18, he can go to a mana stone in order to advance to another class -- either toward light or dark. The character may again change class upon reaching level 38 -- again, either toward light or dark. Take note however, in order for the second class to be open to the character, a special item is required. These combinations make up for a total of six different classes (seven including the original vanilla class). Each class grants the character bonus statistics and abilities otherwise non-attainable.A class tree showing the six different paths.The iconic ring menuAs said previously, the player must form a party of three. During fights, he can control whomever he wants, while the other characters are AI-controlled (two other players can join the game if they each plug in a controller). Combat happens in real-time. After each attack, the character must wait approximately one second in order to strike at full potential once again. As your strikes connect and damage enemies, your special attack gauge will fill up. Once full, the player has the opportunity to initiate a more powerful special attack. The special attack is determined by which type of class the character occupies. Items and spells can be used by bringing up the " ring menu". When the menu is displayed on screen, combat freezes so the player can safely navigate through it. Once an item is consumed or a spell is cast, combat resumes. When all of the enemies have been defeated, a treasure chest may or may not appear. These chests contain rewards for the player and are sometimes trapped.Seiken Densetsu 3 employs a calendar system which affects gameplay in certain ways. There are seven weekdays -- each represented by an elemental spirit -- that cycle continuously. Each day's effect is as followed:Luna Day - Moon magic is slightly strongerSalamander Day - Fire magic is slightly strongerUndine Day - Water magic is slightly strongerDryad Day - Wood magic is slightly strongerJinn Day - Wind magic is slightly strongerGnome Day - Earth magic is slightly strongerMana Holy Day - All elemental magic is balanced. In addition you can sleep at an inn for free.Complementing the calendar system is a day/night cycle. Enemies vary depending on the time of the day, while shops are closed and others are open (such as the black market).Main CharactersAngelaDuranHawkeyeRieszKevinCharlotteCheat: Faster SpellsWhen you are in a battle and use magic from either your Magician or Cleric (or any other char that takes a long time to do a spell) press the item button and stay on the menu for around 3 sec.  When you go back to the battle, your character will use the magic without the waiting time.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/9/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Square Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>PsfeYYql0mo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5827</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588648-seiken-densetsu-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/seiken-densetsu-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/seiken-densetsu-3/3030-1296/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seiken_Densetsu_3</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/bzwuddp.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OD4aFAs.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ND3Q5FP.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/xDeGZBz.png</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/e4aylDH.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/eBaTZo3.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SyjOjbC.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xtQZOKp.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/FYyjUh0.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/5Puw3nC.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/1yXrCAF.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/s1UDLkw.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ElsmCLx.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/zT8XzyC.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/CTbD40q.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/ASuaVOg.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/CtyyYDr.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/Ud6UWg6.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/4c7aSWv.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/pqr3RNV.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>http://i.imgur.com/hjX8iAA.jpg</fanart7>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/pITF8XY.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ZtxRHxv.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/awoIPbX.png</clearlogo2>
</game>