<Game>
	<Name>Septentrion (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>SOS is an Action game, developed and published by Human Entertainment,which was released in Japan in 1993.Cheat: Sound TestWhile playing, press Start to pause the game. Then, in controller 2, hold Select and press R + L. Now, to hear the sounds, press the buttons below:Cheat: Unlock The EndingsThese are all the possible endings per character. Contrary to what some FAQs say, the endings do not have variations if you rescue certain people. The only person that matters is the hero's loved one. Also, Redwin only has 4 endings instead of 5 (in the USA version at least). This has been confirmed by a script dump of the game.Cheat: Characters Follow You AutomaticallyTo have your rescued passengers follow you automatically, press L or R to make them stand on your spot. Once they do and the arrow turns Red, hold L or R. If done right, the arrow will disappear and the passengers will follow you, even through doors.Cheat: Characters Follow You AutomaticallyAfter beating the game, after the credits are over, wait 10 seconds at the "Fin" screen and press A to see the time you took and the points worth of passengers you rescued.Cheat: Characters Follow You AutomaticallyTo skip your character's long intro, press Select + Start.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/4/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Human Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>pP-mFl1vEgQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5961</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/578932-sos</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sos/3030-13078/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/fh2Ffma.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ijO2PFH.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/wAtoBAs.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/x6mTcd3.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/66TndL8.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RI89fAK.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vNyoUw5.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/TFboIzU.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/c7fLTTF.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ZyA7RJT.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/mLLVjsW.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/XyVnHUU.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/gzpCp68.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/eAsv5GU.png</clearlogo1>
</game>