<Game>
	<Name>Shanghai III (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Shanghai III is a Mahjong Solitaire tile game puzzle originally released in the Arcade in 1993, and later saw a Super Famicom port in 1994. The goal is to remove accessible tiles (those that have one of its sides free) from the grid in pairs, and to remove them all before the time limit expires.The game features twelve different tile formations, each of which represents a different animal on the Chinese zodiac: Dog, pig, rat, cow, tiger, rooster, hare, monkey, ram, horse, snake and dragon. Each presents their own difficulties with how their tiles are spread out. Players can also configure the game's settings to allow for more/less time, or more/fewer hints that will highlight possible tile pairs.Neither the Arcade game nor the Super Famicom adaptation were released outside of Japan.		</plot>
	<releasedate>15/9/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Kuusou Kagaku</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571127-shanghai-iii</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shanghai-iii/3030-49786/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/3fNCGA8.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/jT77zU1.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/QqUqqdM.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/d5W2ndD.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/RFUmbwb.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/DtZWw67.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Uj1yfwT.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/6BgDey6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/G4jbhKk.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Vre5sXX.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/S94tzal.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/WFd9LBF.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Shanghai III is a Mahjong Solitaire tile game puzzle originally released in the Arcade in 1993, and later saw a Super Famicom port in 1994. The goal is to remove accessible tiles (those that have one of its sides free) from the grid in pairs, and to remove them all before the time limit expires. The game features twelve different tile formations, each of which represents a different animal on the Chinese zodiac: Dog, pig, rat, cow, tiger, rooster, hare, monkey, ram, horse, snake and dragon. Each presents their own difficulties with how their tiles are spread out. Players can also configure the game's settings to allow for more/less time, or more/fewer hints that will highlight possible tile pairs. Neither the Arcade game nor the Super Famicom adaptation were released outside of Japan.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d4b1de63-24b4-4cad-941a-6fb0ca7679bd.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/86fc7403-b5ce-448e-ad24-6c04d0752923.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Sunsoft</Publisher>
</game>