<Game>
	<Name>Shaq-Fu (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Shaq Fu is a 2D fighting game developed by Delphine and published by EA for the Sega Genesis and Super Nintendo Entertainment System in 1994.The game follows professional basketball player Shaquille "Shaq" O'Neal, who must use the deadly arts of Shaqido in a mystical alternate dimension to rescue a mysterious boy from an army of servants loyal to an evil, powerful mummy known as Sett-Ra. He must be quick, so he can go back to a charity basketball game in downtown Tokyo!Despite the game's smooth animation and crisp graphics, the game was widely panned for its difficult controls, inconsistent hit detection, and silly concept. The SNES version was also known for having less features than its Genesis counterpart (including five less playable fighters and three less stages).It was ported to the Amiga (in Europe only, developed by The Dome and published by Ocean), Sega Game Gear (developed by Tiertex and published by EA), and Game Boy (developed by Unexpected Development and published by Black Pearl) a year later. Ocean was also the sole publisher of the SNES version in Europe.Characters:For details on the characters, see the guide.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>1.2</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>0--ovckCloY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3258</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588653-shaq-fu</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/shaq-fu</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shaq-fu/3030-4855/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/BtUX6GU.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Aftc3Qz.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/61ySpJe.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/LyiSmpG.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/MwNHQq2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/HvEsrIT.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ZJQD4T8.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/5q2YUDF.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/bKwW3so.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/2celDfr.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/uFycX2D.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/lCAtSdO.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/SqBQBhM.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/IwdjsBS.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WHmhgJu.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/FNkfxeE.png</clearlogo1>
</game>