<Game>
	<Name>Shin Megami Tensei if... (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Shin Megami Tensei: if... is a spin-off of the Shin Megami Tensei series that was originally released by Atlus for the Super Famicom in 1994 and later remade for the PlayStation. The game's high school setting, story, and elements of its gameplay such as the use of guardian spirits that affect the player's stats would go on to mark the game as an early precursor to the Persona series. An English fan translation for the Super Famicom version of SMT: if... is currently being worked on by Aeon Genesis, who also created translation patches for the Shin Megami Tensei I and II.TitleThe title screenThe subtitle if... has invited comparisons to the 1968 British film If...., a movie starring a young Malcolm McDowell. Like the Shin Megami Tensei game, the film's primary setting is a school; in this case, an all-boys private boarding school. However, rather than face demons or anything else supernatural, the primary antagonist of McDowell's character is the school itself; the film's climax sees him and his allies take up arms and mount a violent rebellion against the school's established elite.Though coincidences to compare the game and film are present, the title in actuality refers to the notion of the game's plot as a "what if" scenario, as implied in the various questions posited in the games opening and closing scenes ("What if... the school were thrown into a different reality?" etc.).Manga AdaptationThe game also received a manga adaptation by Kazuaki Yanagisawa in the magazine Famicomi that ran from 1994 to 1995 and was subsequently released as a single volume. The manga received a sequel entitled Shin Megami Tensei: Khan that spanned nine volumes. The sequel was translated and published in North America by Tokyopop.Story:Hazama, the antagonistThe primary character in Shin Megami Tensei: if... is a high school student at Karukozaka High School. The protagonist's name and gender are selected by the player at the game's start. As the game begins, the high school and everyone inside it are pulled into a demonic realm, and the school becomes linked with five different worlds based on five of the seven deadly sins. One of the other students, a boy named Hazama, takes credit for the event and asserts himself as the new ruler of the demonic realm. The protagonist must work with other students as well as demons in order to stop Hazama and escape the demon realm.At the beginning of if..., the player character much partner with one of the other students in the school. This choice determines certain storyline events and ultimately the ending that the player will receive.Connections to PersonaThe female protagonist later appears in both the original Persona and in the Persona 2 duology with the name Tamaki Uchida.Gameplay:Fighting a Pixie, a traditional SMT demonShin Megami Tensei: if... is, like earlier entries in the Shin Megami Tensei series, a party-based role-playing game in which exploration takes place from a first-person perspective. Battles are triggered through random encounters and are fought by selecting commands in a turn-based menu format. The player's party is comprised of fellow students as well as demons acquired through demon negotiation and fusion. The game also features a lunar cycle system as seen in other Megami Tensei titles. The phase of the moon changes gradually as the player explores the world, and the current phase affects the aggressiveness of demons and how willing they are to negotiate.A unique aspect of the game is triggered should the main character die. Upon dying, the protagonist will receive a guardian spirit that will alter the player's stats upon leveling up. The nature of this stat growth is affected by the type of enemy that was fought when the main character died, and it is possible for the character's stats to be affected negatively as a result.New FeaturesShin Megami Tensei: if... is the first game in the series to feature the spell Megidola, an "Almighty" spell that is unaffected by the standard elemental affinities. It is also the first game in the series to feature the -dyne level of magic, with spells such as Agidyne becoming the most powerful spells of their respective elements.DungeonsAs previously stated, each of the dungeons linked to Karukozaka High School are based on five of the seven deadly sins, though six in total are represented. Hazama believes that these sins represent the flaws he sees in the students of the school. In the order in which the dungeons are visited, they are:PrideGluttonySlothEnvy/Wrath (The sin represented is dependent on the protagonist's human partner.)GreedThe remaining sin, Lust, is not represented by a dungeon. However, the events of the game transpire after Hazama is rejected by the school nurse, Miss Kayama. Notably, Kayama is the only character that is never endangered by the goings on in the school, and the party is freely allowed to return to her to have their health restored. If the player is playing through the game with Reiko as his or her partner, the true final dungeon of the game is Hazama's mind.Demonic CompendiumSeraph (L-L)Michael (73)Gabriel (68)Raphael (60)Uriel (51)Ophanim (46)Raguel (40)Tzaphkiel (35)Haniel (30)Remiel (29)Amatsu (L-L)Amaterasu (72)Tsukuyomi (62)Take-Mikazuchi (58)Hinokagutsuchi (49)Omoikane (41)Tajikarao (34)Ame no Torifune (30)Avian (L-L)Garuda (65)Zhu Que (47)Yatagarasu (44)Phoenix (37)Jatayu (32)Feng Huang (21)Suparna (16)Megami (L-N)Norn (61)Lakshmi (55)Parvati (50)Freya (43)Hathor (38)Arianrhod (35)Ame no Uzume (27)Deity (L-N)Ardha (85)Vairocana (81)Kalki (76)Baal (71)Odin (67)Horus (64)Thor (60)Indra (57)Belobog (45)Thoth (42)Avatar (L-N)Barong (56)Xuan Wu (48)Anubis (45)Narasimha (42)Sphinx (38)Sobek (25)Holy (L-N)Baihu (47)Pabilsag (40)Bastet (34)Apis (25)Unicorn (19)Heqet (17)Prime (L-N)Salamander (28)Undine (26)Sylph (24)Gnome (22)Flaemis (13)Aquans (12)Aeros (11)Erthys (10)Fury (L-C)Shiva (72)Susano-o (66)Indrajit (59)Wu Kong (53)Chernobog (46)Ares (33)Dragon (L-C)Ananta (69)Rahab (63)Itzamna (58)Qing Long (48)Quetzalcoatl (45)Baek Yong (41)Maya (39)Lady (L-C)Kali (74)Ishtar (70)Durga (59)Kikuri-hime (39)Taweret (25)Vesta (18)Kunitsu (L-C)Arahabaki (66)Take-Minakata (54)Oonamuchi (52)Kotoshironushi (44)Sarutahiko (43)Hitokotonushi (36)Sukuna Hikona (31)Ooyamatsumi (23)Divine (N-L)Dominion (52)Virtue (42)Power (36)Principality (31)Archangel (24)Angel (14)Holy Ghost (9)Flight (N-L)Morrigan (42)Macha (37)Nemhain (32)Aello (28)Celaeno (22)Ocypete (18)Bennu (9)Snake (N-N)Yamata no Orochi (59)Vritra (51)Raja Naga (44)Otohime (38)Mizuchi (34)Naga (25)Nozuchi (23)Yoma (N-N)Hanuman (60)Ganesha (57)Ifrit (50)Loa (47)Tengu (41)Jinn (36)Haokah (31)Isora (25)Apsaras (19)Kinnari (12)Beast (N-N)Griffon (50)Cerberus (43)Gdon (39)Selket (30)Orthrus (26)Nekomata (20)Cu Sith (14)Cait Sith (11)Night (N-N)Nyx (51)Vampire (45)Succubus (32)Incubus (27)Lilim (22)Nightmare (19)Empusa (15)Alp (10)Cyak (5)Jirae (N-N)Muspell (53)Titan (41)Ubelluris (35)Tsuchigumo (27)Dwarf (18)Buccaboo (15)Sudama (11)Kobold (6)Knocker (4)Fairy (N-N)Titania (54)Oberon (48)Cu Chulainn (43)Troll (38)Kelpie (29)Banshee (23)Elf (16)Pyro Jack (13)Jack Frost (12)Goblin (8)Pixie (3)Willy (2)Fallen (N-C)Samael (61)Agares (55)Gaap (49)Berith (44)Decarabia (39)Forneus (35)Baphomet (30)Eligor (24)Buer (21)Caim (17)Gagyson (12)Ukobach (7)Brute (N-C)Yaksa (46)Shutendouji (40)Yaksini (33)Turdak (28)Hannya (24)Azumi (16)Bogle (13)Ihika (8)Femme (N-C)Rangda (59)Volvo (56)Dakini (45)Gorgon (40)Cailleach Beara (37)Arachne (33)Lamia (29)Yomotsu Shikome (21)Hag (15)Vile (D-L)Cthulhu (78)Pazuzu (62)Nyarlathotep (55)Tezcatlipoca (45)Mishaguji (44)Nalagiri (39)Raptor (D-L)Hresvelgr (47)Anzu (34)Gurr (25)Furiae (17)Fu Xi (8)ChonChon (5)Jaki (D-N)Hecatoncheir (64)Girimehkala (53)Ekimmu (46)Cyclops (37)Rakshasa (33)Ogre (25)Orc (9)Gremlin (5)Wilder (D-N)Behemoth (62)Manticore (51)Scylla (43)Black Widow (30)Gyuuki (27)Nue (20)Bicorn (14)Garm (11)Wood (D-N)Yggdrasil (35)Alraune (28)Mandrake (18)Fukuchuuka (?) (7)Shiki (D-N)Corpse (26)Zombie Teacher (9)Zombie Girl (6)Zombie Boy (4)Zombie Dog (1)Tyrant (D-C)Lucifer (99)Angra Mainyu (82)Mara (76)Aka Manah (67)Astaroth (65)Loki (61)Hecate (60)Drake (D-C)Tiamat (70)Azhi Dahaka (65)Nidhoggr (57)Basilisk (48)Tarasque (38)Wyvern (32)Cockatrice (24)Fukuchuumushi (?) (16)Haunt (D-C)Vetala (41)Yaka (31)Maneater (27)Ghoula (17)Ghoul (13)Preta (4)Spirit (D-C)Legion (34)Kuchisake-onna (13)Hanako (7)Ghost (3)Poltergeist (2)Foul (D-C)Old One (49)Doppleganger (36)Black Ooze (26)Chris the Car (16)Jack Ripper (10)Slime (8) English TranslationCurrently there is no English version available, but there is a translation in progress on Aeon Genesis. According to the website, it is 80% done.					</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>21146</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581300-shin-megami-tensei-if</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/shin-megami-tensei-if</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shin-megami-tensei-if/3030-5754/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ub3MFs7.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/HIACVFd.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/u4fSF6d.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/N3grlFi.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/2AhqljK.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/3ntzwWp.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/nWo9ZvP.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/lJBvAYG.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/BpuJ8MS.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/KDr3uAY.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/H4sa3AX.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/wooiqQg.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vl1uiU2.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/rvDUKQ0.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/9h2USPg.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/DrptCeo.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In Shin Megami Tensei: if... the story is about Hazama, a poor and abused boy who goes to Karukozaka High School. In order to get vengeance on his peers he performs a ceremony in the gym (most likely referencing the original Megami Tensei) that transports his high school into Makai, the netherworld, where he has somehow become powerful enough to become Majin-Nou (Demon God Emperor). Back at the school, everyone freaks out and is scared except for a select few.The player assumes the role a nameless male or female student, who armed themselves with defensive equipment and COMP. They investigate the realms of Makai which are based on 5 of the 7 deadly sins, and finally face off against Hazama. In their quest, the player will be accompanied by fellow students and demons recruited through either negotiation or from the process of fusion, or via the Jakyou.There are four possible paths in the game, but unlike the previous games, they are not decided by the alignment system. Instead, right in the beginning of the game the player must choose one of the four main characters as a companion to investigate the misterious events and the Makai. Each main character has a defined path and once one has been chosen, the player is locked on that path. Yumi, Reiko and Charlie visit the worlds based off the deadly sins (Yumi and Reiko visit the same worlds, Charlie visits a few different ones), while Akira puts the player in an entirely different setting. Akira's path is much more difficult and, instead of being segmented among worlds, is composed by just one huge tower very similar to Persona 3's Tartarus. This path focuses much more heavily on the 'Dungeon Crawler' aspect of the game.Each of the worlds raise a few philosophical questions about the nature and consequences of the deadly sins, but the game presents these conflicts in a non-theological manner.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9e2dd954-d8fe-4f06-8c68-c416990547f2.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/44f3d841-8f9e-404b-8531-131fb764d633.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
</game>