<Game>
	<Name>Shin Nekketsu Kouha - Kunio-tachi no Banka (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Well, what can I say about this game? Well, for starters, it's the sequel to classic(!?) NES game, Renegade. Now, before you start running, let me say that it's waaaaaaaaaay cooler. For starters, the plot line is a lot more involved, there's no doors that take you back to the beginning of the game, and there's profanities all over the place. Yeah, I thought that would get your attention.The game is kind of like West Side Story (or Deuce's Wild for the uncultured) meets Double Dragon.You play through the game as the "protectors" of two Japanese High Schools  Riki and Kunio (and eventually two other folks), and they've been thrown in jail for something they haven't done. Naturally, you have to break out of your cell, and you of course do this by beating the piss out of everyone that isn't you. You spend the rest of the game beating the answers to why you've been framed out of all the hoodlums you encounter. Add a motorcycle chase towards the end into the equation, and that's the gist of the game.The game play is straight-forward (it has nothing that hasn't been done before in the first Double Dragon game), but it's still fun nonetheless.Translation Description:What's to say? This is the work of Gideon, and it should go without saying that everything is translated with no errors or glitches that I encountered. The language of the script is a little coarse, but given that it's a Kunio game, it's probably coarse in the Japanese version as well. Anyhow, another job well-done by Gideon.Tips:Password CracksThe passwords in Kunio Tachi no Banka consist of Four digits. The first and third digits is the game's stage.  Here's the a list of all the passwords for each level. The second digit is used for the Bike Stages. In order to go to a Bike Stage, the first and third digit must be 0s, while the second digit must be one of the following numbers. The fourth and final digit is to determine the difficulty level. Even Numbers are for Normal Mode (0, 2, 4, 6, 8), while Odd Numbers (1, 3, 5, 7, 9) are for Easy Mode. This is quite meaningless if you try to go to any scene beyond the first conversation with Sabu, as the game will always be in Normal.1X0X 00-Reset2X0X 01-Beginning of the game3X0X 02-Entrance to Cell4X0X 03-Vs. Gouji5X0X 04-Cell 16X0X 05-Hiroshi visits7X0X 06-Cell 28X0X 07-Escape9X0X 08-Vs. Cops0X1X 09-Title Screen1X1X 10-Vs. Takayama2X1X 11-Entrance to Nekketsu3X1X 12-Swimming Pool4X1X 13-Nekketsu High School, 1F-3F5X1X 14-Vs. Taiki6X1X 15-Entrance to Hanazono7X1X 16-Hanazono High School, 1-3F8X1X 17-Roof of Hanazono9X1X 18-Vs. Ryuuta0X2X 19-From Hanazono to Amusement Park1X2X 20-Amusement Park 12X2X 21-Caraban3X2X 22-Park 24X2X 23-Jet Coaster5X2X 24-Park 36X2X 25-Cart Tracks7X2X 26-Vs. Shinji8X2X 27-Bike Cinema9X2X 28-Docks0X3X 29-Warehouse1X3X 30-Warehouse 22X3X 31-Warehouse 33X3X 32-Vs. Shinji, Round 24X3X 33-Conversation5X3X 34-Docks6X3X 35-Bike Cinema7X3X 36-Vs. Joe and Lisa8X3X 37-Conversation9X3X 38-Vs. Kinji0X4X 39-Pub Exit1X4X 40-Pachinko Parlor2X4X 41-Vs. Hitmen3X4X 42-Inside Parlor4X4X 43-Vs. Misuzu5X4X 44-Inside Parlor 2F6X4X 45-Conversation with Sabu7X4X 46-Outside Parlor, Bike Cinema8X4X 47-Bridge, Lake2X5X 48-Cave3X5X 49-Villa Entrance4X5X 50-Inside Villa5X5X 51-Basement6X5X 52-Inside Villa 27X5X 53-Vs. Misuzu, Round 28X5X 54-Inside Villa 39X5X 55-Conversation between Ken &amp; Sabu0X6X 56-Vs. Ken1X6X 57-Vs. Sabu2X6X 58-Ending050X 59-Bike Stage, Park to Warehouse060X 60-Bike Stage, Warehouse to Pub070X 61-Bike Stage, Pub to Pachinko Parlor080X 62-Bike Stage, Pachinko Parlor To BridgeReviewer: wraithhttp://www.romhacking.net/trans/598/Cheat: Password CracksThe passwords in Kunio Tachi no Banka consist of Four digits. The first and third digits is the game's stage. Here's the a list of all the passwords for each level.  The second digit is used for the Bike Stages. In order to go to a Bike Stage, the first and third digit must be 0s, while the second digit must be one of the following numbers.  The fourth and final digit is to determine the difficulty level. Even Numbers are for Normal Mode (0,2,4,6,8), while Odd Numbers (1,3,5,7,9) are for Easy Mode. This is quite meaningless if you try to go to any scene beyond the first conversation with Sabu, as the game will always be in Normal.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Beat-Em-Up, Side-Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Almanic Corp.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>7.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>Jeq6njUalyo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>23216</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/578854-shin-nekketsu-kouha-kunio-tachi-no-banka</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/shin-nekketsu-kouha-kunio-kun-kunio-tachi-no-banka</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/uz6rfPY.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/dEJiD0R.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/wZjOl8Z.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/D3py3mY.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/QEp9Pxf.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/jyinP72.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/VFSHnFp.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SmcDqJi.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/jdKDuuW.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/t6s80QZ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/fc8HbNf.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/5sLhTUM.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QhAttRp.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/kKOCXU6.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/8J7MX3B.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Kunio and Riki are convicted of a hit and run accident and the two are sentenced to be locked away in the West Nerima Juvenile Correction Facility. However, the two young men pledge innocent of the crimes. The next morning, the duo are visited by Kunio's friend Hiroshi, who informs them that a series of suspicious activities have been occurring in Nekketsu High School and that a man who looks like Kunio has been spotted in town. Suspecting that they may have been framed for a crime they didn't commit, Kunio and Riki set up an escape plan to meet up with Hiroshi. After a successful breakout, Kunio and Riki set out to find the true culprits.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>2pN1krUCiXc</VideoURL1>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0f708ac-d9da-468a-9c08-00239064d6bc.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7f1b910a-d354-411c-ba62-492e4b6bd8aa.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ef2cdcbe-29bc-4592-84e8-8abfcd420b9a.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cf450b3c-f595-466c-a604-a61eefaed444.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6687bd42-de79-4c57-bcc1-78d28d3fbabb.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb64a3f1-db03-4e0e-b8f8-12d036cef5ca.png</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Technos Japan</Publisher>
</game>