<Game>
	<Name>Shodan Morita Shougi (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Shodan Morita Shogi ("Morita's First-Rank Shogi") is a shogi game that is intended for advanced players. Shodan, or beginner/first rank, is the first level of mastery (or "dan") at the game which an advanced player reaches once they pass through the student (or "kyu") ranks. Kazuro Morita is credited as the developer of the shogi software, and so the game is named after him. His name was previously attached to a NES shogi game from the same developers named simply Morita Shogi.Because Shodan Morita Shogi is meant to be a serious shogi simulator, it doesn't have the anime portraits or colorful presentation of some of its intro-level-friendly peers. Like almost all shogi games, it was never released outside of Japan.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/8/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Party</genre>
	<Developer>Seta Corporation</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570818-shodan-morita-shogi</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shodan-morita-shogi/3030-43930/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/wMaQFUF.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/F11tpZO.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/JNB5PkH.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/z9ViIXX.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/DjWtiRW.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/PlZAA3L.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/M6pH93W.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/0QHqj1g.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MeD3Yrk.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/LlYW4S5.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Notes>Shodan Morita Shogi ("Morita's First-Rank Shogi") is a shogi game that is intended for advanced players. Shodan, or beginner/first rank, is the first level of mastery (or "dan") at the game which an advanced player reaches once they pass through the student (or "kyu") ranks. Kazuro Morita is credited as the developer of the shogi software, and so the game is named after him. His name was previously attached to a NES shogi game from the same developers named simply Morita Shogi. Because Shodan Morita Shogi is meant to be a serious shogi simulator, it doesn't have the anime portraits or colorful presentation of some of its intro-level-friendly peers. Like almost all shogi games, it was never released outside of Japan.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ff2651ec-e0a9-4b85-b2f7-6f12a72fd09f.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d3310dc8-6787-4f64-b010-018db5287a74.png</snapshot10>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2e7afab0-deb9-4cea-aba7-9188f828f974.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>SETA</Publisher>
</game>