<Game>
	<Name>Shooter (USA) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>Shooter, a Super Nintendo horizontal space shooter, never actually made it into production but rather served as an in-house tech demo for Punk Development to test scrolling backgrounds.&amp;#x0D;The game demo boots up to a Punk Development logo screen before heading straight into the action. Player One controls the red spaceship, Player Two, the blue. Both ships can fire with the B button and move up, down, left, or right around the strikingly phallic-looking space scenery. The game can also be paused with the Start button (although the starry background will continue to scroll). A few generic-looking space pods parade around as well as what can only be described as giant grasshoppers (spacehoppers?). Crashing into any one of these floating pieces of space debris will cause the player&#8217;s ship to explode. Never fear, after going down in flames, a replacement ship will appear.&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0D;Overall, this demo is very basic. A constant, low humming noise makes up the game&#8217;s entire audio ambiance, unless if you count the single sound effect that plays during the opening. The scrolling level loops infinitely.</plot>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Punk Development</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Co-Op</nplayers>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/SyjZzUY.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/0DYwI8p.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/GPR4J4F.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/p8HwRyr.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RFxF00g.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/JK4GzaD.png</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Shooter, a Super Nintendo horizontal space shooter, never actually made it into production but rather served as an in-house tech demo for Punk Development to test scrolling backgrounds. The game demo boots up to a Punk Development logo screen before heading straight into the action. Player One controls the red spaceship, Player Two, the blue. Both ships can fire with the B button and move up, down, left, or right around the strikingly phallic-looking space scenery. The game can also be paused with the Start button (although the starry background will continue to scroll). A few generic-looking space pods parade around as well as what can only be described as giant grasshoppers (spacehoppers?). Crashing into any one of these floating pieces of space debris will cause the player’s ship to explode. Never fear, after going down in flames, a replacement ship will appear. Overall, this demo is very basic. A constant, low humming noise makes up the game’s entire audio ambiance, unless if you count the single sound effect that plays during the opening. The scrolling level loops infinitely.</Notes>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99d0a106-e75d-4cf8-abd0-da5228b89e71.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/149bd102-993b-4053-a414-05ea724b9cfb.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b5517ec2-5f78-4870-801e-3430a386e1ab.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/08a98e07-f617-42fc-9340-752032d5eda4.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/883b81ae-16f9-4586-a092-1c29c8209469.png</snapshot10>
</game>