<Game>
	<Name>Shounen Ashibe - Goma-chan no Yuuenchi Daibouken (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Shounen Ashibe: Goma-chan no Yuuenchi Daibouken (lit: "Boy Ashibe: Goma-chan's Great Amusement Park Adventure") is a Super Famicom platformer from Nova Co. and Takara. The player alternates between controlling the human Ashibe, as he escorts his friends across a world map while talking to NPCs and following the game's story, and the seal Goma-chan in 2D platformer stages where he must track down eight items by investigating his surroundings thoroughly. While Goma-chan can't be hurt by enemies, colliding with them causes him to lose one of the eight items he's already found - as the stages have a strict time limit, it's best to avoid this situation whenever possible.Shounen Ashibe was originally a Shounen Jump serialized manga before becoming an anime TV series in 1991, a year before this game was released.Cheat: PasswordsAt the title screen choose the second selection and enter the following chain.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Nova Games Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>24816</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/580897-shounen-ashibe</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shounen-ashibe-goma-chan-no-yuuenchi-daibouken/3030-34458/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/u8lt0Xd.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mTALakr.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/0sdUtCQ.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/KWiREIL.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/s96x9UM.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/05A690u.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/eAMyosa.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/GggVgWj.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/4pwVlPq.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/i2jzAjp.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/bPem1YH.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/EZA9jMr.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/8tVCEVV.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Shounen Ashibe: Goma-chan no Yuuenchi Daibouken (lit: "Boy Ashibe: Goma-chan's Great Amusement Park Adventure") is a Super Famicom platformer from Nova Co. and Takara. The player alternates between controlling the human Ashibe, as he escorts his friends across a world map while talking to NPCs and following the game's story, and the seal Goma-chan in 2D platformer stages where he must track down eight items by investigating his surroundings thoroughly. While Goma-chan can't be hurt by enemies, colliding with them causes him to lose one of the eight items he's already found - as the stages have a strict time limit, it's best to avoid this situation whenever possible. Shounen Ashibe was originally a Shounen Jump serialized manga before becoming an anime TV series in 1991, a year before this game was released.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/460da1c9-d1df-4944-a7b5-22ba92ab70e7.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aaf65ffd-72d1-4ea1-b509-4778eb8e1124.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Takara</Publisher>
</game>