<Game>
	<Name>Silva Saga II - The Legend of Light and Darkness (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Silva Saga II: The Legend of Light and Darkness is a turn-based RPG from SETA Corporation and the sequel to their Famicom RPG Silva Saga, which in turn was a sequel to their earlier Minelvaton Saga also for Famicom. The three games constitute a trilogy set in the same world (Minelvaton), and each successive game has allowed the player to revisit the same locations. Silva Saga II starts just before Silva Saga concluded, following the adventures of an amnesiac swordsman who sets out to rescue the first game's protagonist Kyral from the villainous Zolde.Silva Saga II plays similarly to the Dragon Quest games, putting large enemy sprites front and center in its turn-based combat. A difference is the game's party feature: The player can have up to three parties with him at any given time, one filled with story characters, one with NPC mercenaries who lack magic but are very strong and idol deities which lack strength and HP but have powerful magic. Neither of the latter two parties are under the player's control, though switching out the party at critical intervals can greatly assist with some of the game's tougher battles.The game was never released outside of Japan nor officially localized into English, though there is a fan translation from group Dynamic-Designs.	</plot>
	<releasedate>25/6/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Seta Corporation</Developer>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>dXcUQCzMfp4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14777</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570945-silva-saga-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/silva-saga-ii-the-legend-of-light-and-darkness/3030-41830/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/yDea8dF.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/dnwNdyn.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/HdQog5w.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/hOd6ZfI.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/lkcXuZY.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/W79ZJkw.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/B4rbP6O.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CUIPf68.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/cQ6hJKl.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/pa4Xal7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Zjaq61L.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/weJ6G8r.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ynZdhCm.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/dDaZO8x.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Silva Saga II: The Legend of Light and Darkness (シルヴァ・サーガ２?) is a role-playing video game developed and published by SETA Corporation, which was released exclusively in Japan in 1993. It is a direct sequel to Silva Saga for the Family Computer. The player will find similarities with Dragon Quest. Players search out the soldier of light who travels on a journey to defeat the Zolde, son of the Zuhl. Up to 12 mercenaries and deity statues can be combined as well as organized.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ea6c159f-e9c7-4492-91b1-7b8bddf82ed1.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/63617c92-0302-4c37-8293-933f76131be2.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>SETA Corporation</Publisher>
</game>