<Game>
	<Name>Skyblazer (USA) (Beta 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: &amp; GameplayThe player controls the hero Sky (Garuda in Japanese original) on his quest to defeat the Warlord Ashura and rescue the sorceress Ariana (Vishnu in Japanese original).Skyblazer's basic structure is similar to many platformers of the era: he must pass through and conquer a series of stages, defeating the bosses along the way, on his quest to gain power and reach the last stage where Ashura and the dark god Raglan await. There is the occasional branching path as well, which allows the player try a different stage if they're having trouble with the current one. As well as jumping and attacking, Sky can also climb walls and leap off them as well as use several offensive and defensive spells, many of which also increase his ability to traverse a stage as well. Some aerial stages require that Sky take to the air with his wings, a few of which use the Super Nintendo's Mode 7 functionality - these stages play a lot more like a shoot 'em up.Sky has several methods of attack which he gains by finding them spread around the levels. Sky's basic attack, a punch and kick combo, costs no magic points and he can perform it as often as he likes. He can also use the Dragon Slash from the offset, which is a powerful finishing attack that uses a little magic.Additionally, by defeating certain bosses/stages he can acquire:The Comet Flash, which sends Sky flying horizontally. This is invaluable for passing by floor obstacles like spikes and lava.Lightning Strike, which clears the screen of enemies. It's a move best left for emergencies, when enemies threaten to overcome the hero.Star Fire, which fires bullets in eight directions away from Sky.Heal, which gives Sky some health back.Warrior Force, a helpful buff that turns Sky invincible and increases his attack power.Time Stop, a power that freezes all enemies. It can be used on one boss.Fiery Phoenix, the only magic that can destroy Ashura's shield.All these attacks require magic power, which can be found throughout the stages and after defeating enemies. Along with magic power (represented as red potions) and health (represented as green potions), Sky can also collect diamonds. These diamonds will give Sky an extra life should he find 100 of the smaller ones or ten of the larger ones (which count as ten small diamonds each).Cheat: 99 Lives PasswordsEnter these codes to have access to all levels of a map with 99 lives.Cheat: 99 Lives PasswordsT = Triangle shapeO = Circle ShapeX = X Shape- = NoneCheat: 99 Lives PasswordsTo go to the last level with the bonus stage completed, enter: Great Tower complete: 0 T T 0 T X T - X T 0 0 T X T 0 Note:  0 = Circular objects T = Triangular objects X = X-shaped objectsCheat: 99 Lives PasswordsAt the password option press start and match-up the colored squares and hit start to begin on the last stage with 30 lives.Cheat: Caverns of Shirol shortcutIn the second room after riding the gondola up and down the large hill covered in spikes, there is a ledge with a small red potion. Walk up to the corner, crouch, and you will continue walking under the hill. Go through the door, and ride the gondolas across to the other end. You will emerge on a ledge at the end of the third room, right before the bossCheat: Caverns of Shirol shortcutIn the third "room" of the Lair of Kharyon stage, go with the water's flow clockwise until you reach the bottom part of the room. Once you do, swim up as far as you can, and the wall should stop you and push you upwards to a doorway. In the next room, swim all the way to the right, then swim upwards and grab the 1-UP.Cheat: Caverns of Shirol shortcutNow, leave the room via the door right next to the 1-UP and then head back through the door. The 1-UP reappears! You can do this trick until you have 99 Lives, and then return to the stage later in the game and do it again if needed!Cheat: Caverns of Shirol shortcutOnce you've beaten the 'Gateway of Eternal Storms' level, go to the level's icon on the map and press up. You'll get another flight bonus stage, a password hut, and a difficult extra level.Cheat: Caverns of Shirol shortcutIn the first room, go to the right, taking out enemies along the way.  In second room, do the same, but do NOT go to the next room.  About halfway through the room,  (after the first green moving block and fire pit) there will be a platform at the top with a magic restore potion.  To get there, the easiest way is to jump on the second green block as it moves toward you, and then use that to jump up to the platform.  When you get the potion, press and hold DOWN to crouch and then, while crouching, go to the right.  You will crawl through the wall and into a secret part of the room.  Going right will teleport you into a room with two enemies that crawl along the walls; you can either dodge them or kill them with magic.  The only exit to the room is in the upper left corner.  It will take you directly to the boss.Cheat: Caverns of Shirol shortcutNOTE: When you first enter the boss room, the health and magic bars will look like they have the max amount but are empty, and the lives and crystals will both be x99.  When you first get hit or use magic, however, everything will change back to normal.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>-NQqZ-I6-7A</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3260</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588665-skyblazer</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/skyblazer</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/skyblazer/3030-6763/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/cOMD8Tc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/R1dbMEy.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/3MIsXxa.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/9ORh8Ia.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/BeYr8Tr.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/7tcZQ86.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/auqOc8p.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/0jfp0vm.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/JdV2yab.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/7SONwdM.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/jDqpOrC.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/XmqUcBS.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/IB0eMIn.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/AzDxuNU.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/7xSlr3u.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/A43ILxB.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/sw8KHEI.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/H4Ij8hm.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/h72Ry2F.png</clearlogo1>
</game>