<Game>
	<Name>Smart Ball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The player controls a young boy named Jerry, who was a prince and ruler of the Kingdom. Jerry has been transformed into a blob by a mysterious wizard at the behest of his jealous brother, Tom, who has a crush on the young princess Emi. In that incarnation, the player has to played as a little jelly bean with eyes, travelling across a photorealistic grassy landscape. The game itself eventually had graphics and terrain that were now more cartoony and cuteness, which attached to younger viewers.The player also control only lines of defence are in flattening or stretching of his body to hit enemies, and in finding objects like balls to throw at them. The player can also run by holding down by pressing the Y button on the controllers. He can further stick to walls and ceilings by holding down the Y button as you jump towards them. The player can also advance through each level along a filmstrip map, and he/she can revisit previously-completed levels. Each level is a romp up and down hills, jumping between plaforms, and squeezing through pipes. Many enemies will come in the player's way, but they're easy to dispatch. Scattered around each level are a number of plants that open up to reveal balls, power-ups, 1ups, seeds, and jumping enhancers. Similar to Donkey Kong Country, the player must collect all 5 letters that spell JERRY in each level, if collecting them all will net you a couple of 1ups. It can be also be a save point as well.Sony removed the entire storyline from the game, as well as all the towns in levels, in the North American version. However, the English Translation patch of the Japanese version with scenes is available online to play for a Emulator.Tips:Stage SelectWhen the title screen reads 'Push Start Button', press UP, UP, DOWN, DOWN, LEFT, RIGHT, LEFT, RIGHT, B, A, SELECT, STARThttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Smart_Ball</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform, Side-Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagesoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>agbnzzxAw1c</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5862</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588666-smart-ball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/smartball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/smart-ball/3030-21634/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/3rtxThr.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/dZnlqmw.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/QF6JxPp.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/hANd4Jc.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/70uYRSK.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vWsRKUV.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/retjzYF.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/eKRKUgL.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/U9mTbnz.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/c4DBdpb.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vHkUUIr.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/HlS1yDc.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/cEHFhqk.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The whole family will enjoy playing this Super NES adventure. SmartBall is one of the most devilish little characters you'll ever meet. He clings, jumps and bounces his way through life, from the slippery tropics to a dangerous urban battlezone. You'll guide SmartBall through eight dizzying worlds as he takes on everything from flaming firebirds to hidden sandworms.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/328c15d1-ec1e-44ce-889f-db985ea0afa2.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3ca9400e-0378-4978-bd02-a46e11b28d40.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7de6b933-ccc9-419c-90b1-a45cb6533ae6.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bd11af56-2426-4762-83d1-8ac705a864bc.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/786ed175-3439-4d7f-b702-24bddebd5c42.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sony Imagesoft</Publisher>
</game>