<Game>
	<Name>Snoopy Concert (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Snoopy Concert is an Action game, developed by Pax Softonica and published by Mitsui Fudosan,which was released in Japan in 1995.Cheat: Chapter Charlie BrownUse the phone on the left after you have selected a character.Cheat: Chapter Charlie BrownUse the phone on the left after you have selected a character.Cheat: Chapter Charlie BrownThe password is in the form of a telephone number, which you 'dial' on the telephone that appears after selecting a character. Use a password to enter a specific stage within a character's mini-game.</plot>
	<releasedate>19/5/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Pax Softonica</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>24841</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571284-snoopy-concert</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/snoopy-concert</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/snoopy-concert/3030-34569/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/DE7cSKy.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/bSPlpNZ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/bbNbqTi.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/8emMid3.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/JahJ6ho.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/EPZcuGe.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/FLlUvvo.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/czguJK6.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/mOBe8tP.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/VNjLASK.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/df5L6IU.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/2N31LHe.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/8WEbD73.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/xx2nVn1.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The game is a less of a self-contained game and more a collection of four smaller ones; including a point-and-click segment featuring Schroeder. The player controls Woodstock and direct Snoopy as he performs all sorts of errands for different Peanuts characters. The player does a separate game for each character; some of them require him to do a little detective work, or to direct Snoopy to win a race, or to get a character to some place. The ultimate goal in the game is to get everyone in shape for Snoopy's concert. Games can either be played using stereo or monoaural sound. The music was composed by Hirokazu Tanaka (?????) and Minako Hamano (??????),[2] in addition to arrangements of the familiar works of Vince Guaraldi known to longtime Peanuts fans. Many years later the game has been translated to English (by Aeon Genesis) and Portuguese.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/17d2858a-f962-4de1-933b-5c9aa48fef39.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eead17cd-3e14-4c28-a06e-7d3bf9315a19.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Mitsui Fudosan</Publisher>
</game>