<Game>
	<Name>Spanky's Quest (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Spanky's Quest is a 2D puzzle platformer developed by Natsume and published by Taito for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System in July 1992.Originally released in Japan in December 27, 1991 (as Hansei Zaru Jirou-kun no Daibouken, translated to Monkey Reflections: The Adventures of Mr. Jiro), players control an anthropomorphic monkey kid (named Spanky), who must journey through six towers to defeat an evil witch and return home. To do this, he must unlock doors (with keys found scattered throughout levels) while eliminating hostile anthropomorphic fruits and vegetables by various sports balls conjured by popping colored bubbles thrown by him. He can also collect hats (as single-level powerups) which grant different abilities.The handheld version, released for the Game Boy, was originally released in Japan (as Lucky Monkey) on April 26, 1991 (and released in North America at the same time as the SNES version). Unlike the SNES version, there are no keys or hats to pick up (and the concept of attacking with sports balls was changed to "bubble blasts"). However, players can collect bonus pickups (giving more score, collected for each enemy eliminated) and special "letter" pickups (either S, P, A, N, K, or Y, collected by eliminating more than one enemy with the same bubble blast). Collecting each of the six pickups immediately sends the player to the bonus stage.						</plot>
	<releasedate>20/7/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Natsume, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>vGWQPWNK_2w</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5964</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588677-spankys-quest</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/spankys-quest</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spankys-quest/3030-5944/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/vZ2W6dH.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/khvRyHP.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/fZhAww9.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/hznSv2P.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/rBVDaPx.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/XwzpYBr.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Xjpty37.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/BCV4N1T.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/o3b49DT.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vamqJnw.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/xFTM6ey.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JCeJu4H.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/azXbzgv.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/GTiztE6.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/M4JGeCc.png</clearlogo1>
</game>