<Game>
	<Name>Sparkster (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Sparkster and its prequel,  Rocket Knight Adventures, were released at that time in the nineties when tons of mascot based platformer games were being released. Like many of those competitors, Sparkster is a 2D platformer starring an anthropomorphic animal. The twist in this game is Sparkster's rocket pack, which can be used to fly around the level in eight directions for short bursts. Sparkster's quality and pedigree as a Konami game helped ensure it would be more memorable than  Bubsy or  Aero the Acro-Bat ever were.Sparkster is not to be confused with Sparkster: Rocket Knight Adventures 2, which was a direct sequel to the original Rocket Knight Adventures exclusive to the Genesis/Mega Drive. The US/EU version of Rocket Knight Adventures 2 is known as just Sparkster, making it easy to confuse with this SNES spin-off.Gameplay:Sparkster controls like a typical 2D platformer. Many areas feature thin ledges that can be grabbed by Sparkster's prehensile tail and climbed around on. A regular attack with the sword also launches a projectile across the screen, and holding down the button after attacking will charge the rocket pack, which takes about a second. Once charged, holding a direction and releasing the button will send Sparkster shooting away. While dashing with the rocket pack Sparkster will ricochet wildly off walls, floors and ceilings, which is sometimes the only way to reach a certain area. Sparkster can also use a flip move by pressing the R and L buttons, which will cause Sparkster to quickly flip right or left. This can be done in mid air and is a great way to get around, but using it too many times in a row makes Sparkster dizzy and unable to move for a while.In addition, Sparkster has a few unique levels that switch up the gameplay. There's a level where Sparkster pilots giant mechanical ostriches, which run automatically. He can fire ripple laser shots from the bird's mouth and make it go up and down to grab crystals as it speeds by. Towards the end of the game, there is a section where the player controls the game as a top-down shooter. That level's boss fight involves piloting a fighting mech, which is controlled by pressing the R and L buttons to punch with the respective hand.Cheat: Crazy Hard ModePause the game and press A, B, X, Y, L, R.  Unpause and sparkster wont take any damage from hits.  To reverse the code just pause the game and put it in again.Cheat: End PasswordsAt the title screen select password and attack the empty boxes to change them.&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;A: Apple B: Banana C: Crystal N: Nothing&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;T: top row M: middle row B: bottom rowCheat: Raise Score To Desired Point by Defeating Infinite EnemiesIn the first level inside the ship, proceed until you're past the wooden crate walls, which you broke through with your rocket. When ricocheting off walls toward the end of the level (before the boss), there should be a space inside the wall on the right. Jump in and walk in. If you're in the right place, you should find some sort of wooden wall built into the stage wall. Charge into it to break it, and an explosion will show up. Infinite enemies will spawn from the explosions. Maintain a distance from them, face the explosion, and press the attack button repeatedly to kill enemies the second the spawn. Kill enemies until desired score is reached.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami (America), Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>7lCO4Rn7hZs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2671</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588678-sparkster</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/sparkster_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sparkster/3030-19920/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/pJLe1AK.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/h2OLeIo.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/bAEFEEQ.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/8BoDoE2.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/e6Jfxrr.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/dUooFpM.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/nOTQeMo.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/qdX6RBy.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/nwZvBJs.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/T9HJBx1.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YVECG7v.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/kQvcwhq.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/48GKGiB.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/y5iym8b.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/cd7E6uP.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CSN2kHr.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/myz8bJX.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>He's back, and he's one opumped-up opposum! SPARKSTER is jet-packin' into action as the toughest Rocket Knight to ever swing a sword. Grab the controls and blast through nine wild stages in your quest to rid the world of the nasty Colonel Wolfheim and his allies - a tough pack of wolves that aren't here to dance! Oh yeah, and before you get too comfortable - Axel Gear is here. This Rocket-Knight-gone-bad has a score to settle with Sparkster. Our hero will need his revved-up new rocket pack and powerful new attack moves to kick Axel's tail back to the dark side of the planet. Come on. Don't waste time on games that were designed for somebody's little brother. Take Sparkster for a spin and feel what real adventure is! You'll sizzle through the secret rooms in the ancient pyramid and stomp wolf hide in a midair battle. Search for the power-ups and avoid opossum-squelching traps, and see some of the most amazing boss characters ever put into a video game. Feel the opower of the opossum!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dced1d64-19c4-4fca-abb1-42d75dfaa8aa.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ef6967e9-4b31-4286-b43d-19041a072c1f.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3b60903f-b14a-4670-9c24-c88ed12a223b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c4378b10-2acc-4a65-a4a3-853ea2eb6420.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e89263c5-3ecc-4336-902e-d8808841e9b9.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>