<Game>
	<Name>Speed Racer in My Most Dangerous Adventures (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This game is a take on the classic Anime cartoon series, Speed Racer.  You play as Speed, an aspiring race car driver with his trusty car, The Mach 5, along with his GO team, out to travel the world and win every international grand prix on the circuit.Along the way, you fight off the infamous villains of the series, out to stop Speed by any means necessary, even capturing his girlfriend, Trixie.  There are seven levels in all and in between racing levels you'll be on foot in a side-scroll style adventure, fighting off thugs and gangsters, collecting power ups to help you out, including green flags in order to keep your health up (not kidding about that).Cheat: Racer X PasswordsIn the main menu select password and put:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Accolade, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>QZ-tn88LCbE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5965</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588681-speed-racer-in-my-most-dangerous-adventures</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/speed-racer-in-my-most-dangerous-adventures</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/speed-racer-in-my-most-dangerous-adventures/3030-18983/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/tUgVNmI.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/5vWZJdJ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/2sFyYQc.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ydrPy3V.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/DkKP0M1.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/k6oOmE2.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/hsyiLRF.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/EAGcw2l.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/KV0iUYk.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/uzCDpSj.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/lMtXyf4.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JbPY3Y2.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/kCMJQbG.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4aheoLD.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/9fdWD1d.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>EXPERIENCE THE THRILL OF INTENSE RACING ACTION AND DEATH DEFYING SIDE-SCROLLING ADVENTURES. Compete in thrilling high-speed races throughout the world. You'll need everything in the Mach 5's arsenal to take on goons like the Car Acrobatic Team. But that's only half the adventure! Off the track, you control Speed Racer or Racer X in hand-to-hand combat as you battle classic Speed Racer villains. Watch out - they'll kidnap, fight and do whatever it takes to prevent you from advancing in the World Race circuit. CHALLENGES YOU'LL FACE - Leap clear of danger with the Mach 5's autojacks. Zoom through the belly of an erupting volcano in the Fire Race. Rescue Trixie from kidnappers. Prevent the Mach 5 from being sabotaged and defeat Captain Terror.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c0e34b85-bc97-4875-9c75-1e301a30261a.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40be1e60-5dd7-45bf-82ed-e9fa6097415e.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2c13bb94-76a9-4f13-bed9-02a8b53c6294.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6b33f12a-8a27-4714-af54-9692de5aff56.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Accolade</Publisher>
</game>