<Game>
	<Name>Spider-Man and the X-Men in Arcade's Revenge (USA) (Beta) [b]</Name>
	<plot>Every stage of Spider-Man and the X-Men is exceedingly difficult in that they all require that the player have some knowledge of the stage prior to playing. Even knowing the exact layout each stage can be difficult and can require ridiculously precise timing. A great example of this is one of the hardest stages in video game history: the Juggernaut stage, also known as Wolverine's second stage. In this stage the player is being chased down by the boss (Juggernaut) from the very beginning. There are only two ways to damage the boss. The first way to cause damage is to drop anvils down either on his head or in his path. The second way to damage the boss is to slice the Juggernaut with the normal punch move or the uppercut. This requires that the player get close enough to actually hit the boss, leaving little room for error.The game is also loaded with instances of 'cheap deaths' usually characterized by trial and error. For instance, Gambit's second stage consists of a platform constantly moving up. The screen does not shift left or right, it simply shifts up at a constant rate until the boss. Oftentimes a player can choose different paths. Once a path is chosen there is no going back. Unfortunately many paths are death traps. Without any way of knowing which areas are traps the player simply has to learn through luck or through trial and error. Several times a player may take the correct path only to see that the other path is loaded with ammo, stars (which accumulate to an extra live) and bombs. Of course, the player that took the path loaded with items was quickly squished to death by the rising platform. One spot in the middle of the stage is loaded with stars but there is absolutely no way to get to them leaving players to wonder whether it was a programming glitch or just a joke.Many gamers also express disdain towards the games ending which is as short as the game is difficult.Tips:100 Star GlitchIn Gambits First Stage, when you get to the fourth Green Globe (above the B) on the destroyable steps, try to jump on the step below it. Then try to jump over the globe and the star above it, right off the top of the screen. Try to land on the same spot you jumped from(Its kinda like jump right, but turn left when you go back down). Your stars will increase by about 30-60, depending on how well you can land, but DO NOT touch the Green Globe or the single star above it. Let us remember, 100 stars collect in Gambits Stage can lead to a life. By repeating the procedureover and over, you may build up to 8 or more extra lives before the rolling wheel hits you. If you repeat the procedure enough times, you may build up to 99 lives, where from then on out, you can try to beat everyone elses stage without having to beat Gambits First Stage until later.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spider-Man_and_the_X-Men:_Arcade%27s_Revenge</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform, Side-Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>LJN</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>Cn7fQKm3O3w</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5871</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588685-spider-man-and-the-x-men-arcades-revenge</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spider-man-and-the-x-men-arcades-revenge/3030-10085/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/qYlzX4u.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mi8t7Lu.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/3c4zDBP.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/UyndZMe.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/i2VKSVe.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ZSqq5g4.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/aLmcEZI.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Wq86fRI.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/fBRZvdT.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/xG08yJ8.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/LVlQabi.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/xOSaKjU.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/g2Iu1Ig.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/sA688Vz.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QkB6SoG.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/huMWAnp.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/fYXhNnJ.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/h2GpJHP.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/yIF9RYY.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8pj7Fq1.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/cQOxVlD.png</clearlogo1>
</game>