<Game>
	<Name>Spider-Man - X-Men - Arcade's Revenge (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Spider-Man and members of the X-Men have teamed up in this side-scrolling action game to fight against Arcade, who has built a giant amusement park for the sole purpose of trapping and destroying the super-heroes. You first play as Spider-Man, who sees the X-Men get kidnapped by Arcade and follows them. Once you make it inside Arcade's park you can choose to play as Spider-Man, Cyclops, Storm, Gambit, or Wolverine, each of whom are trapped in a different part of Arcade's maze of deadly traps. You must navigate all five of them safely out, using their different skills and abilities while defeating baddies and bosses along the way.Cheat: 100 Star GlitchIn Gambits First Stage, when you get to the fourth Green Globe (above the B) on the destroyable steps, try to jump on the step below it. Then try to jump over the globe and the star above it, right off the top of the screen. Try to land on the same spot you jumped from(Its kinda like jump right, but turn left when you go back down). Your stars will increase by about 30-60, depending on how well you can land, but DO NOT touch the Green Globe or the single star above it. Let us remember, 100 stars collect in Gambits Stage can lead to a life. By repeating the procedure over and over, you may build up to 8 or more extra lives before the rolling wheel hits you. If you repeat the procedure enough times, you may build up to 99 lives, where from then on out, you can try to beat everyone elses stage without having to beat Gambits First Stage until later.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>LJN, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>Cn7fQKm3O3w</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5871</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588685-spider-man-and-the-x-men-arcades-revenge</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/spider-man-x-men-arcades-revenge</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spider-man-and-the-x-men-arcades-revenge/3030-10085/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/qYlzX4u.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/mi8t7Lu.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/3c4zDBP.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/UyndZMe.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/i2VKSVe.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ZSqq5g4.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/aLmcEZI.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Wq86fRI.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/fBRZvdT.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/xG08yJ8.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/LVlQabi.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/xOSaKjU.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/g2Iu1Ig.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/sA688Vz.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QkB6SoG.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/huMWAnp.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/fYXhNnJ.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/h2GpJHP.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/yIF9RYY.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WQJVVqL.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/cQOxVlD.png</clearlogo1>
</game>