<Game>
	<Name>Spindizzy Worlds (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>On it's most basic level, Spindizzy Worlds is, like its predecessor, similar to Marble Madness. Controlling GERALD, you must move through the isometrically viewed landscape (largely flick-screen on the ST). There are two skill levels; the harder one features more of the precarious ledges and falls of Spindizzy. Each one takes you to a different matrix of levels, which can be played in different orders and each consist of 10 screens, with a bonus level at the end.You have limited energy, which can be recharged by collecting crystals. Fuel is limited, and is reduced by contact with hazards - generating a replacement GERALD takes time. There are many gates which are opened by running into spaces of the same colour. There are also aliens to avoid, and most movement is along thin slippery ledges with heavily inertia-based controls.Cheat: Final level passwordsEnter these passwords on the password screen to instantly be taken to the games final levelsCheat: Final level passwordsEnter WwXxYyZz as a password.Cheat: Final level passwordsEnter MIMICHAN as a password.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Electric Dreams</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>WHnrH2Eu8mg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6129</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588687-spindizzy-worlds</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/spindizzy-worlds</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spindizzy-worlds/3030-4385/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/z5jVdn3.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/7N7IGvf.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/1fklXRs.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/h6JbHJ2.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/tfHOHip.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SMKlW9R.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/7uXVp1c.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/M356pXE.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ou6I10P.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/QfJqmlx.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Fl8xMzh.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/4rhvpxX.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/3IzJjeX.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/lm2SaTB.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Ob2TJNI.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>SPINDIZZY WORLDS! JOIN THE REVOLUTION! THE PLACE. A solar system layered with clusters of worlds so perilous, nothing but top speed and intense coordination can transport you from sphere to sphere! While spinning through multiple dangers, objects, and aliens, you must gather the jewels, fuel and bonus levels needed to win your way to more difficult and complex worlds. THE TIME. In such places, minutes become seconds and seconds slip by ...you're always on the verge of time running out. Since fuel supplies deplete quickly and must constantly be replenished, only bold, expert explorers beam themselves into such lethal arenas - but the payoffs are big! THE CHALLENGE. You may get safety from place to place by using lifts or ramps, and by collecting jewels and energy crystals. But danger lurks in every corner, and keeping yourself from the jaws of destruction is an incredible challenge.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6089f80e-e138-4e42-a422-7f12c67774e5.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2e052ad2-a858-4a7e-a41d-f715f8ca6fa0.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/db9aaa4d-5873-49c0-a34e-9a354bdb3318.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b9de547f-42e6-4885-9e49-bfd82475c043.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Asciiware</Publisher>
</game>