<Game>
	<Name>Spirou (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Spirou is an obscure 2D side-scrolling platformer designed by Infogrames based on a popular Belgian comic. Spirou is a bumbling bellboy who looks like he could be Tintin's younger brother. In Spirou, you task is to rescue the world-famous scientist Count Champaignac from the clutches of an evil organization intent on using his latest invention to take over the world. Both games has colorful cartoony graphics with fluid animation and incorporates funny antics. The game is similar to Pitfall, Jungle Book, or any of Infogrames' other licensed cartoon platformers (most notably the Tintin series)  The game was released on the PC and Snes as well as the original Gameboy. There was a Game Gear version being developed but was abandoned.Cheat: Debug ModeEnter the code at the Infogrames logo.  As you press each button, it must be held down until the entire cheat is entered (in other words, by the end of the code you'll be holding d-pad down-left, L, X, and A).  A sound effect will play if the code was entered correctly.  During gameplay, press Select to open the debug menu.Cheat: Level PasswordOn the main menu, select Password and enter the following password.Note: The picture order for each slot is: Spirou, Fantasio, Spip, Count Champignac, and Cyanida.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Infogrames Europe SA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>WoCcMF_d7SU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6130</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/924701-spirou</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/spirou</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spirou/3030-16845/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ijiyFjX.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/4gxPFCr.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/H4vWQzO.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/a3svwgB.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/fBCJEOZ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ktENuCw.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/1TsNhlN.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/62mDs2d.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/3HcB1Cx.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/1OI98wk.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/mlEopS3.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/yaJLjgy.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/pxNkT7e.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WA0HCE6.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/2VdVue9.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>This is a simple platform game, you're in a role of porter, jumping down the streets and buildings, and taking as many points as you can get. There's no strong background story.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ca0c790a-fb31-414c-9e96-59638fbc597e.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e28c8fa-3ca0-494e-af64-07f0242aa964.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>