<Game>
	<Name>Starwing (Germany)</Name>
	<plot>In the distant Lylat star system, imagine yourself at the controls of a futuristic, heavily armed, space fighter - Arwing. Lead the counter-attack on an invasion force of hundreds of alien tanks, fighter ships, laser gun emplacements and super battleships. Maneuver at warp speed through fog-enshrouded canyons, dense asteroid belts and waves of the enemy's best defense. You must use skill and cunning to fight to the enemy's home planet Venom and smash the Core Brain for victory!Cheat: Polygon View ModeAt the continue screen after you lose your last ship, you can play with the polygons on the screen. Here are the controls. Controller 1: Left and Right-Rotate object horizontally Up and Down-Rotate object vertically L button-Zoom in R button-Zoom out X button-Stop rotation A button-Hold it down while rotating to ''draw'' with the object. Release the button to clear the screen. Controller 2: Up,Down,Left,Right,SELECT,START,Y, or B-Changes to a different objectCheat: Black HoleTo enter the black hole, a secret area on the map with no apparent way in, you must enter Level 1-2 (Asteroid Belt) and keep going until you find a spinning asteroid bar. Hit the center of the asteroid bar just before you hit it. Do it with the next 2.  If you hit all 3 bars right before you hit them (fly through where the breakable asteroid was....) A Laughing asteroid will appear. Shoot it repeatedly to open the gateway to the Black Hole.  There are three level warps in the Black Hole. Fly through and look around this Lost ship graveyard....Cheat: Black HoleChoose level three, then go to the asteroid belt and keep shooting the second big asteroid until it is destroyed. A bird-like object will fly out. Do not shoot it. Ram into it to travel ''out of this dimension''. Shoot the paper-like objects. The boss does not have a life meter, just icons (until they display three 7s) Shoot ''THE END'' letters until they are in the right position. The letters will be orange when they are correct. </plot>
	<releasedate>20/3/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Rail-Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Argonaut Games</Developer>
	<rating>8.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>k8dxLr_xVv4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>24237</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588690-star-fox</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/JP4UIJ5.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/YbWBsx8.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/AhhwRvr.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/kq6gUWx.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/nmMZN3r.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/UbdqBLC.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/D6T4Nz8.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/60lx2vO.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/VhLoxom.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ShmWNz0.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/VrQx3cy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/OkmybNz.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/3N7cDET.jpg</banner1>
</game>