<Game>
	<Name>Star Trek - Deep Space Nine - Crossroads of Time (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Title Screen Star Trek Deep Space Nine: Crossroads of Time is a secretly great game. It's an action platformer from a time when most games were platformers.  You take command of various characters from the TV show who must battle it out with Cardassians, Borg, and other recognizable faces from the Star Trek universe.  Shuttle Craft Level Gameplay:The gameplay is simple and mostly consists of platforming and some simple combat. To spice things up there are also boss battles spread throughout the game, as well as an interesting section in which you take control of a shuttle and must navigate through the wormhole and even an asteroid field to catch up to a fugitive. A few other challenges are added and a memorable  a level where you take control of the shapeshifting Odo in a stealth mission aboard a Cardassian ship. The point of the game is achieved, it feels like an episode of Star Trek: Deep Space Nine. Crossroads of Time serves as an excellent example of what a good game was at the time as well as how to do a Tv or Film tie in correctly.Cheat: Level PasswordsOn the Password screen, enter the password CHEESE.  When you are presented with the Password Error screen, press R shoulder, R shoulder, A, B, A, B, L shoulder, L shoulder, Start.  If entered correctly, a sound effect plays as the screen fades out and the game returns to the title screen.  Now enter Options and the extra settings for the stage select and invincibility toggle are at the bottom.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Playmates Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6133</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588692-star-trek-deep-space-nine-crossroads-of-time</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/star-trek-deep-space-nine-crossroads-of-time</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/star-trek-deep-space-nine-crossroads-of-time/3030-19232/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/sdv46ia.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/OOBcvyT.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ddhZYnu.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xWe0THL.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/IUU7qUy.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/RN7AQQF.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Y9Lr5dG.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/qJ3Nq6i.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/9uECunZ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/HCSm4RW.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/jlnfs9S.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/SxZHpMj.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/8IPOCis.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/SHHxB9U.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/wCoHOxw.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/tTe6FHJ.png</clearlogo1>
</game>