<Game>
	<Name>Star Ocean (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Star Ocean is an action RPG for the Super Famicom and was the first game developed by tri-Ace. The game was published by Enix on July 19, 1996 and was never released outside of Japan. A enhanced remake named Star Ocean: First Departure was released for the PSP in 2007.Star Ocean was created by the team behind Tales of Phantasia by Namco and features many similarities to it. The team left Namco due to "creative differences," such as the alteration of the character names, story, sprites, and even the title of the game itself (the original being Tale Phantasia, named after the novel by Yoshiharu Gotanda, the game's main programmer).An unofficial English patch was created by DeJap Translations for Star Ocean and was released on December 31, 2003.Story:Star Ocean begins in Clatos, a town on the undeveloped planet of Roak, and follows a young Fellpool named Ratix Farrence. He is a swordsman in the Clatos Brigade, as is his companion Dorn Marto, who's duty is to defend the town against thieves and robbers. One day, a petrifying disease spreads in the northern town of Cool, turning it's inhabitants to stone. The town healer, who is the father of Ratix's best friend, Milly Kiliet, travels to Cool and tries to use his Crest Magic (also known as Heraldry and Symbology in later games) to cure the disease. Hr is unable to, and is eventually turned to stone himself. When this news returns to the village of Clatos, Ratix, Dorn, and Milly set off to collect Metox, a herb said to cure any ailment, from Mt. Metox.When they reach the top, where the plant is said to grow, they are met by a mysterious light, from which two oddly dressed people emerge from. One is a male named Ronixis J. Kenny, and the other a blonde female named Iria Silvestoli. Ronixis introduces himself as a captain of the Earth Federation starship Calnus. He tells them that the disease that is turning their people to stone was caused by the Resonia, a race the Federation is at war with. He doesn't know why they are targeting their planet though.It turns out that the Resonia are using Roakian blood to block out the part of the spectrum that is visible to the human eye. While this would give them a massive advantage in the war against the Federation, they use it to sneak into Federation HQ and explain that they do not wish to fight, but are being forced by the Fargett, a race that hates the Federation.The group also discovers that the petrifying disease is caused by a monster known as Asmodeus, who originates on the planet Roak. Ronixis decides to travel to Planet Stream (later called Planet Styx), and use the Time Gate located there to travel back in time and gain a sample of Asmodeus' blood. After gaining the sample, they head back to their own time, but get separated from each other, Ronixis and Milly on one continent, while Ratix and Iria are on another.Cheat: Invincible charactersThis glitch allows you to make your entire party (except for Ratix) invincible.  It works by reducing them to 0 HP outside of battle but not actually killing them.  As a result, the game will treat them as still being alive, but not apply the effects of any damage to them.Cheat: Invincible charactersRequirements:One character with either "Rhythmic sense" or "Pitch Sense", but not both, and any music level (higher is faster).One character with neither of those talents, and level 1 in musicEither Guitar song or either Trombone song, and the appropriate instrument.Cheat: Invincible charactersStep 1: Decrease everyone's HP to 1.  Best way to do this is to use a Guitar song (preferably 2) or a Trombone song (preferably 2) with the first character.  You should hear a chirping in the background, and your HP will decrease.  Continue doing this until everyone's HP is at 1 (Ratix does not have to be at 1 HP).  Cheat: Invincible charactersStep 2: Heal Ratix (or at least one character) so that he does not go to 0 HP in the next step.Cheat: Invincible charactersStep 3: Have the second character use either Guitar or Trombone song.  Everyone's 1 HP will go to zero, but the game will still have their walking sprites.  You can neither heal nor revive them now (although you can recover status ailments).Cheat: Invincible characters(This is the glitch)Step 4: Enter a fight.  The 0-HP characters will still be active and attack...and receive attacks, but the enemy attacks won't ever connect.  Milly and Joshua will neither heal nor revive the 0-HP characters.  Note that if all 4 characters in the battle reach 0 HP, it is still a game over.Cheat: Invincible charactersAfter the fight, the 0-HP characters will still receive EXP, and they will recover HP and MP due to Stanima (so you have to reset the glitch).  But the important part is that they cannot be killed or even touched by any means.Cheat: Oracle RoomAfter you have beaten the game, reload your saved game and have somebody use the Oracle specialtiy. You will be sent to a secret area. Each door takes you to a room where you can talk to members of the game's development staff. To exit, take the passage on the lower left or right corner. The lower right corner will take you to the Revorse Tower. The lower left corner will take you to Tatoroy.Cheat: Oracle RoomAfter beating the final boss of the game, use the oracle skill, and go through the south-west door.You\'ll end up in the Tataroy arena. Now go one step up, to arrive in the Seven Star Ruin. This secret dungeon has 30 levels and no save points.It contains super hard enemies, and a even harder boss.At the bottom is some of the best items in the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>19/7/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Enix Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>Yl4ZJQ4Zu-0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6132</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588691-star-ocean</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/star-ocean</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/star-ocean/3030-9032/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/MHWoKQw.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/j8153NS.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/EcXvGU9.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/pXg2mRB.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/TOpb9ow.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/mDfQVjI.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/l1b8VA9.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/nK7zLhR.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ZPJqMzj.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/VA6JPNE.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/iHmGMvR.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/gMNT730.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vU9wJjV.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/WoAj905.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/NsVW43h.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4Yk63QW.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/4VRgc8o.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>A young boy named Ratix lives in the town Clatos on a planet with medieval culture, together with his best friends Dorn and Milly. They belong to respectable families of warriors and healers, and excel in battles kills. One day, a letter from a neighbor town arrives. A strange disease has plagued the town and its inhabitants plead the healers of Clatos to help them. Milly's father decides to go, but he himself catches the disease. The young adventurers must save Milly's father and other people at all costs. But in the beginning of their journey, they discover a crashed space ship with people who belong to a much more advanced civilization. People from two different worlds must work together to solve the grand mystery...</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5fbeeb50-8899-4558-8c57-acfda4d6b278.png</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ec75e23-d864-4ef3-aa5e-7351379c0d84.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/213bc96d-bf04-4125-a2a9-592cda6337e0.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/65bc887c-ab8b-40a7-934f-7ab893f7ce01.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99edeced-5b11-41d4-ae09-c0bae15425d7.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/80309a65-ef83-4ca4-ad9e-5ffab94e35b8.png</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Enix</Publisher>
</game>