<Game>
	<Name>Street Fighter II Turbo (USA)</Name>
	<plot>They're back and they're badder than ever! Faster, stronger and with all new moves, twelve of the greatest fighters from across the globe are ready to do battle! Choose your champion and get ready for the big brawl as they try to earn the right to battle M. Bison for the title. And just when you think you've mastered it all, crank it up a notch and go TURBO!Cheat: CodesThese codes are for the Japanese version.Cheat: Game Posters and Extra EndingFinish a one player game against the computer at level 8 difficulty without continuing.Cheat: Game Posters and Extra EndingAfter the normal ending, instead of the characters battling credits you normally get for defeating the game at level 6 or higher, you get a sequence for each character, similar to the character stats at the game menu screen, using a move to destroy a crate.Cheat: Game Posters and Extra EndingOnce the credits have rolled, a poster will appear on the screen. For Turbo it is a group shot of all eight player characters, for Normal (Champion Edition) it is a picture or Ryu and M. Bison.Cheat: Skip 1-Player MatchesNot really a cheat but a useful trick none thr less. begin a 1 player game as usual but during the game  press start on controller two so that player two joins in , choose player 2's character , say for example Ryu , and then defeat  him.Cheat: Skip 1-Player MatchesOnce the two player game ends you will be taken  back to the one-player tournament ,  now the character you defeated during the two player round will be checked off and you will not have to fight him in tournament mode.Cheat: Skip 1-Player MatchesUsing this trick the only character you will have to beat to complete the game is M.bison.Cheat: Skip 1-Player MatchesTurn on the game and wait until you see the first profile of a fighter. On Controller 2, hold the L and R Buttons for as long as you would like to look at the profiles. </plot>
	<releasedate>20/8/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.7</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>f-B67ddO_OM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2538</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588701-street-fighter-ii-turbo</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/street-fighter-ii-turbo</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/JbqlA6h.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/NQIWdSm.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/MPdtFTO.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/8ZRsFuw.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/nl8Lyir.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/LXgwpcW.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/o2lrGMQ.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/2mvOY2g.jpg</boxart8>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xrOjTYr.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/9vuEBqR.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Pd2zdZx.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/guYlyFu.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/biwFfM8.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/YCG60Ba.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BKAWVgY.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/dGMdjp7.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/EPLyUqo.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Gyj1fKO.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Y34VfLr.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/MoUNKb4.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/sQ0OGyX.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/zf4IBv4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/hJfMaza.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/2C1io45.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/kzLTBhX.jpg</clearlogo1>
</game>