<Game>
	<Name>Street Combat (Europe) (Putative Proto)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ranma 1/2: Chounai Gekitou Hen is the first of three Fighter games on the Super Famicom to be based on the martial arts comedy manga/anime of the same name. The player selects various characters from the show and either plays through their stories in the single player or fights against another human player in versus mode.When the game was brought to the US a year later, Irem decided to graphically rehaul the characters, as Ranma 1/2 and anime in general had yet to enter the western mainstream. All the characters were reimagined as various sci-fi fighter game archetypes, with some undergoing more drastic changes than others. The character of Shampoo, for instance, was only given a slight hair color change and a mask and renamed Lita, while Principal Kuno instead became a skateboarding robot named Helmut.Conversely, the second game in the series, Ranma 1/2: Bakuretsu Rantou Hen, was left largely intact with its American incarnation Ranma 1/2: Hard Battle. The third (Ranma 1/2: Chougi Ranbu Hen) was never released overseas.Characters:Though both rosters are completely different superficially, each character fights identically to their trans-Pacific counterpart.Ranma 1/2: Chounai Gekitou Hen (JP)Street Combat (US)Ranma Saotome (Male)Steven (Robot Suit)Ranma Saotome (Female)Steven (Without Robot Suit)Genma SaotomeTyroneRyoga HibikiCJShampooLitaKodachi KunoDozoTatewaki KunoGI JimPrincipal KunoHelmutAdditionally, the characters of Happosai and Cologne appear during bonus rounds. Their Street Combat equivalent is an old man named Happy. These characters can be unlocked in multiplayer with a special cheat code.Cheat: CodesAt the title screen, highlight 1 Player mode (Vs. CPU) and press Start on both Controller 1 and Controller 2. If done right, the ending will start right away.Cheat: Hidden Characters - Colon and Happy (JP)Go to the title screen and highlight "Vs mode". Press and hold L and R, then press A. This should bring you to a hidden screen, highlight "Who" and choose your character. You will be able to fight as Colon or Happy.Cheat: Hidden Characters - Colon and Happy (JP)During the versus screen, press and hold L and R, then press left or right to switch to any character except Colon and Happy in the game.Cheat: Free 50 credits (JP)Go to the option menu, highlight "credit" and press select for 10 times. The values of the credit will become 50.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Irem Corp.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>2.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6140</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581968-street-combat</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/street-combat</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/street-combat/3030-7092/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/nZXotpo.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/YJDKsRl.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/uXWkLXZ.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7AI6kES.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/zf3YQvL.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/tlpd1z5.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/caORUG2.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/JigYmVv.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/pQlPImz.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/n9Ou7hA.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/lOpTALw.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/DbNyAe4.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/lf5pMRn.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/S0Fu10m.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/8y9weiE.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Ranma learns of a martial arts tournament in which the grand prize is a invitation to see China. Desperate to rid himself of his Jusenkyo curse, Ranma decides to enter the tournament, but the other characters also hear of the tournament and decide to enter as well to either hope to rid themselves of their own curses, or to simply cause Ranma trouble. This game holds the distinction of not only being the first Ranma ½ game for the Super Famicom, but also the first ever Ranma ½ game released and is also the only game in which the character Cologne appears. Since its release it has become quite well known for how, when it was released in western territories, the game was renamed "Street Combat" and westernised extensively with every Ranma ½ character replaced by a more "typical" Western Superhero</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aa7fd4f8-1294-41cf-9f66-647b13e9e892.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a8ec06c-933d-455d-a7fc-6b71efddfc44.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fc49eb77-8ae2-4a54-838e-78515b66e354.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/14196012-1df9-4bf0-8404-522b4ce3e27d.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1f349f86-892e-4abb-a12c-3902e656e884.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3b1afdd5-3136-4e80-adbd-083f0cb91e29.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e9233da-8a9f-44fd-afa6-f0fea4aa5534.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e94779d2-40c6-4b18-819f-d9a45ba64201.jpg</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Irem</Publisher>
</game>