<Game>
	<Name>Strike Gunner S.T.G (Japan) (En)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Strike Gunner S.T.G is a two player shoot 'em up that offers fifteen (ten in the Arcade version) different power-ups and hordes of enemies to fight through. In two-player modes it's possible to combine both players' ships to create a larger, more powerful craft. There are eight stages, each with their own boss. The ultimate goal is to save Earth from alien invaders by using their own technology against them.Strike Gunner S.T.G was originally released in the arcades by Tecmo. The original developers, Athena, would go on to publish the home version for the Super Famicom in their native Japan. This SNES version would also be published in the US by NTVIC and in Europe by Activision. The European version was renamed Super Strike Gunner, but is otherwise identical.Critical ReceptionThe SNES version of the game was awarded the following scores from Electronic Gaming Monthly: 4,7,6,7. From the review, "... A solid shooter with nothing really new or exciting. Lots of enemies to blow away but let too many on the screen and the game slows down".</plot>
	<releasedate>15/10/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>NTVIC</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>l-MO-yqvTPc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2456</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588704-strike-gunner-stg</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/strike-gunner-stg</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/strike-gunner-stg/3030-32941/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/cdK9F8f.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/HJ1aK0P.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ejJt41N.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/KF3nYTh.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/dqAdpS4.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/yDAcYF2.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/kssMXKY.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/z5MX2RZ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/LMNS8lq.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/oPcpy9h.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/RLPmVbW.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/BrrbaH3.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/cdd0Xpf.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Ebcb3IT.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/C2fPCr0.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In the last years of the 20th century, the nations of the world have united to dismantle their massive arsenals of nuclear doom. With the promise of permanent world peace finally at hand, only a madman would still harbor dreams of world domination. Such a madman is the dictator of Sovinia, a small but cunning rebel nation. "In his insane lust for power, he has joined forces with a huge, hostile war force from beyond this planet, armed with weapons more powerful than anything ever seen before by man. The Allied Countries of Earth try to resist, but without nuclear weapons, their efforts are futile. By 2008, most of the planet lies in ruins; then, in an ironic twist of treachery, the alien forces turn against their ally, and set out to complete their conquest and colonization of Earth "Now, with the survival of the human race at stake, the allied countries join forces with the rebel dictatorship in a last-ditch effort to drive out the invaders. At their secret fortress deep in the Amazon Jungle, the greatest scientists of Earth carefully analyze the alien weaponry, and develop the weapon to end all weapons: Strike Gunner. With time running out, and few resources remaining, only two can be built; but those two can combine at will into one superfighter of astonishing power. With an awesome arsenal of offensive and defensive devices at your command, and your own unmatched courage and skill as a fighter pilot, the Earth may yet be saved!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/42f90ced-9458-4e0b-aeca-664a3777e4d3.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40e1f417-5d60-4e46-a902-571b5d5e06f8.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bd5cc5ce-2098-4d37-8b5a-00564057282b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b0a11203-9789-4183-8542-581382e84427.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b4b9163d-02f0-4756-b44f-fb2d43b193b3.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>NTVIC</Publisher>
</game>