<Game>
	<Name>Stunt Race FX (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Stunt Race FX is one of the few fully-3D FX powered Super Nintendo games. Similar to Star Fox, its use of the effect is rudimentary, and the polygons are limited to flat shading and few in number. Stunt Race FX manages to churn out slightly more detailed environments than Star Fox, and they compensate for the increased demands on the chip by lowering the framerate and shrinking the player's view. With the borders in effect and speed/time display outside, there is only about 60% of the screen devoted to actual gameplay.Controls are very similar to other racing games, with the shoulder buttons acting as sharper turns than pressing left or right on the directional pad. Other than gas and brake, all the cars are capable of boost and another button honks the horn. Honking the horn serves a greater purpose than just showing off, however, as it also launches the body of the vehicle in the air, allowing the player to drive over opponents.Cars can also sustain damage, which is repaired by touching red gems located at various points in each track.Race TypesThe bulk of Stunt Race FX is devoted to grand prix style race series, where the vehicles complete four races and the best overall time wins. After the second race the player is allowed a bonus round, where they drive the game's semi trailer in a fixed 3/4 view - each lap that they finish in that behemoth grants them an extra continue, which are welcome in the later races as it's easy to damage the car to the point of self-destruction or be flung off the track by accident. There are four circuits, with generic themes like aquatic (complete with a floating track and underwater tunnels), metro, forest, mountains, etc. Most of the tracks use height to great effect, presumably to emphasize the abilities of the FX chip over a Mode 7 based racing game with a completely flat track.Monster truck ignoring the flooded trackEach track in grand prix is available for time trial races as well, and winning every grand prix race grants the use of the motorcycle, which has all of the strengths and none of the weaknesses of the other vehicles.The Stunt Race portion of the game's title manifests itself in a series of stunt-based races that have the player collecting stars while navigating over, under, and around various bizarre obstacles. Each of the four stunt tracks are divided up into sections that will only open after obtaining all of the stars. Some of them require very careful driving, as they're located at the apex of certain jumps or ramps set high up in each level. Due to its stability and ability to drive through water (and there is a lot in the stunt races), the monster truck is the best bet by far, even taking into account its slow speed.The final, fifth stunt track is unlocked by beating all the others. It pits the player against the other cars in a fixed isometric viewpoint much like an RC racer, and challenges the player to smash into each vehicle (blowing it to pieces) in the shortest amount of time.There is also a two player mode in Stunt Race FX, but it's limited compared to the single player - the already small view shrinks further, and the players are limited to four tracks that have much less detail.VehiclesStunt Race FX features five vehicles, although one of them (the semi) barely counts as its slow, unwieldy, and can only be used during the grand prix bonus rounds. The other four are ranked in terms of speed here:Monster Truck - Huge tires, high durability, fast acceleration, slow speed. The monster truck can drive through water just as fast as regular pavement, although it never hits much of a top speed in either case. Good for beginners, it accelerates fast and can take a solid beating, but it's of little use other than the stunt races.Compact - Tiny tires, and a moderate rating everywhere else, this is sort of a lame duck in the roster of Stunt Race vehicles as it excels at absolutely nothing. It does hit a higher top speed than the monster truck, but its tiny tires guarantee it will grind almost to a halt while driving through water and it cannot match the top speed of the faster vehicles.Racer - Medium-size tires, low durability, slow acceleration, and frightening top speed. The racer is a decent vehicle for the grand prix courses, although it requires much more skill to use due to its high speed and propensity to explode at a moment's notice.Motorcycle - Huge tires, moderate durability, fast acceleration, high top speed. The motorcycle is unlocked through gameplay and it's easy to see why it's not available at the start. It takes some getting used to as it only has two tires and tends to turn differently than all the others, but it can take more of a beating than the racer, has better acceleration, and it's not subject to slowing down while driving through puddles of water.Cheat: Arwing in Night OwlIn the Night Owl stage, there should be four small "StarFox" signs on the walls of the course, that fall if you crash into them. Ram all four signs, and an Arwing from Star Fox will fly in and drop a power-up.Cheat: Control the animation when the game is pausedPause the game and when the pause animation comes up, press R to make the animation run in slow motion.  Press Y to speed up the car in the animation, or press Select to make it run backwards.Cheat: Control the animation when the game is paused To play battle Trax alone, select Battle Trax made and cars for both players. After the green light, wait about two seconds before hitting the gas. Any vehicle not activated by a controller will be driven by the CPU.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>UiZ3YxDGQ7A</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3270</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588705-stunt-race-fx</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/stunt-race-fx</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/stunt-race-fx/3030-19991/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/7uokPnN.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/bY60eYJ.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/JAqIgaJ.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/RcMCbW7.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/KjxVblg.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/r76axEU.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/9kB2HFo.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/tlumi5b.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6LhNkbx.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/R2Oyj2S.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/musJ4Pe.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/HAZT8iW.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/7FSRCda.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Q9vEnCa.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/FlAvBAQ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QabRu8v.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/6HKtj54.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UU3BeQX.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/i06Q86V.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The updated Super FX chip allows you to shift into high gear! Get behind the wheel of a formula racer, a 4WD monster truck, a subcompact or a motorcycle. Each will provide a unique driving experience. Choose from over 20 pedal-to-the-metal Trax. There are the no-holds-barred Speed Trax where you hone your skills and progress from a novice to a master. Stunt Trax provides an obstacle course rally complete with ups, downs and jumps. Battle Trax means head-to-head conflict in surprising terrain. For speed, variety, action and fun, Stunt Race FX finishes far ahead of the competition!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>8hEXEpLiv0I</VideoURL1>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9e622ad-3b40-4ac8-a147-207a5466ee6a.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f4a539ac-e281-41f6-a936-9f15039fcb98.png</boxart8>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/045d70bf-b980-45c1-acea-a995509b404b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d6ef9ef0-8022-41c6-9daf-ed52a1188a7c.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99d877af-09dd-492c-a882-ed734934f386.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>