<Game>
	<Name>Sunset Riders (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Sunset Riders is an action game from Konami that sets four bounty hunters across the Wild West to claim rewards on wanted outlaws. It began as an Arcade game in 1991, which allowed for up to four players simultaneously. It was later ported to the Sega Genesis in 1992, and the Super Nintendo in 1993.The Arcade version was intended to be part of the XBox 360's Game Room, but it never transpired. Gameplay:Sunset Riders has four playable characters: Steve, Billy, Bob, and Cormano. Steve and Billy have revolvers while Bob has a rifle and Carmano uses a shotgun. The rifle and shotgun have a slow firing rate, but fire multiple bullets in a spread. The revolvers only shoot one bullet at a time, but the bullets fire at a faster rate.Players move on a 2D plane while being able to aim and shoot in eight directions. Some stages have two planes, an upper plane and a lower plane, that they are able to jump back and forth. Most stages pits the players going through a stage battling enemies and course obstacles until the reach the end of the level, where the stage boss awaits. Some bosses have henchmen assisting them, making the boss battle more difficult for the players to contend. Once the boss is defeated, the player is awarded the bounty on the targeted outlaw. If two players are present when the boss is defeated, the bounty is awarded to the player who hit the boss the most.Watch out for that log!There are three stages out of the eight that differ from the other five where the players walk and battle their way to the end boss.Stages 2 &amp; 7: These two stages puts the bounty hunters riding on horses throughout the stage until they reach the boss at the end of the level. The players stay on one plane and navigate the level by battling enemies that ride horses along the bottom of the screen along with a wagon where an enemy tosses logs from the back of it to trip the hunters off of their horses.Stage 4: The fourth stage is fought inside a saloon where the bosses stand on balconies at both sides of the stage with a huge chandelier hanging in the middle of the stage.Power-UpsSunset Riders features the following power-ups to assist the player in battling enemies in the Wild West.Rapid Fire: Increases the character's bullet firing rate.Dual Fire: Gives the character a second weapon. Revolvers (Steve/Billy): One revolver shoots forward, while the second revolver shoots upward.Rifle/Shotgun (Bob/Carmano): Dual fire expands the area of the character's bullet spread.1-Up: Gives the player an additional life. Players can also earn an additional life by reaching a particular monetary benchmark.The player can acquire the two power-ups (rapid fire, dual fire) by killing an enemy with the sack, entering doors at certain buildings, or at certain areas of a stage. If the player already has both power-ups, they will receive additional money instead.Bonus StageGet ready!Sunset Riders features a bonus stage that is played after the completion of the second and fifth stages. The player can aim the crosshairs and in eight locations of the bonus stage (essentially in all sides of the screen). Enemies pop in and out of the eight locations. The player earns bonus money on the amount of enemies shot in the stage.Stage BossesStage 1: Simon GreedwellGreedwell: bury him with his money!Simon battles the bounty hunters on a balcony protected by two barrels and henchmen that appear out of the two doors next to him.Stage 2: Hawkeye Hank HatfieldHank battles the bounty hunters by jumping back and forth between crates across the train tracks with henchmen providing assistance.Stage 3: Dark HorseDark Horse battles the hunters while riding on his armor plated horse. Henchmen provide assistance by shooting at the hunters popping out of the saloon's windows.Stage 4: The Smith BrothersThe Smith Brothers battle the bounty hunters inside a saloon with one brother tossing lit lanterns while the other tosses bombs that explode upon impact on the ground.Stage 5: El GrecoEl Greco battles the bounty hunters with a shield and a long whip. He also jumps around a lot to particular spots of the train to leverage his strengths against the hunters.Stage 6: Chief ScalpemChip Scalem battles the bounty hunters on an stage where he uses the three pillars on the stage's background to jump off and toss knives at them. If the hunters are near Chief Scalem on the stage, he will attack them with the knife.Stage 7: Paco LocoPaco Loco fights the bounty hunters on top of a fortified wall while henchmen attacks with guns and bombs popping out of a tree above htem.Stage 8: Sir Richard RoseSir Richard Rose battles the bounty hunters in front of his mansion. Rose can defeat the bounty hunters by firing bullets from his gun as well as slide attack when he's on the ground level of the stage.Genesis VersionThe Sega Genesis version of the game is considerably different from the Arcade and SNES port. Only Billy and Cormano are available to play in this version with four stages that have two parts. The first half ends with the character(s) rescuing a tied up damsel in distress, while the second half ends on a boss battle.The four bosses in this version of Sunset Riders are Simon Greedwell, Paco Loco, Chief Scalpem, and Sir Richard Rose. Most of these bosses are similar to their Arcade and SNES counterparts, with the only difference being the Paco Loco fight, which takes place on a train.The Genesis's bonus stage also differs from the Arcade/SNES version. Within the four stages, players can shoot objects that may yield a sheriff's star for a limited time on screen. If the player collects this star they get to participate in a bonus stage for extra lives and money. The bonus stage pits the character riding on a horse chasing after weaving stage couch where someone in the back hurls prizes towards the screen. The player can collect more than one star per level, but the bonus stage can only be done once. If two players are playing, each player must get their own star or risk being left out of the bonus level.Cheat: Advance directly to final levelEnter the ''Options'' screen and use the d-pad to enter the codeCheat: Advance directly to final levelWhen 1PLAYER, 2PLAYERS, OPTION text is displayed on the title screen, press R, L, R, L, R, L, A, R, L, R, L, R, L, Y.  Now enter options.  You can now select up to 5 REST and 5 CONTINUE for any difficulty mode.Cheat: Advance directly to final levelAt the character select screen, press shoulder buttons L, L, L, L, L, R, R, R, R, R.  Now select a character.  The stage select and sound test will appear on the next screen.Cheat: Play on Very Hard ModeMost people probably aren't aware of this. However, if you beat the game on the Hard difficulty (either by yourself or with another player), the game will start you back at the first level. The amount of rests and continues you had when you beat Hard will be retained (and *not* reset/restored to the default), but any gun powerups you had will be taken away. The game is now noticeably a lot harder; bullets travel even faster, especially in boss fights. Bosses also have extra health. This mode is *not* selectable from the Options menu, so you have to beat the game on Hard every time to attempt it.Cheat: Extra ContinuesStart a one player game. When you run out of continues, before your last man dies, press START on controller 2 so you can play as Player 2 with a full set of continues!Cheat: Extra ContinuesStart a game with player one then get yourself killed. Continue on the game over screen with player two and select the same character as player one did. During gameplay press start on controller one and player one will join as the same character.  Cheat: How to make Richard Rose much easierThis works best with the first player, since you start the battle on the left side of the screen, but the second player can do it too. When the fight starts, move your character just under the right side of the left balcony. You'll want to position him so that he's under the flower pot sitting on the balcony's ledge. From there, jump up, and if you did it right, you'll be on top of the ledge of the balcony (not the balcony itself). Crouch down and begin shooting the enemies that come to you from all sides except the top-right. This works best if you have both gun powerups. As Steve or Billy, you can simply hold Down and Y with both pistol upgrades and you'll never get hit. Do this until all of his guards are gone (except the one on the top-right). Now destroy the statue surrounding him and then the last guard.Normally, with the balcony destroyed, you'd have to handle Richard and his guards at the same time. This way, however, you can focus solely on him without worry. In addition, if you're using Steve or Billy and they have both upgrades, they can actually damage Richard while destroying the balcony, which means you'll basically finish the first part of the fight immediately after the statue is destroyed. This is especially useful for the harder difficulties.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>CQhOkQEDt2Y</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3271</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588706-sunset-riders</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/sunset-riders</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sunset-riders/3030-5690/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4WVkXXn.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/PlIaL2a.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ToqRsA9.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/sFrzAYS.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/i4N0gSC.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/BpdPlbu.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wupTIUE.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/UorHmTI.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/XFFXeI4.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/soNgI8g.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/2Y7LOIC.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FXwZ7uf.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MS3Orz1.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/qmmn3rL.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/uMaD1ZR.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/8cNSzLx.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/HjiCs18.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ULbuHZe.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You're the fastest gun in the West and a bounty hunter voted most popular by the Dodge City Undertaker's Union. But look what's waiting to knock you off your high horse: Shotgun blast for shotgun blast, this game features the same 7 levels you had a showdown with at the arcade. Doesn't that make your trigger finger itch like crazy?! Lead will fly non-stop from authentic old west towns, to desert ambush zones, to Indian villages. Catching up to train robbers and stagecoach bandits will not only exhaust your horse, it'll make you feel like you've just run a marathon with a cactus in your shorts. Search for the hideouts of Hawkeye Hank Hatfield, the Smith Brothers and other notorious outlaws. Along the way be sure to round up special weapons that'll quicken your draw and double your firepower. As a real ladies' man, you'll also be rewarded handsomely for your efforts off the trail. Talk about riding into the sunset! If you think beans and a campfire don't mix, wait'll you see what hits the fan when you mix it up with desperadoes in the bonus bounty stage. Not enough? Oh, buffalo chips - you know it is! Heck, even Clint in his prime (many moons ago) would find this game a fistful.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/94280ee9-8c8a-409e-bbe4-936b48d5774c.png</banner2>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1115c77e-63ec-40b0-9497-57f8faaec186.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e4475104-7cac-49ba-b0c0-2f8dc1968d7b.png</boxart7>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/812973a2-5678-4b73-b55f-48973f3c72e9.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f18c3d90-016d-41d9-bfdd-3c2d49886d7d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d14d5e84-1e4f-4b31-b944-6e609a288e43.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>