<Game>
	<Name>Super Turrican (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Super Turrican is the next generation installment of the famous Turrican Series. Once again it is up to the U.S.S. Freedom Forces to get into their Turrican Assault Suits and drive back the forces of "The Machine".Similar to it's predecessors, Super Turican features large levels that are crammed with secrets and can be explored freely and in any direction. To get rid of the numerous enemies, Turrican can use three upgradeable shots: A spreadshot, a powerful laser and a rebound that bounces off of walls. Additionally, there is a Freeze-Beam that can be used to temporarily freeze enemies. It is fully rotatable, and therefor also a great help in discovering secret capsules. These capsules contain powerups and can often be used to reach secret areas. Last but not least, Turrican has the ability to transform into an energy wheel (as long as he has enough special energy), which enables him to lay mines and even makes him invincible.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/9/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Kemco/Seika</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>D2wu70VFTSU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6177</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588761-super-turrican</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-turrican</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-turrican/3030-9378/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/zbHhyKf.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9q2i6La.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/PsN2nRF.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/krwMKbK.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/FmDjjOt.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/BtUgTQ6.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/nypRaak.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/dMsnAyF.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/tDgWaLz.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/LEqj6sB.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YUEDoYG.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/yuFF9Z0.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/pcBB39x.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/dTR2iDy.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/9HmYzho.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WaDtCay.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/nMY0XOq.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>With so much firepower at your fingertips, you're expected to win, right? Wrong! Even with a super beam, smart bombs and power line super weapons at your disposal, your enemies will see that you face the ultimate in terror! Super Turrican is one of the finest Action/Adventure games you'll ever see, feel, play or hear! That's right, hear! With full-feature Dolby Surround Sound, if the incredible graphics don't toast you, the sound alone is enough to turn your brain into a crispy critter Try and survive 13 levels of the most unusual worlds ever seen Over 1000 screens. High-tech weaponry. Brilliant special effects, 3-D graphics and exhilarating gameplay!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b197b3e6-a857-4938-9d34-8745bb892961.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e32c3464-5273-4825-83b4-edf415625ca2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/11ceb863-7761-4e32-b0d4-9cfa3879bc6b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/902a0251-5e71-466a-b9ff-da9ed5cc5986.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/381011af-6c52-4dfc-aea5-83dfdc494dc8.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/83320b5e-5688-4a8b-8972-868f078d94b8.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/af74c0de-7daf-4a9d-9b14-88fbe08fb97f.jpg</snapshot15>
	<Publisher>Seika Corp</Publisher>
</game>