<Game>
	<Name>Super SWIV (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Imagine if all the mega weapons in the world fell into the wrong hands. And then were turned against you. That's the time for major firepower. You've got to take the wheel of a jumping, whirling, gun-heavy jeep that fires in any direction. Or master the controls of a deadlyfast, missile-loaded helicopter. Both war machines have special capabilities. Both change into different vehicles on certain levels. It's up to you to pick the right weapon. So get ready to collect your flamethrowers, plasma cannons, lasers, guided missiles, nuclear weapons and more. There's no time to assemble forces -- it's just you or you and a partner going straight into the blazing, blasting heart of enemy territory. Make sure you buckle up. And put your finger on firepower.Cheat: CodesDuring the game, pause and press the following buttons on the appropriate stage to skip ahead one stage:Cheat: Power UpAt the beginning of Level 1, steer to the far right to find a yellow container. Blast it open and collect the Bullet tokens to power up.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Side Scroller</genre>
	<Developer>Sales Curve Interactive</Developer>
	<rating>7.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>oRAmj6-prq0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18649</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588336-firepower-2000</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/firepower-2000/3030-1450/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/5DWQNYC.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/dXOi8xt.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JRKKuiK.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/uTrgXq1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/GX5gPGL.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ZRZPofj.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Wifh669.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/oRkRUhq.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/P13bcU4.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/95wAN0w.jpg</snapshot8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8iriHP1.jpg</banner1>
</game>