<Game>
	<Name>Super Play Action Football (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Play Action Football is a follow up to the game NES Play Action Football. The camera angle for the game is isometric and top-down. Because the angles are diagonal, players move towards the top right of the screen as opposed to moving forwards or upwards as with traditional football games. The game features three different modes of gameplay: High School, College, and NFL. Each mode features a quick play option for both 1-2 players, but College and NFL has season long modes as well.High SchoolThe High School mode allows the player to create a school of their choice, including team name, and color of uniform. This mode is the simplest of the three modes in terms of both controls and play selection. Only 8 plays are allowed on offense and defense in order to keep the game to its high school roots.CollegeCollege mode has a season mode in which the player can choose knock-off schools from the NCAA. Mascots and school nicknames are not allowed as Nintendo was not being able to secure licenses from both the NCAA and NFLPA. At the end of each game the player can read a newspaper that would highlight the biggest games of the previous week including the top 20 schools in the nation. 16 plays are allowed for both offense and defense as well as expanding the control set from High School mode.NFLThe NFL mode features the most expansive move list and play selection of the three modes. All of the 28 NFL teams (at the time there were 28 teams) are featured with mascots, however without the license from the NFLPA, real-life players could not be added. The season mode is just as robust as the College mode, featuring a full season mode with proper divisions and a playoff match resulting in the Super Bowl.Cheat: Guranteed Blocked PATThere is a glitch on the PAT that will allow you to block the kick each and every time your opponent goes for one after the touchdown.Cheat: Guranteed Blocked PATHave your player line up over the center before the snap.  When the holder shouts "Ready," press down and the Y button to jump over the line of scrimmage.  If you do this correctly, you will be between the center and the holder.  Do not touch anyone yet, as you get an offsides penalty.  Cheat: Guranteed Blocked PATWhen the holder shouts "Set", press the START button, which brings you to the pause screen that shows the score, quarter, etc.  Wait for one second and press the START button again.  You will still be inbetween the center and the holder, but the game doesn't acknowledge your presence!  This makes the kick easy pickings now.  When the ball is snapped, wait for the ball to pass through you and into the holders hands.  You should easily be able to press Y again to jump onto the holder and snuff the kick.  Cheat: Guranteed Blocked PAT</plot>
	<releasedate>20/8/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>o9jcWFKezlw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6168</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588746-super-play-action-football</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-play-action-football</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-play-action-football/3030-455/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/7YH4Osm.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/0EAuaDq.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/pQeG4Wz.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/D4m2Y82.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/tmyEOD8.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/59zVr83.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/vGhlEbU.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/oyHasZO.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/wlJiLCl.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/DpIMjAV.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/3adTaVf.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/RRe0lFk.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/epscSIp.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/s2aoo6n.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/AmLjP2F.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Full Power Action In Three Football Leagues! Dive, spin and stiff-arm your way to football glory! All 28 NFL teams, 97 college clubs and a competitive field of high school squads are represented. You can choose from up to 32 offensive and 16 defensive plays, then change your offense on the fly with an audible. The realistic graphics feature a close-up on the action and a radar view of the entire field. If you're hot in the college ranks, you'll shoot up to the Top 20 and earn a prestigious bowl bid. Do well in the pros and you'll head for the Super Bowl. Post-game stats announce how each team and each NFL player ranks as the season progresses. One of two players can challenge the computer or two players can face-off in exciting head-to-head competition.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bc60567b-cb74-4725-80fb-d153ae338d08.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/590708b8-4074-4edc-8e10-2e8a9bed3424.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f531950c-4c97-4f44-aef4-11e672ad482f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a042ce52-c0f2-46d7-babe-802db6742840.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>