<Game>
	<Name>Super Formation Soccer 95 della Serie A (Japan) (UCC Xaqua Version)</Name>
	<plot>Super Formation Soccer 95: della Serie A is a Sports game, developed and published by Human Entertainment,which was released in Japan in 1995.Cheat: Super Formation Soccer 95 della Serie A Information* On the Exhibition Player entry screen, whilst holidng X,L and R on the second controller press A. If the lowest entry on the screen turns into hiragana you have been successful. You can now select the entry on the top-right of the Team Selection screen and you will be able to use 3 hidden teams.* Whilst dribbling if you press twice quickly in the direction you are moving the player will jump.* In an Offensive Game in Practice Mode, if you press Select during a Throw in, Corner Kick, Goal Kick etc the remaining time will change to 45 minutes.* If you press Select on the Team Selection screen, you can select 'Random Team'. If you press X, you will see some info about the teams.* If you pause the game during a match and press B the players' names will disappear. If you repeat this, their names will reappear.* Put the cursor over the Situation Mode's 'Cleared' entry and press A and X as the same time. You will be able to select Reverse Mode which has different conditions required to clear it.</plot>
	<releasedate>31/3/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Human Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>wxR6zxbIPEI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26307</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571266-super-formation-soccer-95-della-serie-a</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-formation-soccer-95-della-serie-a</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-formation-soccer-95-della-serie-a/3030-37247/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/En7JXmS.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/fQkJgg2.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/sTmaLMe.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xhjZwCF.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/YaUCZM3.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/t2s2Wv4.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Rs3Klwc.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/MLvuQEv.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CFJNSdy.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/LoL193Y.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/mIwgoe0.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/RNLg7Cd.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/RMEgJq3.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/L0za3ZH.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Super Formation Soccer 95: della Serie A is a Sports game, developed and published by Human Entertainment, which was released in Japan in 1995.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1ce223dc-4df1-4d1f-ad38-16878801bc99.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8bb2a92c-18bf-4610-a68a-b991bbc1e4da.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Human Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>