<Game>
	<Name>Super Ultra Baseball 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Culture Brain's Ultra Baseball (Baseball Simulator in the US) series is a unique baseball statistical simulator. Players have the option to create their own Team, choose manager personalities, uniforms and stats. Additionally players have the unique option of using the Ultra League where players have higher stats and super Ultra powers!Super Ultra Baseball 2 is the fourth game released in the Ultra Baseball Series. The first two games were released in the US under the titles of "Baseball Simulator 1,000. Culture Brain planned to release this game as "Super Baseball Simulator 1,000 2 but later canceled the release.This patch has been 100% translated into English, additionally (thanks to Ryusui's ASM coding) the speed has been changed to MPH, as the original version uses kilometers. I also changed the stadium sizes from meters to fully "Americanize" the translation.http://www.romhacking.net/trans/1393/</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/2009</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Culture Brain</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>BYJgOAFKX4o</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>31469</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571099-super-ultra-baseball-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-ultra-baseball-2/3030-49620/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/q204axa.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/JlBSuGA.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/UGVgaY9.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/E43cW9K.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/R4BPL3X.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/9QwZOzO.jpg</snapshot4>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/f107CSY.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Super Ultra Baseball 2 was released in Japan only, as the fourth game in the Ultra Baseball series  (known as the Baseball Simulator series in North America) These baseball titles included some form of "Super League" where pitchers and batters would have special abilities.  Baseball Simulator 1.000 (1989, NES), also known as Choujin Ultra Baseball  Super Baseball Simulator 1.000 (1991, Super NES), also known as Super Ultra Baseball  Ultra Baseball Jitsumeiban (1992, SNES) NPB licensed.  Super Ultra Baseball 2 (1994, SNES)  Ultra Baseball Jitsumeiban 2 (1994, SNES) NPB licensed.  Ultra Baseball Jitsumeiban 3 (1995, SNES) NPB licensed.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6c5a5515-55d3-4848-a631-663c3e3b4c1c.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/96b28f8c-0dac-4d85-adbe-3327b23a6328.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Culture Brain</Publisher>
</game>