<Game>
	<Name>Super Billiard - Championship Pool (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Here's a straight game of 8-Ball to play against your friends - no trick stuff - with rock 'n' roll riffs dancing on your eardrums. All the thrills of one of the world's most popular games is yours whenever you want it, and you'll never even have to wait for a table! Championship Pool gives you all the excitement of pure pool play, with unique features you may not find in any other electronic billiards product. And this NES pool game is officially endorsed by The Billiard Congress of America. Pit yourself against the computer or challenge up to 7 human opponents using the Party Pool option. Choose from zoom-in and zoom-out screens, and choose the music to get you going! Think you're a shark? Try Tournament Mode where only the best players qualify for the world championship tournament. Play 8-ball, 9-Ball, straight pool or over 15 different games!Chalk up and rack 'em... It's your break!Cheat: 9 Ball Championship Secret WarpTo skip the first four qualifing opponents in the 9-Ball Champisonship, go to challenge mode and select Speed Pool. Get a score of 140 or lower and exit out to the tournament mode. After selecting 9-Ball and your break type you will be warped to the next level automaticly skiping the first four opponents.Cheat: 9 Ball Championship Secret WarpPlay the Equal Offense Challenge and score EXACTLY 13 points in the first round. Quit the game and then start the 8 Ball tournament. After set-up, you'll be sent directly to the World Championships, skipping the first half of the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Card, Billiards</genre>
	<Developer>Bitmasters</Developer>
	<nplayers>4+</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3485</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588248-championship-pool</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/championship-pool</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/championship-pool/3030-13437/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/blgH4K3.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/U0J4i31.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/hCsQ5s0.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/V2Hh3nn.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/HaWbCzF.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ejz4ORF.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/qyLFaPs.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/TKEu29N.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/zzWgkOM.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/Wavhgr4.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/h3MjUWT.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/j9nOCoj.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/lX25w5W.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/jSQDj1Q.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/nU8KktN.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/1tNZBgO.png</clearlogo1>
</game>