<Game>
	<Name>Super Bases Loaded (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Bases Loaded in the first Super Nintendo entry in Jaleco's Bases Loaded series of baseball games, known in Japan as Super Professional Baseball. The game uses an unusual perspective for its batting/pitching, and employs far more realistic-looking athletes. This is counter to Namco's more famous Super Famista/Super Batter Up, which uses super-deformed characters. Super Bases Loaded was followed by the Japan-exclusive Super Professional Baseball II. The second Super Bases Loaded, Super Bases Loaded 2, is actually a localization of Jaleco's later game Super 3D Baseball.Gameplay:Super Bases Loaded plays similarly to actual American baseball, and is housed under most of the same rule sets: one team hits while the other fields and pitches; four balls pitched outside the invisible hit-box constitutes a free base, while three suitable pitches results in a strike out. While many advanced rules are also in effect (such as bunt-strike outs) others - balks, infield "fly-outs," foul-pole home runs - are curiously absent. Additionally, players controlling the pitcher can deliberately pitch at players, resulting in neither the batter nor pitcher being penalized beyond an extra base. When players swing, however, their hit-boxes are eliminated, allowing pitchers to throw balls through the batter, and still receive a strike. There is a ten-run mercy rule limit in effect at all times, and a game can only last for up to 23 innings.Each pitcher and batter has a unique stance. Unlike previous entries that largely randomize hits, the game employs a variable physics engine that accounts for timing, bat, and pitch speed, as well as completion of swing, and registered statistics for both the batter and pitcher. Pitchers' speed and accuracy stagnate after every pitch, allowing pitch speeds to range from above 100 mph to below 60. Gravity involving the ball, however, is largely unrealistic, as balls can remain up in the air for periods lasting over 10 seconds. Bunts, especially, can be nearly impossible to execute without being caught. Likewise, lateral ball travel is also markedly sluggish.Baseball can only be played in Bases Loaded Stadium, under the same conditions. The stadium walls are riddled with fake advertisements parodying real-world counterparts. The audience will cheer after every play, with the same enthusiasm, for both teams.The game includes a robust single-player campaign, challenging players to play a "perfect season," or a season composed of eleven perfect games free of runs, hits, and errors.RosterDespite the North American release sporting Ryne Sandberg's endorsement, Super Bases Loaded contains a roster of twelve fictional teams, each with fictional players and statistics. Players can also choose to edit a team together (literally as "Team Edit"). Individual roster statistics can be adjusted to build near-perfect players.TechnicalRuns at 640 x 480 resolution; supports limited Mode-7 3DUp to two players; can play itself automatically be selecting "Watch" modeSoundtrack consists of ten themes, two of which alternate during playThe baseball that enters the screen in the intro can be controlled via controller slot 2There are no transitory animations for catching the ball, which makes it appear to strike the player's backIf a swing is executed after the ball enters the strike-zone, it will not register, and any ball will not be regarded as a strikeA knuckleball can be enabled by quickly cycling the D-PadCheat: Control the IntroductionWhen the ball appears on the screen (after the Jaleco screen), hold L and R and move the control pad in any direction to move the ball around as it comes toward you.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>9.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>HvzPgYefvsA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>9249</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588712-super-bases-loaded</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-bases-loaded</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-bases-loaded/3030-21659/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/sXLCa8t.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/lrq00Xe.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/XXWIP4z.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/irRGRsf.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/PowqtDH.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/0AvLCcS.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/2Zpy2I8.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/sNJ3sWH.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ao9LMTE.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/sKOGenP.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/2qVqQK2.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/FtgFput.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/QfijRQ1.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/G87WLVS.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/VsfxkKa.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Are you ready to play the perfect game? Bottom of the ninth, one out, man on first, game on the line. You're shading the batter toward second, hoping fora game-ending double play. Suddenly, a line smash, deep in the hole to your left, in one split-second motion you dive, you're up with the ball, you flip it to first to double the runner. Game over? Not yet. SUPER BASES LOADED introduces an exciting new element to the Super Nintendo Entertainment System game play. It rates your abilities in 13 skill categories. The better you get, the harder it gets! It challenges you to play error-free, clutch baseball against the toughest, most talented competition in the game.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33506f3c-87ea-462e-b94d-2c6664871d81.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f8d8cd31-4617-4e73-854b-a0cffb1da1dc.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/01ef780e-4b64-42ad-bdb3-08a30d6a45c8.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2703b39a-fece-498d-8495-c26cc35cae7d.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a73b6111-d17d-4352-982e-b8de3a5716b2.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b4c70795-e494-40d4-8897-9e591e2a5f06.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Jaleco</Publisher>
</game>