<Game>
	<Name>Super Valis IV (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Super Valis IV is an Action game, developed and published by Laser Soft,which was released in Japan in 1992.Cheat: CodesAt the "Press Start" title screen, press: Up, Down, Left, Right 3 times, Select, Select, Y, B and Start. If done right, the stage select menu will appear. Now, while playing if you press Select you'll be able to skip stages. Also, if you pause the game and then press Select, you'll be able to listen to the game's music.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>Ympke_0C8Yk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6327</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588764-super-valis-iv</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-valis-iv</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/a80hUaj.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/NZjExPE.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/mBI9Ldr.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ixUs9bA.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/EuTjgYy.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/PTdKr1E.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xNHbX7r.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/3N3Klaj.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/7pCzRc5.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/q0ThcHN.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5VFmEYS.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/CT2KmGh.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/LJWzrUi.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/LUsLbX7.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Rl1Jbkn.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/jrZxzYN.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The most intense threat to the Valis warrior has come to life. . . Eons ago in the passages of time. . . King Gallagher and his generals began a war to possess the Giya world, using the Ring of Titan which has infinite power. The lord of Giya was angered so greatly by this maneuver, he destroyed the ring and sealed Gallagher and his followers into a crystal pillar and buried it deep under the sea. One electrified evening the red moon broke through the clouds and calmed the motion of the sea. The gigantic crystal pillar suddenly rose toward the sky with a thunderous noise, parting the sea in two. The rising of the red moon awakened the evil King Gallagher and his generals from their crystal slumber. The Valis warrior, Yuko Ahso, has become a Goddess of Valia, and attempts a desperate search for a new Valis warrior to defeat GaIlagher and his forces. The strongest fighter is Lena Brande, the only hope to save Dream World. Lena breaks out of Vecanti and heads for Castle Vanity, a Dream World beauty now defaced and controlled by Gallagher's General Dahlgen. Lena is strong and brave, but are the Dark Forces too much for her? A new Valis warrior is about to be born.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f23bc3cc-00f3-4583-a8f2-5ec4dfdacaee.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d9c0d4c4-4318-4f9b-a048-08cd67721cef.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ba429ff7-366c-4892-b7eb-04dc59dd5785.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2b403717-9a43-404d-b600-8938762cf8ec.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
</game>