<Game>
	<Name>Super Battleship (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Battleship is an adaptation of the famous board game for Sega Genesis and Super Nintendo. The player can choose to play the original board game or play a more sophisticated variant that played more like a military strategy simulation game. In the classic mode, players take potshots at each other's grids in order to sink a quintet of hidden warships. The single-player "super" mode gives the player missions to achieve.The versions are functionally identical, though the Super Nintendo version has numerous graphical improvements due to having more development time and being on a more powerful system. The difficulty in the SNES version has been lowered, possibly due to feedback from the Genesis version.							</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Mindscape</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3273</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588716-super-battleship</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-battleship/3030-21588/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Y5UsxWD.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/8CgAGRV.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/rfghwEB.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/d9h2buc.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/3AmKspl.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/APk0sJu.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/gjQzDdW.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/9mxHMCO.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/bElle2p.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/o0dYiRd.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Discover the thrill of commanding your own naval fleet of warships with this brand new spin on the classic Battleship game. Super Battleship gives you all the tough challenges of the original, plus a whole new arsenal of weapons and features. Ride the high seas with graphics so real the rookies may get sea-sick. Fire your torpedoes, aim your biggest guns and hold onto your brains as you blast your way through every battle. A challenging Campaign Scenario tests your skills in naval warfare strategy. Seek out your hidden enemy before he finds you! But hide your fleet well, or you may find your ships headed for the bottom of the sea!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/38a60b78-7275-4838-9e19-606a4fee31bc.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e841a168-76a6-48b2-9d70-de326a8e3403.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/77305541-fdd1-4b44-9468-17aef2df9b0d.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/81a7cf84-b415-4693-b67f-4b05da895882.png</snapshot7>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Mindscape</Publisher>
</game>