<Game>
	<Name>Super Castlevania IV (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: Simon Belmont, ready for his adventure!Super Castlevania IV (known in Japan as Devil's Castle Dracula) is a 2D action horror platformer developed and published by Konami for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System on December 1991.The first Castlevania game for the SNES, Super Castlevania IV is an enhanced recreation of the original Castlevania adventure, introducing many new gameplay elements (such as allowing Simon to whip in eight directions, allowing Simon to flail the whip around him, a grappling system, and a dedicated button for using sub-weapons) and content.The plot and premise for Super Castlevania IV remains the same as the original Castlevania and its other recreations: players control legendary vampire hunter Simon Belmont, wielder of the Vampire Killer whip, as he sets out through a dark, unholy castle in the year 1691 to destroy the evil Count Dracula.Gameplay:Super Castlevania IV introduced many key features that have become absent in future Castlevania titles. Simon can now whip in eight directions, where he couldn't in the original games. Holding down the attack button, Simon can brandish the whip, making it so that the player can flail the whip, thus granting greater ability to block projectiles. Simon can now use his whip to grapple on to hooks, allowing him to swing over various obstacles. Simon can adjust the length of the whip while swinging using the D-pad. Returning to IV are the spike pits, moving platforms, and other obstacles.Simon begins the first level with a basic leather whip, but can gather up to two upgrades, each increasing length and damage (returning to the short leather whip, should Simon die). Upgrades can also be gathered for sub-weapons, up to level three, though these are much rarer than upgrades for the whip. The sub-weapon upgrades allow Simon to throw whichever sub-weapon he has equipped times the level. For example if the sub-weapon is level two, he can throw two boomerangs instead of one, level three he can throw three etc. Sub-weapon upgrades will reset upon death, and picking up a new sub-weapon.The sub-weapons Castlevania is known for make a return in Super Castlevania IV. In IV, sub-weapons are assigned to a button, wheras they were used by pressing up attack in previous games. This change is due to the eight attack directions. The only other game in the series to assign sub-weapons to their own button was Castlevania: Bloodlines, as it also featured multiple attack directions. Like previous games, Simon must collect hearts in order to use sub-weapons. The more powerful the weapon, the more hearts it consumes. Hearts can be collected from destructible environmental pieces. Hearts can be collected from destructible environmental pieces.The level design is more fit to the whip's new abilities in Super Castlevania IV. There are several things that must be hit by the whip, in addition to all-new grapple hooks. Simon can use the whip to grab onto the grappling hook, and then swing across the obstacle that is in his way.Cheat: CodesNote:  When you reach the screen that says ''Enter Your Name'' leave the space blank, do not enter a name or the password will not work. Cheat: Stage passwordsNote: When you come to ''Enter your name'' Leave the space blank or these passwords won't work.       Cheat: Full ArsenalIn the last stage, before you climb the stairs to Dracula, jump down to the left.   You will land on an invisible platform.   Move all the way to the left of the screen and you will get full health, 99 hearts, a cross, a full upgraded whip, and a III stone.Cheat: Full Arsenal There are three hidden branches from the main path in this game.   The first one is in stage 3-1. There will be a point where you must descend a short vertical shaft. Halfway down here is a wall of pillars to the left. These can easily be demolished, where you will find a small side room containing hearts, cash bags, and some Roast.   The second secret, which is an actual hidden Block, is in stage 6-2. At the very beginning you'll need to pass a hallway with Axe Knights and falling chandeliers. The third archway has a chandelier but no guard. Hit the floor a couple of times and it'll crumble, revealing a stairwell into a secret area.   The last one is in Block 9-2. The third section has you jump across a bed of spikes at the beginning. After this you'll see several whirlwind tunnels and some coffins. The last upper platform on the right has a coffin and a tunnel. Let the tunnel suck you in and you'll find a hidden area full of bonuses.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>8iak17nQT1Y</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1308</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588726-super-castlevania-iv</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-castlevania-iv</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-castlevania-iv/3030-11443/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Castlevania_IV</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/KWKXyjU.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ZkNbVDd.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Mp4jAFu.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/IS9GiSL.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/CD486xo.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/QlnfTMX.png</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/AWD0EzQ.png</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/7Hmn3WG.jpg</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://i.imgur.com/hUVV9zd.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://i.imgur.com/WOqsu9i.jpg</boxart10>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/dmHgI0Z.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/sccFd31.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/w6XD44m.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/kCTLlDv.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/bADUrWk.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/pQUdHt4.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/cAgLNXD.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/O3dvFYB.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/z5DYdHI.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/rb9Lkln.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/bt7Cxb1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/jYaTiXD.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/Uzpm3nh.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/qbi0o9E.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Bsck7d7.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/ZlVcEQ2.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://i.imgur.com/9CuUvie.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://i.imgur.com/dAvS6tL.png</clearlogo4>
</game>