<Game>
	<Name>Super Goal! 2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Goal! 2 is the second Super Famicom/SNES game in the Goal! franchise of soccer games developed by TOSE and published by Jaleco. Like previous games in the series, Super Goal! 2 uses a bird's eye view of the pitch, with the two goals vertically oriented. The Japanese version is named Takeda Nobuhiro no Super Cup Soccer and licensed by Nobuhiro Takeda, a well-regarded Japanese soccer player.Super Goal! 2 received a sequel, Takeda Nobuhiro no Super League Soccer. This sequel was never released outside of Japan.TeamsSuper Goal! 2 features 24 international sides. Each side has their own stats for aspects like speed and defensive skill, with some teams vastly overpowering others.This is the full list, with trigrams:Argentina (ARG)Belgium (BEL)Brazil (BRA)Cameroon (CMR)Denmark (DEN)England (ENG)France (FRA)Germany (GER)Greece (GRE)Ireland (IRL)Italy (ITA)Japan (JPN)Latvia (LAT)Mexico (MEX)The Netherlands (HOL, for Holland)Norway (NOR)Portugal (POR)Russia (RUS)South Korea (KOR)Spain (ESP, for Espania)Sweden (SWE)The United States of America (USA)Uruguay (URU)Wales (WAL)Here are the original 24 teams of Takeda Nobuhiro no Super Cup Soccer. A few countries have been replaced, and these are marked with asterisks (*). Some of the trigrams are also different.Argentina (ARG)Austria (AUT)*Belgium (BEL)Brazil (BRA)Cameroon (CMR)Colombia (COL)*Denmark (DEN)England (ENG)France (FRA)Germany (GER)Ghana (GAR, possibly a phonetic error)*Italy (ITA)Japan (JPN)Mexico (MEX)The Netherlands (HOL)Romania (RUM, possibly a phonetic error)*Scotland (SCO)*South Korea (KOR)Spain (ESP)Sweden (SWE)Switzerland (SWI)*The United States of America (USA)Uruguay (URU)Wales (WEL)(Greece, Ireland, Latvia, Norway, Portugal and Russia do not appear in the original Japanese version. Austria, Colombia, Ghana, Romania, Scotland and Switzerland do not appear in Super Goal! 2.)	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>kSuLEg2QzAY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6159</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588733-super-goal-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-goal-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-goal-2/3030-32962/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/tQMVcMq.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Pr2GBSz.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/iNxISF6.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/iQWO6h9.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ZYQqCPn.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/K9Sn3uQ.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/xUAXN4m.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/PXea0Cg.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/sRKV2W0.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/y32eVm3.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/yvrKckr.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/w7xJg0A.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/27TnRqM.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/x0mMyoK.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Super Goal! 2 is a soccer game with the two game modes: Tournament and Exhibition, that can support two simultaneous players for one on one action, and has 20 International teams to choose from including Germany, Brazil, Argentina and U.S.A. just to name a few along with players modeled after their real-life counterparts. Players can customize each game to their liking including rule set-ups, stadiums, team formations and including the soccer ball design. It features real-life rules and regulations and soccer moves including bicycle kicks and slide tackles. It also has a password feature for player's to pick up and play at their leisure.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8cafbc73-a825-4a26-8041-838ce9bd4c4f.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0876c9d-47b0-43a1-b115-0fa6705e8a81.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Jaleco</Publisher>
</game>