<Game>
	<Name>Super Morph (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Super Morph's plot is of a child who is given a temporary ability to change between states of Solid, Liquid, Gas coming in the forms of a cannonball,a rubber ball, a water droplet, and a cloud. The player must go through over 36 challenging levels set in 4 different zones collecting special cogs from each level in order to fix a machine capable of turning him back into a normal boy.Gameplay::Before playing takes place there is a cutscene of a young boy outside his uncle's house. Once the boy goes inside the house, a scientist lets the boy try out his new machine which can allow him to change state. The machine works but something goes wrong and the machine explodes sending most of its parts everywhere. The boy must now using his new abilities go around all areas of his uncle's property and find all the missing cogs.When the game starts, the player has a choice of which area to start in. The choices are: Laboratory, Garden, Sewer or Factory. There are 12 levels in each stage, each get harder as you go along. There are also hazards for each of the forms you change into: the rubber ball will inflate when it touches spikes, the bowling ball will burn when exposed to fire, the water drop will sink when in liquid, and the cloud can be sucked in by fans. The objective for each level is to find a cog which is hidden somewhere in the level. Once you have found all 36 cogs the uncle can fix the machine and Morph can change back to his normal form, a boy.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Morph</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform, Side-Scrolling</genre>
	<Developer>Sony Imagsoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>SxErMK_LIkg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2204</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/917292-super-morph</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-morph/3030-37109/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/F9HFcl0.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/7QEyJRd.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/qI6CGMN.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/KcjGRAH.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/90jrvVE.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/LeQD4pj.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/yHPtWvn.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/TptNb1u.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/27rLLqc.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6yZ2xpF.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/pouf4lM.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/yfaSHpL.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/o33ilXL.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/TPL6tZP.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Young Morris Rolph has been trapped in limbo due to a malfunction on Dr Krankenpot's new teleport machine (how come characters with German-sounding names in computer games and films are always evil or stupid? Even Darth Vader sounds German.). Now he's been split into his 4 component parts, represented by liquid, gas, a hard ball and a bouncy ball, and he must get through 24 levels (36 on the special A1200 version - mirroring the game's plot-line of improved technology causing more problems for Morris) to retrieve the parts of the machine so it can be rebuilt to bring him back to life. The gameplay is vaguely influenced by Lemmings, as the levels are populated by lots of points which can't be crossed in all forms - walls, fires, gaps, thornbushes and suchlike. You get a set number of transformations on each level, although extra ones can be picked up at times, and there are heaters and freezers dotted around which cause transformations in some states. All this is done against a time limit. Like Lemmings 2, you can take on the next level in each of the worlds at any time, so you have to be stuck 4 times before you can't progress.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1a37096d-1a97-4758-b773-87effffa64ab.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5673d83e-8c2c-4a46-ad8e-8be9ceb06299.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sony</Publisher>
</game>