<Game>
	<Name>Super Bases Loaded 2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Bases Loaded 2 is the sixth game in Jaleco's Bases Loaded series of baseball sims, and the second for the Super Nintendo. Unlike Super Bases Loaded, which was based on the first Super Professional Baseball, this game is instead based on a separate Jaleco baseball game Super 3D Baseball - a baseball sim that experiments with a 3D viewpoint, made possible with the Super Nintendo's Mode 7 graphics and a special DSP chip included in the cart. Jaleco's Super Professional Baseball II, the sequel to the first Super Bases Loaded, did not receive a US counterpart.As with previous Bases Loaded games, the team names and logos are fictionalized but use actual American cities involved in MLB. 							</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>6145</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588713-super-bases-loaded-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-bases-loaded-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-bases-loaded-2/3030-21660/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/iV6Kyky.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/lcGpGER.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/EH9WyfA.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/F1qFs6P.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Wvw2FSy.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/lyWVxnx.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/YXwzFtp.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/WYDDLry.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/kaQ8yFe.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/FtGIqeN.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/WmWpMGI.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1TlCnX4.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/kGsmU0e.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In your hands is the most realistic, easy-to-learn, and - to put it plainly - FUN baseball game ever created! Jaleco's Bases Loaded games for the NES and Super NES have always set the standard for video game baseball, selling over 5 million copies worldwide. Super Bases Loaded 2 continues the tradition. For one thing, it's the first Super NES baseball game to employ the DSP chip, a new technology that allows 3-D movement like you've never seen before. After every crack of the bat, you actually follow the ball with an amazing 3-D "camera" perspective. But it takes more than cutting-edge technology to make the ultimate baseball game. So be sure to check out a few of these awesome features: - Battery-backup keeps track of all teams in the league. - CUSTOM TEAM option lets you design and save your own teams. - Adjustable season lengths - from 10 to 162 games. - Detailed, ever-changing player stats keep track of every play you make. - Make play as easy or challenging as you want with AUTOMATIC FIELDING and ERRORS options. - Detailed info on leading hitters and pitchers is available at any time. - Updated fatigue factors recreate pitching with stunning realism.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/691f48b5-daf6-47ec-8a1b-7336885cee3b.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/66f47948-16d7-4253-a465-03697d63130f.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/747600c1-b827-474d-9115-2d19240e5410.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/13fb9b8d-fd3c-4866-80cb-ee6d3ce07191.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Jaleco</Publisher>
</game>