<Game>
	<Name>Super International Cricket (Europe) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Super International Cricket is a cricket game for the Super Nintendo that was released in Australia, Europe and Pakistan in 1994. The sequel to International Cricket on the NES, it was developed by Melbourne House (as Beam Software) and published by Nintendo.Although featuring much improved graphics over the original version, Super International Cricket also suffered like its predecessor by missing official team and player licensing.Melbourne House followed Super International Cricket with two sequels, Cricket 96, which was developed in 1996 for EA Sports, and Cricket 97 the year after that.Trivia:The Sri Lanka team includes one "D. Mendis". Duleep Mendis was a real-life Sri Lankan cricketer.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_International_Cricket</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>7.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>21jZqqooNYA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6166</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581107-super-international-cricket</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-international-cricket/3030-21668/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/tW43HIy.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/o5HspNO.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/8ttiG4R.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/r5hbSGw.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Tr5Jlp0.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/VnvoTrX.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/wtWizPn.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/47uqeMW.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/T1oYDCp.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/UsAEHZO.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/KJMuVWn.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/gXkG1qg.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/0XpiueF.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/tkL3GZ5.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/lsaEu4k.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The sequel to International Cricket on the NES, it was developed by Melbourne House (as Beam Software) and published by Nintendo. It features much improved graphics over International Cricket and gameplay superior to all modern cricket games. However, Super International Cricket also suffered like its predecessor by missing official team and player licensing, has a one-track sound loop and one stadium. Eight teams are included: Sri Lanka, Australia, England, South Africa, New Zealand, India, Pakistan and the West Indies.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2c5d51e3-0bcb-4f0c-988a-548d475c1109.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8c25a90e-57c3-41a9-8481-008fe5b4da07.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>