<Game>
	<Name>Super Castles (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Castles is a 1994 strategy game developed and published by Victor Entertainment. It is based on, and sources, Interplay's 1992 computer game Castles. The goal of the game is to place and design the towers, walls, ramparts and moats of a number of castles in strategically sound locations and then organize the funding and manpower to construct them by managing the local populace. Players need to stay on top of their workers' happiness, monetary and nutritional needs in order to get their castles built in time.Super Castles is one of a handful of Super Nintendo games to use the SNES Mouse peripheral. It was released exclusively in Japan. </plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Victor Interactive Software</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571210-super-castles</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-castles/3030-50760/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/jt5QmE2.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/WbofwSa.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/8Iw1kvP.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ZwTS8bg.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RMttdBN.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/SDGNCXN.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/cP6oiRV.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/EQVB2iF.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Jz3kO0p.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/dE2f4eU.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Notes>Super Castles is a 1994 strategy game developed and published by Victor Entertainment. It is based on, and sources, Interplay's 1992 computer game Castles. The goal of the game is to place and design the towers, walls, ramparts and moats of a number of castles in strategically sound locations and then organize the funding and manpower to construct them by managing the local populace. Players need to stay on top of their workers' happiness, monetary and nutritional needs in order to get their castles built in time. Super Castles is one of a handful of Super Nintendo games to use the SNES Mouse peripheral. It was released exclusively in Japan.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0da5742c-9a0e-4fa9-a5e8-e9eb84a0a9c3.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40a7b0ae-f5e5-4e4f-8055-719b03ceacdb.png</snapshot10>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ae212870-83ae-4044-a9e0-ce5134576e82.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d495f145-a6b9-4cdf-9ef9-4e81e9c8df5b.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0e50af39-a9e9-48cc-b5c7-833774cc6077.png</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Victor Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>