<Game>
	<Name>Super Chinese World 2 - Uchuuichi Butou Taikai (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Chinese World 2: Uchuu Ichibuto Daikai (roughly "Super Chinese World 2: The Number One Cosmic Martial Arts Contest") is a martial arts brawler/fighter game featuring the martial arts twins Jack and Ryu (also known as Jacky and Lee) in another battle against innumerable foes. This sequel to Super Ninja Boy takes the duo into space to take down a conglomerate of evil alien martial artists who have kidnapped the leaders of the planets they've invaded. The pair move from planet to planet, beating up henchmen before finally taking down the boss in fighter-style duels (which one or both brothers can take part in).The game also features a competitive fighting mode for up to two players (and includes an option to watch two CPU opponents fight). This mode allows the player to play as any of the bosses encountered in the game. While the core game retains a few of its RPG elements, like character levels, the turn-based battles have been removed for the sake of a more action-focused game.Super Chinese World 2, unlike its predecessor, was never released in the US. A localization of the game named Galactic Defender was canceled mid-development. The game would be followed in 1995 with the third and final game in the Super Chinese World series: Super Chinese World 3: Chou Jigen Daisakusen.Cheat: Debug MenusAt the password screen, enter the following Japanese characters to access the special password screen (format is Row #, Column #): - 1,7 - 3,9 - 2,6 -. If done right, you'll enter a secret green password screen. Enter the following passwords to access the different debug menus.Cheat: Debug MenusAt the password screen, enter the following Japanese characters. Format is Row #, Column #. Once you enter the characters, select End and you'll get an error message. Select it 2 more times and the game will start on the last galaxy.Cheat: Debug MenusIn the password screen, enter:Cheat: Debug MenusAt the password screen, enter the following Japanese characters. Format is Row #, Column #.Cheat: Debug MenusAt the password screen, enter the following Japanese characters. Format is Row #, Column #.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Culture Brain Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581819-super-chinese-world-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-chinese-world-2-uch-ichibuto-daikai</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-chinese-world-2-uchuu-ichibuto-daikai/3030-1017/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/z3PYAjl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/grALPFv.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/DDxr1XX.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/edlLp1V.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6KgBZuT.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/dU9z5Ow.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/YUagjLq.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IW9PnPE.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/CjLufKA.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/eRGyLxN.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/gk17gUP.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/GQQ9MzY.png</snapshot10>
</game>