<Game>
	<Name>Super Donkey Kong (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Donkey Kong is back with a new sidekick, Diddy Kong, in a crazy island adventure! Challenged by the crazed tribe of reptilian Kremlings, they endeavor to get back their stolen banana horde! Armed with lightning-quick moves, chest-pounding muscle and awesome aerial acrobatics, our duo is ready to face their cunning adversaries. With the help of Donkey Kong's quirky family and his wild animal mounts, they squabble and scamper their way through the unending monkey mayhem.Cheat: Jump in mid-air.This works in the stage, "Mine Cart Carnage". Hit the Star Barrel in the level, and then either die or pause and press "Select". Enter the stage again. When the Star Barrel explodes, IMMEDIATELY press Y and B simultaneously. You should now be jumping in the air, keep jumping by pressing Y and B in succession. You can use this glitch to jump all the way to the end of the stage.Cheat: Jump in mid-air.NOTE: Do not backtrack to the beginning, as the glitch will stop functioning when you go back to the start.Cheat: Blast through mine cart carnageNear the begining jump over the cannon and fall next to the wall underneath. You should get blasted out of a cannon and sent in a cart almost all the way to the end of the level.Cheat: Blast through mine cart carnageTo make this work you must use a save game.On your last life die as Diddy Kong.Then press start at the "Game Over" screen. When Cranky Kong appears press down,Y,down,down,Y. You will be brought to a room with 3 of each golden animal.You can enter any of these bonus games as often as you like.To exit, just press start, then select. You will be brought back to the last place you died in your save game.Cheat: Blast through mine cart carnageAs soon as you start the level, walk left back into the entrance. You will warp to the end of the stage, where some manuevering will get you past the level.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Rare Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>8.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>SbHL8-XkXMA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>131</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588282-donkey-kong-country</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XwhWuya.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/SkOXjos.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/sDLz1Iu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/8iN7uGV.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/AK393mv.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/iIQq2cl.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/DNAXcZT.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4jI9UrS.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/306Pqf5.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nXYUfu1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/wFHLrUo.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/r2crvno.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/JKl02fc.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/yhbQpFb.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/omQjlMq.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/JQ2K9uR.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/PN5IL9D.jpg</banner1>
	<banner2>http://i.imgur.com/oqYu0th.jpg</banner2>
	<banner3>http://i.imgur.com/PHxvBJa.png</banner3>
	<banner4>http://i.imgur.com/trySAvG.png</banner4>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/GdEx7Pe.png</clearlogo1>
</game>