<Game>
	<Name>Super Ninja Boy (USA)</Name>
	<plot>One day a spaceship came down from the heavens and into the skies of Chinaland. It began broadcasting an image of peace. Soon Emperor Chin was holding a peace conference with the space ship's leader, Rub-A-Doc. Rub-A-Doc visited with some of the other places in the world before departing to the heavens and leaving the world. All seemed peaceful however there seems to be trouble starting up, strange monsters have been seen throughout Chinaland. Could the increase in monsters be somehow related to the recent visit from Rub-A-Doc? The ninja masters of Mount Edin, Jack and Ryu are sent to investigate...Super Ninja Boy is an action RPG for one or two players. In a two player game, each player controls either Jack or Ryu. In a one player game, only Jack appears.A second player may join at any time by visiting a convenience store.As mentioned, this game is an RPG and contains familiar RPG elements such as equipping differing kinds of weapons, equipment and gaining levels. The Ninja Boys are treated as a single entity and so these statistics are shared between Jack and Ryu with equal values. Battles with the enemy, either through random encounters or visible on the map is where the action starts. The characters enter a side-scrolling 'battle mode' where they may jump, fight, use their special techniques, items and spells... as well as activate various 'bonuses' on the battlefield by breaking open the bonus boxes. A battle is over and experience points awarded when a pre-determined number of enemies are defeated or the Ninja Boys are defeated.When bosses are encountered, the gameplay changes to a turn-based system. Each turn, commands are given to Jack &amp; Ryu, which include usage of special items and skills accuired during the game, who then perform actions based on those commands. The enemy's turn takes place the same way. The battle ends when one side of the conflict runs out of hitpoints.Cheat: CodesEnter these passwords to unlock bonus features:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Culture Brain USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>DVJ9F8MHs00</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2672</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588742-super-ninja-boy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-ninja-boy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-ninja-boy/3030-17548/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Ninja_Boy</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/NTxwgx6.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9Yzp85q.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/VzozviL.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/nv0ygp5.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/93JVh9W.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/yxQ9xvE.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/TnYdQeH.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ifYIl4J.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/zgHnwMU.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rvucPXq.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/DeEj5pY.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/W7WO3lV.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/dGM6nom.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/sQlgjz5.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>A peaceful life in quiet Chinaland was suddenly thrown into disaster after the Universal Peace Conference was over. The Emperor's concerns kept growing until Jack and Ryu decided to go out and settle the problem. The places they visited during their expedition were: Chinaland, Mysteryland, Fairyland and Futureland. The more they advanced, the more suspenseful it became. What they found out was a devastating plot. There are loads of exciting action, cool items, neat vehicles, great attacks and magic spells available. They are all yours to blow adversaries out of the way of the once peaceful Chinaland.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9848d8fe-438e-4014-85b2-bebbca650183.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/42141f40-17b7-4665-86f2-e51d22541561.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5159e885-aca3-44df-8228-1e6de3fd1f90.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6647b7ff-75f1-4f9c-9747-6a36d63a0be4.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Culture Brain</Publisher>
</game>