<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario Kart (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Mario Kart is a racing video game, developed by Nintendo EAD and published by Nintendo for the SNES. It was the first game of the Mario Kart franchise. It was launched in Japan on August 27 1992, in North America on September 1 1992 and in Europe on January 21 1993. It was also released for the Virtual Console in Japan on June 9 2009, North America on November 23 2009, and in Europe on April 2 2010.In Super Mario Kart the player chooses one of eight characters from the Mario franchise. Each has different capabilities unique to them. During races players can pick up power ups to help them win the race.Gameplay:In Super Mario Kart the player is tasked to take control of one of the characters and finish before anyone else. The racers race in a go-kart. The player's viewpoint during the race is behind his/her's go-kart.Game ModesThe very first race is about to begin. And... GO!Super Mario Kart is split into two singleplayer modes (Mario Kart GP and Time Trial) and three multiplayer modes (Mario Kart GP, Match Race and Battle Mode). In Mario Kart GP one player playes against seven CPU controlled characters in three cups of five races. At first there three cups that can be played on two difficulties (50cc and 100cc). By finishing first in all three cups on 100cc difficulty, a new cup is unlocked, the Special Cup. By winning the fourth cup on 100cc difficulty, the 150cc difficulty level is unlocked. In time trial mode the players race alone, with the goal of beating the other players time.In multiplayer, Mario Kart GP is the same as in singleplayer, except now there are 6 CPUs and 2 player controlled characters. In Match Race, two players compete against each other without any CPU players on any track in the game. In Battle Mode two players still go head to head against each other without CPUs on the track, but this time on special tracks created specifically for this mode. Each player starts with three balloons which are to be destroyed by the other player. The first player to have all of his balloons destroyed losses the battle.DriversMarioLuigiPrincessYoshiBowserDonkey Kong Jr.Koopa TroopaToadItemsGreen Shell, which can either be fired in a straight line forward or dropped into a stationary position.Red Shell, which acts as a homing missile and will attack the driver in front.Banana Peel, similar to the green shell, with the exception that its forward shot is fired in an arc.Feather, which allows the user to jump once - useful for getting over obstacles or finding shortcuts.Mushroom, which gives the user a temporary speed boost.Star, which makes the user invincible to everything, and also causes others to spin out on contact.Lightning Bolt, which shrinks all other drivers and causes them to drive slower.Coin, which adds a few coins when used. 100 coins will NOT award an extra life.Ghost, which can steal one item from another driver.Shrinking Mushroom, which will cause the shrunken effect to anyone who touches it (only usable by CPU controlled Princess and Toad)Fireball, a stationary weapon that spins around in a small circle (only usable by CPU controlled Bowser)Egg, similar to a banana. (Only usable by CPU controlled Yoshi)CircuitsMushroom CupMario CircuitDonut PlainsGhost ValleyBowser CastleMario Circuit 2Flower CupChoco IslandGhost Valley 2Donut Plains 2Bowser Castle 2Mario Circuit 3Star CupKoopa BeachChoco Island 2Vanilla LakeBowser Castle 3Mario Circuit: 4Special CupThe Special Cup is unlocked after obtaining gold medals in the Mushroom Cup, Flower Cup, and Star Cup on 100cc difficulty. Once a goal medal has been earned on 100cc in the Special Cup, the difficulty 150cc is unlocked.Donut Plains 3Koopa Beach 2Ghost Valley 3Vanilla Lake 2Rainbow RoadCheat: Small RacerWhen at the character select screen (only in racing) hold Y and push A and your chacter will become small. This will not effect speed whatsoever, it will only make it so your opponents can run you over to slow you down. Hold Y and push A to make yourself big again.Cheat: Small RacerGo to Time Trial or 2P Match Race, put the cursor on Mushroom Cup and press: L,R,L,R,L,L,R,R,A. If you haven't unlocked Special Cup already, it'll be available now.Cheat: Continue playing after you lose (Battle Mode)When you're on your last balloon, hop over a banana peel. After the music changes and the screen darkens, you can still drive your kart around. You can even pick up items, use them, and the Star music will play if you obtain it.This glitch stops working if you stop your kart.Cheat: Continue playing after you lose (Battle Mode)When playing Battle Mode with another player, obtain a Feather. Once earned, you use it to jump to the out-of-bounds area on the course. If you jump far enough, your character will be dragged back to the course but, for unknown reasons, remain invisible on your opponent's screen (and sometimes yours), with only the balloons visible, making it much harder for them to find you.Cheat: Continue playing after you lose (Battle Mode)When you get a Mushroom item, approach a wall on the track, preferably a corner wall that juts into the track. As you approach it, release B to decelerate and then press A to use the Mushroom and use L/R to hop "into" the wall. Once the wall is bumped, only hold L/R to keep the boost. The boost will keep going forever so long as you don't bump into anything else on the course.Cheat: Continue playing after you lose (Battle Mode)You'll need to obtain a Feather item for this. Once obtained, go ahead of the starting line and make a U-turn. Once in line with the starting line, back up to the side of the track and somewhat ahead of the starting line. Drive and leap forward over the lava at the edge of the track, onto the stony area beyond it, thanks to the Feather; be sure to land behind the starting line as well. You'll be dragged back to the track by Lakitu, and mistakenly labeled as being one lap ahead.Cheat: Continue playing after you lose (Battle Mode)On this track, when the lap begins, drive forward from the starting line and make a U-turn some point thereafter. Drive back to the starting line and, as you approach it, hop off of the left side (from your view - right on the track map) of the track and fall and "die" behind the finish line. When Lakitu grabs you back up, he'll drag you forward and past the finish line, and mistakenly glitch the game into thinking that you've just done a whole lap. You can only do this every other lap at the most, though, so only on the 1st, 3rd, and 5th laps in succession, or on the 2nd and 4th in succession.Cheat: Continue playing after you lose (Battle Mode)This trick only works on courses which have walls of blocks to the right or left of the starting line (whichever side is towards the center of the track). When a race begins, drive to the right of the finish line and begin ramming it with your kart, about in line with the actual starting/finish line. You'll suddenly begin to warp ahead laps, albeit somewhat randomly depending on where you hit the wall. It is best to hop a lot whilst bumping the wall, and aim for the center of the colored segment that is in line with the wall.Cheat: Continue playing after you lose (Battle Mode)When you get a Feather item, drive through the course as normal. As you near the finish line, make a hard drift to the left so that you're almost off the left side of the course and nearly perpendicular to the course when you finish the lap. Use the Feather at this point and you should hop in the air and back behind the finish line before you "die". Lakitu will drag you back on to the course and you'll get the extra lap counted.Cheat: Continue playing after you lose (Battle Mode)You'll need a Feather item for this. Once obtained, drive around the course as normal. As you pass the starting line, begin a hard drift to the left or right (whichever is towards the out-of-bounds area of the course's outer edge). As you approach the wall bounding the course, use the Feather. If your drifting is tight enough, you'll leap up, over the wall to the out-of bounds area, and back in without actually needing to be dragged back to the course. (Sometimes, even if you are dragged back, this glitch will still work.) You can then cross the finish line again to get the extra lap counted.Cheat: Camera PanChoose any character and go to any time trial and finish it without making any mistakes.  Now, when you watch the little replay clip of your race, press L or R to make the camera swing around your character.Cheat: Camera PanIf you finish three races in the same place, you'll earn an extra continue.Cheat: Camera PanWhen you have a ghost that you'd like to save in Time Trials, hold L, R, and Y at the menu screen that displays after you've completed a Time Trial race and press X. The name of the course on which the ghost was saved will be highlighted in yellow on the Course Select menu. To race against the ghost you saved, choose the course(the one highlighted in yellow) and hold L or R while pressing B when the screen asks ''Is this OK?'' and the arrow is pointing to ''Yes''.Cheat: Camera PanSelect 1P Time Trials and then on the select driver screen, press START on 2nd controller. It will bring up a driver select for COM. Select who you want it to be. You can now race a ghost driver anytime.Cheat: Camera PanThis speed boost can occur at the beginning of a race. When the three lights begin to count down, if you press the Acceleration button just before the second light lights up, and you hold it until the race starts, you get a boost of speed. If this speed boost is timed and positioned right, it can easily put you in first place right from the start.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/9/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>AlAmXXNz5ac</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>41</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588738-super-mario-kart</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-mario-kart</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-mario-kart/3030-19071/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Mario_Kart</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/1hUIFzH.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/EedNgIJ.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/sXbiVB9.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/RDQAwmU.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/022j781.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/fFN29fe.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/rAuDQLE.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/rS6y5fK.jpg</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://i.imgur.com/YwAK1gZ.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://i.imgur.com/WDNLQ07.jpg</boxart10>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/hb67Uor.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Q5yp4mL.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Pn18T4f.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/HfdBsUY.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/IAPIykb.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/j0oC2By.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/QYI3tkh.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/BrR53XC.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Drgk6wS.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/CuiLjBv.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/07rMnW6.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/AjLWv0y.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/V1nLqDX.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ovAWCGV.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/gHYF5q4.png</clearlogo1>
</game>