<Game>
	<Name>Super Turrican 2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Super Turrican is back, and once again the USS Freedom Forces have to prevent the evil Machine from harming innocent civilizations. This requires the player to jump and shoot his way through large levels filled with lots of enemies. To get rid of all the enemies, several different weapons can be used, most of which are already familiar to players from previous installments of the series: a Laser, a Spread-shot, and a(improved) Rebound. There is also the option to gointo "wheel-mode" for a limited time to become invincible, lay mines and shoot rockets. The Flamethrower is new to the series as well as the Rope, which can be used to climb walls, cling to platforms or pick up out-of-reach items. Much like in side-scrolling shooters, you can now pick up homing missiles as secondary weapons. The biggest difference to previous Turrican-games however, is the fact that in Super Turrican 2 almost half of the levels are strictly linear and don't feature any large secret areas that have become somewhat of a trademark of the series.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ocean Software Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>5EvIIdLWLYY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6178</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588762-super-turrican-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-turrican-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-turrican-2/3030-9307/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/jsp0TLq.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/0Sf49Kh.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/qF05Oo4.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Ysf32Nb.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/1NKbk4e.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zVxy23e.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/c2SJqMd.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/cTE9PLZ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/RiY27Bn.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/F9ClOHj.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nqSjIdP.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/pUE0sGO.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/6nPZSBx.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/rgF1CAd.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/RyaRuPc.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/YLSuJhX.jpg</clearlogo1>
</game>