<Game>
	<Name>Super Real Mahjong PIV (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Real Mahjong PIV is a mahjong game developed by Affect for multiple consoles and Japanese computers. It is the sixth game in SETA Corporation's Super Real Mahjong title, but the fourth proper game in the series, hence the IV numeral. It features three female anime characters that the player can play one-on-one mahjong against.The Arcade and computer versions (FM Towns, NEC PC-9801, Sharp X68000 and Windows) have some amount of cartoon nudity. Most of the console versions (PC Engine CD, 3DO and Super Famicom) censor/remove these scenes.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>Affect</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/565330-super-real-mahjong-piv</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-real-mahjong-piv</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-real-mahjong-piv/3030-38663/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/EUbX4KN.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/SveOPRE.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/tL0Jbn5.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/k57yNmv.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SQ7V684.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/NnqRsvP.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/CnPDDpE.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/J6bX6P9.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/cvvElGi.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/4drszXf.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/OcCbF6r.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/JnFn13F.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Originating in the arcades, this installment of the Super Real Mahjong series puts the player in the role of a mahjong club member who competes against three female opponents. Rounds won by the player lead to undressing animations; however, while the computer version has explicit nudity, console versions are censored. All the versions have the same opponents, cutscenes, and gameplay rules. The computer version adds a versus mode in which girls can compete against each other, while the Super Famicom (SNES) version has a so-called "puzzle mode", which reveals parts of a puzzle as the player wins mahjong rounds.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d8689b4-b8eb-4757-9e02-cc743ef06ccf.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2ffffed6-335c-460d-b149-4cf9d3092155.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>SETA Corporation</Publisher>
</game>