<Game>
	<Name>Super Punch-Out!! (Japan) (NP)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Punch-Out!! is the sequel to the original game on the Nintendo Entertainment System, Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!!. Although Super Punch-Out!! does not contain the likeness of Mike Tyson, it brings over familiar characters from the first Punch-Out!!! The returning characters are Super Macho Man, Bald Bull, and Mr. Sandman. Super Punch-Out!! was released in October 1994 in North America, in March 1995 in Japan, and on January 26, 1995 in Europe.Gameplay:Super Punch-Out!! has similar gameplay to the original. The player faces a single opponent, and is able to sway left and right, and execute both right and left punches to the body and head. From there, however, there are several subtleties to the gameplay that make Super Punch Out!! a much deeper experience than the original.Basic PunchingThe four normal punches players can throw vary in speed and strength. There is an inverse relationship of how fast a punch is to how powerful it is. From quickest and weakest to slowest and most powerful, the order of the punches is as follows: Left Jab, Left Body, Right Jab, Right Body. Mixing the punches up accordingly may yield extra hits or extra damage, so finding the proper mix of punches can yield quicker K.O. times for time trials.As in the original Punch Out!!, they player can throw a powerful uppercut, but instead of stars, this time there's a meter that fills up as they fight. This meter does not deplete as players use it. Instead, getting hit by an opponent depletes the meter. (The amount is based on the damage of the punch.) The uppercut, furthermore, is simply one of four available "special" punches. Players can also deal a vicious hook to the body, and rapid punches to both the head and body. The difference between the head and body special blows is the speed and power with which the blows connect, with shots to the head being slightly quicker and less powerful and shots to the body being slightly slower and more powerful.Counter PunchingCounter-punching is much more fleshed out and flexible this time around. In the original Punch Out!!, there were a few rare instances during which players could hit their opponent just as he was about to land a punch (throwing a body punch at Von Kaiser or Great Tiger as they crouch to launch an uppercut, or tagging Bald Bull in the head just before he throws a jab). In Super Punch Out!!, the counter punch's rate of success is much higher and the appropriate techniques are called out in the game's tutorial. When the opponent is about to throw a left-handed punch, the player can counter with a right-handed punch, and vice versa. One must also take the height of the blow into consideration. If he's about to throw a jab or hook at the player's face, they counter with a jab to his face; similarly, if he's about to throw a hook at their body, or crouches for an uppercut, they must counter with a body blow. The challenge is in reading the opponent's tell--each punch's tell is distinguishable from one another, but sometimes only subtly so (most difficult being the difference between a hook to the face and a hook to the body). Mastering the counter-punch is key to speedy victories and--in some cases--survival, as a successful counter-puncher ends up nullifying many opponents' attacks before they can even be unleashed.Dizzy SpellsSuccessful counter-punching or otherwise dominant performances will sometimes yield a "dizzy" animation, in which the opponent either doubles over, sways from side to side, or otherwise stumbles about. Hitting the opponent with a power punch during a precise moment in these "dizzy" animations may yield an instant knockdown and, in rare cases, result in a full 10-count and victory.Other DifferencesSuper Punch-Out!! sports a Time Attack mode, which allows players to fight against fighters from any circuit they have beaten to try and improve their K.O. times.Unlike the original, in Super Punch Out!!, speech bubbles will appear from both sides of the screen, representing orders and hints coming from the opponent's coach. These often clue the player in to which technique their opponent is about to unleash, giving them time to take proper action.Techniques employed by the fighters in Super Punch Out!! require a much higher level of suspension of disbelief in relation to the original Punch Out!!. Several fighters use weapons and what would normally be illegal blows and tactics, including but not limited to: overhead blows; grabbing and throwing; kicking; spitting; headbutts; juggling balls; elbows; and a walking stick.Super Punch-Out!! contains four circuits. However, unlike Mike Tyson's Punch Out!! the final boss does not have its own circuit. The circuits--and the fighters within--consist of:Minor Circuit Gabby Jay Bear Hugger -- uses illegal two-handed overhead strikes Piston HurricaneBald BullMajor Circuit Bob Charlie Dragon Chan -- uses illegal kung fu kicks Masked Muscle -- uses illegal spitting and headbuttsMr. SandmanWorld Circuit Aran Ryan -- uses illegal grab-and-throw tactics Keike Kagero -- uses illegal strikes via his long hair Mad Clown -- uses illegal juggling balls which he throws at Mac, as well as illegal two-handed overhead strikesSuper Macho ManSpecial Circuit Narcis Prince Hoy Quarlow -- uses illegal Kung Fu kicks and strikes with his walking stick Rick Bruiser -- uses illegal elbows Nick Bruiser -- uses illegal shoulder chargesReception:When Super Punch-Out!! was released it was praised for the style of its graphics, the simple controls and the diversity of the characters.IGN said that the game overall was great but that it lacks the appeal that the original game has. They also said that the sound and music was not as memorable.The game has a 83.5% score at GameRankings.Re-ReleasesSuper Punch-out!! was available as a bonus for GameCube owners of Fight Night Round 2 for the missing online play found in the Xbox and PS2 versions. Also, if the player beats Super Punch-Out!!, Little Mac will unlock as a playable character in Fight Night Round 2.In March 2009, Super Punch Out!! was re-released on the Wii's Virtual Console service in Europe, Australia and North America. The Japanese version was released in July the same year.The game appeared on the Wii U's Virtual Console in North America on December 26, 2013.Opponent DetailsBelow are statistics for the opponents, grouped by circuit:Minor CircuitThe Minor Circuit is the easiest circuit in the gameGabby JayGabby Jay is the first opponent in the Minor Circuit. The instruction booklet says he was trained by Glass Joe, who is the only person he's ever won against.From....FranceAge.... 56Weight....110lbs.Record....1-99Quotes:First Match: Let me win. I've lost so many times I forget how winning feels.Rematch: I like winning! Keep challenging me, it's good for my ego.Ending: I'll never retire! I can win at least one more! C'mon!Bear HuggerBear Hugger is the second opponent in the Minor Circuit. He, like many other fighters, is a semi-offensive stereotype, this one being that of Canadians.From....CanadaAge....32Weight....440lbs.Record.... 17-12Quotes:First Match: Watch out! I am a killer- I am the Bear HuggerRematch: You've come back for another spanking, eh?Ending: I've heard someone can beat me in 17 seconds.Piston HurricanePiston Hurricane is the third opponent in the Minor Circuit. He was a fighter in the original Punch Out!!! in the arcade. His stereotype is Cuban.From.... CubaAge..... 25Weight.... 170lbs.Record..... 21-10Quotes:First Match: Can you ride out the storm or be caught in my "Hurricane Rush"?Rematch: Hmmph!! Don't you know when to give up?Ending: My Hurricane Rush must not have worked...Bald BullBald Bull returns from Mike Tyson's Punch Out!!! He is the last opponent in the minor circuit. His stereotype is Turkish.From....TurkeyAge....36Weight....290lbs.Record....34-19Quotes:First Match: You'll be down for the count with one punch from my "Bull Charge"Rematch: You've got a lot of guts to challenge me again!Ending: Don't be so proud. I pulled my punches when we fought. Major CircuitThe Major Circuit is the second circuit in the game. This is where things start to get difficult.Bob CharlieBob Charlie is an original character for Super Punch Out!!! He is the first opponent in the Major Circuit. His stereotype is Jamaican.From....JamaicaAge....26Weight....140lbs.Record....24-13Quotes:First Match: "People who can't feel the rhythm are so lost, do you have the rhythm?"Rematch: "Hey you! You don't seem to have the rhythm."Ending: "Hey mon! Let's have fun once more!"Dragon ChanDragon Chan is the second fighter in the Major Circuit. His stereotype is Chinese.From....Hong KongAge.... 22Weight....130lbs.Record....15-7Quotes:First Match: "You will find yourself face down... When you wake up."Rematch: "Same results each time. The world of fighting is a harsh one, isn't it?"Ending: "When I woke up... It was me lying on the mat"Masked MuscleMasked Muscle is the third fighter in the Major Circuit.His stereotype is Mexican.From.... MexicoAge.... 29Weight.... 240lbs.Record....19-5Quotes:First Match: "You should give up now senor"Rematch: "Cheater? I don't know what you're talking about, amigo."Ending: "Have your bruises healed yet amigo?Mr. SandmanMr. Sandman returns from Mike Tyson's Punch Out!!!, presumably to get revenge for Little Mac beating him down right before he reached Super Macho Man.Stereotype: None really. But before Bob Charlie he was the only African-American in the series.From.... U.S.AAge.... 28Weight.... 230lbs.Record .... 29-3Quotes:First Match: "Had your goodnight kiss? 'Cause I'm about to put you down for the night."Rematch: "I hate holding back. This time I won't hesitate to use all my power on you"Ending: "Ready for your nap now? I demand a rematch!"			</plot>
	<releasedate>1/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>5dORukGBkaM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1307</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588747-super-punch-out</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-punch-out</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-punch-out/3030-6029/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Fh7aaJ6.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/FXlnnrd.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/plu0mbL.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/1jvZ2sA.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/ytvxTSU.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xJDIap0.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/fYNfpUL.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6BnrvjA.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/lfVTLkL.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/mwnoYLG.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/fjoZdGD.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/tdHPoEN.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/QtLJUBx.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/OWUwXAb.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/zUaoXYO.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/fDqyp9X.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/aSV7KRq.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/mUw54JR.png</clearlogo1>
</game>