<Game>
	<Name>Super Smash T.V. (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The year is 1999. Television is cashing in on the blood lust of its viewers. Violence dominates the screen.Topping the ratings are the TV game shows that offer the ultimate in prizes: your life! Winning and losing has become "destroyed or be destroyed." One show stands as the toughest, most spectacular, most dangerous, and most rewarding contest of all: SMASH TV.Alone, or in a pair, powerfully armed contestants are sent into a closed arena. There, before a live studio audience and devoted TV viewers from around the globe, they battle opp2onents - human, humanoid, and inhuman - and search out the cash and prizes that will make them SMASH TV Grand Champions. Ready for prime time?The future is now. You are the next lucky contestant...--From the SNES Super Smash TV instruction manual.Tips:Extra Lives and ContinuesOn the Player Select / Skill Select screen, enter this code: Down, L, R, UpKill all EnemiesEnter the stage select code first. Begin playing. Press and hold SelectSound Test ModeOn the Player Select / Skill Select screen, enter this code: L, R, L, L, RSpeed-Up CodeAt the player/skill selection screen, press left, right, left, up, R, RStage SelectPress Right, Right, Up, Down, R, L, and Start on the Player Select Screen.View the Programmer ScreenWhen the Beam Software logo appears, press and hold buttons L, R and B.http://www.consoleclassix.com/snes/super_smash_tv.html</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>lV92TwNc4gc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5863</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588753-super-smash-tv</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/smash-tv/3030-16194/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/xaSb9Oh.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Ov4SsTS.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/3irlllo.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/erMI18c.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Y4bepYb.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/L6wJXaM.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/txhFpdK.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/fYLYnMf.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/65PMJia.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/qbKJBOK.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/PnDOlx3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Dj8YxiW.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/BRbOgBm.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/YnixuiK.png</clearlogo1>
</game>