<Game>
	<Name>Super Off Road - The Baja (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Off Road: The Baja (Super 4WD: The Baja in Japan) is a third-person off-road rally driving game sponsored by Ivan "Ironman" Stewart and features The Baja 1000 race: a course that covers roughly 1000 miles down Mexico's California Baja peninsula.It is the sequel to the original Super Off Road, otherwise known as Ivan "Ironman" Stewart's Super Off Road. Unlike its predecessor, which was released in the Arcades and on multiple home systems, The Baja was created specifically for the Super Nintendo. Gameplay:The player has to balance avoiding too much damage to the vehicle, which is caused whenever the player veers off into rougher terrain, and navigating their way to each leg's checkpoint within the time limit. Money is added by finding bags of cash on the field and reaching the checkpoint quickly, and subtracted whenever they collide with another vehicle. This money can then be spent on upgrading the player's 4WD rally vehicle.The player can take part in the Mexico 250, Ensanada 500 and Baja 1000 races, each progressively longer and more difficult than the last, or practice any of the first four legs of the Baja 1000 in the Pre-Run practice mode. Progress is saved via a password system.				</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Tradewest, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>1.8333333333333333</rating>
	<VideoURL>00JWFikO0ak</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3276</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588744-super-off-road-the-baja</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-off-road-the-baja</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-off-road-the-baja/3030-22272/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/QVvvJR4.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/y5RpbNa.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/C9ztSOp.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/K1PqDRr.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/5g783J0.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/crQJ6XS.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/xD1Xnc8.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/MC48qd2.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/C9pXCcm.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rygg6hS.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/2odrv5i.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/DgJkyQJ.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/AqrdsHO.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/MyT7inF.png</clearlogo1>
</game>