<Game>
	<Name>Super Star Wars (Europe) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Star Wars is a sci-fi action platformer (including vehicular combat levels) developed by Sculptured and published by JVC for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System in June 1, 1992. The third platformer based on the 1977 film Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope, Super Star Wars has players controlling the farmboy Luke Skywalker (with the option of playing as rogue smuggler Han Solo or Han's Wookiee companion, Chewbacca, on certain later levels), as he attempts to save a group of freedom fighters (the Rebel Alliance) from the Galactic Empire by embarking on a mission (along with Jedi Knight Obi-Wan Kenobi) to rescue a rebel leader (Princess Leia Organa).The game was later published by Lucasarts in Europe and Victor Interactive in Japan, as well as re-released in North America by Nintendo. The game received two sequels (based on the film's two sequels) over two years: Super Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back and Super Star Wars: Return of the Jedi. On August 10, 2009, the original game was again re-released in North America on the Wii via Virtual Console for 800 Wii Points ($8). Another platformer based on the film was released on the Game Boy Advance in 2004 (Star Wars Trilogy: Apprentice of the Force).Gameplay:Super Star Wars features fifteen different levels. Eleven of these use either Han, Chewbacca, or Luke, unlocking each character as the plot progress. Each character comes equipped with a gun that can be upgraded throughout the course of the game that allows increased rate of fire and in one instance, homing ability. However, there is little difference between the characters until Luke reaches receives his lightsaber which functions as the game's only melee weapon. Luke may switch between his pistol and lightsaber at any given time. There are also two landspeeder levels, where Luke must get to his next destination while shooting Jawas. In the final two levels, Luke must pilot an X-Wing and destroy tie fighters and destroy the Death Star. Both the landspeeder and X-Wing levels use Mode 7 graphics.Super Star Wars is notorious for it's difficulty with numerous onslaught of quick enemies, unforgiving pitfalls, difficult boss fights, and lack of any password system or other game saving feature.WeaponsLaser BlasterFlame BlasterProton SeekerRapid Ion GunPlasma Wave BlasterLightsaberPower-UpsPlasma Shield - Temporary invulnerabilityThermal Detonator - Clears screen of enemiesHealth (Small and Large) - Regains healthTime - Increases time to finish the level. Counts down from 50.Bonus - 2x Points. Several can be picked up to increase the multiplier by 2,with 8x the maximumHealth Sword - Increases size of health bar to hold approximately one large health.Extra Life - One more life	</plot>
	<releasedate>1/6/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>JVC Musical Industries, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ky7bcCuK_Ao</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2658</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563218-super-star-wars</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-star-wars</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-star-wars/3030-14450/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/7CtKNVV.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/LK68hIR.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/nvKuVMI.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/0HYfrrx.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/M27XGZe.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/5wqBNHy.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/FJNMjCt.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/gAi1X9t.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/w8Ded4q.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/jBl10Dd.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/IanSeHQ.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VlcHIHQ.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/6XQh6sx.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/d8zj1wH.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/KpFmO7X.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/RoU2ySU.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/Acajzoc.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/AbW8Jn2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/3wmW6bL.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/paNTxXB.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/68Abx54.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/4Hy8lJa.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Join Luke, Han and Chewbacca in their fierce war against the evil Empire. Battle treacherous aliens. Pilot two vehicles in high-speed, first-person, 3-D sequences. Fight your way through the wastelands of Tatooine to the hostile streets of Mos Eisley and beyond. So grab your blaster, strap on your lightsaber, and take on the fight for galactic freedom.</Notes>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1c18b8d5-df0c-4c45-84df-163427cfa0c6.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6c9db170-c8db-4750-8658-0bf5bf913856.jpg</boxart8>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4bfdb9b2-f726-4164-9da5-44fb9f6cb56d.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/01a75582-8c30-4377-8995-343761c01199.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/78b385ac-66fe-4f36-afd2-d54fdabb64d2.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ed563a0b-1a28-4c7e-9ff0-c241f1beed38.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99c27f15-eb04-4546-b892-854842e07ad3.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f84e2355-fc1d-41cb-9b2d-8b09daa3b295.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c6f94f22-ad80-43c8-8112-62147257aeb4.jpg</snapshot16>
	<snapshot17>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a82b24ac-a0c8-4b86-a083-8d8eaab51227.png</snapshot17>
	<snapshot18>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d4fc812b-bb47-4b84-ba05-d5810650d3e1.jpg</snapshot18>
	<Publisher>JVC</Publisher>
</game>