<Game>
	<Name>Super James Pond (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>James Pond is primarily side-scrolling game starring the James Bond spoof hero, James Pond. James Pond is a walking fish with body armour, who is in a battle with his adversary Dr. Maybe. Dr. Maybe has captured lots of penguins as well as toys. Given the code name RoboCod (a pun on RoboCop), the remaining penguins send James on a mission to rescue the other penguins, retrieve the toys and defeat Dr. Maybe.James starts outside a giant castle that turns out to be Santa's toy factory. There are many doors there, two and two situated next to each other. Each door leads to a stage with many toy-theme levels, 50 in total. Hostile creatures lurk about in these levels, and they come in all thinkable forms. There are no weapons in the game, so James must jump upon them to defeat them. After completing two stages (doors), James goes on to another door where a boss is awaiting.James's body armour enables him to extend his body vertically to incredible lengths and grab hold of the ceiling. This allows him to travel along the ceiling and drop down on the top of an unsuspecting enemy. James can also pick up items that provide points. Power-ups include extra lives and wings that grant James the ability to fly. From time to time James may enter a vehicle, namely a car, plane or (flying) bath.Product Placement:In the original UK version of the game, the penguins featured as in-game product placement for the McVitie's biscuit company's Penguin Biscuits, making it one of the earliest games to use this form of advertising. According to a 1994 article in the UK edition of PC Gamer, Penguin outsold arch-rival KitKat for the first time in the product's history soon after the release of the game.Tips:InvincibilityAt the start of the game, collect these 5 items in this order:CakeHammerEarthAppleTapPower ComboCollect the following items in order to refill your power batteries-Penguin, Oil Can, Wine Glass, Earth and Racket-spelling POWER.Unlimited LivesGo to the Sports level and play until you find a giant white ball on it's own. Collect the items in this order: Lips, Ice cream, Violin, earth and snowman. Now you will have unlimited lives.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Pond_2Cheat: InvincibilityAt the start of the game, collect these 5 items in this order: Cake Hammer Earth Apple TapCheat: InvincibilityCollect the following items in order to refill your power batteries - Penguin, Oil Can, Wine Glass, Earth and Racket - spelling POWER.Cheat: InvincibilityGo to the Sports level and play untill you find a giant white ball on it's own. Collect the items in this order: Lips, Icecream, Violin, earth and snowman. Now you will have unlimited lives.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>American Softworks</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>_KgW2w0FYu0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3274</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588736-super-james-pond</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/james-pond-2-codename-robocod/3030-397/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/DtSZ36G.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Zqd2Ux6.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/sHWmdJI.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/gqWHBo9.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/9GamhNB.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xizegyr.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/VHycP3s.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/SVffNeB.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/t49KlQr.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/345BCyK.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ivtqNll.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/xbnd1cM.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/xlFmxXq.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/J31XEAE.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/dd1YHJE.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dr. Maybe's dangerously fishy plans for world domination continue. In a slimy effort to sabotage the worlds largest toy factory, he has planted penguin-bombs in toy factories inside the North Pole! James Pond bubbles to the rescue in another massive oceanic adventure!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5688fe06-f6da-461c-a5e8-56894ed8c62d.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a280f3d1-82a8-4ddb-b7cc-a7f645988638.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ef74b881-e859-4933-b11c-32ac8eb4777f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab970aac-0997-4f2c-9df0-2ffe6a262bc4.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>American Softworks Corporation</Publisher>
</game>