<Game>
	<Name>Super Donkey Kong 2 - Dixie & Diddy (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Okay kid, wipe that drool off your chin and listen up if you really want to learn something about this game. Sure, it's got newfangled computer graphics and what Diddy calls stereo sound that 'rocks heavily and with little resistance!' BUT, the game play? Well, they FINALLY added some proper challenge to the game - a snap for me of course. AND THE STORY? You sure ask a lot of questions, kid! Kaptain K. Rool and his cruelest cut-throat Kremlings have kidnapped that flea-bitten ape Donkey Kong. I figured I'd rescue him when the little pip-squeak DIDDY pops up along with his girlfriend, and they head off fixin' to prove themselves heroes or something. Come to think of it, I haven't laid eyes on those two for quite a while. I just may have to help them out after all!Cheat: Access the Sound testWhen you get to the game select screen highlight two player contest and press down 5 times to get to music test and another 5 times to get to cheat mode. Once in cheat mode, press these buttons to activate the cheats:Cheat: Beat Screechs Sprint Without RacingOnce you get half way through "Screech's Sprint" you will transform into the bird, and, normally, you will fly up to Screech and the race will start.  If you come up right behind Screech to where the race will not start yet, and you fly upwards (you must have both characters at this point for this to work), you will then hit the the ceiling and hurt yourself causeing yourself to blink.  Quickly, while you are still blinking, pass Screech and head off to the rest of the level without having to worry about doing it in good time.Cheat: Extra ending Deafet K.K.Rool in the secret lost world boss to see an extra ending.Additionally, collect all 40 DK coins for an alterate extra ending.Cheat: Extra endingTo unlock the Lost World, you must pass the first world. In the all the other worlds, you will start to find a ''Klubba's Koisk'' in each world. When you visit one, a Kremling named Klubba will ask you to give him 15 Kremcoins to enter The Lost World. If you do give 15 Kremcoins to Klubba in a particular world, you will unlock one particular level of the Lost World.Cheat: Rickety Race - Boost BarrelIn Rickety Race, when you jump into the minecart, hold left. When the light turns green you will go backwards and hit a hidden "+" barrel which will cause your cart to drastically speed up -- even allowing you to plow through the first three racers instead of having to jump over them.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Rare Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>9.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>8PjfATqzN7Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1525</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588283-donkey-kong-country-2-diddys-kong-quest</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/t2GQsUJ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/WbHsodQ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/I9NgHSR.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Vgqhl2m.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wyipkDa.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/CXWdxXb.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/CpQrLYH.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/lq13NGy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/0Nbvlc8.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/FAsIOKR.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/4Ewzs6y.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/iEm8bWI.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/hrrZzlm.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/BoAWAJo.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/XeXDwWc.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/IW9iYJl.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/VdkLuvX.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/14NxFbC.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>http://i.imgur.com/u4WExtA.jpg</fanart7>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/id4Lq9R.png</banner1>
	<banner2>http://i.imgur.com/gXUwIuK.png</banner2>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/b5B9Hkm.png</clearlogo1>
</game>