<Game>
	<Name>Super Inindou - Datou Nobunaga (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Inindo: Way of the Ninja, or Inindo Datou Nobunaga in Japan, is a fantasy JRPG that is based loosely on the Warring States Era of Japanese history. The premise of the game sees the player control of a band of heroes and mercenaries in a quest to defeat the tyrannical daimyo Nobunaga Oda before he can conquer all of Japan.Koei developed and published the game for many home systems as a companion for their more realistic Nobunaga's Ambition series of strategy war sims set in the same historical period. It was eventually remade with better graphics for the SNES, where it is known as Super Inindo Datou Nobunaga in Japan.Gameplay:The game uses a turn-based combat system to fight battles while exploring dungeons. Many of the game's dungeons are optional, but the player must take risks. The game features a time limit, and the player's party must be sufficiently leveled and powered up if Nobunaga is to be defeated before the time limit expires. This means that the player must be willing to take on optional content to increase the party's strength without allowing too much time to pass.Cheat: Gain Money Without Passing TimeThis method is a lengthy, but otherwise practical way to earn money without having to fight in battles or performing tasks that all use game time. First off, you need a Healer Companion on your team (Like a Sage or Hermit), and they have to have the Special Skill(s) Cure 1 and/or Cure 2. Second, you have to be in a Castle/Village that sells Health Food and/or Energy Pills. All skills in this game do not use magic, making this moneymaking method very practical. With the Cure 1, you can convert Health Food (that costs 40) into Body Healer items (that costs 80) and with the Cure 2, you can convert Energy Pills to Energy Ups. Stock up on Health Food (Or Energy Pills if you have Cure 2), give them to your Healer, and use Cure 1 so that all Health Food turn into Body Healers. Once you have all converted Health Food to Body Healers, sell these Body Healers for 56 Gold, earning a 16 gold piece profit. Same thing with Energy Pills, convert with Cure 2, and sell the Energy Ups for profits. Repeat the Buy, Convert, and Sell process as many times as you need to so you have all the money you can ever have so you can buy strong weapons and items in a town.</plot>
	<releasedate>19/7/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Koei</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>IfjJEuNMApI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1990</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588388-inindo-way-of-the-ninja</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/inindo-way-of-the-ninja/3030-4729/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inindo:_Way_of_the_Ninja</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/PBNSp7W.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/iyxj2SM.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/5sBIfop.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/3XKy53x.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/lINefes.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/CQEWUj7.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/FVUzg1e.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/M9re7ci.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/lhectDc.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/tCQFTkN.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/sUpl2eK.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/T3vwnsa.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/d9ACB6b.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/zpSYG0L.png</clearlogo1>
</game>