<Game>
	<Name>Super Rugby (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Rugby is a competitive Rugby Union game from TOSE and Tonkin House released in late 1994 for the Super Famicom. Despite featuring an internationally popular sport, the game was never localized or released outside of Japan. It is based on the real-life eponymous Rugby Union league that features teams from South Africa, Australia and New Zealand.The game depicts the action via a horizontal perspective, and zooms in when the ball is held by a player. When the ball is kicked, the camera zooms out to let the player see the entire pitch. The game includes scrums and all the other rules and features of Rugby Union.</plot>
	<releasedate>21/10/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>TOSE</Developer>
	<VideoURL>tpGxzt081js</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571154-super-rugby</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-rugby/3030-42892/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/mvOO3I8.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/d2JQuvR.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/JmZH4JH.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/bcUkuiV.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Nsszsjk.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/p97Q70V.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/XugyNpx.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/EvRmwiz.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/SLpHFgn.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/BLvMOs2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/4sPy7qn.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Based on the real-life eponymous Rugby Union league that features teams from South Africa, Australia and New Zealand. The game depicts the action via a horizontal perspective, and zooms in when the ball is held by a player. When the ball is kicked, the camera zooms out to let the player see the entire pitch. The game includes scrums and all the other rules and features of Rugby Union.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2bacf886-6197-4db6-b89b-c3e136d1d4e9.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/69f297ab-0f29-48c3-8c8d-8da18d4b99ce.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Tonkin House</Publisher>
</game>