<Game>
	<Name>Super Bikkuriman (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Bikkuriman is a fighter game from BEC (Interbec) and Tom Create, based on a popular collectible sticker franchise. Specifically, the game is based on the 44 episode 1992-93 anime adaptation with the same name, and features most of its cast of characters in the roster. The game includes two modes: a single-player elimination tournament against increasingly difficult computer opponents, and a versus mode for up to two players.In the single-player mode, the player can only choose from two characters: Phoenix and Tiki. The two characters fight almost identically. They fight through the other six characters from the versus mode and a "clone fight" against the character they did not select. Beating the game leads to the ending and a password (A, B, L, R, X, Y, Start) that allows players to select the same character as their opponent in versus mode.CharactersPhoenixTikiMaster Poseidon Dark HeraSaladdinLittle MinosDevil ZeusDavidasCheat: Play as the same character in versus modeTo play as the same character in versus mode, on the title screen press A, B, L, R, X, and then Y. Now press Start. Both players may now select the same character for a single fight. (The code must be reentered after every match.)</plot>
	<releasedate>29/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Tom Create</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570905-super-bikkuriman</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-bikkuriman/3030-40729/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Gto03n0.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ahYxBcz.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/COlFJlC.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/N2kiyhT.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Ob9pXN9.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/7oNFljE.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/yxfuol5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/aICZS4b.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/sP2mXEq.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/KxiXS06.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/qh48nxc.jpg</snapshot9>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/AAbZy4N.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Super Bikkuriman is a fighter game from BEC (Interbec) and Tom Create, based on a popular collectible sticker franchise. Specifically, the game is based on the 44 episode 1992-93 anime adaptation with the same name, and features most of its cast of characters in the roster. The game includes two modes: a single-player elimination tournament against increasingly difficult computer opponents, and a versus mode for up to two players. In the single-player mode, the player can only choose from two characters: Phoenix and Tiki. The two characters fight almost identically. They fight through the other six characters from the versus mode and a "clone fight" against the character they did not select. Beating the game leads to the ending and a password (A, B, L, R, X, Y, Start) that allows players to select the same character as their opponent in versus mode.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be46a9a5-0201-4982-8234-ef95242e3918.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/72903da4-dc0a-438f-a4c2-5653666a7005.png</snapshot10>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d2752533-d750-4cd2-a1a8-65d62e599473.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Interbec</Publisher>
</game>