<Game>
	<Name>Super Strike Eagle (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The player pilots the titular F-15 Strike Eagle, like in the other games in the franchise, but instead of using polygonal 3D graphics like the PC games, the game uses three different perspectives depending on mission and enemies, utilizing the strengths of the SNES hardware in regards of 2D graphics.When taking off the game starts in a third-person Mode 7 mode, it then switches to an overhead world map, where the plane can be moved between objectives and encounter enemy jets and avoid missiles along the way. When enemy planes are encountered the game switches briefly to a first-person cockpit mode, where enemy planes are depicted as sprites. When the jet arrives at mission-critical targets, it switches to an overhead bombing mode, using Mode 7's scaling and rotation abilities to its fullest.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/3/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>MicroProse Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>Vl15fVJlhbg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6175</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588758-super-strike-eagle</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-strike-eagle</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-strike-eagle/3030-39278/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/RB2eA2I.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Vgj4o60.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/gY3ojtk.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/Xbj2SeM.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/4XA0djP.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/uZanOtC.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/b4rurba.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ygNCdKK.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/qLtYqSE.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4X6sIR3.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/7NOdLLg.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rvu1mkA.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Q3Z9MEz.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/H2p6zsQ.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/UJ8I5eB.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6PEjFxf.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/MmuMP4e.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>It it's realistic flight simulation you're looking for, Super Strike Eagle is sure to blow you away! And blow your enemies away, too! In astonishing 3-D flight, you'll deliver staggering doses of firepower in vicious dogfights! You'll devastate chemical warfare plants and strategic targets! And you'll fly scores of dangerous missions through several war theaters! Of course, your opponents are well-equipped, too. But with one of America's most advanced jet fighters at your disposal, you're certain to give them a warm reception!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b43ea240-47f2-4fba-b1b5-3516a227a627.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2757ce8c-90fe-4b44-a80f-a69b38cecdb7.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/227becbe-fb3b-4316-b479-9094cb51f31b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5678124e-0ff5-4ca0-9b82-91614ea694c2.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>MicroProse</Publisher>
</game>