<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario All-Stars and Super Mario World (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The newer, 16-bit introduction to the 1985 classic, Super Mario Bros.This package contains both SNES launch title Super Mario World and the remade, 16-bit versions of the NES Super Mario Bros. games from the Super Mario All-Stars cartridge. There are no changes to the original All-Stars beyond the introduction of Super Mario World and a unique sprite for Luigi, retaining the same menu and title screens as the original.The game was bundled with the Super Nintendo in the US and Europe from December 1994 onwards. It was also made available separately.Games IncludedSuper Mario Bros (1985)Super Mario Bros. The Lost Levels (1986 Japan, Unreleased in America)Super Mario Bros. 2 (1988)Super Mario Bros. 3 (1990)Super Mario World (1991)Cheat: Acceleration Glitch (Super Mario Bros. 3)Note this glitch requires the use of a SNES controller that allows you to press both Left and Right on the D-Pad simultaneously. This glitch also only works on Super Mario Bros. 3 and only on the All-Stars releases of this game. By pressing both Left and Right, Mario (or Luigi) will move very, very quickly to the right - much faster than is normally possible, even when your P-Meter is maxed. This makes it much easier to get to the goal in a small amount of time (thus meaning more points) and also makes some gaps, previously uncrossable, now crossable.Cheat: Acceleration Glitch (Super Mario Bros. 3)Power Switches are those in-game blue buttons that reverse the rolls of the coins and solid bricks and vice-versa upon jumping on top of them. During the split-second "pressed flat" animation of the button after usage, you can use Yoshi to lick it back up--when you spit it out, it will be an entirely new Power Switch that will extend the duration of the effect of the switch.Cheat: Hidden White Mushroom Houses (Super Mario Brothers 3)If you get a certain number of coins in certain levels, you unlock a secret white mushroom house holding a powerful item. Below are the levels and the number of coins needed in each level.Cheat: Hidden White Mushroom Houses (Super Mario Brothers 3)To get World 9 in the Lost Levels, beat all 32 levels (World 1-1 to 8-4) in order without using any Warp Zones and you will go to World 9. If you beat World 9 you can go to Worlds A-D (which you can access if you beat the game with warping though).Cheat: Hidden White Mushroom Houses (Super Mario Brothers 3)To access Worlds A-D, simply beat the game once through without warping.(saving and quitting does not affect this. Simply going through every level at least once on one file will do it.)Cheat: Inverted World Map (Super Mario World)Complete teh Special World, then enter the Star Road that appears. The world maps colors will be inverted and some of the enemies will have morphed into new monsters.Cheat: Inverted World Map (Super Mario World)Once you have beaten the final Special World level (Funky), the whole world map (and caves too) will be in a completely new color. Most enemies will now look different too. This looks like Dinosaur Land changing over from "summer like" to "fall like"Cheat: Inverted World Map (Super Mario World)In Super Mario World, go to the Special World. If you sit there and do nothing for a few minutes, the Super Mario Brothers theme will start playing! It goes back to the Special World music if you leave the map by any way (going to a level or exiting). Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)To ''hide'' behind scenery, simply hold down for a couple seconds while standing on a white block. Then your player can ''hide'' behind scenery for about thirty seconds.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Complete the game and watch the ending. Now start a new game. You will start at World 1 with 28 P-Wings.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Beat a stage with your time ending in the same digit repeated twice as the tens place of your Star total, and you'll be awarded an extra life.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Example:With 17 stars, beat the stage with your time ending in 11.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)At the end of the game, when Bowser uses his jump attack on you, duck if you are big Mario, or stay still if you are small Mario. Bowser will break the bricks, but he won't hurt you. If you are small Mario, you can run right through Bowser and not get hurt.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)In other words, Bowser's lower half is harmless, but his upper half can still hurt you.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Complete levels until you get to toads mushroom house, where you get to open a chest for an item. Get the item, save and exit. Now reload the file and the levels you finished will still be completed but toads house will be back so you can get the item again! :D Repeat until you have as many as you need. Also this works for the extra lives slot and the memory card game houses too.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Try holding an item (shell, trampoline, etc) and cross the Goal line. The item you're carrying will turn into a 1-Up muhroom.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)To turn a wandering hammer brother (the ones that walk about on the world map) into a white ship full of coins, collect a number of coins that is a multiple of 11. Make the tens digit in your score match the multiple of 11. Stop the timer at the end of the stage that you are playing in on an even number.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)One combination would be: 11 coins, 9,310 as your score, and the timer at 104. This only works in worlds 1, 3, 5, and 6.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)After you beat a castle or fortress you cannot normally re-enter it. To re-enter a castle or a fortress press L+R at the same time and you will enter the castle/fortress.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Make sure you're Fire Mario/Luigi when you reach Bowser. Blast him with fireballs, but don't grab the axe just yet. Instead, wait the timer out, but make sure you're next to the axe when there's about 50 seconds left. Now get ready and time your jump on the axe so the Timer reads '000'. Once you reach Toad and the game adds the Timer to your score, you may notice that it changed from '000' to '999'. Thus the game thinks you finished with '1000' on the Timer and times that by 5. Note: this does not work on the Original NES version of the game.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)To get the N-Spade card game to appear on the World Map. You must do gain 80,000 points as one player, and successfully beat the stage that you broke the 80,000 points with.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Go to world 1-3 and find a potion. Now find the vase next to the brick building all the way to the right side of the level. Drop the potion and go into Sub-Space and then warp into the vase (stand on top of it and press down). You will warp to World 4.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Go to world 3-1 and go through the door to the large waterfall with all the clouds. Now jump down and land on the platform in the center and enter. Take the potion and drop it near the vase. Enter Sub-space and warp through the vase (press down on the vase). You will warp to World 5.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Go to world 4-2 and get the potion. Now find the vase and put the sub-space door next to it (drop it from atop the vase). Now enter sub-space and warp. Welcome to World 6.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Go to world 5-3 and get the potion (make sure you can squat-jump to the vase, you need to get someone with a good jumping ability or use an enemy to give you a boost.)Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Put the sub space door near the vase and enter sub space and warp into the vase. You are now in world 7.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)These secret items will allow you to warp. Here are their locations.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Level 1-3Find the white block near the end and crouch on to of it for 5 seconds. Then proceed to the goal, and go behind it. You will find a Mushroom house with a Whistle.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Level 1 FortressFly over the top of the level when you find the first door with your raccoon powers, and find a hidden door at the far right on the ceiling. It leads to a warp whistleCheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)Level 2 Hammer BrotherGet the Hammer from one of the Hammer Brothers here and use it to destroy the rock at the upper right corner of the Level 2 Map. Then engage the hammer brother on the other side. You should get a chest with a Warp Whistle.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)To warp to Worlds 2, 3,or 4 during World 1-2, go to the end where the 2 platforms are rising, get on the first platform, and use it to jump onto the highest structure in the middle, then jump on the next rising platform, but this time, when it reaches the top, jump onto the TOP of the level. Walk foward and drop down the small jump, and you can now warp to Worlds 2, 3, or 4 by going down the desired tube, and pressing down.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)To warp to World 6,7 or 8 during World 4-2, go to the place where three blocks are can be seen (where a pipe can also be seen). Jump below the third block where you can reveal a secret block but be careful on jumping below the 1st block because you can't break it thus going to the secret warp world unless you are a small Mario. Then step on to it and break the 2nd and the 3rd block. After you have done this, go down, then jump again below the second block now (it should have been broken now). The position of the two revealed blocks must be a stair from right to left. Anyway, step on to the 2nd block then braek the 1st block and there you can see the vine going up. Climb until you reach the day light again. Get some coins if you wish and you can now see three pipes like in the secret warp Worlds 2,3 and 4. Go down your desired pipe.Cheat: Hide behind scenery (Super Mario Brothers 3)At the very end place of world 4-2 (where you can see the pipe going to the flag) jump on the long pipe and break the brick above it and go through the end and you can see the pipe going to the World 5.Cheat: To access this warp, you must be Super or Fiery Mario. Go to the pipe at the end of the level and jump on top of it. Jump up and break the block over top of the part of the pipe farthest left. Then, position Mario on the edge of the pipe, with one foot hanging off the edge. Duck, then jump backwards as far right as possible.  If done just right, Mario will slide through the pipe and the bricks. Walk over to the warp zone area and enter the middle pipe. This pipe will take you to world 5, level 1. The same area can be acessed from a pipe in the same place in 4-2. However, this is meant to be a warp zone to 5-1, whereas the 1-2 warp to 5-1 is a glitch. After completing the jump trick in level 1-2, you can also go down either of the other two pipes, both of which will take you to Minus World -1. Cheat: This only works with mushrooms and fire flowers. Reveal a power up from under any block which contains one. Now jump onto the power up and release the A button. As Mario is transitioning to the next power up, hold down the A button, and Mario will jump in mid-air!Cheat: Go to either 1-4, 2-4,3-4, etc. and get to Bowser. Make sure you are Big Mario and try to jump over Bowser or run under him. Stand near the Axe and Bowser will start to walk towards you. As he gets near you, jump high, and touch Bowser and the Axe at the same time. If you do it correctly, you will hear the sound as if you were to shrink, but you will just flash and stay big.  Go to the next stage, and get a Mushroom. (Yes, there will be a Mushroom instead of a Fire Flower.) When you touch the Mushroom, you will shrink. Then get a Fire Flower, and you'll have Fire Power as small Mario. (Note: after you do the Bowser/Axe trick, enemies that touch you will be able to kill you when you are Big Mario. When they touch you while you are small Mario after getting the Mushroom or Fire Flower, you will turn back into Big Mario.) Cheat: This glitch only works in the castle levels where you fight Bowser at the end - for example, World 1-4, 2-4, 3-4, and so on. It is best to defeat Bowser with Fire Mario or Fire Luigi beforehand, as you must wait out most of the timer to execute this glitch. At the end of the castle levels, there is an axe which you must touch to end the level. If you time your jump correctly (a full jump as the timer goes from 002 to 001 often works) and land on the axe while the timer reads "000", you'll continue as normal to the usual sequence at the end of the castle. However, your timer bonus (50 points per second remaining) will be calculated as if you had 999 seconds, not zero, left on the clock. This allows for an easy 49,950 point boost! Note that this glitch, if executed on levels using a flagpole, will prevent you from earning the bonus in that level.Cheat: Get to world 3-1, and become Super Mario. At the end of the level, by the staircase before the end flag, you will see two turtles coming down the stairs. Jumping over the first one and then jumping on the second one should cause it to hit the star and bounce back. From here, jump on it and keep yourself off the ground for unlimited 1-ups.Cheat: After beating the game, if you do not turn off the console, you will return to the title screen. There, you can press the B Button to start as desired in World 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, or 8.Cheat: If you just walk along the sea floor, Bloopers will never be able to kill you because they are forced back up just before they hit the floor(or you).Cheat: If you run out of lives and want to continue then at the game over screen press and hold A then press start at 1 player (or 2 player) and you will start at the beginning of the world at which you died!Cheat: To warp to Worlds 2, 3,or 4 during World 1-2, go to the end where the 2 platforms are rising, get on the first platform, and use it to jump onto the highest structure in the middle, then jump on the next rising platform, but this time, when it reaches the top, jump onto the TOP of the level. Walk foward and drop down the small jump, and you can now warp to Worlds 2, 3, or 4 by going down the desired tube, and pressing down.Cheat: To warp to World 6,7 or 8 during World 4-2, go to the place where three blocks are can be seen (where a pipe can also be seen). Jump below the third block where you can reveal a secret block but be careful on jumping below the 1st block because you can't break it thus going to the secret warp world unless you are a small Mario. Then step on to it and break the 2nd and the 3rd block. After you have done this, go down, then jump again below the second block now (it should have been broken now). The position of the two revealed blocks must be a stair from right to left. Anyway, step on to the 2nd block then braek the 1st block and there you can see the vine going up. Climb until you reach the day light again. Get some coins if you wish and you can now see three pipes like in the secret warp Worlds 2,3 and 4. Go down your desired pipe. Cheat: This is a pretty commonly known secret. If you touch the flagpole of any level with either 1, 3, or 6 seconds left on the ones place of the timer, you will get that amount of fireworks. For example, if you touch the flagpole with 126 seconds left on the time, you will get six fireworks! Cheat: Well this secret is so easy. At the very end place of world 4-2 (where you can see the pipe going to the flag) jump on the long pipe and break the brick above it and go through the end and you can see the pipe going to the World 5.Cheat: While playing, pause the game, hold Up, B &amp; A on controller 2 and unpause.Cheat: Method 1:Use any character and run right toward an enemy at full speed. Just a split second before you think you're about to get hit, jump! With good timing you'll be able to jump yet again in midair! Cheat: Method 2:This is yet another way to jump in midair. Stand on the ground while you have 3 or 4 life units and let an enemy run right into you. You'll lose a life unit, but you'll be able to jump in mid-air.Cheat: This is most easily performed in World 1-1. Grab a POW block, and carry it to the set of logs. Wait for a log to bog over the waterfall, then throw the POW block so that it hits solid ground. For some odd reason, this will cause the log to fly high into the air. Strange, eh?Cheat: Go to world 1-3 and find a potion. Now find the vase next to the brick building all the way to the right side of the level. Drop the potion and go into Sub-Space and then warp into the vase (stand on top of it and press down) You will warp to World 4!Cheat: Go to world 3-1 and go through the door to the large waterfall with all the clouds. Now jump down and land on the platform in the center and enter. Take the potion and drop it near the vase. Enter Sub-space and warp through the vase (press down on the vase) You will warp to World 5!Cheat: Go to world 4-2 and get the potion. Now find the vase and put the sub-space door next to it (drop it from atop the vase) Now enter sub-space and warp. You now warped to World 6Cheat: Go to world 5-3 and get the potion (make sure you can squat-jump to the vase, you need to get someone with a good jumping ability or use an enemy to give you a boost.) Put the sub space door near the vase and enter sub space and warp into the vase. You are now in world 7!Cheat: When fighting Bowser in the final level of the game, his lower half will not do damage to you. That means you can avoid damage from his ground-pound attack by ducking if you have obtained a power-up at some point, or, if Small Mario, you can walk under him and through him without sustaining damage!Cheat: In the game, you need to wait until the N-Spade card game - which appears with every 80,000 points you earn - spawns and moves to the spot of a fortress on the overworld map. If you go there now and play it, the fortress will as if you had beaten it afterwards, being collapsed and unplayable. Note, however, that the bridges and locks affected by defeating the fortress normally will still not unlock or reappear, so only do this when these things are not required.Cheat: In World 3-4, about halfway through the level, you'll slide down a long hill to get on another long hill which has some Koopas on it. Take one of their shells further to the right. As the Lakitu appears above, return back to the left. There are two ? Blocks, with a pipe and some bricks between them and wood blocks on the ground. Let the Koopa shell begin bouncing between the wooden blocks and on-screen. The Lakitu's Spinies will almost always launch or crawl down to be killed by the shell; the shell will subsequently rack up more points and lives as time goes on and more Spinies are added.Cheat: When you come across a Kuribo's Shoe, make sure that you have a Tanooki Suit equipped. Just before you jump into the Shoe, transform into a statue. Mario will turn gray and enemies will be unable to touch him.Cheat: In this game, when you normally jump on enemies in sequence without touching the ground, the points you earn will increase from 100, to 200, to 400, to 800, to 1,000, netting a 1-Up on the sixth sequential jump and all those after. However, if your fifth (the one after 800 points) jump lands on either a Lakitu or Boomerang Bro., you'll begin getting 1-Ups right then! This glitch was fixed in Super Mario All-Stars.Cheat: At the start of World 7-1, there is a doorway you're meant to go through. Instead of doing that, run at it and jump at its top-right corner. If done with ample acceleration (and sometimes crouching just before jumping - that can help) you can glitch into the wall and skip the majority of the level.Cheat: Whenever you find a white block (such as the one in 1-3 that leads to the Whistle), stand on it and hold Down until you go through it. Then enter a pipe. In most cases, once on the other side, you'll be unable to be hurt by enemies for the remainder of the level (although sometimes also invisible).Cheat: In World 3's first fortress (just after 3-3), there are several doors you're meant to go through in the level, guessing which is the correct one. If you enter a door and it's wrong, you can immediately press Up before falling to go back through the door. Further, doing this on the third and fourth doors will warp you, instead of to the gray pipe like the other doors, straight to the boss room.Cheat: Complete the game and watch the ending. Now start a new game. You got 28 P-Wings! Cheat: Note, however, that this will not work on the Japanese versions of the game, where you simply stay at the ending screen until you turn off the console.Cheat: In Bowsers castle at the end of the game, it is possible to make it so he DOES NOT SPIT FIRE AT YOU.  This trick is easy and only requires getting to world 8 with a P-wing.  First off, use your P-wing on the map before entering the Final Castle.  YOU MUST GET TO BOWSER INTACT.  If you get to the Bowser fight room and the Bricks that he smashes through are not flush with the rest of the floor, then you are in the wrong room.  Now, when you reach Bowsers room, FLY straight up and to the left.  You will be able to walk on a wall above the screen.  Drop down on the other side. You will be in another room to Fight Bowser in.  When you drop, you will be on a door that opens to the princess.  Ignore this room and DO NOT GO TOO FAR TO THE LEFT.  If you do, you will have to fight Bowser and he will still have his Fire Balls. Fly back over the wall to the first room you were in and start the Bowser fight.  He will still throw his head back and make the sound of spitting fire, but nothing will come out.   ;)Cheat: Get to World 1-2 as Raccoon Mario, with the tail. Climb the hill at the beginning and jump over the horizontal pipe. Stand there for a bit and a whole bunch of Goombas will start walking out of the pipe. Wait for 2-3 of them to come out of the pipe, then jump ontop of one and HOLD A to fly high into the air. Now that you are in the air, use your tail to slowly glide down from the air. On you landing, be sure to land on a second Goomba. Repeat this process for as long as you can. Eventually, the points you get for hitting each Goomba will turn into extra lives. This can be done for as long as you desire to do so. This can also be done in 2-Fortress, and 7-5, but it is most notably done in 1-2. Cheat: To ''hide'' behind scenery, simply hold down for a couple seconds while standing on a white block. Then your player can ''hide'' behind scenery for about thirty seconds.Cheat: To turn a wandering hammer brother (the ones that walk about on the world map) into a white ship full of coins, collect a number of coins that is a multiple of 11.  Make the tens digit in your score match the multiple of 11.  Stop the timer at the end of the stage that you are playing in on an even number.  Cheat: One combination would be:  11 coins, 9,310 as your score, and the timer at 104.  This only works in worlds 1, 3, 5, and 6.Cheat: Get through an airship and defeat the boss as a frog, Hammer Mario, or Tannooki, and you'll receive a letter from the King that reads a little differently.Cheat: To get the N-Spade card game to appear on the World Map. You must do gain 80,000 points as one player, and successfully beat the stage that you broke the 80,000 points with. Cheat: You could just use the warp whistle at level 7... If you want to go straight to level 8, you must use a Warp Whistle to proceed to the Warp Zone, then use another warp whistle IN THE WARP ZONE. You will be transported to the level 8 pipe at the bottom of the screen.Cheat: These secret items will allow you to warp. Here are their locations. Level 1-3 Find the white block near the end and crouch on to of it for 5 seconds. Then proceed to the goal, and go behind it. You will find a Mushroom house with a Whistle. Level 1 Fortress Fly over the top of the level when you find the first door with your raccoon powers, and find a hidden door at the far right on the ceiling. It leads to a warp whistle Level 2 Hammer Brother Get the Hammer from one of the Hammer Brothers here and use it to destroy the rock at the upper right corner of the Level 2 Map. Then engage the hammer brother on the other side. You should get a chest with a Warp Whistle.Cheat: If you get enough coins in a certain course, you can get a White Mushroom House! A White Mushroom House in worlds 1,3,5,7 have P Wings A White Mushroom House in worlds 2,4,6 have Anchors Levels and required coins: 1-4 (44 coins) 2-2 (30 coins) 3-8 (42? coins) 4-2 (22 coins) 5-5 (28 coins) 6-7 (78 coins) 7-2 (42? coins)Cheat: In 8-4, as you approach the end, you'll cross a pit of lava guarded by two Parakoopas before entering a pipe. This pipe leads to a flat area (except for a dip and a pipe). Past said dip and pipe, you'll find the first Bowser, a fake one that is nonetheless difficult to beat because you cannot instantly kill him with the axe like normal - you must either dodge him, or kill him with Fire Flower fireballs. If you cannot (or do not want to), approach the gap just after the pipe while dashing at full speed - do not jump over the gap. You will run into the wall by doing so. Hold Right on the D-Pad for a while until the first fake Bowser is on-screen (you do so because the camera will not scroll otherwise). When he is about one-third of the way across the screen, you can then just hold Down and you'll automatically scroll past him, still stuck in the wall, although the camera is not scrolling. Once past him, you are free to continue on - you are not required to defeat this Bowser.Cheat: In World 1-1, go right until you see a Red Koopa boxed in by some bricks. Hit the second brick on the bottom and obtain the Mushroom from it. Then break the third brick and either the leftmost or rightmost one, trapping the Red Koopa on a single brick. You can then stomp on it, and then on its shell like in the original Super Mario Bros.'s infinite-lives trick, infinitely bouncing it back on the wall before you can touch the ground.Cheat: This glitch only works in the castle levels where you fight Bowser at the end - for example, World 1-4, 2-4, 3-4, and so on. It is best to defeat Bowser with Fire Mario or Fire Luigi beforehand, as you must wait out most of the timer to execute this glitch. At the end of the castle levels, there is an axe which you must touch to end the level. If you time your jump correctly (a full jump as the timer goes from 002 to 001 often works) and land on the axe while the timer reads "000", you'll continue as normal to the usual sequence at the end of the castle. However, your timer bonus (50 points per second remaining) will be calculated as if you had 999 seconds, not zero, left on the clock. This allows for an easy 49,950 point boost! Note that this glitch, if executed on levels using a flagpole, will prevent you from earning the bonus in that level.Cheat: Before you touch the flag at the end of a level, make sure your coin total is a multiple of 11. (00,11,22,33,44,55,66,77,88 or 99). Touch the flag when the last digit of your remaining time is the same digit as your coin total and you'll receive a 1-Up.(For example, 55 coins and 275 time left, or 11 coins and 081 time left) Cheat: To warp back to World 1, you must be in World 3-1. Near the end of the stage, jump onto the spring and fly over the flagpole. When you land, run forwards, and you'll find the warp pipe that takes you back to World 1.Cheat: When you're in World 1-2, jump onto the bricks at the top. Run forwards, and you'll go past the pipe to exit the stage. Keep running, and soon enough, you'll find the warp pipe that takes you to World 2.Cheat: To warp to world 3, you must be in World 1-2. When you reach an area where there is a pipe, a few bricks, and a Steel-Shelled Koopa, hit the first brick on the left. A beanstalk will pop out. Climb up the beanstalk, and at the top, run forwards until you reach the warp pipe that takes you to World 3.Cheat: To Warp to World 4 you must be in World 1-2.  When you get to the moving platforms jump onto the platform.  While on the platform get a running start then jump to the to the small brick ceiling then jump again to the next brick ceiling.  Keep going until you see 2 pipes.  Go down the pipe that's on the far left.  You will be led to a secret area with lava.  Make sure that Mario or Luigi is small.  Run under the small lava pit that's positioned under a brick wall.  After you make it under the lava pit keep going until you see a pipe.  Don't go down the pipe.  Instead, search for a secret coin block that's located one space to the left of the lava pit.  Then get on the coin block and look for a coin block that's  located one space to the right of the coin block that you are on.  Jump on next coin block and jump up to brick wall ceiling.  You should find a Warp Zone that leads to World 4. Cheat: To Warp to World 5 you must be in World 8-1.  After you pass the 3rd Hammer Bro go down the next pipe you see that points upwards.  You will be led to a secret water area.  Collect the coins and exit.  When you exit you will end up outside.  Go up the stairs and you will see a pipe that leads you back to World 5.Cheat: You must be at least Super Mario to do this. Near the end of World 5-1, when you see two rows of floating bricks past two Red Paratroopas, hit the rightmost brick of the top row to release a vine. Smash the brick next to it, and then climb the vine. After going through the small bonus area, you will be dropped off on a pipe right next to a Warp Zone that takes you to World Six.Cheat: Near the end of world 5-2, when you encounter the trio of tiny elevators, try to go as high as you can, so you can jump off the last elevator and reach the top of the ceiling. Continue to run right, making sure to jump when the ceiling ends, and you will eventually reach the Warp Zone for World 7.Cheat: In World A-2, about halfway through the underground part of the level, you'll find a set of staircase-like blocks. You can break through the blocks above them and get on the upper portion of the area. From there, you can run and jump heading right and past the warp pipe heading outside - this takes you to a World B warp zone.Cheat: When you are in World A-3, use the spring to get over the flagpole at the end of the stage. From there, run forwards until you reach a pipe. It takes you to World C.Cheat: In World B-4, go to the very last pipe in the level (it's next to a lava pit). Jump in the pipe and you will be taken to a Warp Zone area that will lead to World D.Cheat: In world 5-2, when you reach the three elevators, hop on the first one and use it to hit the brick immediately left of the elevator. Climb the vine that sprouts from the brick and travel through the small bonus area to reach the Warp Zone that'll take you to World 8.Cheat: Once you defeat Bowser, quickly enter this code while the princess is being freed.  Hold the buttons until the credits show up. A very strange Easter egg I must say.Cheat: Enter a level with Yoshi, Cape Mario, and a Fire Flower in reserve. Position yourself under a berry in a way that you can get the fire flower [I]and[/I] get the berry at the same time. If you happen to eat the flower and the berry at the same time, the game will freeze. Several things have been reported while using this glitch. Sometimes when the game freezes, your coin count will rise until you quickly have 99 lives. Press Start and Select to exit the leve. One person's game froze, horizontal lines appeared on the screen, and weird music kept looping over and over again. Then came a buzzing noise, and he was returned to the file select screen, with his file deleted. Thankfully, that's not normal. Even so, this is an interesting glitch to exploit every once in a while.Cheat: For this glitch, you'll need to get Fire Mario and Yoshi in Yoshi's Island 2. Near the end of the level, there is a Piranha Plant in a pipe near a Dragon Coin. Stand on said pipe, about 2/3 of the way across. Pay attention to the Rexor to the right. When he is walking left and about 3/4 past the Dragon Coin, crouch, then press X+A simultaneously. Mario will jump off of Yoshi as Yoshi attempts to eat him, and you'll get some weird glitchy item in your item storage. (If you did it wrong, the game just crashes horrifically.) If you summon this item during a level, and then grab it, the level is then completed, provided that Mario does not die while attempting to walk off-screen. Note that the orb only works once, and you need to get it again to complete another level.Cheat: In Chocolate Island 5, play the level as normal. Past the midpoint in the level, you'll begin to see a bunch of Spinies trapped in unmoving blocks (which are removed by a silver P Switch). Get the nearby blue and silver P Switches and try to drop one on top of the other so that they completely overlap each other; when done properly, attempting to grab one will grab both. Nearby, also, are some yellow flip panels, with a blank spot in the center. Get in the center and run right as much as you can. Let go of the switches and, suddenly, ? Blocks will begin appearing, spewing a multitude of Yoshi Eggs. Once a Yoshi hatches, these eggs will spew 1-Ups instead.Cheat: First all you need to do is find a switch ( the kind that changes the square outlines into brown blocks ). You also need to be on a yoshi. Normally when you hit the switch, it will flatten and disappear. When you jump on it, quicky turn around and eat it with your yoshi, if you do it fast enouph, you will have it in the yoshis mouth. You can spit it out and use it again.Cheat: Complete The secret world. (With Stage names Such as Awsome  and Tubular.)And then Enter the second Star road that Appears after you Complete "Funky" And the world Map will Have A diffrent Color Pallete and some enemies will look different.Cheat: Beat a stage with your time ending in the same digit repeated twice as the tens place of your Star total, and you'll be awarded an extra life. Cheat: Example:With 17 stars, beat the stage with your time ending in 11.Cheat: If you sit at one of the levels in Special World for about 2 minutes, you'll start to hear a Super Mario Brothers remix!Cheat: Try holding an item (shell, trampoline, etc) and cross the Goal line. The item you're carrying will turn into a 1-Up mushroom.Cheat: When you beat a castle you normally cannot enter it again.  Go to the castle you want to play again and Press L+R at the same time. </plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>OPcV9uIY5i4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3275</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/920979-super-mario-all-stars-super-mario-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-mario-all-stars-super-mario-world</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-mario-all-stars-super-mario-world/3030-544/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Mario_All-Stars#Super_Mario_All-Stars_.2B_Super_Mario_World</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/MAbP1On.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/hq12Al1.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/eWOjdxh.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/ceWay72.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/cmHkn4R.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Tokbhhu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/oNtZmYy.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8kp9ECd.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/YMTLcHQ.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/lQpGo8q.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/PJpy1re.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/pSNjLMb.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/tN7ej5q.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/y0XMO2l.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/WSuXHE3.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/isRaYwU.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/VGeiSuV.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/mvbqRtl.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/j3f8lBD.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/iAWLCKz.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/T7l16ES.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>http://i.imgur.com/RYtSxxp.jpg</fanart7>
	<fanart8>http://i.imgur.com/nNsc5aD.jpg</fanart8>
	<fanart9>http://i.imgur.com/7Hmar3J.jpg</fanart9>
	<fanart10>http://i.imgur.com/9A5lN2t.jpg</fanart10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/GGL7obu.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/x2TE2Cb.png</clearlogo1>
</game>