<Game>
	<Name>Super Fire Pro Wrestling - Queen's Special (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Long before the WWE introduced the Divas wrestling matches, in Japan there was a more serious affair, where wrestling skill was more important than breast implants, and matches were "real" (as far as wrestling goes) instead of pillow-fighting or bra and panties fights.In this game in the Fire Pro Series, the cast of the All Japan Women's Pro-Wrestling promotion are available, all fighting to win the Red belt, the highest prize of the federation. It's also possible to fight in single matches, tournaments, Battle Royal and Elimination matches. The usual array of options in CAW is present, being possible to create 16 new Wrestlers.Gameplay:, as usual is the series, is dramatically different than in most western games. Each wrestler has a bunch of moves, ranked from weak to strong. While it's possible to connect any of them from open situations, while grappling only when the opponent is already beaten the most powerful moves can be successfully used.Cheat: Unlock the boss charactersTo unlock the hidden boss characters Bull Nakano and Akira Hokuto, complete the "CHALLENGE" mode in either the singles or tag team tournament.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/6/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Human Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>28839</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/580115-super-fire-prowrestling-queens-special</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-fire-pro-wrestling-queens-special</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-fire-pro-wrestling-queens-special/3030-11265/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/9bJZAzE.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/bSCujnZ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/kuy4oHz.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/aYFa27i.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/2HozAWP.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/fi21biT.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/c8iQrkQ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/SQBkjGq.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ZpnmMik.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/3ZBSqqu.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/RqpIHRJ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/EUuzSeh.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/GR2maeu.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Super Fire Pro Wrestling: Queen's Special is based on All Japan Women's Pro-Wrestling. Every wrestler has three different variations of moves that work at different times; grappling only become available to the player after using the strongest move to weaken the opponent. Creating up to 16 customized wrestlers is a possibility; with a generous display of wardrobe options.[2] The referee has the ability to be knocked out. He cannot do pinfalls or count out opponents who are outside the ring while unconscious. Like in actual wrestling, rope breaks can be ordered by the referee. This game features genuine female professional wrestlers from All Japan Women's Pro-Wrestling; unlike the non-Joshi Fire Pro games which featured carbon copies with false names. Bull Nakano and Akira Hokuto can be unlocked for completing the challenge mode. While lacking in a proper story line, players can choose from a variety of gimmick matches.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3df1ce97-9b74-49b9-9da2-102fabac5fc5.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9799e78-5972-47a7-ac52-fa5e5c51e342.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Human</Publisher>
</game>