<Game>
	<Name>Super R.B.I. Baseball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Super R.B.I. Baseball is the first appearance of the R.B.I. series on the Super Nintendo.  It features 700 major MLBPA players and has all 28 teams along with the complete 1994 roster, but doesn't feature an MLB license, instead the teams nicknames are omitted and team colors are altered.There are six modes to choose from: Exhibition, Home Run Derby, Defense Practice, Playoffs, League, that has the player compete against each team in the game in succession and Game Breaker which lets the player choose from 17 scenarios to win the game under certain conditions.  They can also choose different Division Champion line-ups that range from 1989-1993 or All-Star Lineups from 1989-1994.The graphics of the game are presented in a cartoonish-way and the stadiums are "authentic", but altered to distinguish themselves from the actual MLB stadiums.  The game doesn't feature a battery back-up like many other baseball games, but Series championships can be saved using passwords.  Jack Buck also lends his voice talent to the game calling play-by-play commentary.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/6/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Time Warner Interactive, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>0.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6169</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588749-super-rbi-baseball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-rbi-baseball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-rbi-baseball/3030-38287/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/iLAGusS.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/wmW8pxh.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/7kLvBaU.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/oTv5NYN.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ejg4a3y.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/vwJoxio.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/xVF6JNO.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IEh7ydJ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/iBDffvU.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/NZVtUFH.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/zbQbU2Q.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/XGyaCkH.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vjBGqls.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/5VjrtW2.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>TAKE ON THE PROS! You've got nearly 700 real major league Baseball Players from all 28 Big League rosters at your control. And you can face them all on their turf - from Chicago's friendly confines to the Big Green Monster in Boston. Step up to the plate as Juan Gonzalez, Frank Thomas, or Cecil Fielder and sink a pearl in the K.C. waterworks, or see what it feels like to stare down the barrel of a loaded cannon when Duane Ward, Randy Johnson, or Roger Clemens lights up the radar at 90 MPH. You can even create your own Dream Team - how would Jose Canseco look in Florida teal or Ken Griffey, Jr. in Yankee pinstripes? You can replay classic baseball moments with the Game Breakers module and rosters of every division champ since 1989. You can even warm up your glove in Defense Practice mode. With Super RBI Baseball, it's a whole new ball game...</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>niw9N2KgB_M</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a9bd5fe4-c277-4d57-9886-732c8093d9e6.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/220c8c60-14d1-4466-96ab-a395292e288b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/add88ec2-458f-4251-8f8d-24195c95129b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b42a4bb1-8336-4fe8-ba67-deb5add5ebee.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Time Warner Interactive</Publisher>
</game>