<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario World (Europe) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Mario World (known in Japan as Super Mario World: Super Mario Bros. 4) is a side-scrolling platformer developed by Nintendo EAD and published by Nintendo for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System on November 21, 1990 (in Japan), August 31, 1991 (in North America), and April 11, 1992 (in Europe).One of the launch titles of the SNES (and bundled with early systems in North America), Super Mario World is the fifth main game in the Super Mario series. (starring Nintendo's mascot, Mario, and his brother, Luigi). The game follows both Mario brothers as they explore Dinosaur Land (known for its large amount of dinosaurs) to find and defeat the evil Koopa king Bowser (and his seven underlings, the Koopalings) while rescuing Princess Toadstool.Along with new abilities (such as the "Spin Jump"), a new power-up (the "Cape Feather") and more obstacles, the game introduces dinosaur companions (known as Yoshi) that Mario and Luigi can ride. Yoshi, known for using their long tongues to snare and eat enemies, have become a fan-favorite among the series (giving them their own games and spin-offs, most notably this game's prequel).Special bundles of the SNES in 1994 included a compilation cartridge mixing Super Mario World with Super Mario All-Stars. The only difference in this version is a new sprite set for Luigi. The original game was later ported to the Game Boy Advance on February 11, 2002 as Super Mario World: Super Mario Advance 2. Along with a special version of the original Mario Bros., the port includes a variety of differences, including Luigi as a selectable character (who now has unique features, such as his floating jump from Super Mario Bros. 2), new voice acting, and the ability to save anywhere. The original game was also digitally re-released in Nintendo's Virtual Console platform for the Wii (on February 5, 2007) and Wii U (on April 26, 2013).Gameplay:Super Mario World plays like a standard sidescrolling platformer (similar to the previous Super Mario Bros. games), where players must guide Mario or Luigi through over 75 stages, split into over seven unique areas (or "Worlds"). Each stage has a goal to reach, usually a giant moving goalpost (known as Giant Gates) at the rightmost part of the level (rarely a special mysterious exit reachable by a keyhole, requiring Mario/Luigi to carry a large key).YoshiYoshi's first appearanceMario can ride Yoshi in all stages of the game except for castles and fortresses, and can make Yoshi shoot out his long tongue to snare and eat enemies.Power-UpsThroughout each level (usually in special Blocks), Mario and Luigi can find power-ups to give themselves special abilities:Super Mushroom - Transforms into Super Mario/Luigi, giving them a taller stature while allowing them to get hit once without losing a life. They can also break some Blocks by hitting it from below and Spin Jump on Rotating Blocks to break them. This power-up glides across the ground before collected and can sometimes be found by running over special areas (like some bushes). All Yellow Exclamation Blocks contain this power-up. Running over checkpoint gates as regular Mario/Luigi automatically puts them in Super form.Fire Flower - Transforms into Fire Mario/Luigi. In addition to the benefits of the Super Mushroom, they can now throw fireballs (which can damage and destroy most enemies) by tapping the X or Y buttons. Performing a Spin Jump also throws fireballs on both sides of them. This power-up is usually stationary before collected. In the GBA remake, getting hit while in Fire form changes them into Super form (similar to Super Mario Bros. 3).Cape Feather - Transforms into Cape Mario/Luigi. In addition to the benefits of the Super Mushroom, they can now glide across the air by holding the X or Y buttons. In addition, making a running jump allows them to fly through the air (allowing them to sail with the cape by holding Up and Down on the joypad). This power-up floats left and right downward before collected. All Green Exclamation Blocks contain this power-up. Jumping on Super Koopas cause them to drop a Cape Feather.Somewhat similar to Super Mario Bros. 3, players can have the ability to store spare power-ups for use at a later time. If a player collects two of the same power-up (or if they collect a Super Mushroom while in Fire or Cape forms), it will be placed in the Reserve Box at the top of the HUD. Getting hit (or pressing the Select button in-game) causes the item to slowly descend from the Reserve Box. Also new to the game are Roulette Blocks, which can carry either of these power-ups (along with the Starman power-up below) and is chosen when the player hits the block.In addition, Mario and Luigi can find two rare power-ups that do not permanently transform them, instead temporarily giving them a special ability:Starman - Grants them temporary invincibility, allowing them to bump onto any enemies to defeat them. Unlike previous games, players can chain combos by bumping onto enemies in quick succession (giving them easier extra lives). Usually found in Roulette Blocks.Power Balloon - Temporarily inflates them allowing them to hover in the air and gradually float upwards. Found in only four levels and is not necessary for normal game progression (only required for reaching secret exits). Worlds:Dinosaur Land.There are over 75 levels in the game, each split into multiple areas (or "Worlds"). These worlds (along with the Koopaling boss in that world):Yoshi's Island (Iggy)Donut Plains (Morton)Vanilla Dome (Lemmy)Cheese Bridge (Ludwig)Forest of Illusion (Roy)Chocolate Island (Wendy)Valley of Bowser (Larry)While each world can be progressed in a narrow path, the game features an abundance of secret exits and alternate paths leading to hidden levels, bonus areas, and special shortcuts. Some of the more notable secret levels include the four Switch Palaces (allowing players to unlock special Exclamation Blocks for use as platforms and a way to earn power-ups), the Butter Bridge path (an alternate way to traverse both the 3rd and 4th Worlds), the Valley Fortress (a way to skip most of 7th World and end up at the back door of Bowser's Castle), and the Top Secret Area (a hidden one-screen level in Donut Plains that gives players free power-ups and a Yoshi).Bonus WorldsIn addition, there are two secret areas only accessible through special Star Roads hidden throughout the game: Star World and Special Zone.The Star World (up in the clouds) acts as a special "fast travel" area between most of Dinosaur Land (from the Donut Plains to the Valley of Bowser). There are five Star Roads that lead to it, each with their own accompanying level. Reaching the secret Keyhole exit in each level opens up a path between the level and another Star Road (eventually making a circular path). All levels in this area also have a hidden red, blue, or yellow-colored baby Yoshi (allowing players to gain Yoshis with special abilities).By completing both normal and Keyhole exits allows a new Star Road entrance to the Special Zone: eight challenging levels that must be completed sequentially (each with a level name resembling '80s slang for something positive). Completing all eight levels gives them a one-way Star Road back to Yoshi's House while changing the color scheme of the overworld (giving it a Fall apperance) and giving some enemies a Fall theme (Koopa Troopas wearing Mario masks, both jumping Piranha Plants and Beanstalks becoming haunted pumpkins, and Bullet Bills resembling crow-like Pidgits).While four of the Star Roads have no exit routes in Dinosaur Land (unless previously unlocked), the fifth Star Road immediately links to the front door of Bowser's Castle, allowing players to skip a large majority of the game.Enemies:Amazing Flying Hammer BroA flying enemy, throws hammers. Can be killed by hitting the bottom of his platform.Amazing Flying Hammer Bro.Banzai BillA large Bullet Bill, shoots out of nowhere and can be avoided by ducking or killed by stomping on its head.Banzai BillBlarrgA lava monster that jumps out of the lava at Mario. There is a glitch that actually allows Yoshi to eat them.BlarrgBlurpA fish that endlessly swims in one direction.BlurpBob-OmbA walking bomb that blows up after a set amount of time or when jumped on.Bob-OmbBony BeetleA mummy incarnation of the Buzzy Beetle.Bony BeetlesBooA ghost that shies away when looked at. When looked away from, the boo chases Mario.Three BoosChargin' ChuckA football playing koopa. They are known to throw footballs and baseballs. They also charge towards Mario.Chargin' ChuckBuzzy BeetleA koopa that is immune to fire balls.Yoshi can swallow them whole unlike koopas.Buzzy BeetleBullet BillA missile shot out of a cannon that aim for Mario.Bullet BillCheep-CheepA fish that swims in a set pattern.Dino RhinoA rhino that shoots fire and can only be killed while running around.Dino RhinoDry BonesA skeletal Koopa that pops back up after being jumped on.Dry BoneEerieA "Ghost Yoshi" that floats towards Mario.EeriesFishBoneA fish that swims after Mario when seen.FishBoneFishin' BooA boo that bobs down attempting to hit Mario with fire.Fishing BooFishing LakituA Lakitu that lures Mario with a 1-UP. When the 1-UP is collected, Fishing Lakitu acts like a normal Lakitu and throws Spinys.FIshing LakituFuzzyA black ball of fuzz that spin in a circle and can only be killed by a Starman.FuzziesGold Bowser StatueA hopping statue of Bowser.Gold Bowser StatueGoombaA popular enemy. In this game, they can be picked up and thrown after being jumped on.Mario holding a Goomba.LakituA flying koopa that throws Spinys.LakituMagiKoopaA wizard koopa that shoots blasts. Whenever those blasts hit blocks, the blocks turn into enemies, such as Koopas and Thwimps.MagiKoopaMecha KoopasRobotic Koopas that can be thrown when hit.Mecha-koopaMonty MoleMoles that pop up out of the ground and chase Mario.Monty Mole ArtworkMega MoleLarger monty moles that chase Mario. They can be ridden across spikes.Mega MoleNinjiCreatures that hop up and down in an attempt to hit Mario.Ninji comparison from SMB 2, Super Mario World, and Paper Mario.Pipe LakituLakitus in a pipe that pop up and throw Spinys.Pipe LakituPiranha PlantPlants that come up from pipes and try to hit Mario.Piranha PlantPodobooBalls of fire that hop up from lava trying to hit Mario.PodoboosPokeyWalking cacti that move towards Mario and can be eaten by Yoshi.PokeysPorcu-PufferFish that are covered in spikes and chase Mario.Porcu-PufferRexDinosaurs that walk randomly and have to be jumped on twice unless they are spin-jumped onto.RexRip Van FishA sleeping fish that chases Mario when passed by.Rip Van FishSpinySpike covered Koopas thrown by Lakitus.Mario avoiding Spinys.Sumo Bro.Giant Koopa that stand on overhead blocks and attack by stomping their feet. This sends lightening bolts toward the ground that will catch the ground on fire when they hit.Sumo Bros. attacking MarioSuper KoopaFlying Koopas. The ones with flashing capes will drop a Cape Feather when hit.Super KoopaSwooperBats that hang on the ceiling of caves and swoop down at Mario.SwooperThwompGiant blocks that drop down at Mario.ThwimpSmaller blocks that hop in patterns.A Thwimp (left) compared to a Thwomp (right)Torpedo TedBullet Bills of the water. Drop down from boxes and swim towards Mario.Torpedo TedUrchinSea Urchins that swim around in patterns.UrchinVolcano LotusPlants that spit several fireballs.A Volcano Lotus from the Super Mario World T.V. show.WigglerCaterpillars that get angry when Mario jumps on them.Wiggler			</plot>
	<releasedate>20/8/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>htFJTiVH5Ao</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>136</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/519824-super-mario-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-mario-world</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-mario-world/3030-1334/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Mario_World</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Pjv0AN1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/1kL21y9.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/vRkUfyd.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/EloEDDM.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/d3Nmqil.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/IHsxEUB.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/4uKZ2Y4.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/V0YUkFB.jpg</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://i.imgur.com/XfIOvZt.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://i.imgur.com/gUaku7l.jpg</boxart10>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/LJ8ZEqc.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/DCEDl2U.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/VadHHvu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/mnV7Gr5.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Q2FyW5y.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/vAiXjeZ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/xuvnMud.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/gQ3m4ju.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/JnekmOr.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/fpIVwZ4.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/lrJsVTu.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/vkeLoIa.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/rqWPgO7.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/5aiPp1T.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/qfU7LvZ.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/o2T5VsE.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>http://i.imgur.com/UfhUoUx.jpg</fanart7>
	<fanart8>http://i.imgur.com/60YwzXi.jpg</fanart8>
	<fanart9>http://i.imgur.com/Ok7995K.jpg</fanart9>
	<fanart10>http://i.imgur.com/W8f3b8O.jpg</fanart10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/n9dOFl4.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/VI0I9va.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Mario’s off on his biggest adventure ever, and this time he’s brought along a friend.  Yoshi the dinosaur teams up with Mario to battle Bowser, who has kidnapped Princess Toadstool once again.  Guide Mario and Yoshi through nine peril-filled worlds to the final showdown in Bowser’s castle. Use Mario’s new powers and Yoshi’s voracious monster-gobbling appetite as you explore 96 levels filled with dangerous new monsters and traps.  Climb mountains and cross rivers, and descend into subterranean depths.  Destroy the seven Koopa castles and find keys to gain entrance to hidden levels.  Discover more warps and thrilling bonus worlds than ever before! Mario’s back, and this time he’s better than ever!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>Vxg5eOPmzHI</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/47e31fbe-dca3-4fd9-8d9a-c90bf5ccb88f.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/911c8ac8-7245-4c8d-92cc-0052c490421b.jpg</boxart11>
	<boxart12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7c71e78f-a6c4-452d-b8dc-23a6cfda64df.png</boxart12>
	<boxart13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1a175c33-1c72-4524-bc46-9f88b566cb16.jpg</boxart13>
	<boxart14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b79d9599-7fb4-4d3d-acd2-a507ccbf3b5a.jpg</boxart14>
	<boxart15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c1e82628-c55f-4114-af5f-3e1305594050.png</boxart15>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e01ce1ed-9e84-4dec-bf74-e898e0a50e47.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1e14d6d4-ef22-49b2-ab6b-d2f103b6bb6f.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9ad85c7f-9685-41e3-aab3-42143b8eb213.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/558e1f24-69c2-407e-91b3-ff5c45e87df3.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1999b610-38ad-4874-82f6-3f719b7f86e0.png</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>