<Game>
	<Name>Super Adventure Island II (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Master Higgins finally marries his lovely girlfriend Tina. But out of nowhere, a powerful tropical cyclone destroyed the idyllic mood of their honeymoon. And not only this: it separated the ardent lovers again. After the winds stopped blowing, Tina found herself somewhere on a tropical coast. As for Master Higgins, he went to the king of Waku-Waku and, along with his main quest to save his brand new wife, got an assignment to save also a princess, whom the king was about to marry. Is there a connection between those two events?..No, this is not a detective/mystery game, but platform arcade action. What distinguish the game clearly not only from ordinary platformers, but also from the first Super Adventure Island, are its light role-playing and puzzle-solving flavors. You don't have a time limit, but huge levels with many secret sub-levels to find, puzzles to solve, and treasure chests to unlock. You also can have equipment, such as swords, shields, etc. By defeating enemies, you gain health items, money, etc. Your HP is measured by hearts, and it can increase during the game if you find appropriate items. You also encounter random enemies while traveling on a world map.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson Soft Company, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>MekPBn4y25I</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2083</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588708-super-adventure-island-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-adventure-island-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-adventure-island-ii/3030-17034/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/MYhdcxu.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ObgXnwA.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/obqNOlN.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/EsqbmvK.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8q4xujQ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/YAGSG4x.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/vVbN89j.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/m4ZWnU6.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/sk4KNtK.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/K8KxE0D.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/SIx2V08.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ur1HGJR.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/X49HS4r.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QluMd22.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/LdHcf9I.png</clearlogo1>
</game>