<Game>
	<Name>Super Hanafuda (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Hanafuda is a 1994 Super Famicom game that simulates hanafuda: a type of traditional card game where two players have to earn points by creating certain combos with the cards in their hand and the cards face-up on the table. Nintendo themselves are known for being producers of hanafuda cards before they eventually moved to video games, and many hanafuda simulators were created for Nintendo platforms to homage their history.Super Hanafuda was joined that year by Honke Hanafuda and Hanafuda Ou, both for the Super Famicom. The same developer/publisher team would go on to create Super Hanafuda 2 in October 1995.</plot>
	<releasedate>5/8/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Party</genre>
	<Developer>Use</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571109-super-hanafuda</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-hanafuda/3030-49686/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/dfuirmQ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/l8XSZAu.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/RhLUh2Y.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/xaWxrC7.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/hgGKCMf.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/dLoScQ3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/X29UqT3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/lIknpJr.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/EZM9bvJ.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/8tniKzD.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/BUUjQ0I.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Notes>Super Hanafuda is a 1994 Super Famicom game that simulates hanafuda: a type of traditional card game where two players have to earn points by creating certain combos with the cards in their hand and the cards face-up on the table. Nintendo themselves are known for being producers of hanafuda cards before they eventually moved to video games, and many hanafuda simulators were created for Nintendo platforms to homage their history. Super Hanafuda was joined that year by Honke Hanafuda and Hanafuda Ou, both for the Super Famicom. The same developer/publisher team would go on to create Super Hanafuda 2 in October 1995.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2a294e5b-431d-4093-b211-fc8cbb493126.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/62073200-2d6b-4054-9eba-e85ee6f6e515.png</snapshot10>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b40737ad-03aa-42fb-abe2-7c94bf639114.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3bbdc81b-7f3c-40dc-9098-504ad82059a9.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8f75997a-893f-408f-8627-43f3cece970d.png</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>I'Max Corp.</Publisher>
</game>