<Game>
	<Name>Super Fire Pro Wrestling X Premium (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Fire Pro Wrestling X Premium (hereafter SFPWXP) is a technically-focused wrestling game released for the Super Famicom in 1996 in Japan. It features more than 80 wrestlers, most of whom are based on real personalities from Hulk Hogan to Ken Shamrock, but with the names changed to avoid copyright infringement. It developed a significant U.S. following through the use of emulators, including fan-made translation patches to change Japanese text to English and convert the fake names of the wrestlers into their actual names.  Unlike the typical western wrestling games, SFPWXP does not feature &#8220;sports entertainment&#8221; trappings such as cage matches, ladder matches, folding chairs, breakaway tables, or any strong personality elements for the individual characters (with the exception of taunts). Instead, the game focuses on the more technical aspects of wrestling, including a very deep roster of suplexes and submission holds. SFPWXP contains an exhibition mode, singles and tag team Championship &#8220;Quests,&#8221; a 4-Man Battle Royale, and an elimination tournament. Gameplay:SFPWXP uses a fairly unforgiving timing-based system for grappling (unlike other more button-mash friendly wrestling games), where the player must press the button for the grapple they want (weak, medium, or strong) at the exact moment the two wrestlers put their arms together for a collar-and-elbow tie-up. The player with the better timing is the one who gets to execute their attack. Your opponent must be weakened before the medium or strong attacks are possible, otherwise they are automatically reversed. Create-a-WrestlerSFPWXP was among the first wrestling games to feature an in-depth create-a-wrestler (hereafter CAW) program, with a capability of storing up to eighty CAWs on one cartridge. The player can choose the CAW&#8217;s appearance, outfit, stats (distributed from a fixed number of stat points, with more stat points available if the single-player Championship &#8220;Quest&#8221; modes have been completed), and move set.  The amount of moves available to choose from are extensive, and include not only dozens of strike attacks, grapples, running attacks, and diving attacks, but also multiple special grapples from the top rope (including several variations of the Superplex), a wide variety of attacks from inside the ring to the outside (i.e. a Cross-Body Plancha), and many, many more. Unlike more modern games, there were no restrictions on what types of moves could be performed by different sizes of wrestlers, so a light-heavyweight could easily perform a Power Bomb on a heavyweight (assuming the heavyweight was sufficiently weakened). It was a common practice in the years following SFPWXP&#8217;s release for players using an emulator to upload save files full of CAWs to special fan sites. Additionally, players would post step-by-step guides for CAWs, allowing other players to make the CAWs themselves and develop a custom roster, as the existing save files could not be mixed and matched. Notable CharactersSome of the more well-known wrestlers who had unauthorized carbon copies pre-loaded into SFPWXP are:  Hulk Hogan The Undertaker The Steiner Bros.The Legion of DoomVaderThe Ultimo Dragon SabuThe Great Muta Chris BenoitTAKA MichinokuJushin &#8220;Thunder&#8221; Liger Ken ShamrockJohnny AceCheat: Unlock all hidden charactersTo unlock all the hidden characters, complete the two tournaments (in any order) in "Title Match" modeCheat: Unlock all hidden charactersTo unlock the hidden "Title Match" mode, complete the World Championship mode in either the Singles or Tag team division.Once World Championship mode is completed, Title Match mode will be added to the menu selection screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1997</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Human Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6156</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575480-super-fire-prowrestling-x-premium</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-fire-pro-wrestling-x-premium</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-fire-pro-wrestling-x-premium/3030-14721/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/51woaRm.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/d93Amt0.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/2Ngzag0.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/NRIz9SA.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/SbfelTI.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ksD5BNo.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/YHHARcP.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/uG3vC2I.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/xcM4uAu.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/GxOYAbm.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/wfoYL9H.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/g92TxVn.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In this final appearance of Fire Pro series on 16-bit consoles, the usual roster of over 150 wrestlers from several wresting promotions worldwide including several styles from Shoot or Pancrase to American and Lucha are joined by 80 Create-a-wrestler slots, plus secret wrestlers such as legends Gotch or Thesz or the roster of Blazing Tornado. While all fighters have fictional names, a lot of them are perfectly recognizable by their attire, stance and style. The CAW mode allows the player to create a wrestler from scratch, setting how they look (choosing face, size, clothing and setting colours) and fight, with several styles and stances available, as well as over 500 moves, each more suitable for certain styles and skills. To make them fight more realistically when controlled by the AI, the CAW mode also allows one to set move priorities. Five game modes are available, including World Championship (single and tag), Battle Royale, 5-man Elimination Mode, League Battle and the One Night Dream Match. There are several referees available (each with their own quirks) and variant rules, from allowing fighting outside the ring without count-out (or disallowing it) to the disabling of disqualifications from illegal moves.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ed6c417d-28ee-4ae4-b885-da4c2f7c0fff.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4611703b-1d05-43f7-bea5-e9aa51daac74.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Human Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>