<Game>
	<Name>Super Momotarou Dentetsu II (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Momotarou Dentetsu II is the second "Super" game in the long-running Momotarou Dentetsu series and the third overall. It was the first game in the series to be released on the Super Famicom: both Momotarou Dentetsu and Super Momotarou Dentetsu were Famicom games (though the latter was also released on the PC Engine and Game Boy, like Dentetsu II).The games focus on each player's burgeoning real estate corporation, allowing the players to take turns and move their trains around the board to buy properties and trade resources. It plays similarly to the Parker Brothers board game Monopoly or the Itadaki Street games.</plot>
	<releasedate>7/8/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>Make</Developer>
	<VideoURL>Z7II4yUHBS0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>23947</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570857-super-momotarou-dentetsu-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-momotarou-dentetsu-ii/3030-40216/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/zKcLX0S.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/fftLzjO.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/I7pUljt.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/llaASFw.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zmFG7tc.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/1ZiJAMS.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/HTEz4tN.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/vXzAYJ4.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/rcw5rUv.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/qtVFqAB.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/I8U28iy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/WuPqrBu.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Super Momotarou Dentetsu II is the second "Super" game in the long-running Momotarou Dentetsu series and the third overall. It was the first game in the series to be released on the Super Famicom: both Momotarou Dentetsu and Super Momotarou Dentetsu were Famicom games (though the latter was also released on the PC Engine and Game Boy, like Dentetsu II). The games focus on each player's burgeoning real estate corporation, allowing the players to take turns and move their trains around the board to buy properties and trade resources. It plays similarly to the Parker Brothers board game Monopoly or the Itadaki Street games.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4eeee351-5fbd-4dd0-b840-f4d7a15160a0.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/13bb7e84-fcda-4fcc-8e8e-84dd889e1cdb.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e8665184-bfe3-4612-94ea-eb73463b7600.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/64798f9e-d624-4c0f-8407-6b57457593c9.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/876ed679-5151-45c7-8de8-4e16a6115542.png</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</Publisher>
</game>