<Game>
	<Name>Super Star Wars - Return of the Jedi (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Staying close to the formula of previous games in the series, the story Super Return Of The Jedi is based on the movie of its namesake. This time, the 19 levels of the game follow the adventures of the Star Wars heroes as they try to rescue Han Solo from Jabba the Hutt, and the following ground and space battles that comprise the &#8220;Battle of Endor&#8221;. The vehicle levels include a landspeeder approach to Jabba&#8217;s Palace, the speeder bike chase on Endor, and the flight of the Millenium Falcon to destroy the 2 Death Star.Gameplay:In addition to the 3 playable heroes of previous games (Han, Luke and Chewie), Super Return Of The Jedi adds Leia and Wicket the Ewok. The number of available players changes each level. The controls are the same as those of Super Empire Strikes Back, however Luke cannot use a blaster and only has 5 force powers. Some levels switch from controlling the heroes to piloting a ship. There are 3 difficulty levels; Easy, Brave and Jedi. A password system allows players to start at any level provided they enter the correct password. Levels:Tatooine 1Tatooine 2-Boss: Palace Door GuardJabba's Palace-Boss: Bib FortunaDungeon-Boss: Giant Purple FogRancor Pit-Boss: RancorSail BargeInside Sail Barge-Boss: Jabba the HutSpeeder Bike ChaseEwok Village 1-Boss: EV-9D9Ewok Village 2-Boss: DragonImperial Base-Boss: Imperial ShipFalcon BattleBunker-Boss: Shield Generator Death Star-Boss: DarktroopersDeath Star SurfaceTower-Boss: Royal Guard, DarktrooperFinal Battle-Boss: Darth VaderEmperor's Throne Room-Boss: Emperor PalpatineDeath Star Tunnel	</plot>
	<releasedate>1/6/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>JVC Musical Industries, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>cYMrO7EX8cI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2660</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563220-super-star-wars-return-of-the-jedi</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-star-wars-return-of-the-jedi</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-star-wars-return-of-the-jedi/3030-4692/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/qx4dCmH.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/CqGYL7f.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/MGKaxtv.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/mtCnE1S.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/GFrB2do.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/ti8UuKm.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/jCDcaZJ.jpg</boxart7>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/flVOGFb.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/nrMAkaR.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ytdfeY1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/iUnAoN2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/N66L3bx.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/PgFI9PZ.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/snvjXDB.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/zJN035G.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/9Ke8L4t.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/mnFr8B3.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/OO6OIX4.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/nQGIoRp.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/4beqP9S.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/S6xMmoL.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/MvEHjIr.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/VKtTyk2.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/pwQkMil.png</clearlogo1>
</game>