<Game>
	<Name>Super Batter Up (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Famista is the first in Namco's Family Stadium (usually abbreviated to Fami Sta, or Famista) series of baseball games to be released on the Super Famicom. It is the first of five Super Famista games for the system and has the unique distinction among those five as being the only game that was released in the US, re-branded as Super Batter Up.As with the first game in the series, which was released as RBI Baseball in the US, the American version changes the series's trademark chibi-fied athletes to give them more realistic proportions. Both versions have the licenses to feature athletes from their respective national associations (Nippon Professional Baseball and the Major League Baseball Players Association), though the American version doesn't have the necessary Major League Baseball license to use the actual team names.There are single player and two-player modes, as well as a league mode.Cheat: View Player DataAt the title screen, press R, R, R, R, R, R, L, L, L, L, L, and L, then press Start to view Player Data.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>EVCUh0HpKrE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6147</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588715-super-batter-up</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-batter-up</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-batter-up/3030-24454/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XDL81kX.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/L4NRgx8.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/UI9mEci.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/1HIDU4n.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/gjHM9ZH.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/dbvnECy.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/sWXg7cn.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/JxUgulB.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/QyVix0m.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/LraZrqF.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/4Bjr3O1.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KPHTgcE.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/c369iPp.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>MAJOR LEAGUE ACTION Super Batter Up delivers grand slam action. Three stadiums and twenty-six teams staffed with real Major League Players to choose from. Pick your favorite team and go head to head with a buddy or go it alone in league mode for a season of serious slugging. Perfect play control puts you in the batter's box, on the pitcher's mound, and in the field. Wallop home runs over the fence, throw smoking fastballs, or dive for hard to catch flys: Big League thrills. Change the lineup or call in a pinch hitter-Super Batter Up is better baseball. - Major League Baseball Players and their statistics. - 8 packed megabits of baseball.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d1ea1e61-70b8-447f-9b64-291767c8b395.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1ad4bbca-a2d0-4075-8a0b-1acf1913cb59.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/638b5006-9f96-4623-92f2-6e71d8d2d589.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/132d6bac-b6bc-46c8-b5e8-3b05225777b1.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>