<Game>
	<Name>Super Tetris 2 + Bombliss (Japan) (Genteiban)</Name>
	<plot>Super Tetris 2 + Bombliss is one of the many versions of the famous soviet puzzle game, the first one available for the Super Nintendo, and an updated version of Tetris 2 + Bombliss.As the title would suggest, the game features both standard Tetris as well as another similar game called Bombliss. Tetris offers three game modes: standard marathon (A-type), start with garbage (B-type), and rising garbage (C-type). There is also a two-player versus mode where clearing rows sends garbage to the other player.Bombliss is slightly different from normal Tetris. Arranged on the board and in some dropped pieces are bomb squares. Completing a row does not clear the blocks in the row, but will trigger any bombs in the row which will destroy blocks. Different sizes of bombs will generate larger explosions. Bombliss is offered in standard marathon mode, a puzzle mode where a set board must be cleared using set piece drops, and a 2-player versus mode.Cheat: Change MusicThe game doesn't present you an option to change the music, but if you pause the game while playing and then press Select, you can choose from 7 songs.Cheat: Change MusicStart a 1 Player mode, select Tetris Mode A, B or C and on the level select screen, press L + R + Select on controller 2. You should hear a sound if done right. Now you'll be able to select from 9 special levels.Cheat: Change MusicAt the "Select Player" screen, enter the "Eliminate Name" menu. Highlight "Exit", hold Down + A + B on controller 2 and press Start on controller 1. If done right, you'll have the option to clear the memory, which will delete all the save files at once. Do so and you'll be back at the title screen. Now start a "2 Players" game and all the blocks will be Line Blocks.Cheat: Change MusicStart a 2 Player game, select Tetris mode. At the settings screen, select a Height of 1 or more. Now hold L + R + Select and press Start. If done right, all the blocks will be stacked in order instead of appearing all over the place.Cheat: Change MusicStart a 1 Player game, at the screen where you choose between Tetris or Bombliss, hold Left and press A to see your Tetris ranking or hold Right and press A to see your Bombliss ranking.Cheat: Change MusicWhile playing, pause the game, hold L + R and press Up to see the complete background of the stage.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>28775</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581085-super-tetris-2-bombliss</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-tetris-2-bombliss</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-tetris-2-bombliss/3030-30710/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/H209rr7.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/KIgplaH.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/foGoRkx.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/MSzapqT.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/GzLsGgN.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/fkxNNJo.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/jA8rjWs.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/rhCEVbL.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/IhRPOwo.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/8YCYnOk.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/aifBcJW.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/GKNAQL5.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Sx6rp1I.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Deo6qHU.png</clearlogo1>
</game>