<Game>
	<Name>Super Bomber Man 2 (Japan) (En)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Bomberman 2's single player mode focuses on alien invaders, named "The Dastardly Bombers", who kidnap Bomberman from Planet Bomber in their enormous spaceship. Bomberman must take down the five invaders and save Planet Bomber from destruction.Single PlayerWith each section of the spaceship (of which there are five), Bomberman must progress through six normal levels by destroying every enemy, activating all the capsules (which alternate on and off when bomb blasts hit them) and finding the exit. Bomberman must then fight that area's Dastardly Bomber in a one-on-one battle in the seventh level and then in their boss machine - a large personalized mech suit - in the eighth. The single player involve taking out each one of the Dastardly Bombers by entering each of the worlds and taking out each area. Unlike in the previous Bomberman game, the area has changed from a closed square, to an open area with different map layouts.Castle Stage - Magnet BomberMagnet Bomber is the first of the Dastardly Bombers Bomberman faces. He is able to magnetically attract and repel bombs, making it hard to line them up correctly while fighting him.Magnet Bomber's boss machine - Iron Gigue - is a giant robot that can only move laterally, sending out frequent punches. If it rolls over a bomb, the bomb will vanish, so the player will need to lead the slow-moving robot into blasts. Flame Stage - Golem BomberGolem Bomber is a huge red leviathan that tends to use Bomberman's own bombs against him by throwing them around with the Power Glove power-up.Golem Bomber's boss machine - Breast Fire - is a multi-podded machine that moves in straight lines in random directions. It attacks by stopping, firing a quartet of fireballs that slowly fall to the arena and creates bomb blasts before moving again. Though dangerous, it's own fireballs will damage it, making it possible to defeat Breast Fire without the player ever having to lay a single bomb.Amusement Park Stage - Pretty BomberA female bomberman (bomberwoman?), Pretty Bomber uses the "Heart Bombs", which move around on their own chaotically, to ensnare Bomberman.Pretty Bomber's boss machine - Mask Change - is a giant sun-shaped face that moves diagonally around the arena. It doesn't actively engage Bomberman unless he destroys one of its heart-shaped projectiles. Factory Stage - Brain BomberBrain Bomber is, obviously, the brains behind the Dastardly Bombers' operation. He is particularly weak in a one-on-one fight, being able to only drop one bomb at a time with a minimal blast radius. He does, however, have the remote control bomb upgrade.Brain Bomber's boss machine - Robo Bomber - resembles a gigantic white Bomberman like the player. He moves slowly around the arena in a random path. His enormous bombs, when they explode, create unorthodox blast areas that can be hard to gauge. Dark Stage - Plasma BomberThe leader of the Dastardly Bombers, Plasma Bomber, fights with his own special looking bombs. He is able to throw bombs, but doesn't have any other specific advantages - he's just very fast and deadly.Plasma Bomber's boss machine - SkeleGuard - resembles a skeletal version of Iron Gigue and fights similarly, moving laterally across the top of the screen. It has more methods of attack, however.After defeating SkeleGuard, Plasma Bomber appears to surrender, but is shot down by an unseen assailant. The true final boss battle begins against General Ganzu, a floating eyeball enemy. Ganzu is impervious to explosions, so the only way to damage it is by throwing bombs at it with the Power Glove. Because it speeds up the more it is damaged, it becomes harder to accurately aim the thrown bombs (and avoid getting hit).Multiplayer:The multiplayer "Battle Game" allows up to four players (with the Super Multitap peripheral) to compete in twelve different arenas, each with their own specific features and conditions.Super Bomberman 2 introduces the "Golden Bomberman" rule, in which the winning player of the previous tournament plays a roulette game to randomly select between six power-ups (including the Geta - or Clogs - a gag item that makes the player slower). In the new tournament, that player's bomberman turns golden-colored and begins every match with that power-up.Secret CodesEnter 5656 on the passwords section to enable Sudden Death in multiplayerCheat: 2 Extra Battle Mode StagesConnect the  Hudson Super Joycard controller, then turn on the Turbo feature. Now, when the title screen / mode select appears, hold X for six seconds or so. When performed correctly you will hear the pause jingle. Two new stages will be added in battle mode.Cheat: 2 Extra Battle Mode Stages[I](Note: This requires a Multitap.)[/I] At the title screen, enter Battle Mode by pressing A on a controller in socket #5. For the duration of your game, you can now jump by pressing Y in every zone except Zones 2 and 3.Cheat: PasswordsGo to the password screen and enter these passwords:</plot>
	<releasedate>12/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson Soft Company, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>kd5cTJC8VDs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2534</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588721-super-bomberman-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-bomberman-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-bomberman-2/3030-12414/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/b2GMdwe.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/X1I9ocU.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/Y4V4uNN.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/2z78R3t.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/OeUh0L0.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/nGDtBOf.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/rfYYkQH.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/9UI8lyF.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/t4pj6Fw.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/6b18ELM.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/I2ffF7F.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FnIsRgy.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/7ELAT5Y.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/8mMXRhH.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/GZbSl9l.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/SLXPoee.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/uwOuj2z.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/FaAQf1g.jpg</clearlogo1>
</game>