<Game>
	<Name>Super Battletank 2 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>In this sequel to Super Battletank, the player takes control of the feared M1A2 Battletank in 16 missions centered in the Middle East.  After they are attacked by an unknown group of enemies on both land and air, the player is tasked to root out these enemies and stop any further attacks on Coalition forces.Much like its predecessor, the gameplay is a first-person tank simulation, using radar to scout out enemy tanks and using the main turret gun to disable and kill any opposing tanks, jeeps, APCs and various other heavy weapons including SCUD missiles.  If the player encounters and air resistance, they can mount their Phalanx machine gun to cut down enemy choppers.Players also have smoke screens that can temporarily make them unseen to any enemy forces, plus they can call in supply drops to replenish their armor and ammo as well as air support that can level any opposing force in their wake.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Absolute Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1</rating>
	<VideoURL>Ul1HNI-Ve3Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6149</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588717-super-battletank-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-battletank-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-battletank-2/3030-32829/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/dSKejz8.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/MjdIXZc.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/HkAsD3F.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/N2hbXH4.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/oOYFVA4.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/lYtezDp.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/nr8X6Fn.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wcRcUKy.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/mtcLcbW.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/t4vcLMG.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/fqOVxU1.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/g7zgw8e.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/A5klMFb.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/8sCEErZ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/jogzICQ.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Ykzy1jl.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vNQJD1O.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/hY6d94R.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The Ultimate Armored Combat Game! Explode across the sands at the helm of the Army's consummate war machine - the M1A2 battletank! With 16 MEGS of incredible realism, SUPER BATTLETANK 2 powers you into a new dimension of video game warfare as you barrel through enemy lines, encountering a more numerous and cunning foe than ever before! Packed with more of the amazing digitized graphics and senses-shattering firepower that made the original Super Battletank: War in the Gulf a runaway bestseller, SUPER BATTLETANK 2 treads where other tank games don't dare, and leaves them in the dust! - Take part in ruthless day and night combat scenarios with an expanded arsenal of sophisticated weaponry, including an on-board camera that displays full-motion video of enemy termination! - Heart-stopping ambush scenarios take you topside for relentless armored duels and furious helicopter attacks! - Ultra-realistic animated sequences feature PATRIOT missile launches and F-15 airstrikes that you call in to bomb the battleground!</Notes>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4607ea26-d651-4e91-ac53-0156d2958ff2.jpg</boxart7>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/53be2961-da01-4992-9cd3-4ae0bd064b60.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ad161485-17dc-4454-a880-5f59507c8027.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/605313c3-d82c-4fb5-bcdd-43edfcda204d.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Absolute Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>