<Game>
	<Name>Super Street Fighter II (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Street Fighter II: The New Challengers is the fourth iteration of Capcom's genre-defining Street Fighter II originally released in the Arcades in 1993 on Capcom's new CP System II board. It follows Champion Edition (which first allowed players to play as the four Grand Masters Sagat, Balrog, Vega and M. Bison) and Turbo: Hyper Fighting (which increased the speed and balanced the game further). The most notable addition are four brand new characters: Cammy, Deejay, T.Hawk and Fei Long. It would eventually be followed by Super Street Fighter II Turbo Edition, considered the definitive Super Street Fighter II.Gameplay:This remake of  Street Fighter II featured a new scoring system that kept track of combos, first attacks, and reversals. Additionally, four new characters join the returning twelve characters from the original. Super Street Fighter II is also the first game in the SFII series to give full move sets to the boss characters. Previously in Street Fighter II: Champion Edition and Street Fighter II: Turbo, whilst the four boss characters were available, they did not have different animations for some punches and kicks. Although this was expected for Balrog (being a boxer), it was unusual to see a character doing a punch when pressing a kick button, or vice-versa.Aside from the bosses' added moves, some of the main characters' moves were adjusted in some ways. For example, the differences between Ken and Ryu became more defined - Ryu focusing on deadlier fireballs, and Ken's fierce Dragon Punch being able to set opponents on fire.CriticismFor all the additions and improvements Super Street Fighter II makes over  Street Fighter II: Turbo, its biggest failing is arguably that it does not include the same degree of speed that made Street Fighter II: Turbo such a hit. It is perhaps for this very reason that, in most cases, this game is overlooked in preference to its follow-up -  Super Street Fighter II: Turbo.Characters:Returning charactersSSFII featured four new characters Ryu Ken Masters E. Honda Chun-Li Blanka Zangief Guile Dhalsim Balrog Sagat Vega M. BisonNew characters Cammy Dee Jay Fei Long T. HawkCheat: Different Color Outfits!To get diffirent color outfits for the characters use different buttons to select them.Cheat: Different Color Outfits!To edit what button does what right before a fight, simply hold select sometime before the versus screen appears, and do whatever you would normally do, until the edit screen appears. This should work in any mode, and in versus mode you can even select if either player should be CPU, or human.Cheat: Different Color Outfits!Select Arcade Mode normally. When you start your fight press START on the controller 2. Then select for the second player the same figther the CPU was using and beat it. You will see yourself in the second fight!  Repeat this until you find M. Bison(Vega) and fight for your life! Cheat: Different Color Outfits!When you select your fighter, press and hold all 3 punches or all 3 kicks until the outfit changes color.Cheat: Different Color Outfits!Group Battle usually limits you to two instances of each fighter, but this code increases that number to eight. From the Game Start screen, enter Group Battle mode. Then, using the second controller, alternately and repeatedly tap L and R until Vega laughs. Choose Match Play or Elimination from the menu. You and your opponent will now be able to use up to eight instances of each fighter.Cheat: Different Color Outfits!When you start the game wait for the first profile and hold: L+R on 2P</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>m5L4lq3rj2A</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2792</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588757-super-street-fighter-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-street-fighter-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-street-fighter-ii/3030-6665/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/lbZvJCb.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/9DwstwL.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/GFmQEHQ.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/dkrSVWu.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/exHs9k4.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/RnfaAtD.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/tTmxz55.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/jDXajQr.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/XXQ34Nh.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/YZYtR0R.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/5nftmGr.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/kFKXDwg.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/bp3YlTE.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/KVPtvgA.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/1GjJab0.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/VpcLPAL.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/VJZv8Gm.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/CI2f8vd.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/2wfxRRi.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/Ibfegky.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/113EqsC.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/JCE72d6.png</fanart6>
	<fanart7>http://i.imgur.com/wR4Wiap.png</fanart7>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/FXTPMOM.png</clearlogo1>
</game>