<Game>
	<Name>Super Zugan 2 - Tsukanpo Fighter (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Zugan 2: Tsukanpo Fighter is a mahjong game for the Super Famicom published by J-Wing. The game is based on the Super Zugan anime, about the student Hideyoshi Toyotomi and his severe misfortune whenever he is coerced into playing high-stakes mahjong with his three delinquent colleagues. The one light in his life, his buxom girlfriend Akina, is a lot more intelligent (and lucky) and tries desperately throughout the series to convince him to stop. It is the follow-up to Super Zugan: Hakotenjou kara no Shoutai, which was released earlier the same year.Super Zugan 2: Tsukanpo Fighter allows the player to construct a four-person game out of one of the many characters from the anime and a setting of their choice. The game is distinctive for showing the opponents sitting around the table, remarking on bad plays and showing various emotions depending on how well they're doing.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>J-Wing</Developer>
	<VideoURL>JkXzNQtUToE</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/580883-super-zugan-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-zugan-2-tsukanpo-fighter/3030-50812/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/LvITBzx.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/o5Y6kHh.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wDZsJKr.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ZjY8Jc6.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/xOY7Qck.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Notes>Super Zugan 2: Tsukanpo Fighter is a mahjong game for the Super Famicom published by J-Wing. The game is based on the Super Zugan anime, about the student Hideyoshi Toyotomi and his severe misfortune whenever he is coerced into playing high-stakes mahjong with his three delinquent colleagues. The one light in his life, his buxom girlfriend Akina, is a lot more intelligent (and lucky) and tries desperately throughout the series to convince him to stop. It is the follow-up to Super Zugan: Hakotenjou kara no Shoutai, which was released earlier the same year. Super Zugan 2: Tsukanpo Fighter allows the player to construct a four-person game out of one of the many characters from the anime and a setting of their choice. The game is distinctive for showing the opponents sitting around the table, remarking on bad plays and showing various emotions depending on how well they're doing.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d6128fff-fbd3-43b1-8e69-40ec9f642fa5.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/25c2d496-60e8-4aa8-b2b3-723407e602e4.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b98e5acd-0de6-4b51-9e09-2282d8a55b30.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9f9ab2a-53fa-4b2a-a006-108c63d75f7c.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3aca2021-367e-47c7-993a-f81f5183339f.png</snapshot8>
	<Publisher>J-Wing</Publisher>
</game>