<Game>
	<Name>Super Black Bass 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Bassin's Black Bass with Hank Parker is a Sports game, developed and published by Starfish,which was released in Japan in 1994.Cheat: Debug ModeHold X + Y on controller one, A + B on controller two, and turn on the SNES. The words ''Debug Mode'' will appear on the screen. Begin a game and use these commands while in the game:Cheat: Getting the BuzzbaitThis lure is found in the third tournament. Go to the southeastern part of the area, and select "Cast" in the Timber area. Eventually, you'll find this lure, and it will be added to your collection of lures for you to use.Cheat: Getting the BuzzbaitTo get the Crayfish, you must be in the second tournament. In the second tournament, search the middle to northeastern part of the rocks and this lure will eventually be found if you keep casting. Be careful not to break your boat, though. The Crayfish is an extremely useful lure, so it's nice to find it!Cheat: Getting the BuzzbaitThis lure is found at the first tournament. Go to the eastern part of the area, and select "Cast" while under the trees. After awhile, you'll obtain this hidden lure. It will be added to your lure collection for you to use.Cheat: Getting the BuzzbaitOn the fourth tournament (The very last one), search in the western side of the dump and keep casting in that western area of the dump, and the lure should be found shortly after.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Starfish</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3145</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588207-bassins-black-bass-with-hank-parker</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-black-bass</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-black-bass-3/3030-46898/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4gB2WJp.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/y09RFz3.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/W9NKvyM.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ew16Ubk.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/FA7iv1e.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/LGXIS71.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/wQeMquD.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/nXbK396.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/L7sgBcY.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/s1QioK0.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/oPNiMPS.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/H340M09.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/3TrCLu7.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UP7Q6G6.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/xK40IZt.png</clearlogo1>
</game>