<Game>
	<Name>Super Bomber Man 4 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The fourth addition to the Bomberman series for the SNES.  This game is almost identical to Super Bomberman 3 only with new levels and a new story.A small twist in this game is that instead of choosing the traditional bomberman or a country specific character players get to choose between bosses from the previous game when playing battle mode.  Each character has a special power from a jet pack to throwing abilities.Cheat: Battle Stage PasswordsEnter the passwords below using the 'password' option in the main menu, and you will be able to play different stages in battle mode. After entering the password, you will be taken back to the main menu. Simply select the 'battle game' option, then the first or third option, and you will be able to play different battle stages than usual.Cheat: Battle Stage PasswordsEnter this code on the password screen, and you'll be taken back to the title screen. When you play a round of single mode (all players vs. each other player), the one who reaches the goal for wins turns gold the next round. This doesn't work for tag matches (multi-player cooperation matches)</plot>
	<releasedate>26/4/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson Soft Company, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-5 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>OV9_Rmb8BUk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14786</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575223-super-bomberman-4</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-bomberman-4</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-bomberman-4/3030-10163/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/j4Ke0rs.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/16LOVHy.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/dFYaVCM.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/kFEEiUL.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/AZYMirD.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/CH9ffQc.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/NYPFnps.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/xYGS9rr.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/TRG6YDw.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/f1rRFWe.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/CLRyXXk.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ySvfE9b.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/O7X7Tqe.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/yUoTaQZ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Super Bomberman 4 is a Puzzle game, developed by Produce and published by Hudson, which was released in Japan in 1996.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7d3ddc32-df9f-4d4f-b69a-7e922a4b9b73.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/117c80ff-5105-4883-ac8a-ec11eab1646b.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1c436a91-0b38-4274-96bc-e3cf0ae22d48.png</snapshot11>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hudson</Publisher>
</game>