<Game>
	<Name>Super Star Wars - Teikoku no Gyakushuu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Pursued across the galaxy, and your Rebel Forces now marshall new strength on the remote ice world of Hoth. Although tracked by probe droids, attacked by ice monster, and confronted by an army of gigantic Imperial Walkers, you must not give in. You are the Alliance's only hope. Learn the ways of the Force, then test your skills in this fast-paced, action-packed sequel to the high game, Super Star Wars&amp;reg;.Cheat: CodesEnter the codes on the main menu:Cheat: Level Passwords (Brave difficulty)When the game turns on, one of the options will be "Password." Scroll to it and enter these.Cheat: Level Passwords (Brave difficulty)When the game turns on, one of the options will be "Password." Scroll to it and enter these.Cheat: Level Passwords (Brave difficulty)When the game turns on, one of the options will be "Password." Scroll to it and enter these.Cheat: View Build DateTo view the date the game was built on, simply have a Super Scope plugged into the second controller port. The build date will be displayed at the bottom of the title screen.Cheat: Change IntroOn the Game Start, Option, and Password screen, press Y four times. If entered correctly, you will hear a tone. Select ''Game Start'' and press Start. Wait for the title ''Star Wars'' to fade off. Then, when the introduction comes on, use the Control Pad and L and R to rotate and scroll the words around the screen. You can also move the Star Destroyer around, too. That is all the code does.Cheat: Change IntroAt any time during stages where you control one of the heroes (not during stages where you control a vehicle IE snow speeder or spaceship), press and hold down the following buttons: A, B, X, Y and Down. While holding these, press Start to access a Sound Test. Use Left and Right to cycle through the tunes, press A to select the desired tune and listen to it. While still playing the selected tune, you can press Start to resume gameplay. Whatever tune you selected in the Sound Test will be playing in place of the stage's normal music! In effect, you could be in the middle of say, stage one with the boss theme or the ending theme playing instead of the Imperial March! Remember, on stages where you pilot vehicles this code will not work.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Sculptured Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>kRwo7xvbAD0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2659</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563221-super-star-wars-the-empire-strikes-back</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-star-wars-the-empire-strikes-back/3030-8627/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/QUHYnA9.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/QkghiIi.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/sUPT4mK.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/7TaHRcC.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/BoP0fFU.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/pjD3oXr.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/p5gTF9g.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ubPQWt1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/v2RJqDW.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/PfY1T9Z.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/sj1W3ES.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/R5H4dla.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/myhNVbU.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/hAm8I4z.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/920ZT1P.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/7NSZvl8.jpg</fanart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/EFWXF9s.png</clearlogo1>
</game>