<Game>
	<Name>Super Fire Pro Wrestling III - Final Bout (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Fire Pro Wrestling III Final Bout is the third Super Famicom game (of eight) from Human Entertainment's Fire Pro Wrestling series. The action is once again presented in an isometric ring, and players must use timing-based button presses to effectively grapple and pin their opponents. The player can choose from a number of wrestlers, many of whom are from international circuits like the WWE and WCW, who are all homages to actual wrestlers under different names. The player could also make their own wrestler in the game's "create-a-wrestler" editor mode, a series staple.Super Fire Pro Wrestling III Final Bout was closely followed by a rerelease, Super Fire Pro Wrestling III EasyType, which simplified the controls and made the timing parts less stringent. It was released a mere five weeks after the original game. Though it lacks the editor mode, all hidden wrestlers are unlocked from the offset.Notably, Super Fire Pro Wrestling III Final Bout is the first Fire Pro Wrestling game Goichi "Suda51" Suda worked on. He would go on to pen the controversial story in 1994's Super Fire Pro Wrestling Special. Cheat: Hidden Boss battlesUsing the built in password system (located under the "LOAD" then "PASSWORD" options), input any ONE of these passwords to fight one of the hidden Bosses in the Singles or Tag Team Tournament.Once one of the codes is inputted correctly, press "EXIT" to activate.Cheat: Hidden Boss battlesTo play as the "Victory Musashi" clone tag team in World Championship mode, at the menu selection screen choose the "LOAD" option then, choose "PASSWORD" (the second choice). Now, type AAAAAA as the password and choose "EXIT". If done correctly, you will begin World Championship mode with a special tag team made up of two clones of Victory Musashi.Cheat: Hidden Boss battlesTo unlock the hidden boss palettes in "EDIT" mode,  select  the "LOAD" option from the mode selection screen . Now, choose the second option "PASSWORD". Now, type in "KICHIJOJI" as the password and choose "EXIT" . Then, from the mode selection screen, choose "EDIT" mode. If done correctly, you will now be able to choose from and customize the hidden boss palettes in "EDIT" mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Human Club</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>28843</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/580152-super-fire-prowrestling-3-final-bout</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-fire-pro-wrestling-iii-final-bout/3030-47896/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XTrEiwx.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/UCCGuZH.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/wmeqTyj.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ADm2Szc.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Wy0pPV1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/9qJJJIx.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/011qd4m.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Ne5GFjP.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/A6j1FQn.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6GLXnuC.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/fYineXm.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vO5uM5D.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/rtvUdLq.png</clearlogo1>
</game>