<Game>
	<Name>Super Tennis (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Tennis, released in 1991 in Japan and North America and on June 1992 in Europe, is a tennis game exclusive to the SNES (games of the same name exist on the MSX and Sega Master System, but are only similar in name and are otherwise completely different). The biggest feature is its Circuit mode, in which players partake in a tennis season with the objective of finishing with the most ranking points and thus as number one in the world. The year consists of four grand slams and four smaller tournaments, and each takes place on one of the three typical surfaces: hard, grass, and clay. The surfaces, like in real life, vary in bounce and speed. The game also includes the option to play exhibition matches, either singles or doubles, as well as twenty different characters of varying stats and strengths. For example, Phil is a strong serve-and-volleyer, but struggles during baseline rallies, while John's speed and consistent groundstrokes make him a fine baseline player.PlayersThe following players appear and are selectable in the game:MenThe character select screen.Matt -- powerful strokes; consistent serverBrian -- strong serve-and-volleyerPhil -- strong serverJohn -- powerful strokes; offensive baselinerMeyer -- defensive baselinerRich -- strong volleyerHiro -- accurate strokes; strong returnerSteve -- all-rounderRob -- strong serverMark -- "bullet" servesWomenAmy -- all-rounderKim -- strong serve-and-volleyerLisa -- powerful strokes; offensive baselinerErin -- strong returnerDonna -- strong all-round player, but with weak servesDebbie -- accurate strokesColett -- defensive baselinerNancy -- strong server; baselinerYuki -- consistent playerBarb -- powerful strokes; offensive baseliner							</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>F7rw3cDWgSg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3278</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588759-super-tennis</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-tennis</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-tennis/3030-18664/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/cNmYt1m.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/3cCZvxj.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/D8HIyxl.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/4inSCPF.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/lWzcvGu.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/hgbhgH2.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8P3lPFo.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Y0QE8bl.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/b6E5HtW.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/cBdpihK.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/A1nOey1.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5LetpZs.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/M4YBhJX.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ejegTW8.gif</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/X68cV9n.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ieGOeOM.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/bIXu8iL.png</clearlogo1>
</game>