<Game>
	<Name>Super Tetris 3 (Japan) (En)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Tetris 3 is the second sequel to the Super Tetris series. It was developed by TOSE and published by Tetris license-holders Bullet-Proof Software on the Japanese Super Famicom exclusively.It continues to add new modes, following Super Tetris 2's inclusion of the chain reaction-heavy Bombliss mode. Super Tetris 3 has three such bonus modes:Magicaliss, a colorful variant that introduces rainbow pieces and gray pieces as well as a means to change the color of shapes by rotating them four times. Gray pieces drop in combinations of one, two or three pieces rather than the standard four-piece tetromino and these pieces cannot be cleared the standard way. Instead, they float in mid-air when the line disappears. In order to remove them, the player must form lines of the same color. Rainbow tetrominos are considered "wild cards" and will be counted as red, blue or green when in a line with the same uniform color.Sparkliss, which is a fantasy-themed variant of Bombliss in which the player is setting up gems to create larger chain-reactions. By clearing lines with gemstones in them, the gemstones will explode and take out a number of nearby pieces. Putting four gemstones into a square creates a much more powerful gemstone bomb. This mode also has a puzzle variant in which the player is given a specific grid layout and a finite number of pre-determined pieces and must clear the board.Famliss is simply the game's name for its four-player multiplayer mode. Rather than sending garbage to other players after clearing lines, there is a rotating bonus at the bottom of the screen that will activate as soon as the line(s) vanishes. It can either clear lines or add lines. </plot>
	<releasedate>16/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action; Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>xgLaARvGF_k</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>25772</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581086-super-tetris-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-tetris-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-tetris-3/3030-30711/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ve5kils.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/pTfLyLH.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/WtaDYOd.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/9Fix4gq.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/nxmEvLD.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/axFqoP8.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/eVHgA7R.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/bQr2JXu.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BanSDYQ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/uIOXZAd.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/EWzX0iH.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/nnRSkNZ.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/0yEfuYE.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/yS440Er.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Super Tetris 3 is yet another version of the famous soviet puzzle game. However, despite what the title may suggest, contained within are actually four different versions of Tetris: Tetris Classic, Familiss, Sparkliss, and Magicaliss. Tetris Classic, of course, is the basic version of the game, which comes with an endless mode and a 25-line "standard" mode. Familiss, as the name might suggest, is a family mode for up to four players simultaneously. Sparkliss, meanwhile, is very similar to Bombliss from Super Tetris 2, only with a medieval fantasy theme and different explosion patterns. Sparkliss includes both a stage mode and a puzzle mode. The most unique mode is Magicaliss, which has never shown up on any other version of Tetris. In Magicaliss, pieces come in three basic colors, and by rotating the piece, the player can choose between them. Creating a line entirely out of one color will clear all blocks on the screen of that color. There are also grey pieces, which can only be cleared by creating a line made entirely from one color, which will cause all grey blocks on screen to become that color. There are also rare rainbow pieces which will act as any color. Besides these additions, the game itself is basic Tetris. Tetris Classic, Sparkliss, and Magicaliss can also be played in a two-player battle mode, besides the four-player Familiss mode.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/38c8e105-5459-4fb6-8414-9886bf961d70.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/52032c65-3e91-4094-9fb6-f243bc6b62ac.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5a18f6f1-0191-43c6-8f10-2691265b373b.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/afaf6a7b-3430-454c-8502-c45042c0fd5c.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3e8cc618-5e6c-496c-a44d-e1f9b31fc8f0.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a3f83416-7d06-465e-81ea-a55c01c12507.png</snapshot14>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Blue Planet Software</Publisher>
</game>