<Game>
	<Name>Super Robot Taisen EX (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Robot Taisen EX is the fourth game released in the Super Robot Taisen series, though is not a true sequel to the 3rd Super Robot Taisen but rather a spin-off. It begins the Masou Kishin storyline, which continues in Super Robot Taisen Gaiden: Masou Kishin - The Lord of Elemental and the Super Robot Taisen OG Saga entries.Like the rest of the games in the series, Super Robot Taisen EX is a strategy game that takes various characters and mecha from numerous manga/anime franchises, as well as a smattering of original characters. It was originally released for the Super Famicom in 1994 and later saw an enhanced version for the PlayStation in 2000. This version was added to the PSOne Classics range on PSN.Featured SeriesA list of the anime series which are featured in the game. Series that premiered in the Super Robot Wars series in this game are marked with "(new)".Mobile Suit Gundam 0083: Stardust MemoryMobile Suit Zeta GundamMobile Suit Gundam ZZMobile Suit Gundam: Char's CounterattackMobile Suit Gundam F91Mazinger ZGreat MazingerUFO Robo GrendizerGetter Robo GDemon God of War Goshogun (new)Aura Battler Dunbine (new)Banpresto Originals (original characters created for the game)Masoukishin - Lord of Elemental (Banpresto original storyline; new)New FeaturesChapters: The game is split into three chapters, each based on one of the originals from SRW 3: Ryuune, Masaki, and Shuu. The player can choose Ryuune's and Masaki's in any order, while Shuu's story is always last.Interactive Scenarios: After playing one of the aforementioned chapters, the player has the option of carrying the decisions made in that chapter into the next, setting up events that would not happen otherwise. A somewhat similar system is used in the SRW Compact 2 trilogy, in which the player can carry save data containing unlocked characters (among other things) to the next chapter via the Wonderswan's internal memory.Upgradeable Weapons: Weapons can now be upgraded.Cheat: Neo GranzonOnce you've completed Masaki's and Ryuune's route, your save file should have the letters "MR" meaning Masaki and Ryuune. Restart the game and on the Banpresto starting blue screen press "Down, Up, Left, Right, L, R" before the screen fades. It should turn pink and when you start Shuu's route, you will start with Neo Granzon instead of a regular Granzon.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Sci-Fi</genre>
	<Developer>WinkySoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>31472</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581823-super-robot-taisen-ex</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-robot-taisen-ex</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-robot-taisen-ex/3030-23085/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/vKowOfh.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/aIxe0r3.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/wBnyDk9.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Yfnbuo0.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/msFxpJ4.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/i5pbKTB.jpg</snapshot4>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/FBfduuu.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Super Robot Taisen EX is a Strategy game, developed by WinkySoft and published by Banpresto, which was released in Japan in 1994.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/197f068d-7f12-47d4-95f5-b768f527e7e2.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/19cf9e37-d57f-449b-b66c-e80bfef5537a.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Banpresto</Publisher>
</game>