<Game>
	<Name>Super Fire Pro Wrestling (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Fire Pro Wrestling is the first of eight Super Famicom games in Human's venerable wrestling series. As with the other games in the series, players assume the role of a fictionalized (but based on a real person) wrestler and compete with others in the ring, either in one-on-one matches or as part of a tag team. The gameplay is focused on performing timing-specific moves to wear down the opponent until they are weak enough to be successfully pinned, or put into a hold until they submit the match. Players can also land punches and kicks on their opponents, or throw them. Most of the fictional wrestlers are Japanese in origin, though a few (like Hulk Hogan and The Ultimate Warrior) are from the WWF (the former WWE).Cheat: CPU vs CPU Exhibition match.To watch two computer controlled opponents (CPU) face each other, hold the "X" button at the mode selection screen and choose "Exhibition" mode (the second option from the mode selection screen). While still holding the "X" button, select any Wrestler.  Now, with the second controller, choose an opponent to play against. If done correctly, both player's wrestlers will now be controlled by the Computer and  a CPU vs CPU match will begin. This code also works with tag team matches as well.Cheat: CPU vs CPU Exhibition match.To unlock the 3 hidden bosses (B.G. Bull, Ittetsu Wakamoto and Rikouzan) in any mode other than the World Tournament or Dojo modes,  Simply hover your cursor over the desired mode you wish to play, hold the "L" button and press "Start" until you have reached the character  selection screen for that particular mode. If done correctly, the three hidden bosses will be unlocked and now visible to choose from.Cheat: Different RefereesSelect Password on the Main Menu and enter these passwords. These passwords work even though it really doesn't use up all 30 spaces on the Password screen.Cheat: Different RefereesUsing the game's "Password" system, enter this code to fight against Rikouzan in the final battle of the second singles tournament.Cheat: Different RefereesUsing the game's built in "Password" system, input this code to fight against a special Tag team comprised of the hidden Bosses Rikouzan and B.G. Bull in the final match of the second Tag Team Tournament.Cheat: Different RefereesUsing the game's "Password" system, enter this code to fight against Star Bison and B.G. Bull in the final battleof the tag team tournament.Cheat: Different RefereesUsing the game's "Password" system, enter this code to fight against Star Bison and B.G. Bull in the final battleof the tag team tournament.Cheat: Different RefereesUsing the "Pass Word" system, enter any one of these passwords to begin either the second singles or tag tournament.Cheat: Play as the hidden bosses in World Championship mode.To play as the hidden bosses B.G. Bull, Ittetsu Wakamoto, and Rikiouzan in the World Championship Mode, hold the "L" button and hover your cursor over League mode (the 4th option from the mode selection screen). Next, a small window will open asking you to choose how many players will be competing in the League mode. While this window is open, press the "Y" button to be brought back to the main menu. The cursor should now be placed over World Championship Mode (the first option from the mode selection screen). Choose World Championship mode in either the singles or tag divisions . If done correctly, the three hidden bosses will be unlocked and now visible to choose from in World Championship mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Human Club</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>28840</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/580109-super-fire-prowrestling</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-fire-pro-wrestling/3030-43984/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4TAGGil.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/j0vvumM.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/OP1Bftc.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/FV54008.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Y6uznWy.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/y9CEV4d.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/wWF5yiz.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/M8xwkWU.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ckTprb7.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/fhwhqBi.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/luBVdSB.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/VEebPQw.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/wpP0XJX.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Fire Pro Wrestling has taken Japan by storm, and now it has come to the Super Famicom! 110 unique move are at your disposal, and this is the most realistic simulation of wrestling ever!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7f90e60e-cbf0-49e9-8e24-c3d843d814f9.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c5a11d14-10f2-450a-b6ae-6789b3637bc7.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Human</Publisher>
</game>