<Game>
	<Name>Super Bomber Man 5 (Japan) (Caravan Event Ban)</Name>
	<plot>A special gold cartridge that came with an issue of Coro Coro comics was produced, featuring extra battle mode maps.Cheat: Cheat CharactersIn Config Battle Mode go to Password Load - enter these:Cheat: A list of all the passwords in the gameThey should be entered under the "Options" screen off the main menu. Each password changes either Battle Mode or Normal Mode, and after a correct password entry the game will automatically take you to the appropriate mode.Cheat: A list of all the passwords in the gameHave you ever wanted to play as carbon copies of the Fiendish Bombers in Config Battle Mode, but disliked how the game limited your palette and item selection choices?  Well, with these passwords, you can play as versions of the bosses with their correct palettes and all the Power-Ups they have when you fight them! (However, they still can't use their special moves, such as throwing Power-Downs or summoning enemies.)* = Gold Bomberman has maxed out Bombs, Fire-Ups, Speed, and holds the Remote Control, Soft Block and Bomb Pass, Power Glove, and Punch Glove items.  He's the equivalent of a fully-powered Single Player character.* = Subordinate Bomber's portrait is glitchy and will put junk graphics on the status bar, but this won't effect gameplay.  Do no let him win a Single Match or he will crash the game.  He's perfectly safe to use in a Tag Match though.  His stats are the same as his boss form if you kill Pirate Bomber first.Cheat: A list of all the passwords in the gameThey should be entered under the "Options" screen off the main menu. Each password changes either Battle Mode or Normal Mode, and after a correct password entry the game will automatically take you to the appropriate mode.Cheat: Configure CheatIn the Configure Option in the Battle Mode, Input 23D830 as a password to aquire the following: The character you get is a red Subordinate Bomber (The guy that helps Pirate Bomber when you fight him as a boss.) who isn't normally playable. On his stats screen, his Bomb and Speed levels are at 8, The number that tells the level of his firepower is screwed up (Changing it will mess up your screen), he'll have all of the special items (I.E. Kick, Punch, Throw, Wall Passer, etc.), and he'll still have 98 build points left! Save him, and he'll be shown on the character select screen as a red X and his face is a red Bomberman because Hudson Soft didn't create a face of him. Playing as him will often cause weird, messed up sprites to appear on screen.Cheat: Configure CheatThis requires Hudson's Super Joycard controller.Have the X switch on the controller set to the middle and on the title screen hold X for about 6 seconds. A sound will confirm on success. These are the same stages found on the gold cartridge.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/2/1997</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson Soft Company, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>CufHKUo1V5s</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14787</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/562899-super-bomberman-5</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/super-bomberman-5</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-bomberman-5/3030-3354/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/pW1Etx7.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/uOaMoMq.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/YghzzdJ.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/twZwnfx.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/HyYXwwv.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/W98urBd.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/eMyghHv.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/YgAjY4b.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/kbxJ7Tg.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/2MojjLu.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/yVg9I0h.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/9xNsRyG.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ZqKMo8q.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/yzfJBND.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>An evil Bomber named Emperor Terrorin who has the power of Time itself has freed various criminal Bombers from their prison cells in orbit around Planet Bomber. Setting them up in a warped time and space, Shirobon, Kurobon, and their Louie (Rui) companions must travel through stages and defeat them before going up against Emperor Terrorin himself. Super Bomberman 5 (スーパーボンバーマン5), released by Hudson Soft in early 1997, was the final Bomberman game released on the Super Family Computer - the Japanese version of the SNES. The game was released in two variations: a standard cartridge and a gold cartridge, which was sold exclusively through CoroCoro Comic. The gold cartridge included extra maps in battle mode.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/156675b4-e1cd-4d65-87c9-d6dc4e0ae612.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/711f1561-b949-42fb-99cf-a1268b002f65.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/29edb88a-4625-43d4-961b-b9e660cffe85.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8c48780f-c4e4-402c-bab8-ddf2e5301c2b.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>