<Game>
	<Name>Super Probotector - Alien Rebels (Europe) (Sample)</Name>
	<plot>Welcome to 2636, the year the Notorious One gets even, with an unprecendented alien onsalught orchestrated to push 16-bit technology and its commandos to their ultimate reaches.Plunge through a molten hot massacre on a high speed voyage to the guts of the archenemy alien. Scope out the side and top perspectives and backgrounds that do a 360 to engulf you in 3-D sensation. Pick off solar slimedogs like the Mutant Megasquitos and the Psycho Cyclers while you scale over walls, swing from girders and ropes, hitch rides on a missile, whatever it takes. Sweat through six gut splitting stages, including the Battle of the Blazing Sky and the Mucho Grande Badlands.The graphics are so real the explosions will nearly knock you off your feet. And the Boss Enemies are so gigantic, your screen can hardly hold them. You'll need to wrap both hands around artillery powerful enough to make today's weapons look like squirt guns. The Contra legacy is alive and dangerous!Cheat: 30 Lives (Japanese Version)This is for the japanese version only. At the title screen do a hadoken style motion that is Down, Down+Right, Right and press start. You should hear the player dieing sound effect if done correctly. You should position your cursor before entering it or you will start a 2 player game. You can position it above options and when you enter the options menu it will say Player Lives 30. The code remains enabled unless you change how many lives you start with in the options. If you do you must reenter the code. Cheat: 30 Lives (Japanese Version)At the title screen, quickly press: Right, Right-Down, Right and X. If done correctly you'll access the sound test.Cheat: 30 Lives (Japanese Version)At the title screen, quickly press: Down, Down-Left, Left, Up-Left, Up and Start for a 1-players stage select. Down, Down-Left, Left and Start for a 2-players stage select. If done correctly you should see the stage select screen.Cheat: Infinite livesNote: It will speed up the process if you use a turbo controller.When you get to level 3, fight your way through the stage until you get to the mini boss "The Flying Squito Nest" (the mini boss after you climb the building). Make sure you have the machine gun as your weapon or this won't work. Position your character as far to the left of the screen as you can and have him facing the right. Tape down the Y button and turn on your turbo mode. Set your controller down and come back in a few minutes to get a lot of lives (your lives max out when they get to 29).</plot>
	<releasedate>20/4/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Side Scroller</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>8.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>6lMxDTGrHYQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>300</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/563543-contra-iii-the-alien-wars</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/contra-iii-the-alien-wars/3030-3016/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/xRD7fky.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Jpi7KkT.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/y0K0Kf4.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/EwPYw5X.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/VyK4BPo.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/4Yuh7lh.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/kwPOiWi.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/zWzBSe5.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/NSzKfNQ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/u4e06Wh.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/FNEAred.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/PoReDs1.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/uYRGzeJ.jpg</banner1>
</game>