<Game>
	<Name>Super Aleste (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>'Space Megaforce&amp;trade;'. The game's thrilling speed is its most attractive feature. The enemy movements are fast. Your shots and the enemies' shots are fast. Finally, the scrolling is fast. The screen filled with battle action just overflows with high speed shooting excitement. On top of that there is the Shot Control System operated wiith the 'R' button. You can attack the enemy in a multitude of ways with a weapon using this system. Naturally, the features of the Super NES&amp;trade; such as rotation, enlarging, and shrinking functions are used to their fullest and huge enemies never before possible are packed into this exciting MEGA game!Cheat: Extra ending scenesThis only works in the Japanese version of the game.To get an extra ending scene, press the L and R buttons after the credits are over. If done correctly the screen will change to the extra scene instead of restarting back to the intro. There's an extra scene on each difficulty level.Cheat: Extra ending scenesOn the main menu, press Select twice and hold it. The option selection should be highlighted. Press Start. During game play, the last digit of the score will indicate the level of danger, with zero displaying for low danger areas to seven for high danger areas.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Shooter, Side Scroller</genre>
	<Developer>Compile</Developer>
	<rating>8.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>SpmEaffVnQI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18648</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588676-space-megaforce</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/space-megaforce/3030-3838/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/948HQ6e.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/razKKHr.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/gFxFQnA.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/L0IOk2N.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/8IPwZ0v.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/BkVoC7b.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/CKkuoJo.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/WQsDOUE.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/MmRNyhO.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/zrhl56t.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/wVMAy54.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/1wjAINd.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/fFxUZlY.jpg</banner1>
</game>