<Game>
	<Name>Syndicate (Europe) (En,Fr,De) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Syndicate is a  cyberpunk  isometric  real-time tactical game developed by  Bullfrog Productions and released in 1993 to critical acclaim. An expansion pack,  Syndicate: American Revolt (1993) and a sequel,  Syndicate Wars (1996), have also been released. On February 22, 2012 a  remake was released by  EA Partners and developed by  Starbreeze Studios.BackstoryAs the world of today slipped into the future, multinational corporations grew in size and profit. They came into positions to own small countries and to exercise direct influence over the world's governments. They practically became the world's governments, undemocratically controlling the lives of people through commerce. These corporations became known as Megacorps.One of the Megacorps, a European one, invented the CHIP. A device that is inserted into the neck and stimulates the brain stem to alter a persons perception of the outside world. The CHIP numbs a person's senses to the misery and squalor around them better than any drug and sold millions around the world. It could convince a user that the sun shone when it was raining and that they were more beautiful than they really were.The CHIP, like some  drugs, also made the user open to  auto-suggestion, allowing them to be manipulated by the Megacorps. The CHIP became a perfect tool for the Megacorps to manipulating the populace and to gain power with. It didn't take long before the Megacorps were corrupted and became crime Syndicates, fighting amongst each other for monopoly over CHIP manufacturing and control over the world.And in the year of 2096, the Syndicates have not only upgraded the drug they push, but also the way they fight. Instead of using ordinary thugs, they now use teams of custom-built  cyborg  agents to do their dirty deeds.Gameplay:The player takes on the role of a young executive in a small European Syndicate. The objective of the game is to spread the Syndicate's control globally.World view screenThe world is divided up into 50 territories. To gain control over a territory, the player must complete a mission in that territory. Missions objectives include the assassination of an important person, the elimination of rival agents or kidnapping. Once a territory has been gained, the player can start to collect taxes within it. The taxed amount can be adjusted, but if raised too high, the population can become rebellious against the Syndicate.The player selects a mission from the World map and can then select and outfit agents with weapons and  cybernetic modifications. Between missions, the player can also research new weapons and modifications. This is necessary if the player is to achieve the ultimate goal of world domination.During a missionIn the missions the player controls up to four agents from a fixed isometric view. This is to reflect the fact that the player's character is sitting in an airship high above the city map. The player tells the CHIP controlled agents where to move and where to fire. They will not react to any event unless the player activates Panic mode. During missions, the player can kill  civilians and destroy many things without consequence.Weapons: Pistol: Very cheap, but basically worthless. Medium range. Shotgun: Short effective range, but does more damage than the hand gun. Uzi SMG: Fast rate of fire, medium range and comes with plenty of ammunition.Long Range Rifle: Very long range and extremely accurate.Flame Thrower: Devastating, but with a very short range.Mini Gun: Gatling gun with a devastating rate of fire and an incredible range. Laser Gun: Will cut through anyone or anything that gets in it way.Gauss Gun: Portable rocket launcher. Hell yeah.Special EquipmentPersuadertron: A short range weapon that fires a small dose of chemicals, which will make the target lose all their free will and follow the agent who fired.Access Card: Plastic card that allows some security doors to restricted areas to be opened. Will also identify the agent carrying it as a Police officer to other Police units.Scanner: Scans for possible threats and items in the area.Time Bomb: High powered explosive that will, after a set time period, blow with devastating force.MediKit: Will restore a single agent&#8217;s health completely.Energy Shield: Will, during a very short time span, completely protect the agent against all projectile weapons.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Ocean Software Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>P7N5e1_67U0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6229</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588769-syndicate</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/syndicate</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/syndicate/3030-10865/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/j3IMBYu.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/aZldD9t.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/HoqX2HS.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/AKeFnyZ.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/syEDhsS.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/9DLORBq.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/0u5vhiM.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/dtSJwoT.jpg</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://i.imgur.com/Y1rdTCb.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://i.imgur.com/dFu8ntZ.jpg</boxart10>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xBWbo5v.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/PZuw1Cg.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/TCAAxeJ.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/gbtmCHv.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Tfxnfsx.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/YIMLhOE.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/eOa0sYg.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/la2NfxP.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Bzl11UC.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/jAT9gRC.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/XRDS7nJ.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Vni5P7E.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In the future, the world is controlled by a handful of global corporations (syndicates).  You are the Marketing director (hit man) for one of these companies.  It is your job to take control away from the competitors.  The job is not one of diplomacy, but one of brute force and physical control.  Advance your way to the top of the corporation by successfully completing your missions and managing the money you make from your territories. The gameplay is visually reminiscent of X-Com, with an angled top-down perspective, but it is real time rather than turn based. You have missions ranging from infiltrate and capture, to seek and destroy. In each of these you direct a team of four agents as they move through the world shooting at anything that gets in their way. You can upgrade and modify your agents, as well as equip them with tools you have researched or liberated from opposing syndicates.  As you complete missions, you gain more funds to use for purchasing agents or researching upgrades and equipment.</Notes>
	<boxart11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/95051fbb-21bf-4de0-bfa4-3ca3d91b48d3.png</boxart11>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2e86ddb5-33e7-4575-b45e-cf3ec5759e14.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/50e35a85-6416-4166-8555-e011a11942c5.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb1568c9-5017-4f1c-9b32-5ba0bd92061b.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Laguna</Publisher>
</game>