<Game>
	<Name>Tecmo Super Baseball (Japan) (En)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Tecmo Super Baseball is a 1994 Super Nintendo and Genesis baseball game and part of Tecmo's "Super" series of sports games. The game is licensed by the MLBPA but not the MLB, so it contains the names and likenesses of all the athletes active in the MLB at the time but not the team names. Instead, the game uses generic city names for its teams, as well as featuring two All-Star teams.The batting/pitching uses the genre's standard camera angle of having the pitcher at the top of the screen with the batter at the bottom, but the game uses an unusual perspective for its fielding, which follows the ball rather than switching to an overhead view. The player automatically switches to the closest fielder in the ball's trajectory, allowing the player to quickly reach it and return it. The camera will continue to follow the ball as it is thrown around.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Tecmo, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6248</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588773-tecmo-super-baseball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/tecmo-super-baseball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tecmo-super-baseball/3030-22849/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/96z4jXg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/YcuwLBP.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Mcxpx4s.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/02Mt4b0.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/qELT9af.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/zkm1Kql.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/s7S1l31.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/l6Zi3K9.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/y99YNeJ.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/IjJKfvC.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/VqNm4JC.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/K1rapkz.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/A7uYEhA.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/N6D2RUU.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Officially licensed by the Major League Baseball Players Association, Tecmo Super Baseball is the most exciting game ever made for your Super NES. While most others can focus on only pitching and batting, Tecmo Super Baseball is the first to provide you with a realistic fielder's point of view. The field perspectives created by Tecmo's exclusive Flying Camera give you a feel of the game you've never experienced before. From the first pitch to the last out, you're in control of both the offense and defense, and right in the middle of the action with large graphic pitching and batting perspectives. Only Tecmo delivers real baseball action.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/df6e00b4-e6a9-480b-8684-a3d4563436ae.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/10d2d1e6-f38f-40f1-8836-1d23ae48b03a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ad3f5879-21fa-4c41-a99c-304b40c70326.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0737bffa-785d-43fa-b270-2780a1cd572d.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Tecmo</Publisher>
</game>