<Game>
	<Name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Tournament Fighters (Australia)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tournament Fighters (known in Europe as Teenage Mutant Hero Turtles: Tournament Fighters, and in the Japanese SNES version as Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Mutant Warriors) are 2D fighting games developed and published by Konami for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System and Genesis on December 1993, and for the Nintendo Entertainment System (only in North America and Europe) on February 1994.Based on the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles franchise, each of the three fighting games pits the titular ninja turtles (Leonardo, Donatello, Raphael, and Michelangelo) against a variety of mutants, aliens, and martial artists from the series (usually to rescue their kidnapped mentor, Master Splinter).Each of the three games are known for having completely different fighting game engines, storylines, and character rosters. Each game also have their own unique gameplay mechanic: the SNES version has a Super Meter for powerful super moves, the Genesis version has super moves available at low vitality, and the NES version has a special "ball" power-up for a bonus special move.Tournament Fighters is the last in the franchise to be released in the 1990s (creating a ten-year hiatus ending with the tie-in game to the 2003 animated series). The NES version is also known both as Konami's last game released for that platform and as one of the few fighting games released for that platform.Characters:Each of the three games have different assortments of playable characters with minor overlap. All playable characters (with the exception of Aska and Sisyphus) have appeared in previous comics and the animated series. The only characters that are playable in all three games are the ninja turtles themselves:Leonardo - The leader of the turtles and has a serious personality. Known by his blue headband and dual katanas.Donatello - The brains of the turtles who is often working on his inventions. Known by his purple headband and bo staff.Raphael - The surly wiseguy of the group. Known by his red headband and dual sais.Michelangelo - The easy-going "party dude". Known by his orange headband and dual nunchaku.SNES VersionShredder - The leader of the Foot Clan and the turtles' eternal nemesis: a ninja warrior adorned with spiked armor. Known in the game as "Cyber Shredder".War - A fierce monster with large claws. Referred to in-game as an "intergalactic lifeform".Aska - A ninja girl hoping to open her own dojo with her prize winnings. She is an original character exclusive to this game.Wingnut - A mutant resembling a bat.Chrome Dome - An android that Shredder once built to exterminate the turtles.Armaggon - A mutant, resembling a shark, from the future.Rat King - A crimelord who has a legion of rats at his beck and call. (boss, unlockable in Versus mode with a cheat code)Karai - A high-ranking member of the Foot Clan and a powerful martial artist. (boss, unlockable in Versus mode with a cheat code)Genesis VersionCasey Jones - A street vigilante who fights with improvised weapons.Ray Fillet - A mutant resembling a manta ray.April O'Neil - A news reporter (and usual damsel in distress for the turtles) who now takes part in combat.Sisyphus - A mutant resembling a scarab beetle. It is an original character exclusive to this game.Triceraton - Member of an alien species resembling a anthropomorphic triceratops (boss, only playable with an external cheat tool)Krang's Android - A disembodied alien brain and Shredder's oft-cohort (boss, only playable with an external cheat tool)Karai - (boss, only playable with an external cheat tool)NES VersionCasey JonesHothead - A Chinese-American firefighter who was magically transformed into a dragon.ShredderStory:NES VersionThe turtles have been challenged by Shredder, but before they fight him they decide to have a tournament between themselves to see who is ready for the encounter.SNES VersionA tournament has been organized and fighters from all over have entered, Shredder of course being one of them. The turtles decide to enter the tournament in order to stop Shredder and prove their strength in battle.One of the unique features of the SNES version was the different turbo speeds. At the highest setting, this game was faster than Street Fighter II Turbo at the highest setting.Genesis Version Master Splinter is kidnapped by four purple turtles. When the real turtles find out, Krang appears and tells the turtles that he has Splinter with him and that the only way to rescue him is to go to Dimension X and meet Krang. Endings:The endings on the NES version are basically the same for all four of the turtles. The only difference is the portrait of the turtle which the player used to beat the game. In the ending the winning turtle accuses Shredder of being up to one of his lousy tricks. Shredder says that they have not seen the last of him, he then gets up and runs off-screen. Splinter comes floating into the screen, drops down in front of the turtle and says "You have performed well my sons. Now let us celebrate our victory."Endings (SNES)CharacterEnding RaphaelRaphael gives his thanks to Splinter and April by giving them a pile of gifts. Raphael then tells them he is happy to have friends as good as they are. MichelangeloMichelangelo decides to take a vacation in the Bahamas to do some surfing, then invites the other turtles to come along. LeonardoLeonardo says his daily training has paid off, and now he must set new goals and set out to achieve those goals. Leonardo then goes right back into his training. DonatelloDonatello goes back to working on his latest invention which then blows up. He then says he might have some money left over to start a new invention. AskaAska is happy to be able to finally realize her dream of teaching younger people in the ways of Ninjitsu. She then exclaims she will have the best dojo in the entire world. ShredderShredder says he knew he would win the tournament and that he has defeated the turtles for the last time. He now has his sights set on conquering Earth. WarWar exclaims that he won and that has shown the other fighters not to mess with an intergalactic life form. ArmaggonArmaggon exclaims that it is only natural that he won the tournament and that he is the strongest living being on the planet and must now conquer it. WingnutWingnut only entered the tournament to pound some heads. He pounded everyone else and ended up winning and now will be able to waste even more money. Chrome DomeChrome Dome now has the money to purchase the necessary computers in order to extract his faulty program. He will finally be able to exist in peace. Critical ReceptionElectronic Gaming Monthly gave the SNES version review scores of 9,8,9 and 9 out of ten. Ed Semrad wrote, "This has got to be one of the best fighting games next to Street Fighter 2, (and in some cases better than SF2). The voices are crisp and clear, plus the control is absolutely wonderful! Another factor that I truly like is the story mode set up with dialog boxes unraveling the whole plot! There are plenty of combos that will get you going! Another great hit from the pros at Konami".		</plot>
	<releasedate>4/9/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami (America), Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>PcFk_sP4dV8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3283</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588778-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters__</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-tournament-fighters/3030-4896/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/WbjjaFP.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/IffYl23.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/RJGiOiU.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/XcHnhGM.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/VyN2ifR.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/mgSprD9.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/fvbxrZH.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/qlozZM0.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ySqjS7D.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/OIT6Wqo.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/vB37iBo.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/RTyjrdf.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/b1tA8me.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/vsSyAEF.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/OGzm4b1.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/dkWXjw2.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/1Cbhxkh.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/5Zm3EBY.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/qKnjcPa.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/hlCBFKP.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>http://i.imgur.com/XH3DJgG.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>http://i.imgur.com/oZE4KZM.jpg</fanart7>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/roKq54R.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/1odwx3K.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Trash the surf board and heave the 'za. It's a whole new breed of Turtles and they're fixated on fighting. We're dead serious, Tournament Fighters takes dude-on-dude demolition to new heights of intensity with 4 modes of pain-producing battles, deadly warriors, secret arenas, astounding graphics and sound effects that'll make you cringe! Clash with Krang-created clones of the Turtles, Casey Jones, April O'Neil, Ray Filet and Sisyphus, plus bosses Triceraton, Krang's Android and Karai. There's flying body presses, knee drops, head butts, rocket punches, elbow smashes, somersault throws, you'll feel and inflict them all. And the settings include Magma Ocean Planet, Jungle Planet, and every other bizarre corner of Dimension X!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>KHVqKJWI9uc</VideoURL1>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f14c282c-3d38-4d3e-8f98-6ddbb18ecd95.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/defd35fc-c9ee-4dec-acc0-e445319981bd.png</boxart7>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/20878cb8-abc5-4ecf-84e9-011d2d645910.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1a5169be-6a2e-4514-8ff7-c52b878328e3.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7eae7f8a-7996-4a5f-b8cd-12bee61211cc.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/311fe4ec-9075-422d-bac3-a7832e83501f.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6f5d7cc3-657b-42d4-95eb-4b28f9c3bce4.jpg</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2700b985-3f49-4a05-8a59-7ce949618cff.jpg</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/da0c1feb-9fd2-49ed-8d2c-5696d9113949.jpg</snapshot16>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>