<Game>
	<Name>Tenchi Souzou (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>A boy's curiosity triggers events that leads to the resurrection of life to this planet.In the Distant past, a calamitous struggle between light and dark took place on this planet. The clash of the two opposing powers scoured the planet's surface entirely of life, and those two forces fell into a deep sleep...In the world on the inside of the planet, there exists just one small village of Crysta. Ark, a mischievous teenage boy, somehow causes a crisis in the village that makes him necessary to leave. His trip to save his fellow villagers eventually becomes a journey across time to resurrect the planet. On his epic journey, Ark must resurrect continents, revive all forms of life, and re-establish civilization. What fate awaits Ark at the end of his journey?Cheat: Almost Free Saving and Inn in LitzIt normally costs you 10 Gems to get to the Diary in Litz, which is in the inn room with your bed.  However, if you pay the man guarding the door for your room but never actually use the bed (use the food on the table outside instead) you can heal and save for free!Cheat: Almost Free Saving and Inn in Litz(Note: you will have to use the bed to trigger a cutscene after beating Bloody Mary)Cheat: Easy 500 gemsIn Louran, go to Temjin's house and talk to him. When he asks you what to do with his money, tell him to take it to his grave. Later on, when Louran transforms into a ghost town, go to the cemetary and check the most northwest grave. It's Temjin's. Guess what, the guy took your advice and you've just become 500 gems heavier.</plot>
	<releasedate>19/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Quintet</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>WBjHrRLvzzo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>1783</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588784-terranigma</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/terranigma/3030-13828/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/86frTNC.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ayhtURE.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/yxQggTs.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/CKe4QBk.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/czmz3w1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/MVgHyv8.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/02xXb0D.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ECoBm7z.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/uS4HIuR.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/8MADdOu.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/OzlPhRf.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/UF2j4HU.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/VIf8HCI.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/2dwZsQQ.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/gng5NwH.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>http://i.imgur.com/noSHhXQ.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>http://i.imgur.com/J7Y5sG8.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/cMZyLg1.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/W5i6zcB.png</clearlogo1>
</game>