<Game>
	<Name>Tengai Makyou Zero (Japan) (Shounen Jump no Shou)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Tengai Makyou Zero is a turn-based RPG created by RED Company and Hudson for the Super Famicom in 1995. The game is the fourth entry in the Tengai Makyou franchise and is the only game in the series to be released for the Super Famicom.Tengai Makyou Zero lacks the cut-scenes, voice acting, and CD quality music that the franchise is known for due to the limitations of Nintendo's hardware. However Zero's presentation not only competes with the rest of the series but it is also one of the most graphically advanced titles on the Super Famciom thanks to the cartridge's SPC7110 decompression chip. The SPC7110 chip was developed by the Seiko Epson Corporation and it allowed Red Company to compress over 72mbits of game data into Zero's already hefty 40mbit cartridge. Zero's cartridge also contained an internal battery that powered a real world clock that would unlocks special time specific events in the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>RED Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<VideoURL>UTInJjbdLgI</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581824-tengai-makyou-zero</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/tengai-maky-zero</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tengai-makyou-zero/3030-15375/</giantbomb_url>
	<wiki_url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Far_East_of_Eden_Zero</wiki_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/MjCIu0X.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/j8MqzmO.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/xmwIVzp.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/5BZxYJE.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/m6YWh3V.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/uurKOO9.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Gm0LU2M.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/wuOpmlj.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/FbIGljB.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/NFRmIDN.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/FtrahsX.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/6RqMtGU.gif</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/yP3dvxv.gif</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/79PWvOQ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Tengai Makyo Zero is a side-story to the first three Tengai Makyo games (for PC Engine CD). The ancient land of Jipang is a lot like the medieval Japan, but is is ruled by godly and demonic powers, and is made up of six countries, the most powerful one being the Ryu (Dragon) Kingdom. The younger of two brothers has been recently chosen to be the king of the Dragon Country. The elder brother decides to kill him and to take the throne. His soul is possessed by the demon Ninigi, and he plots a further destruction of Jipang. The hero of the game, a young boy named Higan, lives in Hikagi Village. After the village has been frozen by the possessed king of Ryu, Higan realizes he was chosen by a mysterious Ancient Flame to free Jipang from the claws of Ninigi. The game is a traditional RPG with turn-based combat viewed from over-the-shoulder perspective. The characters can attack physically, cast magic spells, as well as perform special techniques, unique to each character.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f8339058-79cb-459c-8749-191faada816c.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b3995c1d-e1a3-4eef-9c8e-e398eb4ca9da.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c15ab09-6f74-4f13-b848-c1ce7ede86af.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>