<Game>
	<Name>Tenshi no Uta - Shiroki Tsubasa no Inori (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Reyard is a young man who lives in the town of Farell; his father is a skilled blacksmith, and the youngster hopes to follow the same career, enjoying a peaceful life. But everything changes when a wandering group of performers arrives in the town. Reyard meets Kurana, one of the artists, who was adopted by the leader of the troop, and is hoping to find her true parents. The two meet several times, and Reyard realizes that he has fallen in love. However, when Kurana tells him she will leave Farell soon, he is unable to express his feelings. Only when he hears that the duke of Bern is determined to marry Kurana, even against her will, Reyard understands that he has to do something...Tenshi no Uta: Shiroki Tsubasa no Inori ("The Prayer of the White Wings") is the third game in the  series. It starts a new story, but is set in the same universe; the stories of the two previous games are referred to in this game, and recurrent characters appear. The game is a traditional Japanese-style RPG with top-down navigation, random enemies, turn-based combat (viewed from first-person perspective), linear story progression, and automatic leveling. The stand-out feature of the game is the ability to communicate with monsters encountered in battle, by learning "monster languages". It is possible to convince the monsters not to fight, and even trade and acquire rare items from them.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/7/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Telenet Japan Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571100-tenshi-no-uta</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/tenshi-no-uta-shiroki-tsubasa-no-inori</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tenshi-no-uta-shiroki-tsubasa-no-inori/3030-37322/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/VLSf0Xp.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/7YwxLu0.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/NvniP3g.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/DaP1axt.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Yf3H7S9.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/LdzujKd.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/XretpNr.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/C2qCrOb.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/pxMQFRm.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/XM32HAX.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/DgRTVI3.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/YJGByLy.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Jo4MRPq.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Tenshi No Uta: Shiroki Tsubasa no Inori (天使の詩 〜白き翼の祈り is a video game published by Nippon Telenet Japan for the Super Famicom in 1994. It is the third episode in the Tenshi no Uta RPG series, but is not a true sequel to the first and second episodes previously released on the PC Engine.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9342b95f-ef74-44d8-abf3-b5044de5a34f.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b016e8b-0f93-475d-a258-17ad8a6bcaa4.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9f79b641-2e01-49bb-a7f6-c5480163fdfd.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1fc8bf2d-cdd5-4966-859b-5110cb092a4d.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Nippon Telenet</Publisher>
</game>