<Game>
	<Name>Tetris & Dr. Mario (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Two of the most popular puzzle games return, but now together in an exclusive compilation for SNES. The games have a slight graphical update when compared with the original Game Boy and NES games, but the gameplay remains totally faithful to the games released for both platforms.In Tetris, the main objective is to pile blocks that will fall down continuously, in order to create a row or "line" without spaces. For this collection, the game comes with two bonus options: 2 PLAYER GAME (absent in the NES version) and VS. COM (absent in both versions), with 3 CPU opponents available, each one representing a difficulty level (EASY, MEDIUM, and HARD, respectively).In Dr. Mario, the objective is to eliminate all the viruses contained in a big bottle. Dr. Mario (situated in the upper-right side of the screen) will throw capsules with 6 different color combinations (Red-Red, Red-Blue, Yellow-Yellow, Red-Yellow, Blue-Blue and Blue-Yellow) in order to line up at least four viruses or capsules of the same color horizontally or vertically and to make them disappear. In this compilation, the game comes with a bonus option: VS. COM, where you'll face the CPU players: Blue Virus (EASY), Yellow Virus (MEDIUM), and Red Virus (HARD).For competitive players in both games, there is Mixed Match, where you and a friend can play Tetris and Dr. Mario like a tournament! Adjust the handicap levels, play time, music, and other settings to balance your different skills. The game order is: TETRIS B-TYPE (clear a certain amount of lines), DR. MARIO (disinfect a predetermined number of viruses) and TETRIS A-TYPE (clear lines until the time expires). At the end of the time limit, the player with the highest score is the winner.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>bmAFDRMEDXs</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3280</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/575629-tetris-and-dr-mario</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/tetris-dr-mario</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tetris-dr-mario/3030-6805/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/YU5Whfi.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/8wLwFFg.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/necTGdi.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/zdCLHQD.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/mWzrXNH.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/rCtCAbY.jpg</boxart6>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/8bRbPgP.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/uZujQNk.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/yjwStWg.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/2KEwcnp.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/uFAKMgs.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/cjffSVC.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/HipIfPg.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/gd4tKaV.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/cij7E2Q.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/cDFgKea.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/oKQDmLb.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/FK1C7KU.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/h3wWpkF.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The two greatest puzzle games are now together in one exciting game pak only on Super NES! TETRIS: The relentless building block video puzzle from Russia is back and enhanced for Super NES. Play solo, with a friend or challenge one of three computer opponents in this exciting and addicting game! DR. MARIO: Those nasty viruses have returned. Dr. Mario, vitamin pills in hand, is ready to eliminate them once more. In addition to the ever-popular 2-player game, now you can challenge the computer in the guise of the Blue, Yellow or Red Virus. MIXED MATCH: Combine Tetris and Dr. Mario and what do you get? One exciting contest for 2 players! Race against the clock to outscore your opponent while playing both Tetris and Dr. Mario!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1ee592cf-343b-4ff5-8c56-2eaf3c615321.png</banner2>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cf9b67fd-23c1-4c8c-b9f3-4a77b7c78b4f.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/03e726a1-6029-4127-936c-a3ec4cf86eea.png</boxart8>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd3ec492-7578-4894-ac8f-9bb428fb26ec.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/52a2e471-86ff-4c39-b3f4-06768df4c2f4.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5bb8416b-1156-45ce-93c9-a28638e56669.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>