<Game>
	<Name>Tetris Attack (USA) (En,Ja)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Tetris Attack is the North American version of Panel de PonTetris Attack is the North American version of Panel de Pon (Paneru de Pon), initially a Japanese game which was one of the founders of the now commonly found "tile swapping" mechanic of puzzle gameplay. The core gameplay consists of a well partially filled with either 5 or 6 distinct types of tiles, depending on the difficulty level. Adjacent tiles may be swapped horizontally with the cursor, and matching three or more tiles vertically or horizontally will result in the tiles clearing after a short delay animation, during which they become immovable. Additional points may be earned with either "combos," which involve clearing more than 3 tiles simultaneously, or "chains," which require that the tiles above a clearing set fall into another clear. During play, the stack of tiles will slowly rise to the top of the screen, though clearing tiles will pause this advance. After a grace period after the stack reaches the top of the well, the game will end.The version of Panel de Pon included in the Japan-only Nintendo Puzzle Collection has more differences from the original game than any other game included on the disc. The game is essentially the same as Pok&#233;mon Puzzle League, as it is a version of the game skinned as "Panel de Pon 64." Thus, it features many of the same things as Pok&#233;mon Puzzle League (such as a 3D mode, new characters, updated graphics, and a new four-player mode, which wasn't in Pok&#233;mon Puzzle League). Despite these changes, gameplay-wise it is nothing more than an enhanced version of Panel de Pon.Game Modes:There are 5 major game modes in Tetris Attack. In most modes, a difficulty level may be selected, and in some modes an initial speed may be selected; this may be confusing to new players, but while the difficulty level affects the rate at which death occurs, the number of tile types in play, and the rate at which tiles fall upon finding themselves in mid-air, the initial speed merely controls the speed at which the stack rises.EndlessThis mode allows the player to select a difficulty level and speed, and allows nearly limitless play. The name of the mode is misleading, however, as gameplay will necessarily end: either the player will die, or reach 99,999 points, upon which the game will end. Should the player reach this maximum point score, credits will be rolled.Time TrialThis mode provides a 2 minute length of time in which to earn as many points as possible. The difficulty and speed may be set prior to the game. This mode may be played with either 1 or 2 players.Stage ClearThe Stage Clear mode requires that players clear the stack down to a particular "clear line" to pass each stage, of which there are several per character in the game. In addition, there are certain "boss battles," in which the player must earn points as quickly as possible to reduce the boss's HP level to zero.PuzzleThis mode involves a collection of designed puzzles, of which there are ten per character in the game, as well as many "special" levels, totaling 120 levels. Each involves a set of tiles that must be cleared completely within the predetermined number of tile swaps.VSA screenshot of gameplayThe VS mode is the only game mode to feature the Garbage mechanic, as well as the only mode which features a computer-controlled AI. In it, each player attempts to stay alive and force the other player to lose first. This may be done by dumping "garbage blocks" upon the other player, by creating either combos or chains. Increasingly large combos will result in larger-width as well as multiple single slabs of garbage to be dropped on the player's opponent, while increasingly large chains will result in thicker single blocks of garbage. Clearing garbage may be done by matching three or more tiles adjacent to the garbage, upon which all the garbage in contact in the stack will flash and begin transforming into normal tiles, starting from the very bottom and progressing to the top of the garbage stack. These tiles, though revealed, are not in play until the entire stack has transformed, upon which it will fall onto the existing stack; this lag time is in turn an excellent time to anticipate and create large combos and chains. However, garbage created with chains consists of single multilayer blocks; these blocks will not completely transform with each attempt - instead, only the bottom layer will become normal tiles, while the rest will transform back into a single block.In addition, there are special tiles in the VS mode which are gray and marked with exclamation points. These appear only sporadically, and, when matched, create special "steel" garbage blocks to be dropped on the player's opponent. These are unique because they do not clear when in contact with regular clearing garbage - they must be cleared separately. This effectively limits the clearing ability of one's opponent, and is particularly useful when sandwiched between two large segments of regular garbage.Characters:YoshiBumptyFlutterGargantua BlarggLunge FishPrince FroggyLakituPoochyHookbill the KoopaNaval PiranhaKamekBowserScoring:As mentioned above, tiles may be cleared in either "combos" or "chains" for additional points.CombosCombos are achieved by clearing more than three tiles simultaneously. This can be done either through clever tile manipulation, or by matching tiles to inactive rows as they appear on screen. A more advanced method, called "garbage chaining," involves matching tiles in play with clearing rows of garbage from above. This is particularly useful for dealing with single blocks of thick garbage.The scoring details of combos are as follows:4 tiles: 20 points5 tiles: 30 points6 tiles: 50 points7 tiles: 60 points8 tiles: 70 points9 tiles: 80 points10 tiles: 100 points11 tiles: 140 points12 tiles: 170 pointsChainsChains are much more difficult to plan and execute than combos, and are thus worth substantially more points. Tiles must fall from above a clear into another clear to create a chain; once this condition is failed, the chain ends and a new one must be initiated. There are several advanced techniques involving chains, many of which are detailed in Advanced Gameplay Mechanics below. Noteworthy, however, is the fact that Tetris Attack does not in fact recognize chains of longer than 13 - rather than the standard x14 or x15 icon which would be the expected result of further chaining, players are presented with a x? icon and rewarded no points whatsoever for their continued efforts.Another nuance in the scoring system involving chains, however, is that of "bonuses." When a normal clear is made alongside a chain, that clear is awarded the same number of points as the current chain clear, instead of the standard clear amount. Thus, a standard strategy when trying to score points quickly is to quickly build out to a x13 chain, then instantly initiating as many standard three tile clears on the side as possible to maximize the number of points earned on the chain.The scoring details of chains are as follows:x2 chain: 50 pointsx3 chain: 80 pointsx4 chain: 150 pointsx5 chain: 300 pointsx6 chain: 400 pointsx7 chain: 500 pointsx8 chain: 700 pointsx9 chain: 900 pointsx10 chain: 1100 pointsx11 chain: 1300 pointsx12 chain: 1500 pointsx13 chain: 1800 pointsx14 chain: 0 pointsAdvanced Gameplay MechanicsSeveral nuances in Tetris Attack's engine allow for unique techniques while playing Tetris Attack. Since most rules are calculated on a frame-by-frame basis, some of the basic physical rules of the game can be bent - others may be broken. For instance, it is possible for a single tile to very briefly, while in the process of shifting between two columns, support two sets of falling tiles above it, just long enough to register the above tiles as a clear should they be positioned as such. This is particularly useful as a last-resort when attempted to keep chains alive. It is also possible, though vastly more difficult, to swap tiles in midair as they fall, and to swap tiles "through" clear arrangements such as they do not trigger the clear.Story and Multiple EndingsChoosing one of the friends to free.Tetris Attack's story is rather loose: there appears to be some sort of curse which has befallen all the major characters (who were enemies from Super Mario World 2: Yoshi's Island, but are apparently now friends) except for Yoshi, and Yoshi must therefore battle each character in a VS mode match to free them. Upon freeing Lakitu, Bumpty, Poochy, Flying Wiggler, Froggy, Blargg, Lunge Fish, and Rafael the Raven, the gang continues on to defeat Hookbill the Koopa, Naval Piranha, Kamek, and finally Bowser (in difficulty levels above easy) in the Cave of Darkness to win the day. Upon completion on hard, a code is given to the player to unlock "hardest" mode, and upon completion of hardest mode without dying, another code is given which allows the selection of characters prior to each match rather than only matches in the Cave of Darkness; the point is to choose characters other than Yoshi, as hinted at in the dialogue. Each level of completion involves a different set of dialogue at the end. However, this final step to achieving the VS mode "perfect" ending is rather superfluous, as it is no more difficult than beating the game on hardest without dying without the character selection.Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsGo to 'vs' in the menu selection, then go to the 'password' menu. Input one of these codes:Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsCheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsCheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsCheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsGo to the 1P menu, then 'stage clear' and then to the password section. Enter one of the following to go to the corresponding level:Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsAfter the title screen select 1 player game, then the fourth selection, then the second and enter the following chain.Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsAfter the title screen select 1 player game, then the fourth selection, then the second and enter the following chain.Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsAfter the title screen select 1 player game, then the third selection, then the second and enter the following chain.Cheat: 1-P vs. Mode PasswordsEnter these at the 1P vs. password screen. When it says ERROR! keep pressing the B button to backup to the menu that says new game and password and select new game. Choose a difficulty level and start the game. Now when you loose it will say you have 43 or 90 continues.Cheat: Guaranteed Victory vs CPUIf you have a controller with a "turbo" option for buttons A or B, you can use the following exploit against the CPU so that you [I]always[/I] win! Cheat: Guaranteed Victory vs CPUFirst, when you turn on the game and Yoshi appears in front of a blue screen and says "Nintendo," press B, A, L, L. You should hear a confirmation code when you input the cheat correctly. This will remove the "freeze" that occurs when you or your opponent makes a combo or a chain. In other words, the blocks never stop rising. After entering the cheat, activate turbo for either A or B. Once you are competing against your CPU opponent in splitscreen, place your cursor over any two blocks or one block and an empty panel, and hold down turbo. The panels will switch back and forth so quickly that your blocks will not rise, nor will garbage blocks fall on you! Eventually, the speed of the rising blocks will surpass the CPU's ability to get rid of them and you will win! Cheat: Guaranteed Victory vs CPUAlthough it takes a while in later stages, you can use this exploit to beat every difficulty in VS Mode.Cheat: Guaranteed Victory vs CPUIn any of the sessions hold down the "R" button.  You can now control the cursor and try out the chains, combos, and skill chains on your own.Cheat: Guaranteed Victory vs CPUIn Time Trial, you get progressively more and more points for larger chains until the 13x chain. However, if you keep a chain going any longer than the 13th link (x?), you don't get any chain-link bonus points. For this reason, you should never let a chain go past the 13th link in time trial.Cheat: Secret CharacterGo to the Player vs. Player character select screen, then hold L + R on both controllers for a few seconds. If you did it right, the question marks (?) at the bottom of the screen will be replaced by bosses.Cheat: All EndingsGood Ending: Beat the game using no continues.Cheat: All EndingsBad Ending: Beat the game with at least one continue.Cheat: All EndingsAfter you've beaten the game on Medium difficulty or higher and the credits are rolling, hold SELECT and you can use the Control Pad to move Yoshi around in the background.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>W-kXJa_5R4Y</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3281</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588787-tetris-attack</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/tetris-attack</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tetris-attack/3030-13130/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/GMKoRXO.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/oLBpyzN.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/oJO4LY0.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/St3Qn3h.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/57Rp1VC.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/NkeA11Y.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wG38W3a.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/5EOxsuJ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/mbPwW2X.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/dtBqBDK.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/TaIk0jl.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/zTCjbfq.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/DFgmL3p.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/DA9geel.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/t6eHGEE.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/40Tk7kl.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/RND9Mdy.png</clearlogo1>
</game>