<Game>
	<Name>Thunder Spirits (Japan) (En)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Thunder Spirits is a 1991 SNES port of the arcade title Thunder Force AC, which itself was a modified port of the highly-praised Sega Genesis title Thunder Force III developed by Technosoft. The port was published by Seika Corporation.When compared with the Genesis title, gameplay-wise they were nearly identical, with the only real differences being the Heads Up Display being moved from the top to the bottom of the screen, minor alterations to some of the levels, and the removal of the ability to choose the order in which you completed the levels. However, it suffered from the notorious "slowdown" that plagued many early Super Nintendo titles when too much activity on the screen at once would overtax the system. A loss in music and sound effects quality was present as well.Cheat: CodesEnter the code while the game is paused.  After the code has been successfully entered, press the following buttons to change the properties of your ship:A - upgrade/add weaponsB - downgrade/remove weaponsX - add support gunsY - add shieldCheat: Extra Configuration OptionsAfter beating the game, check the Config screen (Select+Start on the title screen), and extra options will be added to the menu, ranging from number of reserve ships to a Sound Test.  </plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Seika Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>yiFV_-ENxjc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6298</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588789-thunder-spirits</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/thunder-spirits</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/thunder-spirits/3030-9798/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/1nzbdbg.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nCaVsap.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/ydTHXds.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/5dBzL1f.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Q2Eondk.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/0o9hfkg.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zfmcUru.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/q6EHYdF.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Q8wuWl2.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/XbG0WXa.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/U7j6uh6.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/t651T7B.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/0peFAoA.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/gQ1xSrw.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/bpEtiV0.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DFTZpaV.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/fwqAqwL.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Fasten your seat belts! It's gonna be an eye popping, pulse pounding, mind blowing ride! Your super-powered starship is under attack on land, air and sea in this Action/Arcade thriller. But you're prepared to go out with a bang. Zap! Blast your way through a fire storm. Splash! Use the wave weapon to pulverize an enemy. It's an 8-stage intergalactic fight to the finish. And even the multi-level scrolling and haunting sound effects are out of this world. Boss characters with the most chillingly realistic graphics try to show you who's the boss. But if you're quick enough and smart enough, you can prevail.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b983ded0-3b12-476f-b22c-6f1aadb08984.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/624ad999-cdd7-406c-8b97-09ae9a5b7ecc.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/21c69106-1413-44a5-b9fc-674b95beeba1.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f3f7019f-221f-4299-8816-f600176eb5ee.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Seika</Publisher>
</game>