<Game>
	<Name>Time Slip (Europe) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Time Slip is a 1993 Super Nintendo Entertainment System game developed by Sales Curve and published by Vic Tokai. The game is very similar to the Contra franchise (more specifically, Contra III: The Alien Wars), but was criticized for being of exceptionally lower quality. The game was criticized for its poor artificial intelligence, sloppy control, no continues, and general lack of challenge. Reviewers agreed that the game's music was its best aspect. Time Slip holds a 36% average on Game Rankings.Plot:Dr. Vincent Gilgamesh gets in the time machine.Time Slip stars Dr. Vincent Gilgamesh, a scientist from the year 2045 who discovers an alien plot to take over Earth. To prevent an invasion of an alien race called the Tiamatians, Dr. Gilgamesh travels to various eras of time to defeat the aliens (as they have found a way to exploit rifts in time).The background of the Tiamatians is simple; they are from the planet Tiamat. The aliens want to find a planet similar to Tiamat, so they send a probe through the rift called the Torquemada II. Through use of that probe, they find Earth, and intend to turn it into Tiamat II. By then, scientists on Earth have discovered the rift as well, and have been studying it for years.If the player gets a game over during gameplay, Dr. Gilgamesh fails to prevent the aliens from conquering Earth, and it is hinted that his birth is even prevented.Gameplay:Time Slip was criticized for being far too easy.The game is very similar to Contra III: The Alien Wars. Even movements mirror those of Contra III. Time Slip does have its numerous differences, however. One such differences is the TGS bar (essentially a power bar, that must constantly be refilled). This TGS bar is what keeps Dr. Gilgamesh alive, and if it runs out he dies. To refill the bar, players must be picking up crystals scattered throughout the levels.Every level is filled with various enemies, a mid-level boss, and a level boss. The game was notoriously easy, even with its later bosses. Scattered throughout the levels are traps based on the time period Dr. Gilgamesh is in. Similarly to Contra III, the player can upgrade weapons as gameplay progresses. By picking up power-ups (found in boxes that must be "shot" open), the player can improve the weapon (although these upgrades are lost after death). Time Slip even contains some vehicles for the player to use, although they do not dramatically alter gameplay.Time Slip, unlike Contra III, has no continues, and rather starts the player out with nine lives. In addition, there is no code to expand the player's lives (Contra III contains the famous Konami Code). Time Slip has no way to save the game either, and no password system, so if the player dies, they have to start completely over.								</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Vic Tokai, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>8CkaV1-dhJo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6299</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588792-time-slip</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/time-slip</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/time-slip/3030-21340/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ghGPQlf.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/BRn3jLN.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/JEl2xuv.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/93Yw9P7.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/CXMs4G6.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/4N9aMmA.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/pv1Ll2y.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/WBTwjnH.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/PNJm9fV.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/GJS3rRS.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/JUnv2Rn.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/GtIEHJg.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/3Bj8g8I.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Feg8RMS.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/SsIxMSR.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/WVS0Zr2.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>On the reptilian planet of Tirmat, scientists have discovered a rift in space and plan to use it to transport the planet's inhabitants before the planet is extinguished by sending their elite army through the rift and invade their closest neighbor...Earth.  However, to ensure their success they send their army into Earth's past in hopes of avoiding any modern weapons and increase their chances of saving their planet.  However, Earth has learned of their evil plot and has developed a experimental time portal and has sent their own one man army to stop them. The player takes control of Dr. Vincent Gilgamesh who has acquired a massive arsenal including pistols, machine guns, rocket launchers and many more heavy weapons and must travel through various time periods including Medieval times, prehistoric times, Ancient Rome and Egypt and even the distant future.  The gameplay is similar to Contra where the player advances through the stages, shooting at various enemies and collecting power-ups and must also avoid various traps and pitfalls scattered throughout the levels.  There are also the standard bosses at the end of each stage.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6279068c-81d4-435a-a79b-03b534a6e9fd.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f4c95318-641a-44a5-9ee7-6c6621f9d065.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/41c7bdb5-4158-4566-833a-c5b1f3933f9c.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sales Curve</Publisher>
</game>