<Game>
	<Name>Timon & Pumbaa's Jungle Games (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Timon &amp; Pumbaa's Jungle Games includes Jungle Pinball (self explanitory), Burper (a shooter type game, using pumbaa to belch gas), Hippo Hop (a platformer), Bug drop (similar to tetris) and Slingshooter (a shooting with a slingshot game) accessible directly from the menu. The object in this game is to have fun while Timon and Pumbaa from The Lion King entertain the player with glimpses of jungle living, especially when certain mini-games require the player to consume insects. The PC version featured a full voiceover, complete with humorous introductions to games. The SNES version does not feature the voiceover, but has some sound effects from the PC version intact. The PC version also has a new game called Bug Drop, a Puyo Pop styled game.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Timon_%26_Pumbaa%27s_Jungle_GamesCheat: View creditsAt the title screen, press up + X + L + R to view the credits.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>THQ</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>2205</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/924942-disneys-timon-and-pumbaas-jungle-games</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/disneys-timon-pumbaas-jungle-games</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/disneys-timon-pumbaas-jungle-games/3030-6921/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ZRWll3T.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/YIrPvQG.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/6OcSLOm.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/gIT8J5O.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/xF2SsD6.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/fOtWRYp.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/3UHc7ZO.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/0VxqXpC.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/8ZmWKhr.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/cSLSHgd.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/3Pyu7MJ.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/U4ZaahF.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/CzYbwEw.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/tOFFA9D.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8IU9IAv.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Y5Af9qZ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Play different arcade games with The Lion King characters Timon and Pumbaa: Hippo Hop - Help Timon travel across the river while collecting the grubs for Pumbaa's grill.  Be sure to avoid the hyenas! Jungle Pinball - A zany pinball games with hyenas, elephants, gophers and more! (similar version released later as Disney's Hot Shots: Timon and Pumbaa's Jungle Pinball) Sling Shooter - Shoot berries at various targets popping up. (similar version released later as Disney's Hot Shots: Swampberry Sling) Bug Drop - A Tetris-like game.  Play against the computer or a friend. (not in the SNES version) Burper - Collect grubs while avoiding/destroying unwanted ones with Pumbaa's powerful burps. The main menu has many hidden animations that can be found when you click on various objects.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b3456a38-5fa8-4e96-9293-ea9b969e978d.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b7f02390-dcec-4bb8-80fd-f6f6fb473e91.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>