<Game>
	<Name>Tin Star (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Tin Star is a Western-style on-rails shooting game with robots exclusive to the Super Nintendo in the US. It was developed by UK studio Software Creations and published by Nintendo themselves.The main character of the game is a sheriff named  Tin Star sent to East Driftwood to clean up the town. Tagging a long is his trusty sidekick Mo Crash and his horse Aluminum. Tin Star goes to the town of East Driftwood to stop Black Bart, the leader of the Bad Oil Gang.Gameplay: And keep 'em up.Acts are replaced with days and in days there are levels called scenes. The game starts on Monday, and goes through until Sunday. At the start of every day is a shooting gallery  mini-game. The training consists of trying to keep one or more jugs in the air for as long as possible by shooting the jugs. Every time a jug gets shot, the more more money the player receives. The jugs also change color if they are in the air long enough. If the player waits, the game will change and the player will instead try to juggle the bottles while shooting a target to gain money. The game play is an  on-rails shooter that is either in first person view or in a 2D mode where the player can see Tin Star, but cannot control him. In this mode Tin Star moves independently, and aims his gun wherever the player is pointing the crosshairs. Tin Star not only has to take down enemy robots, but remove hazards like birds, dynamite and other objects. At the end of certain levels there are mini-bosses, which often appear more than once in the game. One of the boss showdowns.At the end of the day after several stages, there is a main boss fight which is a one-on-one showdown in the street. This fight consists of the player shooting a cylinder from a revolver from one of the four corners of the screen and then shooting the boss in the middle of the screen.Cheat: Changing Tin Stars colorAt the title screen, when you start a new game, press A, B, X, or Y to change Tin Star's color. Cheat: Secret BonusTo earn a chance at the Secret Bonus in a level, simply beat the level without shooting a single health canteen.  Sounds simple, but it was very difficult to figure it out!</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>zU3eB6QRMuU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>9251</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588794-tin-star</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/tin-star</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tin-star/3030-22002/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/IT5xz3P.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/zwrEPrp.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/VLVw2Xq.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/NXGe3es.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ieZVGKv.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/OCwVbda.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4H2gNq2.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ElQv7z6.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/BBULjN9.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/NAhItby.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/VeNrz4z.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/xnACOjY.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ObUVZZN.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>There's a new sheriff in town! YOU are Tin Star, the latest in a long string of lawmen to challenge the Bad Oil Gang. Your job is to run the gang out of town. The main tool of your trade? A blazing six gun, of course! Tin Star has made a promise to himself that he will boot the Bad Oil Gang out of town in one week's time. He must face the gang in a variety of action settings, including a train robbery, a barroom brawl, a cattle stampede and a jail break, just to name a few. At the end of the day, you may even have an old-fashioned quick-draw showdown. Are you up to the challenge of the Old West? The gunslinging action, cartoon graphics and humorous dialogue make Tin Star one of the most entertaining games to ever hit the trail. There are seven full "days", or stages, of action awaiting the new sheriff. Practice stages allow players to get the feel of the game quickly, and bonus rounds are awarded for outstanding performance. The Wild West was never this wild!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cfcf9e09-5868-4c30-8135-c1652692c628.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5a65a030-01e2-4c98-bcbc-ed7d13f936a4.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/af07919e-f05a-4753-bc48-be6d3a88dd9d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fc671bc8-d4a3-443d-b1f3-5efb673400a0.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>