<Game>
	<Name>Tintin - Prisoners of the Sun (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Tintin: Prisoners of the Sun is an Action game, developed and published by Infogrames,which was released in Europe in 1997.Cheat: Cheat ModeAt the first screen that appears after booting, enter the code. As you press each button, it must be held down until the entire code is entered. The words CHEAT MODE and the number will appear if entered correctly. For Cheat Mode 02, during gameplay press Select to open the debug menu. You can hold R to freeze action, too. An extra option, SNES, is also added to the options screen.Cheat: Level PasswordsI have the passwords set up as such:1|2|3------4|5|6------7|8|9</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1997</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Infogrames</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>GKSbWCQOyFU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3672</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/921828-tintin-prisoners-of-the-sun</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/V3MxliZ.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/2qAQQNI.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/LUPzMwN.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/kwnfTqh.png</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/gWv10r4.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/wA6VRWA.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wpHlFnZ.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/pG5R5fJ.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/pikPLW9.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/2CgEZ6W.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/tBbNSoJ.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/jN2bJqx.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/uSb2HF3.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/CUVj3QG.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/VBSSlR9.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vlciIUG.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Y7bj8e1.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The Adventures of Tintin: Prisoners of the Sun is based on the Belgian comic book of the same name. The basic plotline is the same: Professor Cuthbert Calculus gets kidnapped and the player, in the role of Tintin, needs to rescue him. The rest is more loosely adapted: in contrast to the comic, which is mostly based in Peru, this game offers many different locations all over the world. The gameplay itself is a typical platforming action: Tintin walks through the levels while avoiding the enemies. Pretty much everyone, e.g. little girls and security guards, is out to hurt Tintin who has no means of defending himself. This means the most important aspect is learning enemy placements, their patterns and how to avoid them. But he has to hurry because of the time limit. Required for success is the usage of the two playing plains: from the player's perspective in the foreground and further towards the background. Tintin can switch between the two at any time.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f37dae2f-4c64-4d76-9084-9bbe9a3c6445.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/abe84908-7d23-46a6-ae98-6b5e99acc84f.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Infogrames</Publisher>
</game>