<Game>
	<Name>Tiny Toon Adventures - Wacky Sports Challenge (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Tiny Toon Adventures: Wacky Sports Challenge is a multiplayer competitive sports game featuring the characters of Tiny Toon Adventures released for the Super Nintendo and Game Boy. In this game one to four players guide Buster Bunny, Babs Bunny, Plucky Duck and Dizzy Devil as they compete in different sporting challenges. These events range from comedic takes on track and field, weightlifting, soccer and various other athletic pursuits. The SNES version is one of the few titles to utilize an SNES multitap, allowing up to four players to join in on the games.The game is known as Tiny Toon Adventures: Dotabata Daiundoukai ("Tiny Toon Adventures: Great Slapstick Athletic Meet") in Japan, and as Tiny Toon Adventures: Wild &amp; Wacky Sports in Europe. It also features multiple cameos from the other Tiny Toon Adventures characters. 		</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Konami (America), Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.6666666666666665</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>0sGLie4Hwpo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6302</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588796-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-sports-challenge</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-sports-challenge_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-sports-challenge/3030-15537/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/8j6GumB.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/sNj1LLS.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JTdt5uM.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/1rn9i77.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/VMUUqBJ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ZAKUYJL.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/NJUibhM.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/qLj0OBx.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/cLhI4Gl.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/veNRnDV.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Iuerjoc.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/I3ToWta.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/1WjT52v.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CYMScPh.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/re8PVKQ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Humor! Wackiness! Sports! ls that what you're looking for? if so. this game's got it! Plus cool graphics. STARRING YOUR FAVORITE TINY TOON ADVENTURES CHARACTERS FROM THE ANIMATED TV SERIES!! You can play as Buster Bunny. Babs Bunny (no relation). Plucky Duck or Dizzy Devil! You'll also run into your other favorite cast characters. HIDDEN BONUSES!!! TWELVE DIFFERENT EVENTS!!! MULTIPLE SKILL LEVELS WITH DIFFERENT HAZARDS!!! Face it. if you want a laugh riot. sports action. and tons of replay value. then this is the game you're looking for! Just check out those screen shots. BUY THE GAME. PLAY THE GAME. BE THE GAME. Besides. where else are you going to find Bungee Jumping, Chicken Race. Ice Cream Toss, Weight Lifting and eight other games in one convenient package?</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dc89edb3-2cab-45ee-8187-f2054bdaf0ef.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/734f4402-342f-4d94-97d8-6ebabc9ee023.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b67292a4-dacc-49ac-bc92-18702b8f8e14.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b08d61d8-33f1-432d-8fc4-20e4207a6439.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f4969fb4-6b33-472c-b08f-9787ead20b5c.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>