<Game>
	<Name>TKO Super Championship Boxing (USA) (Sample)</Name>
	<plot>Louis. Marciano. Ali. Tyson. You. That's right, now you've got a chance to be considered one of the greatest fighters of all time with TKO SUPER CHAMPIONSHIP BOXING for the Super Nintendo. You'll have the chance to step into the ring against some of the toughest boxers you've ever seen as you try to work your way towards a shot at the championship. Your eight opponents each have their own unique fighting style, strengths, and weaknesses that you'll have to learn quickly if you want to have a chance to win the bout. You can go head-to-head against a friend, take on any of the eight computer-controlled boxers, or face them one by one on the road to the world championship. Thanks to TKO SUPER CHAMPIONSHIP BOXING, the "sweet science" has never looked sweeter!Tips:Championship Mode Passwords:Enter the following passwords when selecting Championship mode...YMMNVB Start game at Advanced Final Level with max. abilitiesVMYYBPN Start game at Advanced Level 2 with max. abilitiesTMYYBQN Start game at Advanced Level 3 with max. abilitiesVYMMNFB Start game at Advanced Level 4 with max. abilitiesMMYMNGB Start game at Advanced Level 5 with max. abilitiesTYMMNHB Start game at Advanced Level 6 with max. abilitiesSMYMBJN Start game at Expert Final Level with max. abilitiesNYMYNCB Start game at Expert Level 2 with max. abilitiesRMYMBDN Start game at Expert Level 3 with max. abilitiesQYMYNRB Start game at Expert Level 4 with max. abilitiesTYMYBGN Start game at Expert Level 5 with max. abilitiesVYMYBTN Start game at Expert Level 6 with max. abilitiesLast BoxerSFVJDVKhttp://cheats.ign.com/objects/012/012533.html</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Sofel</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>PScpZgV3MDk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6303</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588797-tko-super-championship-boxing</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/tko-super-championship-boxing-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tko-super-championship-boxing/3030-28262/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ZEKfkSI.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/vCR05a4.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/bPw6sej.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/w5u3gvX.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/URbcVf0.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Yjj0Wy6.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/gnO0Ox6.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/iIyR4tw.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/GVGhJir.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/kMaAlCn.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/olaoSk7.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/PKk36Sf.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/U9PdyOC.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/wZINHVZ.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/E0u1bm9.png</clearlogo1>
</game>