<Game>
	<Name>Top Gear 3000 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Top gear 3000 is a racing game for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. It was published by Kotobuki System Co Ltd and developed by Gremlin Interactive Ltd in the UK. The game was released in the spring 1995.Story:Set in the year 3000 and organized by a anonymous race or individual. The competition  starts far away from earth, on alien planets on the other side of the galaxy. Below is the text from the introduction of the game:&#8220;Once every millennium, one of the greatest events in the galaxy begins... It is a race. A car race. It starts at the furthest reaches of the galaxy and ends at the center. For the winner riches beyond belief. Knowledge of the race is passed from generation to generation. The identity of the organizer has been lost through the mists of the time. Or maybe it has never been known. But even the youngest child knows on a certain date... all he has to do is look to the skies... for a sign. The time has arrived. YOU are in the race. GOOD LUCK&#8221;Gameplay:In all, there are 48 different tracks, with varying  environments throughout the game. Cars can be upgraded before a race and the settings are more extensive than in previous versions of Top Gear. The player can set armor combination's on the vehicle to help protect it, as well as alter the paint job, change the gear configuration, set boost settings and modify and enhance the engine.  Weapons are also featured throughout the game, used best for defensive purposes.One of the prime features of the game is the use of the Super Nintendo multi-tap allowing up to four players to play the game simultaneously. The screen is split four ways and if there are fewer than four players, AI opponents will fill up the remaining places. The game features championship and VS modes. The championship mode has the option for 1 player full screen and 2 player split screen. The multiplayer game has 2, 3 and 4 player options. Reception: On its release it received mixed ratings.  The March 1995 issue of Game pro scoring it 4/5  and Nintendo Power giving the game 3.2/5Cheat: Cheat CodesGo to the passwords screen and enter:Cheat: System PasswordsEnter these passwords at the password entry screen to go to the corrosponding system.Cheat: System PasswordsEnter the following passwords at the PASSWORD screen. All passwords start the game with 6 Million+ Credits/ALL car upgrades set at Level 6(max.)/ALL optional upgrades.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Kotobuki System Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>mMVU1_RNmFE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2210</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588803-top-gear-3000</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/top-gear-3000</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/top-gear-3000/3030-3215/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/oSvZpgW.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/UXQB1Mz.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/eN9483Q.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/RFD0ZyX.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/bKzyuRl.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/MZ88BiB.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/6WdOqf7.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/6N8IheD.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/wed53gG.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/FMWCOxH.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Ie6OYYM.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Ok4tcqw.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Dg7GqHd.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/3s6Dv3Q.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/q7qUc5Z.png</clearlogo1>
</game>