<Game>
	<Name>Top Gear 2 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:In Top Gear 2, players race on tracks spanning the globe, earning money for upgrades along the way. Tracks feature backgrounds from each country like Australia, Great Britain and Japan. Some tracks feature weather effects like rain, snow or fog. Each event features 20 racers for the player to drive against. The game uses a password system, rather than saving progress.CareerThe game features a robust career mode featuring 16 territories with 4 tracks from each. After each race, players are given points that go towards that country's ladder ranking. The player must be at the top of the ladder at the end of the 4 races in order to qualify to move on to the next territory. The territories are (in order)Australasia (Australia and New Zealand)BritainCanadaEgyptFranceGermanyGreeceIndiaIrelandItalyJapanScandinaviaSpainSwitzerlandUnited StatesUpgrades:In addition to points for rankings, after races players are given money to put towards upgrading cars. Money can also be picked up by driving over icons that sometimes appear on tracks. Players can upgrade:Engine - Boosts top speedDry Tires - Helps the car turn betterWet Tires - Used on rainy tracksGearbox - Increases the number of gearsNitro - Each upgrade adds one more burst of nitro during racesSide/Rear/Front Armor - Decreases the amount of damage takenRespray - Changes the color of the car. Resprays are free upgradesCritical ReceptionWhen the SNES version was released Electronic Gaming Monthly gave the review scores of 7,7,7,6 and 6 out of ten. Mike Weigand, who gave the score of 6, wrote, "...if you liked Top Gear, then you will probably also like Top Gear 2! This time there are some improvements over the original -- most notably the scrolling is much smoother! Good weather conditions, too".Cheat: Cheat PasswordOn the Main Menu, choose "Continue Game" and you will see the password screen.There are some versions that you access the password screen by choosing "Continue" and then "Password". On these versions this cheat doesn't work, because there isn't "?" to type on the password.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>KEMCO U.S.A., INC.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>aHatg2MXAKE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2209</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588804-top-gear-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/top-gear-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/top-gear-2/3030-3718/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/gfPdJBl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/KhofTlk.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/fyzqUvn.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/TAL88mH.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/DbePO6n.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/GFcmtbF.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/3c5y4Ui.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/058txa5.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/DVTKr58.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/x7MRTyZ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/3kKYLVe.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/uJIEfiO.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/F5rkfnW.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Hj6ohvL.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vgwb5OL.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/cY953Bk.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>WE'LL MAKE THIS QUICK. YOU'RE HOLDING THE NEW, SUPER-ACCELERATED #1 WORLD LEADER IN RACE GAMES. ITS JAMMED WITH TWICE THE PROGRAMMING HORSEPOWER OF THE ORIGINAL TOP GEAR. SO YOU CAN SCREAM THROUGH 64 CITIES IN 16 COUNTRIES. TWISTING. TURNING. JUMPING. SPINNING. AND FLIPPING. AT SPEEDS OVER 200 MPH. SOLO, OR HEAD-TO-HEAD. DAY OR NIGHT. RAIN OR SHINE. FOG OR SNOW. PLUS, IF YOU WIN ENOUGH PRIZE MONEY, YOU CAN BUY INCREDIBLE ENGINE, TIRE, TRANSMISSION, NITRO SYSTEM AND ARMOR UPGRADES. AND YOU'VE GOT NEW ON-SCREEN POWER-UPS TO KEEP YOU REVVED TO THE REDLINE. SO GM-YOUR REAR IN GEAR. BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING HALF-FAST ABOUT IT.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/97f73d12-742a-4144-81fd-0c7537782b41.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0e199874-0ac5-467d-be2d-76c4c44c4618.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a92a2cfb-c270-49a0-b803-5f2054a0edb2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0c965820-2b49-463b-abcb-e4a16056a7d1.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/92245c01-3489-442a-aebd-72b4cefd0f37.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Kemco</Publisher>
</game>