<Game>
	<Name>True Golf Classics - Wicked 18 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:True Golf Classics: Wicked 18, also known as Devil's Course in Japan, is part of T&amp;E Soft's series of golf simulators. The earlier games in the series, True Golf Classics: Waialae Country Club and True Golf Classics: Pebble Beach Golf Links, both took place on actual golf courses but Wicked 18 presents an entirely fictional course with outlandish and even fantastical elements such as lava and floating islands.The game uses the series' now traditional 3D view for each course, presenting a rough idea of the topography of the area and the distance from the hole. Wicked 18 has a considerable amount of higher walls and cliffs than a normal mostly flat golf course, and the player can experiment banking shots off these steep inclines.As was the case with Waialae Country Club and Pebble Beach Golf Links, the game saw releases for the Sega Genesis, the Super Nintendo and the NEC PC-9801. Wicked 18 was also released for the 3DO.		</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>ZS-pXrEoHCU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6345</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588847-wicked-18</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/true-golf-classics-wicked-18</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/true-golf-classics-wicked-18/3030-41248/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Pzt6xXA.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/A0B5jMT.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/JmC7LNz.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/PQZ6NMq.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Jlf9Rfx.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Ft72ELy.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ch6o89e.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/dQ6oXfy.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YT0VD9G.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/7xLkN1U.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ZqhAoal.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/cKyu2l6.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6JnBUCW.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/HLwJhFo.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Wicked 18 is a golf game with a twist. The player takes control of a golfer on the most extreme 18 holes of golf with tall mountains, canyons and various objects and obstacles ready to stop the player at any time. There are four different game modes to choose from: Stroke, Match, Skin and Tournament with the ability to play against three other friends in a heated match. There is also a battery back-up that saves the players progress after each hole is completed.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2da820ab-5610-4606-ae0e-6487cb8e1f08.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0e6ec8ef-167a-41bd-9b20-e4393245a683.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/183caee7-512e-4b2f-820a-cee82d226900.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Bullet Proof Software</Publisher>
</game>