<Game>
	<Name>Turn and Burn - No-Fly Zone (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Turn and Burn: No-Fly Zone is a first-person combat flight sim for the Super Nintendo. Like many combat flight sims, the goal is to shoot down enemy aircraft by tracking them with the radar and then targeting them with their various weapons. The player's vehicle is an F-14 Tomcat fighter jet.The game was released in Japan as Super Dogfight, where it was published by Pack-In-Video. Absolute Entertainment published the game in the US, and Sony Imagesoft in Europe.The game is the sequel to Turn and Burn: The F-14 Dogfight Simulator, a 1992 Game Boy game.Gameplay:In Turn and Burn: No-Fly Zone players fly an F-14 Tomcat fighter jet under "the President's orders" to maintain a no-fly zone. They are equipped with 3 types of missiles, machine guns, and access to one aerial refuel every level. A typical mission consists of taking off from a carrier, shooting several airplanes or land installations, and returning to the carrier. The shooting gameplay is fairly typical for the era, with the player able to perform simple aerial maneuvers over a uniform blue ocean, and primarily locating enemies using a radar. Objects in the sky and ocean are rendered using sprites which change in size based on their distance from the player. There are only a few sizes of sprites for each object, but the game runs at a higher frame rate than many similar games of the time.The cockpit view is notable for being very detailed and providing the player with a wealth of information. It also includes some light graphical touches, such as a flight yoke that moves as though it was being controlled by the player. However, the cockpit takes up approximately two thirds of the screen, leaving little room for the player to actually see enemies. Pressing the triggers pulls up left and right over the shoulder views respectively, which also include a detailed portrait of the pilot and part of the plane.The difficulty of landing necessitated that the developers include a separate mode accessible from the main menu that allows players to practice it.		</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Absolute Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>Qchb6A07QsU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6314</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588813-turn-and-burn-no-fly-zone</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/turn-and-burn-no-fly-zone</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/turn-and-burn-no-fly-zone/3030-33040/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/oBiQVCk.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/lYU1k4m.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/UkLskvk.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/dzH9wJg.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/yU3uBCq.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/eUpm3n3.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/FA9q0ov.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/aQJRU6a.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/agTslQx.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/WDeuL75.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/VMtAlt2.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/6SjoZNx.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/TgFrcL2.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/qJA7Ucd.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/nq2XfLp.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In Turn and Burn: No-Fly Zone the player gets in the cockpit of the famed F-14 Tomcat and launches into a series of sorties on enemy fighters.  The game is a simulation with real instruments and gauges and authentic weapons such as Sidewinders, Phoenix missiles and the M61A1 Vulcan Cannon to shoot down enemy fighters scattered throughout the stages.  Players also land on their carrier in both daytime and night time missions. The game also features Mode 7 scaling.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1a984372-7813-4c7e-b621-158eca127ff5.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b2247f81-d56c-447d-b21a-fccf883dcdcb.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sony</Publisher>
</game>