<Game>
	<Name>Ultimate Fighter (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ultimate Fighter is a fighting game, developed by Culture Brain and published by Natsume Co. LTD. Released on the Super Nintendo in 1993. It's an updated re-release of Hiryu no Ken S: Golden Fighter, which received a US localization as well as various updates including an option to speed up the game.Gameplay:Ultimate Fighter is a fighting game which contains single player and multiplayer modes. The single player mode plays like a brawler with the occasional one-on-one fight against various strong opponents. While in Versus Mode the player has the choice of selecting the following characters:Ryuhi (Ryuhi is the only playable character in the single player mode)Min MinFalconFishJakeJoeLeoMusashiSanadaSawamuraWillyZebraWith the exception of the first two, each subsequent pair of characters are palette swaps. This allows two players to effectively play the same fighter.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	<Developer>Culture Brain</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.3</rating>
	<VideoURL>1hFCFhPbRtw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6318</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588819-ultimate-fighter</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ultimate-fighter</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ultimate-fighter/3030-22953/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/3gFiziN.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/hxjABEz.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/H4PTA2z.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/v9LQaSS.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ixF3JMd.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/E3t26Mj.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/JHWf4c8.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/SFLeIwZ.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/1TBapt6.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rRbQ9tl.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/yHcyKor.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/NvOanqc.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/OsYGwrg.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/tV5uR4t.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/2GuN3LX.png</clearlogo2>
	<Notes>Get ready for furious fighting action with ULTIMATE FIGHTER! The evil enemy made a raid on Rick's master's training school, took symbols and swords away, and left a letter of challenge behind. Rick, having vowed to be a true fighter, took up this challenge to win back the lost items. Sharpen your fighting skills and prepare for devastating, bonecrushing battles. Rick's fate is in your hands. The challenge addressed to him is also made to you. The success of his quest depends on your courage, cunning, and flawless martial arts technique.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eb8a8f62-9708-4eb8-89cc-4fed771610e1.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/08164ba7-87eb-4270-9352-7fd7cf773153.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/56679323-ce75-4b54-9c8a-05d42b39bfa2.png</clearlogo3>
	<clearlogo4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8fbcd52b-a92f-4122-88cf-f72d9e37f133.png</clearlogo4>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/80d6f069-ac4d-4078-9fee-075ed7eee543.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Culture Brain</Publisher>
</game>