<Game>
	<Name>Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The masked ninjas return.Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 is a 2D fighting game developed and released by Midway on November 1995 for arcades.It is a direct update to Mortal Kombat 3, adding new characters (all of which are the return of masked ninjas), arenas, special moves, and game modes (including an 8-player tournament mode and 2-on-2 team matches), while tweaking gameplay mechanics and character balancing. It is regarded as the most competitive game in the Mortal Kombat franchise (prior to its 2011 reboot). A special version of Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 was later released for consoles (known as Mortal Kombat Trilogy).In order to free up space on the game's memory, the screens detailing the game's story, as well as all of the biographies and picture endings for the original characters, have been removed. Regardless, the game's story is no different from Mortal Kombat 3 (involving Outworld emperor Shao Kahn's invasion of Earthrealm).Gameplay:Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 is built off of Mortal Kombat 3 and retains most of its gameplay mechanics. There are four attack buttons (High Punch, High Kick, Low Punch, and Low Kick) and dedicated Block and Run buttons. Players have a "Run Meter", which limits their ability to run forward, and "chain combos", in which players can perform pre-programmed combos (by linking normal attacks together) that ends with an attack that sends the opponent flying. The combos are known for not necessarily requiring the user to be 100% accurate on the timing of the button presses, allowing the player to basically press all the buttons in the combo quickly and the combo would essentially play itself out. Each character has new special moves, chain combos, and gameplay balances.BRUTALITY!Fatalities, Friendships, Babalities, Mercy, and Animalities return from Mortal Kombat 3. However, the Super Nintendo and Sega Genesis versions sacrificed Mercy and Animalities for a new type of finishing move: Brutalities. Brutalities are long, complex combo strings that, when performed successfully, end with the victim exploding into a shower of blood and body parts. Brutalities require the player to enter the first ten button presses in the combo, and the game takes over from there, depicting the character beating the other character faster and faster until they explode.The game also marks the return of the Endurance Match (originally in Mortal Kombat), in which the player must defeat two opponents consecutively instead of one to win a round. The "Choose Your Destiny" screen reflects this, adding one Endurance Matches to each "tower". Additionally, there is a "Master II" difficulty, adding another Endurance Match to the "tower" while making the game more difficult.More "Kombat Kodes", six-digit codes that are entered cooperatively on the versus screen, have been added, including the ability to change the stage to whatever both players feel like playing. There are now three "Ultimate Kombat Kodes", ten-digit codes that are entered during the Game Over screen, with three new characters to unlock. The Mortal Kombat Arcade Kollection removed Kombat Kodes from the online component in the game.Game ModesUltimate Mortal Kombat 3 also includes three gameplay modes, each requiring a different amount of credits to start:Mortal Kombat - Traditional game mode with one-on-one fights.4 Player 2-on-2 Kombat - A multiplayer tag-team fight in similar vein to Endurance Matches.8 Player Tournament - A single-elimination tournament for eight players.Shao Kahn's Lost TreasuresNew to Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 is the concept of Shao Kahn's Lost Treasures, in which completing the game gives the player a choice between a group of bonuses ranging from battling secret characters to watching a demonstration of each Fatality in the game. These groups are restricted by the difficulty the game was completed on. 8-Player Tournament mode also gives the player access to Shao Kahn's Lost Treasures at the end.Novice Difficulty and higherShows the character's endingPlay a clone of Galaga (only previously accessible through a Kombat Kode or reaching 100 battles)Battle with ErmacBattle with Noob SaibotWarrior Difficulty and higherRandom TreasureFatality Demonstration #1Fatality Demonstration #2Fatality Demonstration #3Endurance Match against Noob Saibot and ErmacMaster Difficulty and higherEndurance Match against masked Sub-Zero and Noob SaibotEndurance Match against Noob Saibot, Ermac, human Smoke, masked Sub-Zero, and MileenaMaster II DifficultySupreme Demonstration (shows most Fatalities, Babalities, Friendships, and Animalities)Characters:The 22 playable characters (including the three unlockable characters)The game includes 19 playable starting characters, two unplayable bosses, four playable secret characters, and one unplayable secret opponent. All of the playable characters (including the previously-hidden Smoke) from Mortal Kombat 3, along with Kitana, Reptile, Jade, and Scorpion from Mortal Kombat II, are the default starting characters in the game. Through new "Ultimate Kombat Kodes", Mileena, a masked Sub-Zero, and a new ninja character (Ermac) are unlockable as playable characters. A pre-indoctrinated version of Smoke, known as Human Smoke, is playable by holding a special button combination when choosing the robotic Smoke.Noob Saibot is still a hidden, unplayable opponent. However, because of the inclusion of masked male ninjas, he is no longer a palette swap of Kano (except in the Sega Saturn version). Featured in the game's opening gameplay montage is Rain, a dark purple palette swap of the male ninjas that serves as nothing more as a fake hidden character for stirring up rumors. Noob Saibot and Rain, as well as the three unlockable characters, are starting characters in the Super Nintendo, Sega Genesis, and Game Boy Advance versions.CharacterDescription (Additional Notes)ActorKitanaKitana is a warrior princess from the realm of Edenia. Although she appears youthful, she is actually well over 10,000 years old. She is key character in the forces of good in the Mortal Kombat universe. Kitana has one of the most damaging projectiles in the game,her Fan Toss. She also has a decent anti-air and her fan-lift which is used to combo after.Becky GableReptileReptile is one of the many ninjas in the Mortal Kombat franchise. As the series has gone on, he's become more outwardly reptilian. His Force Balls are a force to be reckoned with -- slow moving and easy to combo after. Reptile can also go invisible, and has a fast projectile acid spit.John TurkSonyaSonya Blade is a fighter who has appeared in nearly every Mortal Kombat game.Kerri HoskinsJaxMajor Jackson Briggs or "Jax" is a special forces operative from Mortal Kombat II who uses his fists of steel to take down enemies. His arms are the result of a cybernetical enhancement. He excels in close-range combat, with a variety of grabs, including his anti-air backbreaker. Jax also has a projectile and his Ground Pound, which will hit any ground-based enemy.John ParrishNightwolfNightwolf is an Apache shaman who joins Mortal Kombat to protect the world. Nightwolf is a great ranged character, with some good projectiles and a counter to projectiles also. He also has a fantastic combo-extender in his axe lift, which can hit a number of times.Sal DivitaJadeJade is an Edenian fighter who was first featured as a hidden character in Mortal Kombat II. Jade is known for her powerful multi-hit combos.Becky GableScorpionScorpion is one of the many Ninjas in the Mortal Kombat universe. As always, Scorpion has his spear, as well as a teleport-punch. He also has his scissors kick takedown and air throw.John TurkKanoA member of the black dragon clan and wanted man. Kano was one of the fighters in the original Mortal Kombat. His cannonballs are quick and Blanka-like.Richard DivizioMileenaMileena is a female fighter in the series famous for her rivalry with Kitana and what she hides under her mask. She has a Sai projectile that is quick and damaging. She also has a teleport kick and Rolling Thunder which hits hard and fast.(Secret character in all but the Super Nintendo and Sega Genesis versions)Becky GableErmacErmac is an entity composed of legions of dead souls, and was created by Shao Kahn. He has a variety of telekinetic slams and multiple combos with his axe-as a result, he is a threat in every range.(Secret character in all but the Super Nintendo and Sega Genesis versions)John TurkSub-Zero, masked versionSub-Zero is an iconic ninja in the Mortal Kombat universe. His moves include a freeze and his ice clone, which allows him to make a clone of himself. If and when the opponent touches it they will become frozen. He also has a slide, which allows him to traverse the battlefield quickly and surprise opponents with a low hitting attack.(He is featured twice. Once as a masked ninja, the other without a mask. The masked version is a secret character in all but the Super Nintendo and Sega Genesis versions)John TurkSektorSektor is a cyborg ninja whose mission is to terminate Sub-Zero. Known for being a very irritable character, Sektor can use hard-to-evade heat-seeking missiles as projectiles. He also has a fast teleport uppercut.Sal DivitaSindelSindel is an Edenian fighter who first appeared in Mortal Kombat 3. As well as being able to fly, she has some outstanding projectiles and her scream.Lia MontelongoKurtis StrykerKurtis Stryker is a riot control officer who was recruited by Raiden as one of the Defenders of the Realm in Mortal Kombat 3. Often regarded as one of the most irritating characters in the game because of his great keep-away and his gun, which is a fast mid-range projectile.Michael O'BrienCyraxCyrax is a yellow cyborg. He was listed as "Mustard" during Mortal Kombat 3's early development. He has multiple bomb projectiles and a projectile energy net that freezes the opponent in place.Sal DivitaKung LaoKung Lao is able to strike from a variety of positions. He is a very flexible character, because This is because he has a projectile and a teleport (from which he has multiple follow-ups), as well as a spin attack, which on contact, makes the opponent fly away dealing high damage. He also has some great aerial pressure via his dive kicksAnthony MarquezKabalKabal is the current leader of the Black Dragon Clan. Thought of as the best character in the game because of his lightning-fast dash attack and damaging combos, Kabal is a frightening character.Richard DivizioSheevaSheeva is a fierce Shokan warrior; a four-armed fighter. By pressing down and then up, she can jump on her opponents head. She also has a good projectile, but nothing else, and so is normally regarded as low-tier (so, not a threat).(Not available in the Super Nintendo and Sega Genesis versions)Stop-motion miniatureShang TsungShang Tsung is an evil sorcerer and one of the main antagonists from the game. Shang Tsung can transform into every non-boss character in the game, and also can shoot from one to three skulls from his hands and from the ground.John TurkLiu KangLiu Kang is regarded as the main character. He can throw fireballs and morph into a dragon. His attacks include a flying kick and bicycle kick, which both allow him to travel across the screen very quickly. His fireball projectiles allow him to change to a defensive character fairly quickly whilst charging up his bicycle kick.Eddie WongSmokeA former member of the Lin Kuei clan and a longtime friend of Sub-Zero. Smoke first appeared in Mortal Kombat II as a hidden character to fight against. One of his attacks is a teleport uppercut.(He is featured in both a robotic form and human form. His human form is unlockable.)Sal DivitaMotaroMotaro is a Centaur who was first introduced in Mortal Kombat 3. He is one of the monster creatures of Mortal Kombat, and is allies with Shao Kahn. Motaro's attacks include shooting lasers out of his tail, teleporting, galloping. he can reflect projectiles shot at him. His tail whip attack reaches across almost the full-screen, and his kick smashes the opponent back a long way.(He is featured as a boss character and is only playable in the Super Nintendo, Sega Genesis, and Game Boy Advance versions)Stop-motion miniatureShao KahnShao Kahn is the Ruler of Outworld. His attacks include a charge attack, and attacking with his sledgehammer. He taunts the player by pointing and laughing at them. He is the final boss character.(Only playable in the Super Nintendo, Sega Genesis, and Game Boy Advance versions)Brian GlynnNoob SaibotNoob Saibot is actually the original Sub-Zero from Mortal Kombat 1. He's seen as one of the most powerful characters in UMK3 because of his fantastic projectile, which makes the opponent's attacks do absolutely nothing, and his Noob-throw, which makes Noob throw Noob at his opponent, who, in turn, throws the opponent at Noob. He is a secret opponent.(only playable in the Super Nintendo, Sega Genesis, Game Boy Advance, and special Wave Net arcade versions)John TurkArenasThere are five new arenas in Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3: Scislac Busorez (an anagram for "Classic Subzero"), Scorpion's Lair, Jade's Desert, Kahn's Kave, and The Riverfront. The Bank and Hidden Portal from Mortal Kombat 3 are removed. Noob Saibot's Dorfen and The Church, despite not being in the arena rotation, are now playable via new Kombat Kodes, which allow the players to fight in any stage they choose. This brings the total number of stages to 16. The level rotation works a bit differently, as the first five stages loop once before moving on to the Mortal Kombat 3 stages. The Balcony is always the stage played when facing Motaro. The Pit 3 is always the stage featured when fighting against Shao Kahn. Noob Saibot's Dorfen is always the stage featured when facing Noob Saibot. Scislac Busorez is always the stage featured when fighting Mileena, Ermac. or masked Sub-Zero.Scorpion's Lair includes both a Stage Fatality (in which the player uppercuts the opponent to the lava behind them), and a mid-match stage transition to Kahn's Kave. The Subway and The Soul Chamber still transition to The Street and The Balcony. The Subway, The Bell Tower, and The Pit 3 all still have their Stage Fatalities.Scislac BusorezScislac BusorezScorpion's LairJade's DesertKahn's KaveThe RiverfrontThe SubwayThe StreetThe RooftopThe BalconyThe BridgeThe Soul ChamberThe Bell TowerThe GraveyardThe Pit 3Versions &amp; PortsThe game was released for the Super Nintendo, Sega Genesis, and Sega Saturn in 1996. It never appeared on the Sony PlayStation due to Sega buying exclusive rights to release it on 32-bit CD-based consoles (as a response to Sony buying exclusive rights to release Mortal Kombat 3 on 32-bit CD-based consoles a year before). To get around this, a rare, special add-on peripheral for the PlayStation was made that upgraded copies of Mortal Kombat 3 to Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3. The game was later infamously ported to the Game Boy Advance on December 12, 2001 under the name "Mortal Kombat Advance". It is considered one of the worst fighting games of all time. An arcade-perfect port of Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 was later released on November 11, 2007 for the Nintendo DS under the name "Ultimate Mortal Kombat", which also included online multiplayer via Wi-Fi and a port of Puzzle Kombat from Mortal Kombat: Deception. Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 was also bundled in special "Premium Edition" copies of the PlayStation 2 version of Mortal Kombat: Armageddon. The game was also loosely ported to the iPhone and iPad by EA Mobile on December 16, 2010. (Restricting the character count to 6 starter characters and 2 hidden characters, while remaking all assets in 3D)An online-enabled version of Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 was released on the Xbox 360 via Xbox Live Arcade for 800 Microsoft Points ($10) on October 20, 2006, days before its intended Wednesday release. This version included 12 achievements worth 200 Gamerscore, ranging from performing certain finishing moves (online or offline) to completing the single-player campaign. The Achievements are notorious for having strange point values, such as 12. This version also includes online leaderboards, adjustable screen sizes (with support for widescreen and standard televisions), and an online mode similar to the "Quarter Match" mode on the Xbox Live Arcade version of Super Street Fighter II: Hyper Fighting. This version was granted "Arcade Hits" status due to high sales, reducing its price by half. However, in February 2010, Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 was removed from the Xbox Live Marketplace due to Midway losing the game's publishing rights. The standalone version of Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 never returned to Xbox 360 under new publisher, Warner Bros. Interactive Entertainment. Instead, a new release titled Mortal Kombat: Arcade Kollection was released on August 31, 2011 for Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 and later on February 1, 2012 for Games for Windows Live. This new release featured another online-enabled version of Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3, as well as online-enabled versions of Mortal Kombat II and the original Mortal Kombat.iOS VersioniOS IconA version of Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 was released for iOS in December, 2010 by EA. Rather than using digitized sprites of filmed actors, all the characters are rendered in 3D. Although the moves and buttons from the original game are included, a simpler set of buttons and moves were created to make play easier using the touch screen. The new layout has a "special" button, which is usually mapped to a character's signature special move. As an example, instead of back-back-low punch for Scorpion's spear, the player just has to hit the "special" button. Also instead of high and low punch and high and low kick, there are just punch and kick buttons. Fatalities are also included, along with babalities, friendships, brutalities, and animalities. While the arenas are the same as in previous versions of the game, they are also newly designed for the iOS version. Uppercutting opponents into other stages is still possible, as well as stage specific fatalities.Playable characters include:Sub-ZeroScorpionKitanaNightwolfJaxSheevaSonya BladeLiu KangStrykerErmac - an unlockable characterJade - an unlockable characterFour modes are available:Arcade: Standard one player arcade mode. Four difficulty levels are available. Each difficulty includes at least one "endurance" level where the player fights two kombatants.Local multiplayer: Play against a friend with an iOS device nearby.Survival: Endless consecutive one-round matches which the player has to win on just one health bar.Shao Karnage: Skip ahead and fight Shao Kahn with no life bars, scoring as many points as possible before time runs out.Extras:Leaderboards: Available for both Survival and Shao Karnage modes.Stats: The player's personal stats, including win streaks, number of fatalities executed, flawless rounds, and more.Bios: The bios of each kombatant from the original game.Lost Treasure: A list of the unlockables the player discovers while playing.Achievements:Master Killer: Complete Grand Master difficulty without losing a round.Tower Power: Complete all difficulty levels.Just Like Perfection: Get 1 flawless victory against CPU.Absolutely Flawless: Get 5 flawless victories in a row against CPU.Redekorating: Uppercut opponent through roof.Merci, merci, mercy me: Beat opponent after a mercy is performed on the player.Auto Kombat: Perform a 5 hit combo.Lin Kuei-Te God: Win 10 multiplayer matches.Soul Destroyer: Win 100 multiplayer matches.Who's Your Daddy???: Perform a babality.A pet is for life...: Perform an animality.I'll be there for you: Perform a friendship.Fatal Attraktion: Perform a fatality.Winning Stryk: Get a 5 match win streak using Stryker against CPU.Motaro, Mo' Problems: Defeat Motaro.You Suck!: Lose to Shao Kahn three times in a row.No, You Suck!: Defeat Shao Kahn.Outworld God: Get a 100% unlock rating.Kopy Kat: Xerox Sub Zero 100 times.Outwit, outplay, outlast: Score 20 or higher in survival mode.Cheat: Versus Screen CodesPlayers one and two must enter these button combinations on the vs. screen with the Y, B, and A buttons respectively. The number indicates the times you must press each button.Cheat: Crispy!After performing a Stage Fatality on 'Scorpion's Lair' you have two choices. You can press and hold both HP buttons to hear Dan Forden say 'Crispy!', or you can press and hold both Run buttons to hear Shao Kahn say 'Crispy!'.Cheat: Crispy!When playing as either Sub-Zero (Classic or Unmasked), freeze your opponent while their health is in Danger and Dan Forden will pop out to say 'Frosty!'.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Williams Entertainment Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>M - Mature</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>eu9QAUrsfaY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3285</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588820-ultimate-mortal-kombat-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ultimate-mortal-kombat-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ultimate-mortal-kombat-3/3030-2178/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/5bnTF2X.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/smukUwB.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/pcxHheY.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/zc5Vuei.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/X2OZDB8.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/e7UvtoF.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/VvZzXtA.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/2ubwAnz.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/nrdZgWF.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/NovNluj.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/d5yrnfw.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/NVql3Tg.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/AiSqJNZ.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/hi9Nv9v.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/kNnP6my.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/JChAruk.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/eUT0AnV.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WNqe8EU.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/iAmuUnm.png</clearlogo1>
</game>