<Game>
	<Name>Ultra Baseball Jitsumei Ban 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ultra Baseball Jitsumeiban 2 ("Real Name Ultra Baseball Version 2") is a baseball game from Culture Brain that was released exclusively on the Super Famicom in 1994. It is the sequel to the original Ultra Baseball Jitsumeiban, which in turn followed Super Baseball Simulator 1.000.While from all appearances a standard Japanese baseball game - the view is behind the batter, the characters are depicted in a super deformed "chibi" style - but there exists "Ultra" teams that have superpowers that they can activate at any time. These powers allow players to hit harder, pitch faster and other useful bonuses.The game was followed by Ultra Baseball Jitsumeiban 3 in 1995.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Culture Brain</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>31471</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571205-ultra-baseball-jitsumeiban-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ultra-baseball-jitsumeiban-2/3030-50762/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/XsD6AXK.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/kxvgcN5.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/PdyOEAk.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/JMQ2UkB.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/5XteziK.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/n7Q6Dy8.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CEIUO1l.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/6uYT1By.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/6hILBeJ.jpg</snapshot8>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Nu4xaEp.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Ultra Baseball Jitsumei Ban 2 is the fifth game in the Ultra Baseball (Baseball Simulator in the USA) series. It was released in 1994 for the Super Nintendo by Culture Brain in Japan only. These Baseball titles included some form of "Super League" where pitchers and batters would have special abilities. Baseball Simulator 1.000 (1989, NES), also known as Choujin Ultra Baseball Super Baseball Simulator 1.000 (1991, Super NES), also known as Super Ultra Baseball Ultra Baseball Jitsumei Ban (1992, SNES) NPB licensed. Super Ultra Baseball 2 (1994, SNES) Ultra Baseball Jitsumei Ban 2 (1994, SNES) NPB licensed. Ultra Baseball Jitsumei Ban 3 (1995, SNES) NPB licensed.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/da33bc38-7b48-4eea-abed-03751c557e1a.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8061aff8-6ba1-48ad-8c19-529432e745d8.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Culture Brain</Publisher>
</game>