<Game>
	<Name>Ultra Seven (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ultra Seven is a 2D one-on-one fighting game that uses characters from the tokusatsu TV show of the same name. The Ultra Seven series is based on the original Ultraman TV show, but updated for a modern audience with a different protagonist who hails from the same planet as Ultraman.Ultra Seven features a single-player story mode in which the player can sometimes choose which of Ultra Seven's capsule monsters (Agira, Micras or Windom) to fight as, and a versus mode in which two players can duke it out.CharactersUltra Seven - The hero of the game.Imitation Seven - An alien robot posing as Ultra Seven.Agira - A bipedal triceratops. An ally of Earth and one of Ultra Seven's three Capsule Monsters. Micras - An enormous horned beast with a goofy expression. Looks a bit like the colossi from Shadow of the Colossus. An ally of Earth and one of Ultra Seven's three Capsule Monsters. Is sometimes referred to as Miclas. Windom - A robotic creature with a beak. An ally of Earth and one of Ultra Seven's three Capsule Monsters.Eleking - A bipedal newt-like creature with electrical powers. King Joe - A robot that could change its shape and separate.  Gander - A moth-like creature that prefers arctic conditions.Gyeron - An avian monster.Dally - A microscopic parasite that Ultra Seven once defeated by being shrunk down. Alien Metron - A member of the alien Metron race, who resemble shellfish. Alien Icarus - A member of the alien Icarus race, which had bat-like ears and advanced technology.Alien Borg - A member of the alien Borg race, robots with mind control powers.Alien Guts - A member of the alien Guts race, bird-like beings with powerful psychic abilities.</plot>
	<releasedate>26/3/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Bec</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570925-ultra-seven</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ultra-seven</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ultra-seven/3030-37438/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/i72hfwS.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/HA2A0m0.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Tcnc50O.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/5r96BM8.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wacpjLN.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/vtwEvuA.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/PfRnf9a.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/mrPtIvE.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/6Qfbkc2.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/jspzFvk.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/erW2pN9.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/s60KbWs.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1oPVmQ7.gif</banner1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/74208d30-f98e-4e18-bc7b-9039197d777f.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8297433e-0ade-4eae-81d4-0ef2d435557b.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9a0ace1-5517-424c-b24e-66cba0ac38dd.png</snapshot11>
</game>