<Game>
	<Name>Umihara Kawase (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Umihara Kawase is a 1994 platformer for the Super Famicom that heavily uses physics in its gameplay. The player, as the eponymous heroine Umihara Kawase (her name is actually an abbreviated Japanese proverb concerning the preparation of salt- and freshwater fish, both of which feature heavily in the game as enemies), must navigate through levels with optional goals and alternate exits using only her fishing line. The fishing line can support her weight, and can be attached to sides of platforms and used to swing across gaps or rappel up and down to reach new areas. Umihara can grab onto ledges and pull herself up once she's close enough to the lip, and later levels require trickier maneuvers, using the elasticity of the fishing line to propel Umihara through the air like Spider-Man.The game's ending is contingent on the amount of total time taken to beat the fiftieth stage. Players can skip ahead by finding harder-to-reach alternate "warp" exits to shave off time, and beating the game within a strict time limit leads to a better ending.Umihara Kawase saw multiple sequels. A 1997 game for the PlayStation, Umihara Kawase Shun ("Shun" means "in season", continuing the fish/cookery theme), is essentially a graphically enhanced remake. The original Umihara Kawase eventually received a fan translation, though was never officially released outside of Japan.Cheat: Hard ModeOn the title screen, press the Select button exactly 100 times. A 5 minute time limit appear in green text next to the start option. If you press Select again, the green text will disappear.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>TNN</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>un9RtvVoD_k</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6319</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/566680-umihara-kawase</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/umihara-kawase</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/umihara-kawase/3030-10095/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/kDA2Y7T.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/LTwAn4k.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/wfg7nQM.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/EzIH3ER.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/SVVeKSQ.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/rngrYH9.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/j8TuxC9.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Waqqnp7.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/P8y6tuY.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/7M4mtgp.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/YtsTD8h.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/iYxi0Jp.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/2wKaJtp.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/mGtBPAp.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/zXe66QQ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Umihara Kawase is an unusual platformer featuring a girl that is captured in a bizarre dream world full of walking fish. Equipped with a fishing line she can swing and abseil from platform to platform using it as a grappling hook. The game's specialty is the detailed physics system that allows Kawase to perform various tricks using the elastic and length variable rope to move around the levels. There are almost 50 fields (levels) but most have multiple exits that allow you to play through the game on different paths without playing every single field in order. You can also record a good game and save it to watch it again at a later time.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/91e384a2-8e42-45cb-8e2f-685da4ce28e3.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f4bc4a99-74ed-414a-b4d8-8db5152ab0e0.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>NHK SC</Publisher>
</game>