<Game>
	<Name>Uniracers (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Uniracers, or Unirally in PAL territories, is a unicycle racing game for the Super Nintendo. Taking place in the "Uni-verse", players control a sentient unicycle, created by the 'Unigod' for the sole purpose of racing other sentient unicycles.Uniracers is a game where tricks are not only a device for showing off, but are also vital for beating some of the computer-controlled unicycles.There are three different types of tracks.Race: Simple point-A-to-point-B race. First one to reach the finish line wins. There are two of these in each tour.Circuit: Like a race, but there are a number of laps to complete before the unicycle finishes.Stunt: A unique mode, there are no CPU unicycles in Stunt tracks. Instead, the player must reach a predetermined point goal within 45 seconds to pass the course successfully.The track layout in every Tour goes Race, Circuit, Stunt, Race, Circuit.Playable UnicyclesThere are 18 unicycles that can be chosen.Mike: Red UnicycleMartin: Dark Green UnicycleAmy: Orange UnicycleMichelle: Yellow-Green UnicycleDave: Grey UnicycleCarol: Pink UnicycleKen: Purple UnicycleAlice: Green UnicycleAndrew: Blue UnicycleMelissa: Yellow UnicycleMalcolm: Teal UnicycleColin: Light Blue UnicycleTony: Black UnicycleCraig: Light Green UnicycleRobbie: Maroon UnicycleSteve: Light Blue UnicycleTour LayoutThere are nine different Tours, including 4 initially marked off Tours, and one hidden Tour. Each Tour is represented by an animal.Crawler (The Snail): Dragster, Zoom Zoo, Bowl, Switcher, Monster.Shuffler (The Turtle): Looper, MegaJump, Jumps, Flat Fun, Infinity.Walker (The Porcupine): Dragrace, Ping Pong, Hill Climb, Hybrid, Short Cut.Hopper (The Frog): Wario Paint, Crock, Downer, East, Hairpin Hill.Jumper (The Rabbit): Wobble, Twinpeak, Skier, Loopback, Small Cut.Bounder (The Kangaroo): Last One, Marathon, Circle, Plinkey, Jumpover.Runner (The Ostrich): Down Up, Highroad, Spine, Boo!, Fire Escape.Sprinter (The Cheetah): Vertical, Flash, Little Dipper, Fruitbat, 123 Jump.Hunter (The Dinosaur): Griller, Two Loops, Neon, Hamster, To and Fro.Hunter Tour TricksThe CPU unicycle for the final Tour, or "Anti-Uni", will throw some nasty tricks at the player to try to prevent the player from beating the game. Note that these effects cannot be activated in two-player action.Barf Mode: The background scrolls crazily, making it disorienting for the player.Invisible Track: Makes the track invisible.Mirror Track: Flips the screen upside down, making it a little tricky to navigate.Reverse Controls: Left moves the player's unicycle to the right, and vice versa.Slow Motion: The game slows down, making it a little easier.Super Bounce Mode: Makes the unicycle bounce very high when it lands.Hedgehog Mode: Makes the game even slower than Slow Motion.MiscellanyThere are a number of interesting things about Uniracers.A group of up to eight players can compete for Unicycle glory in League Mode.The game disallows using swear words, giving the message "Not Cool Enough". This message is also given for entering the name "SEGA" or "SONIC".There is a league mode, where 8 players can join a league and face off, two at a time, for bragging rights.The game saves the top three best times for each course, the unicycle that set the time, and each of the 16 unicycles' best times for each course.If the game is beaten, the player is rewarded with two tabloid-esque newspapers, and a "Whodunnit" screen, with caricatures of the creators' faces on unicycles.Cheat: Also UncoolSATAN is also deemed "uncool" a choice of name (you're told "Not cool enough" when you attempt to choose the name).Cheat: Also UncoolWhen you change a bike name, if you put SEGA or SONIC as a name, it'll be written ''Not cool enough''.Cheat: Easy gameIf you want an easy gold medal, select a course you got a silver medal on and select ''GOLD'' with the arrow. Press START and it will change between BRONZE, SILVER, and GOLD, select BRONZE and race against the easiest opponent for a gold medal! Works with silver too, but in silver, you can only select Bronze or Silver.Cheat: Easy gameNormally, you need a minimum of 2 to make a league, but you can have a league with just one person! If you want to try that, you need to get yourself and one other player into the league. (2 players) After making the league, delete the 2nd player you entered in and check the league again, it should be only you in the league. </plot>
	<releasedate>1/6/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ofJpuIdl31Y</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2212</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588824-uniracers</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/uniracers</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/uniracers/3030-16228/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/f0UqCds.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nhUioY4.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/6rpZ7Wy.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/pdBSG6f.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/jX3mV0L.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/CAUUsmg.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/UgzTPGN.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/IIF2zVi.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/clYqlvi.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/263rV7d.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/G4NunXt.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/4477vCk.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/VIG9VoK.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/XqcCXcz.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Uxzb8Zu.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/uGvALLJ.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/PWlUFew.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/vnaeAIW.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Single-wheeled and single-minded. Uniracers are the best at what they do: accelerate to screen-blurring speed! They're also awesome at pulling flips, twists, turns and catching monster air off the many mondo ramps, hills and half pipes of their race track worlds. The more outrageous the stunt, the faster the Uniracer goes! The sky's the limit! Racing is the entire purpose of a Uniracer's existence. You can race against the clock, against friends head-to-head or in a custom tournament. Challenge the mysterious ghost bike to become the uni-versal champion! It's one of the fastest races on the Super NES yet!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>NWmyjQF1fRs</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9b180c27-eb35-41a4-82bc-b601795f2cb5.png</banner2>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9971b8e-182c-4886-bb49-3dc9b9306bf6.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/749a3ee3-1275-4cfd-950c-da168a734ecf.png</boxart7>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/26810c71-fd7d-4cf4-a68f-f0cedc01f1d0.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b6c6c6e4-5ee8-46c0-9841-7467b03cc780.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9a3be53-54d1-4b86-b7bd-00a61f659da4.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8f858cce-b561-4a20-9680-86b69fbc367e.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5359b0d0-a6c8-4117-8acc-b89dc84e86b6.png</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>