<Game>
	<Name>Ushio to Tora (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ushio to Tora ("Ushio and Tora") is a game based on the manga of the same name. It features Ushio Aotsuki, a young man who discovers the powerful Beast Spear that his ancestor used to trap a vicious youkai monster called Tora (Japanese for "tiger"). Recovering the spear causes not only Tora to be free, but draws many other evil youkai out from hiding. Tora works begrudgingly with Ushio to fight back the wave of youkai out of fear of the spear's power (though as the manga progresses, Tora's reasons for helping become more altruistic).The game is a side-scrolling brawler with short stages that culminate in boss fights with other youkai, similar to the Super Famicom GeGeGe no Kitarou game. The player can choose between Ushio and Tora to control, and each controls slightly differently: Ushio has greater range with the spear and can create shockwaves, while Tora is a powerhouse up close with his claws and can summon bolts of lightning.The game was accompanied by a NES RPG named Ushio to Tora: Shin'en no Daiyu, also published by Yutaka in the same year.Cheat: Stage SelectIn Option Mode, using controller 2, hold down the following buttons: d-pad down, L, A, and press Select.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/1/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Yutaka</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>eP8bH4vByQI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14808</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581930-ushio-to-tora</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ushio-to-tora/3030-46028/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/1GslsTY.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/kYGpTgi.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/MkrFl4d.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/f3Zv4kW.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/U4QW0y3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/JCMOMpC.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/QXnTEDU.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/lNfCanD.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/4oHHKA4.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/elsaP7i.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/nh00kLP.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/EcovDoK.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Ushio to Tora ("Ushio and Tora") is a game based on the manga of the same name. It features Ushio Aotsuki, a young man who discovers the powerful Beast Spear that his ancestor used to trap a vicious youkai monster called Tora (Japanese for "tiger"). Recovering the spear causes not only Tora to be free, but draws many other evil youkai out from hiding. Tora works begrudgingly with Ushio to fight back the wave of youkai out of fear of the spear's power (though as the manga progresses, Tora's reasons for helping become more altruistic). The game is a side-scrolling brawler with short stages that culminate in boss fights with other youkai, similar to the Super Famicom GeGeGe no Kitarou game. The player can choose between Ushio and Tora to control, and each controls slightly differently: Ushio has greater range with the spear and can create shockwaves, while Tora is a powerhouse up close with his claws and can summon bolts of lightning.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/03128542-ad6d-4806-8224-3e99cd303325.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1032a653-f330-4e97-bed0-92cd8a224ae1.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>