<Game>
	<Name>Utopia - The Creation of a Nation (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Utopia: The Creation of a Nation (often referred to as simply Utopia) is a real-time strategy game set in the far future across various distant planets. The goal of the game is to create a colony, build it up by collecting resources and creating new structures, raising armies to take down enemy forces (unique to each planet and each scenario) and reaching a sufficiently high quality of life to achieve "Utopia" status. At which point, the player has cleared the scenario and can move onto the next.The game is highly reminiscent of both Maxis's SimCity and Bullfrog's Populous. It borrows many of the former's elements in its construction elements, such as having a series of advisers to tell the player where they should focus, and borrows the latter's isometric viewpoint and GUI.The game was originally released on the Atari ST, Amiga and DOS in 1991. It later received a Super Nintendo port, which was published in the US by Jaleco, by Epic/Sony Records in Japan and by Konami in Europe. This port is one of a handful of Super Nintendo games to use the SNES Mouse. The computer versions received an expansion data disk named Utopia: The New Worlds, sold separately.						</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco USA, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6325</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588827-utopia-the-creation-of-a-nation</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/utopia-the-creation-of-a-nation</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/utopia-the-creation-of-a-nation/3030-19663/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/TOGmwfe.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/0y0LDOH.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/CGMiBxe.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/8PXKZUw.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/fNJ08C1.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/coKordR.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/hUdgvjU.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/cCjlrnl.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/a62Ps3q.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MYb3hi4.jpg</snapshot8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/AMj0a5D.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/CFB3F4u.png</clearlogo1>
</game>