<Game>
	<Name>Venom - Spider-Man - Separation Anxiety (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Parting is such sweet sorrow! Venom has been violently split from his living costume, spawning five deadly alien Symbiotes. In fierce two-player action, Venom joins forces with his arch-enemy, Spider-Man, to face the new strain of evil brought to life by chilling, computer-rendered graphics. Between the merciless Jury and awesome allies like Ghost Rider and Daredevil, Venom's out to part his Symbiote offspring from their newfound life!Cheat: Level PasswordsEnter these on the password screen:Cheat: Unlimited LivesTo get unlimited lives it's kind of tricky it usualy work better with 2 players but it still possible with 1 player. First get to a boss and make sure you have an extra hero to help you (Captain America, Dare Devil, Ghost Rider ect.) Get the boss to low health and get yourself to 1 life and low health. As soon as he kills you press "L" to get a heor's help he will kill the boos. In the next level you will have zero lives and you can die as many times as you want. BUT  MAKE SURE IF YOU HAVE ZERO LIVES DO NOT PICK UP LIVES IT WILL SET IT TO 1 LIFE AND YOU HAVE TO RE DO IT. If you have zero you can die and it will go to 9. I honestly dont no how many lives you truly have but it is alot probably like 100 but that should be more then enough.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>38BjrJbVmCU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>7624</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588684-spider-man-and-venom-separation-anxiety</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/venom-spider-man-separation-anxiety</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spider-man-venom-separation-anxiety/3030-4181/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/kvQ5OqL.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/W8V1Pdg.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/eO40toR.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/FxHiZgo.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/c1Qjwgd.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/TIJdiaZ.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/NppC6yu.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/HMtscDe.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vaedg3P.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/9fpC1tX.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/UmlZxkK.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Ro2QBMt.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/79Lc6Db.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>http://i.imgur.com/tfH0OQs.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>http://i.imgur.com/HAebssb.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/bAZzAWx.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/fp8tvTT.png</clearlogo1>
</game>