<Game>
	<Name>Virtual Wars (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>As a movie. The Lawnmower Man exploded the boundaries of graphics technology. As a game, it will blow your mind with a dazzling blend of breath-taking 3D and blockbustin action.It all begins in the shadow research agency known as 'The Ship.' Here, the brilliant but maverick scientist Dr. Angelo uses Jobe, a simple Lawnmower Man, as a guinea pig in his Virtual Reality experiment...and creates a monster, transforming him into the superhuman CyberJobe who vows to dominate mankind. Now the race is on to destroy The Shop before CyberJobe can break out of their computer system and reach the global computer network, from which he will be able to control and manipulate the world's computer.In the real world you will battle against CyberJobe's minions, from The Shop security agents to giant wasps, killer primates and unnaturally controlled vehicles. In the Virtual Worlds you will encounter whole new, unique and hostile terrains, fantastic new worlds where the only limit is the imagination. It's here that you will be fighting the CyberJobe and swooping and diving around some unnaturally hostile tunnels and passages, where the speed of light is as dangerous as any enemy dreamed up by CyberJobe. It's here where you will finally encounter CyberJobe, and then the most terrifying manifestation of Virtual Reality possible, and it's here where the battle between good and evil will finally be decided.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>The Sales Curve</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>KgZIfpCvHa8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3210</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588433-the-lawnmower-man</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-lawnmower-man/3030-14840/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Aq812lE.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/q0xaMBQ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/ONa1QrG.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/OSlnS9q.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/S3Bvq5C.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ZqN3enh.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/3t8sFJd.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VAAYUQO.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/mVzpqEC.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/T6yiDYl.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/sfHGguq.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ZfvX1dE.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/F3urAvs.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/uPnceMS.png</clearlogo1>
</game>