<Game>
	<Name>War 2410 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>In the year 2003 geneticists tried to create the perfect soldier. Something went wrong however, and three new life forms turned against their creators: Brutally savage Orcs, cybernetic androids called Cromes and genetically enhanced human soldiers code named M.A.R.S. Players take control of a secretly assembled force and must try to restore order.War 2410 is a turn-based strategy game in which players move various units, such as mechs, tanks, troops or planes over a grid-map. Units differ in movement and attacking range. Some ground units cannot attack air units and vice versa. Terrain also affects combat as some types of terrain, like trees or buildings improve a units defense. Attacked units always counterattack as long as the attacker is within range. The goal of most missions is to destroy all enemy units, while it is sometimes necessary to capture the enemies' bases. Units cannot not be improved or modified and every mission starts with all units already in place.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Advanced Productions, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>jWNk6MKNy3M</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6331</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588831-war-2410</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/war-2410</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Oqm5RHn.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/t1b4wY2.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/Xj9CxKO.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/oGeqNS2.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Q1bnIzm.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/jGRPcuC.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/4Rwycsh.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/VTVtkBU.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/5FQEJW3.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Nwwz5ia.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/9if4iiW.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/NWlXU5C.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/lknAY7Q.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You Are the Last Line of Defense! In the year 2003, geneticists deciphered the code that unlocked the secrets of life. With the new technology, man decided to create the perfect soldier. Something went wrong... Three new life forms, intended to protect and serve, turned on their creators. Brutally savage ORCS, cybernetic androids called CROMES, and genetically-enhanced human soldiers, code named MARS are now battling for world domination. Powerful forces dedicated to restoring order have been secretly assembled. This army is now waiting for you to lead it to victory. The fate of humanity is in your hands!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/081faf45-0d7d-4163-adb8-bceb22f7972a.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/78acb9a3-715e-48fd-a85d-f6c23c05a2be.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f4991947-6b2b-4179-ae5d-3aebcd0f61c0.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5b60a326-0504-4537-90c9-8cab4a96020d.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Advanced Productions</Publisher>
</game>