<Game>
	<Name>Waterworld (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Waterworld is an adventure game that was originally released on the SNES in 1995. It was developped by Ocean and went on to be released on multiple platforms such as the Virtual Boy.  Although it is considered as a licensed game, it's only loosely based on the movie.  Story: The game opens up with text telling you about the universe you're about to explore. This is actually one of the only indications that the game has anything to do with the movie:   The Sun, for millions of years the source of life, but for one planet the source of it's demise. The temperatures climbed, the vast fields of ice at its poles melted and the oceans rose. Centuries later, few people remained on this planet once called earth. The only remaining pockets of civilisation are floating islands of debris called Atolls. You play as the Mariner and fend off Smokers but that's about all the game has in common with the movie. Note: "it's" in the first line is a spelling mistake that the developers made.   Gameplay: The game alternates between 3 different gameplay phases: some levels have you piloting a boat, others have you doing some platforming and then there are the bonus stages:  -Boat levels: You control a sail boat and must fend off Smokers who are riding jet skis, planes and motor boats. They're attacking your Atoll and you must destroy them with your missiles. You must also save drowning civilians.  -Platforming levels: Here you take control of the Mariner and must kill all the smokers to move on to the next level. You start off  with a machete but can get other weapons such as a gun off enemies you've killed. You always play on the exact same level as you're always defending the same Atoll.  -Bonus levels: you unlock these after completing a boat level. It consists of you swimming underwater, trying to get bonus items before you run out of breath. If you run out of breath while underwater, you automatically lose all the items you had collected. These items get you points that you can then spend in the in-game shop to upgrade your ship.Cheat: Level codeEnter these in the password screen</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Ocean Software Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<VideoURL>ljn6zS0CZOg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2214</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588836-waterworld</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/waterworld__</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/waterworld/3030-9919/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Xf97Rjc.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/HGxtOgo.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/SuJIajY.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/tm38iOe.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/HQ9IVbi.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/sHQPmTp.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/0rvYPFZ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/n3g00Cx.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/MfhU8EY.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/yAjbYXO.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/d3Z3SxC.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/dD7y731.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/XnoQcMv.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/kJUnZ1E.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/i0H3FiT.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In the future, Earth's temperature rises and melts the polar ice caps, and Earth lies under a watery grave.  Years later, survivors of this disaster live on boats or man-made islands called Atolls.  Everyone in this new world is looking for a mythical place called Dry Land, which people believe that there is a map to Dry Land on a little girl's back named Enola.  A band of pirates who live an oil tanker called the Smokers are after Dry Land and they are trying to get Enola for the tatoo on her back.  A nameless drifter who has adapted to the new world and this causes him to have gills and webbed feet, gets involved in this whole "quest for Dry Land" so to speak and becomes responsible for Enola and the woman who looks after her named Helen. You play as the nameless drifter only known as The Marnier.  You play through three types of gameplay.  The first type of gameplay involves you sailing in a some-what big area and clearing the area of Smokers. There is a second type of these sailing levels add something else.  You can save the Atollers from The Smokers.  The second type of gameplay is the swimming.  You swim underwater avoiding sea creatures and collecting items for money to use at the shop after you kill off Smokers on the Atolls.  Killing of The Smokers is the third type of gameplay. You run through the Atolls with your big knife at first and then you get three more weapons along the way which are a pistol, a speargun, and a machine gun.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/56b0ae7f-906a-41a1-bd34-8002c28e8a18.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f715c49a-4a09-4f6d-bba7-d2e867e6027d.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Laguna</Publisher>
</game>