<Game>
	<Name>Wayne's World (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The purple blobWayne's World puts players into the role of Wayne, from the popular SNL skit about the fictional public access show Wayne's World, and the hit movie based on the skit. In the game, Wayne and his friend Garth are sucked into the Zoltar the Gelatinous Cube arcade machine mentioned in the movie. They must chase down a mysterious purple blob that captured Wayne's blond-haired friend. Released in 1993, this game came out on the  Super Nintendo Entertainment System, Sega Genesis and the Game Boy.Gameplay:Robo Elvis battleWayne's World is a combination of platforming and shooting. Wayne's main weapon is a guitar, which he can strum to attack with sound waves. These waves can be increased by finding amp upgrades in various levels. The player will face several wacky enemies based on the location, such as a man-eating donut in the donut shop or a person with a mohawk at a backstage level. There is a total of five stages with three levels each. Each level ends with Garth getting recaptured by the large purple blob.															</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.6</rating>
	<VideoURL>rHNuJB86-bY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6337</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588838-waynes-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/waynes-world_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/waynes-world/3030-8565/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/F20eLqK.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/lx2QDfL.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/zF0tJ9z.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/2AGwbtj.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/6TUToqW.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/YEIvgJ7.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/uneyTiw.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ERRiVeo.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/CHAKHVv.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vYwW56v.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/WeYY7zI.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/q1M9OhK.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/YPEMiVW.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/PzIXSmr.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/78FQ2xn.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/d4KUfE4.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Are you ready for this? Number One of the Top Ten Most Bizarre Things to Happen This Year: Garth has been kidnapped! No way, you say? Hway!! It's the work of a most heinous goon - a pixelated purple putridosity called Zantar. And now you, Wayne Campbell, must heartily rescue your excellent sidekick from a fate most unbecoming! Armed with you mighty guitar and the power to Schwing, you must brave the perils of Kramer's Music Store, Stan Mikita's Donut Shop, the Gaeworks nightclub and suburbia. There, you will spar with such dweeboids as monster bagpipes, accordions and kazoos (shyeah, rright!), spewing coffee cups and dangerous disco balls (as if!), hair-whipping headbangers and the strange Psycho Hose Beast (way!) Hello? Are you worthy to face this mega challenge without blowing chunks? Then party on my friend, to the most excellent finish!</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cab8f9c3-fb8f-4f2a-b374-0b73890aa331.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8ca49ede-d922-4172-8991-c8201c22ba8e.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/86510f6e-27f4-4532-a09d-4ad1a599d070.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ae777372-d378-4818-a001-9f45225b8358.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>