<Game>
	<Name>WCW Super Brawl Wrestling (USA)</Name>
	<plot>WCW is known by many wrestling fans, the only real competition for the WWE. (Back then called the WWF) In this game, you combat with greats like Sting, Ric Flair, Dustin Rhodes, and Scott Steiner. Will you succeed?Directions:There are three types of game-play.In single match, you face one opponent.In tag team, you team up with another wrestler to face a team of two!In Tournament, you must win matches to advance, and if you get to the end of the bracket, you win!In Ultimate Challenge, it's kinda like a singles match, sorta. You face one opponent at a time, though. You get many other opponents!There are two modes of play: One Player and Two Player Controls:A Button - Grapple, PinB Button - AttackX Button - ThrowY Button - Leg MoveL Button - Run, climb turnbuckleR Button - Run, climb turnbuckleStart Button - Pause, UnpauseSelect Button - Make tags in tag team matches Reviewer:  LinkOfHyrulehttp://www.consoleclassix.com/snes/wcw_superbrawl_wrestling.htmlCheat: Final MatchUsing the game's built in Password system, enter any one of these codes to play in the title match of the "Ultimate Challenge" mode with any one of the 12 specified Wrestlers..</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>FCI, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6338</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588839-wcw-super-brawl-wrestling</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/wcw-superbrawl-wrestling</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wcw-superbrawl-wrestling/3030-22273/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/mfeeR9D.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/Chdc00N.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/otDA7pT.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/r6WI4BU.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/MxA1KtD.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/lilNv37.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/POlIGec.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/BpvVq2N.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/KiYXuTz.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/HVbElLs.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/3s8QsSe.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/HOTnTzP.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/ACV1MDb.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/9e4bCIW.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/nsOl6kQ.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>STOMP A FRIEND TODAY! How ‘bout Vader's Power Bomb or Ravishing Rick Rude's Rude Awakening to do the trick’? A Figure Four Leg lock by “Nature Boy” Ric Flair might make you feel good. Ricky “the Dragon” Steamboat will take you on a ride you won’t forget. And Johnny B. Badd’s just waitin' to get you good. You wanna step into the ring-shoes of Ron Simmons, Flyin’ Brian, Barry Windham and Sting? Use the signature moves of “The Natural” Dustin Rhodes? Well quit dreamin’ and get in the ring. Wrestle the great ones in individual or tag team action. With dozens of classic moves plus each man's signature moves, its the most realistic action encounter you'll find this side of the square circle. These are the guys you watch on television's WCW Pro Wrestling, WCW Main Event and WCW WORLDWIDE. And Tony Schiavone, Americas premier TV wrestling voice, announces every match. Cmon, Rick “Dogface Gremlin" and Scott Steiner are ready to go a bout with you and a friend, or...you be them. Be 'em all — give yourself a SuperBrawl!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cff4a6e4-7057-4111-bb2f-a90da728ac32.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9774452a-755f-47b8-b348-29dd94c67187.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c4dd565a-c333-496d-844e-72108f8061b3.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2f0d8c62-a485-4ae8-9c2b-3e5b0a432433.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>FCI</Publisher>
</game>