<Game>
	<Name>We're Back! - A Dinosaur's Story (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story is a platformer game based on the 1993 movie of the same name. The player takes the intelligent Tyrannosaurus, Rex, through various stages full of obstacles and enemies to get around. Rex doesn't bite people, but he can throw rocks at enemies until they vanish.The game was published on the Super Nintendo, Sega Genesis and the Nintendo Game Boy shortly after the release of the movie. A Game Gear version was planned, but canceled mid-production. The Game Boy version was published in various countries with graphical changes and new titles.Game Boy VersionsThe Game Boy version of We're Back is one of four different releases from Laser Beam Entertainment on the Game Boy in which all of the game play is the same with only sprites changed. The versions of this game are:We're Back! A Dinosaur StoryThis is the version that was released in the US. The characters in We're Back! A Dinosaur Story are based off of the animated movie of the same name. We're Back!BamseBamse is the version that was released in Sweden. The characters in this version are from a Swedish cartoon created by Rune Andr&#233;asson.  BamseAgro SoarAgro Soar is the version that was released in Australia. In Agro Soar the main character was based on a popular character in Australia named Agro. Agro hosted a block of childrens cartoons and would show skits and stories in between the cartoons. Agro SoarBaby T-RexBaby T-Rex was the original version of the game. Baby T-Rex was an original IP and was not based off of any existing property. Baby T-RexCheat: Level SelectAt the title screen, press Left, Right, Left, Right, Select, A.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Hi-Tech Expressions, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>6342</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588841-were-back-a-dinosaurs-story</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/were-back-a-dinosaurs-story</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/were-back-a-dinosaurs-story/3030-22937/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/BUVRRcp.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/BAI78h1.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/GcH90TE.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/iU6jJud.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/6IRuwsG.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/K6oWHvH.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/BSTqFHt.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/tNRvkSJ.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/2bcGfpa.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/pUvGuEY.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/ofgCTyq.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/0lqFtSz.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/yXe8nJS.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/VVTpDMb.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/YyhBAg2.png</clearlogo1>
</game>