<Game>
	<Name>Where in the World Is Carmen Sandiego (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego? is the first game in the Carmen Sandiego edutainment series of adventure games from Broderbund Software. In this game, the player is cast in the role of a detective with the ACME Detective Agency tasked with solving thefts committed by members of V.I.L.E., a criminal organization headed by the mysterious Carmen Sandiego. A world atlas was bundled with the game in order to assist players with certain clues.Gameplay:At the start of each case, the player begins by traveling to the scene of the crime. By questioning witnesses, clues are gathered which point towards the thief's characteristics, as well as his or her next destination. It is the player's responsibility to gather the information and interpret it correctly. Once the player has enough clues, a warrant for a suspect can be issued. After tailing the suspect from country to country, the player will eventually catch up and, if it's the correct suspect, make an arrest.			</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>10959</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588844-where-in-the-world-is-carmen-sandiego</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/where-in-the-world-is-carmen-sandiego-enhanced</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/where-in-the-world-is-carmen-sandiego/3030-658/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ec8VKNb.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nRPggm5.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/05uldRX.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/BcwZZp9.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/1xeOjoc.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/ai34xuQ.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/LQHWUUU.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/8XdOhA0.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/nd8nIgZ.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/PjhsNb5.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/vqXIouo.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/u3VWGjC.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/E9nuNo1.png</clearlogo1>
</game>