<Game>
	<Name>Whirlo (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: &amp; GameplayXandra no Daibouken: Valkyrie to no Deai, known in Europe and Australia as Whirlo, is a spin-off of Namco's Legend of Valkyrie series and is directly connected to the NES game Valkyrie no Bouken: Toki no Kagi Densetsu, which featured Xandra/Whirlo as Valkyrie's companion.The plot focuses on Whirlo's homeland after it is covered by ash from a nearby volcano and causes various citizens to fall ill and die. Whirlo's own child is endangered, so he leaves to search for a cure to save his son despite the many dangers in- and outside the village.The game is a straightforward platformer with a high-jump mechanic. The player can charge a jump by crouching, allowing Whirlo to jump high distances. Whirlo also has his trusty pitchfork weapon, with which he can perform stabs, downward thrusts and spinning air dash moves - however, all but the basic stab will take Whirlo out of commission for a few seconds before he can recover, thus leaving an opening for enemy retaliation.Cheat: PasswordsAt the title screen select password and enter the following combination.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/7/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<VideoURL>dLvzioQa-nU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2215</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/569362-whirlo</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/whirlo</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/whirlo/3030-4795/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/2fzR80M.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/hzDqSTE.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/RaSmhD3.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/zvSoRPI.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/1K84yj4.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/HMTkuCf.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/x41AksI.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Bz28HmV.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/NjpLj6z.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/vayTl1n.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/N7rMifi.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/5lheBnp.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/1ofPEt2.png</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Q1w4Ifi.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/deTvAKf.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>A platformer title starring Valkyrie's lizard friend Xandra. In the game, which plays as a prequel of the Valkyrie games, you control Xandra as he leaves his enchanted forest in order to get help for his family. This will eventually lead him to meet up with our beloved Valkyrie and mark the beginning of their adventures. Xandra has all the abilities of a standard platformer character, which allow him to jump around and navigate the many obstacles found in the game. Additionally he's armed with a pitchfork which he can use to impale his enemies and stick to some surfaces. Collecting coins allow him to purchase extra lives, but there are no added weapons or spells as in the Valkyrie games.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33296bf3-f4c6-4d37-a1df-53ff6284ec58.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98711562-3503-4386-ae10-22a82daf6e56.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2287f782-54f6-4a0e-b90d-f82bf5c0caa7.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/da68f98c-a376-43f6-ab69-74ceb04dafe2.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>