<Game>
	<Name>Wild Snake (USA)</Name>
	<plot>"Snakes! Why Did It Have to Be Snakes?"The nest of deadly snakes has been disturbed by seismic experiments in a remote location. Now the snakes are slithering to the surface, causing confused terror in attacks on everything that crosses their path.There is a way to control this madness, but it's not going to be easy. The snakes from this nest tend to eat snakes of the same color and design. If you can guide the slithering masses so that snakes of the same type meet and eliminate each other, then the world could be saved from this snake infestation.It's all up to you! Guide the snakes, find matching pairs and keep the population under control!--From the SNES Wild Snake instruction manual.http://www.consoleclassix.com/snes/wild_snake.html</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Spectrum Holobyte</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6346</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588850-wild-snake</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/wildsnake</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wildsnake/3030-21935/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/LO9Ghiz.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/zFLdl97.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/flkQC3t.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/mw9vl5e.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/ERZWrqo.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/PzJiU04.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/i1AMsg4.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/PMqKtSi.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/TzepoTg.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/ZVrXaND.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/hdHgjVz.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/yy9OCKN.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/Mb4T2eB.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CuhqYJN.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/6qgfrTX.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>A deadly nest of snakes. And only you can keep them from getting out! Maneuver each new snake so it touches another of the same kind, making the venomous viper disappear. Sound easy? As long as you con keep matching up snakes, you're in control. But when those poisonous reptiles pile close to the top, you better run for your life! If you're lucky, a King Cobra might appear and devour ever snake in its path. Or the powerful flashing Wild Snake could rid you of all the snakes of one color. But remember, snakes like a challenge, and they move faster and faster as your skills improve.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f8166201-8485-416b-bf57-5bf25403ddf7.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/692c1c54-f89e-4134-a3bc-c501d6ef96b3.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f87c800d-868e-473d-9d46-3b6599ad167e.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2b0a6412-de7e-44e2-8632-4a2fb0e13562.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Spectrum Holobyte</Publisher>
</game>