<Game>
	<Name>Wild Trax (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>The updated Super FX chip allows you to shift into high gear! Get behind the wheel of a formula racer, a 4WD monster truck, a subcompact or a motorcycle. Each will provide a unique driving experience. Choose from over 20 pedal-to-the-metal Trax. There are the no-holds-barred Speed Trax where you hone your skills and progress from a novice to a master. Stunt Trax provides an obstacle course rally complete with ups, downs and jumps. Battle Trax means head-to-head conflict in surprising terrain. For speed, variety, action and fun, Stunt Race FX finishes far ahead of the competition!Cheat: Arwing in Night OwlIn the Night Owl stage, there should be four small "StarFox" signs on the walls of the course, that fall if you crash into them. Ram all four signs, and an Arwing from Star Fox will fly in and drop a power-up.Cheat: Control the animation when the game is pausedPause the game and when the pause animation comes up, press R to make the animation run in slow motion.  Press Y to speed up the car in the animation, or press Select to make it run backwards.Cheat: Control the animation when the game is paused To play battle Trax alone, select Battle Trax made and cars for both players. After the green light, wait about two seconds before hitting the gas. Any vehicle not activated by a controller will be driven by the CPU.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/7/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Arcade</genre>
	<Developer>Argonaut Games</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>7.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>UiZ3YxDGQ7A</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3270</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588705-stunt-race-fx</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/stunt-race-fx/3030-19991/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/7uokPnN.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/bY60eYJ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/bdWB093.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/fqwnbkK.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/OVaXgeV.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/5PV4683.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/zOs4Hpz.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/VZLKk48.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/vuKWXP5.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/k7aNhS0.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/6HKtj54.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/i06Q86V.png</clearlogo1>
</game>