<Game>
	<Name>Williams Arcade's Greatest Hits (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>This is one of the compilations that game companies occasionally come up with. The games are as follows:Defender: In this side-scrolling space shooter, you have to defeat all the enemies to continue to the next level.Defender II: The sequel to Defender. In addition to all the features in the original, you can warp to the other side of the planet.Joust: Knock all the enemies off the vultures and collect the eggs.Robotron: 2084: Shoot the robots with your laser to proceed to the next level. Remember, the last human family's fate is in your hands.Sinistar: Your goal in this game is to mine Sinibombs from asteroids and defeat Sinistar (the big white guy floating around). Also beware of the little aliens waiting to attack you.I like the fact that Williams ported these games to SNES, but I don't get to see the attract screens. I would rather play the games in their Shockwave versions and in Midway Arcade Treasures (PS2, Xbox, GCN) than play ports that don't have the feel of the original.I will list the controls for the games in the order that they're presented in the main menu.Directions:Relive the moments of your favorite arcade hits from the '80s. Controls:A Button - Nothing, Inviso, Flap, Fire Right, NothingB Button - Hyperspace, Hyperspace, Flap, Fire Down, NothingX Button - Bomb, Bomb, Flap, Fire Up, SinibombY Button - Fire, Fire, Flap, Fire Left, FireL Button - Switch Direction, Switch Direction, Flap, Nothing, NothingR Button - Move, Move, Flap, Nothing, Hide Status BarStart Button - PauseSelect Button - Nothing, Nothing, Nothing, Auto-Fire, Slow MotionHints:255 LivesThis will only happen if Sinistar sucks you in on your last life and a UFO appears during this action. A -1 will appear in your lives. Reviewer: MethodOnehttp://www.consoleclassix.com/snes/williams_arcades_greatest_hits.htmlCheat: Start a game as normal, and during gameplay, perform the following sequences with the joystick and start buttons:Cheat: 1. Move right, Fire up, and press the Player 1 start button.Cheat: 2. Move up, Fire down, and press the Player 2 start button.Cheat: 3. Move down, Fire up.Cheat: You must do each part of the sequence within a quarter second of one another, but you may hold each part as long as you wish.  When the third part is done, the programmer credits will pop up and remain onscreen as long as the fire joystick is held upward.  Be warned that you will lose your game if you do this trick, and it must be done without dying.Cheat: This is tricky, but very possible to pull off in most if not all versions of Sinistar. With only no lives remaining, when you fly up to a fully build Sinistar, he'll suck you in and eat you. However, if a UFO is around when this animation is occuring and you get shot before being eaten, the lives will be -1, which will loop back around to 255. Have fun!</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1996</releasedate>
	<genre>Compilation, Arcade</genre>
	<Developer>Midway</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3288</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588199-williams-arcades-greatest-hits</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/williams-arcade-classics/3030-1956/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Olv6F15.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/ImFxyoQ.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/n0AWbnw.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/qrzmBO6.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FIOVJ1K.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/pLqe4jm.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/2AdTDFq.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/zjHoflc.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/An8GtYr.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Y9CEJJi.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/jJ2dhN4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/6hlwWzT.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/JAqTInH.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>THE GREAT HITS THAT MADE YOU A REGULAR IN LOCAL ARCADES ARE NOW COMING HOME! Relive the old days chasing down the dirty scum in Bubbles! Play Defender once again, and navigate your vessel through alien territory! Defender II includes added villains and features not found in the original Defender! Challenge gladiators in a fight to the death in Joust! Once again, Robotron 2084 lets you dash with a mutant force of robots to save the only remaining human family! With the coolest graphics of its time, Sinistar returns with great outerspace battle action! TAKE HOME SOME GREAT MEMORIES AND MASTER YOUR FAVORITE ARCADE HITS ONCE AGAIN!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4d076876-46a6-4e00-a546-c797e3ef636e.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cc470d95-88b6-4056-bdbe-fd957ce2a74c.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/31fe2d4e-d41e-4b96-9f22-2053b534a890.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb7dcaa4-6034-4cbd-8de0-16bac89875b4.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Williams</Publisher>
</game>