<Game>
	<Name>Winter Olympic Games - Lillehammer '94 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt,Sv,No)</Name>
	<plot>Winter Olympics (Lillehammer 94 is added informally and is not part of the official title) is the official video game of the XVII Olympic Winter Games that were held in Lillehammer, Norway in 1994. Published by US Gold. Home computer versions (Amiga and PC) were developed by ID Software (not to be confused with id Software, of Doom fame) and console versions (GG, MD/Gen, Master System, Super NES) were developed by Tiertex. The game featured 10 winter sporting events. There are also major differences between platforms.Players can represent different countries from Canada to England to Brazil. However, the player does not have the luxury of accented letters to make authentic looking French or Portuguese names. It is impossible for the player to name his character "Pel?" because there is no "?" symbol in the game, so players will have to call him "Pele" instead.The player can train freely and compete in both full or mini (events selected by the player) Olympics. During competition, there are both medals and points tables. While in Olympic Gold points were awarded according to the medals table, in Winter Olympics they were given according to the best results, like decathlon. Doing so, it was perfectly possible to someone win the gold medal in short track, and get few more points than other skaters (even not finalists) that got better qualifying times. This scoring method also meant that someone who won gold medals in six or seven events might fall outside the top 10 if is disqualified on the remaining three.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Winter_Olympics:_Lillehammer_94</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>U.S. Gold</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>UvIw8DHtegY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6350</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588854-winter-olympic-games-lillehammer-94</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/winter-olympics-lillehammer-94</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/winter-olympics-lillehammer-94/3030-8749/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/NmyfQWO.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/S4Tb1Vv.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/uOsuc00.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/N8zKEyF.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/tCIep5p.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/RKW6vaJ.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/rcR3mia.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/qyRUvRJ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/2a4M1uq.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/dt8csV2.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/DtDLltw.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Wl3FsbD.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/aCkZhQZ.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/sjoqq0C.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Oq9idVy.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Play the hottest game on ice and snow - Winter Olympic Games, the official licensed version of the 1994 Lillehammer Olympic Winter Games. Ten events with actual courses used in Lillehammer. Compete with 1 - 4 players, or challenge Olympic Game records. Sixteen countries to represent including Canada, United States, France and Japan. Eight languages including English, French, Spanish, German and Norwegian.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d71e6ce-7691-4d0c-a840-b2c7c073de83.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3fc8d660-6952-430e-92f4-9b4451ef2dfe.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/190e1dd2-e940-4065-b3a8-25361397dcbc.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>U.S. Gold</Publisher>
</game>