<Game>
	<Name>World Heroes 2 (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:World Heroes 2 is a 2D fighting game developed by  ADK and published by  SNK for the  Neo Geo. It is a direct sequel to  World Heroes, adding six new playable characters and one new boss. Death Match mode from the previous game received an overhaul, adding and removing obstacles (mine fields, moving saws, laser beams, slippery floors, and smaller arenas) while completely changing the lifebar system to one large tug-of-war lifebar. Gameplay additions include taunting (standing far back while pressing the throw button), throw reversals (throwing at the moment you're being grabbed, can cause "throw battles") and projectile reflection (blocking at the very moment a projectile reaches you, similar to the  Just Defend system of  Garou: Mark of the Wolves).The game was ported to the  SNES and  TurboGrafx CD by  Takara. The original version of the game was released on the  Neo Geo CD with an arranged soundtrack and released on the  World Heroes Anthology compilation for the  PlayStation 2.Characters: Hanzo (based on Hanzo Hattori) Fuuma (based on Fuma Kotaro) Kim Dragon (based on  Bruce Lee) Janne D'Arc (based on  Joan of Arc) Julius Carn (based on  Genghis Khan) Muscle Power (based on  Hulk Hogan) Brocken Rasputin (based on Grigori Rasputin) Mudman Ryoko Izumo (based on Ryoko Tani) Captain Kidd (based on William Kidd) Erick (based on Erik the Red) Johnny Maximum Shura (based on Nai Khanom Tom)Neo Geegus (boss, based on  T-1000) Dio (boss)Cheat: Boss CodeAt the title screen, press Select, A, Up, R, Up, Select. You should then hear a ringing sound. Now to play as one of the bosses, hold the following buttons and go to the Player Select Screen:Cheat: Character ending glitchComplete Arcade mode (1P Game mode) with any character on default settings.After the credits, select Versus Battle Mode and win with any character. After the match,the winning character's ending will be played with weird looking glitch graphics. .</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>TAKARA Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 VS</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>eRkuaxyS8jM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6357</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588864-world-heroes-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/world-heroes-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/world-heroes-2/3030-19626/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Kuoyc0P.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/LGtLQx4.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/llyHW60.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/xH4Xab6.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/NfNFnRo.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/ESOFgs0.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/j95vdLd.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BCp7GIY.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/lP6J92R.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/D5cIgKr.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/L9YRqjl.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/JEvfNX9.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/gTra0xF.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/aZlV6E9.png</clearlogo1>
</game>