<Game>
	<Name>World Class Rugby (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:World Class Rugby is a rugby game developed by Denton Designs and published by Audiogenic Software for multiple platforms in Europe and Australia in 1991. The game was eventually licensed to Japanese publisher Misawa which produced a Super Nintendo version of the game two years later that used Mode 7 for its top-down perspective and various cartoon depictions of rugby players on the title screen and half-time screens. This version was eventually ported back to Europe via Imagineer.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Misawa</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>6354</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570903-world-class-rugby</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/world-class-rugby/3030-5401/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/8KBj7Wj.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/UPybrp6.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/8EYsii9.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/4jZ3zNL.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Hq23XHM.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/0bwgt80.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/tCcdjoC.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ZDhuTXG.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/kFMSPcG.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/kiw0J43.jpg</snapshot8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/0kM2AHu.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/Ihrfkz3.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Sixteen best teams compete for the World Cup, an ultimate test of your skills against the very best in the game. 3D perspective, sound effects and the atmosphere takes you to the very heart if the action. You are on the pitch battling it out with the heavies in the scrum, tackling the wingers, jumping for the ball in the line out and experiencing the triumphal sensation of scoring a Try. Single Game, World Cup and League for 3 to 8 teams. One or Two players option. Option to change team names, players names, skills and physical attributes. Instant action replay</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2f7dfe0a-620a-46e3-a676-f7aa681842fc.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6a58b455-8a18-453f-bcc8-6686b1260b94.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Audiogenic Software</Publisher>
</game>