<Game>
	<Name>Wrecking Crew '98 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Wrecking Crew '98 is the sequel to the NES game Wrecking Crew. Wrecking Crew '98 was released in Japan on the Super Famicom on May 23, 1998. The game introduced several new features, as well as adding new characters. The game's story involves the fact that Bowser begins a large construction campaign. This is depriving the Mushroom Kingdom (and its inhabitants) of sunlight, so Mario decides to destroy the constructions. Foreman Spike, Gotcha Wrench, and Eggplant Man from Wrecking Crew all return to stop Mario on this quest.Gameplay:What the typical gameplay screen looks like.The gameplay of Wrecking Crew '98 is very similar to the original game. Panels are eliminated by smashing them with the hammer, or by getting three of the same colored panels in a row (either vertically or horizontally). After playing for a little bit, brick panels begin falling in. These panels are covered in brick, so they require one smash to show their color. More brick panels appear the longer the match goes on. Four panels in a row of the same color create an obstacle for the opponent. Various panels do different attacks on the opponent.Playable CharactersMarioLuigiBowserForeman SpikeGotcha WrenchKoopa TroopaPeachEggplant ManOnigiriOnnanokoOyajiDoguCheat: New LevelsTo get new levels do the following things: </plot>
	<releasedate>23/5/1998</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Pax Softonica</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22642</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571526-wrecking-crew-98</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/wrecking-crew-98</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wrecking-crew-98/3030-22787/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/QCnogDz.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/w8Hf6Ov.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/aFQtYiG.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/o3lkNlF.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/zpR6IMw.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/otQc68C.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/RhXN8KR.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/lDfqQbs.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/YlSYYZC.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/F9LnRpo.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/qeZeVGV.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/vjmvTvS.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/JS7jFsy.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Mario, on his way home from a trip, discovers that Bowser has been conducting a construction campaign of building high-rises in the Mushroom Kingdom which are depriving the local plantlife of sunlight. Refusing to tolerate this, he brings out a mighty blue hammer from a chest inside his house and embarks on a mission to demolish the offending structures. Mario's old nemesis, Foreman Spike, along with a Gotcha Wrench, Eggplant Man, and more new and old enemies, are once again out to stop him on his quest, however.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9cf85352-4d16-4d8a-bcc6-b4f2ff0b3572.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6e56c8e7-59db-4d2b-afcb-d66176e6769b.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>