<Game>
	<Name>WWF Raw (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:WWF Raw is a wrestling game developed by  Sculptured Software and published by  Acclaim or LJN for multiple platforms. It is named for the TV show WWF Raw which regularly aired matches between WWF (now WWE) wrestlers and wrote stories around those bouts.The game uses a horizontal perspective of the ring and has multiple different modes based on events from the TV show: One-on-One, Tag Team, Bedlam, Survivor Series, Royal Rumble and Raw Endurance. Depending on the system, the player has a roster of up to thirteen WWF wrestlers to choose from. As well as regular attacks and signature moves, wrestlers will frequently get locked into a grapple and the player must mash buttons to escape and use the advantage to throw their opponent.Featured WrestlersSNES, Genesis &amp; 32X Versions 1-2-3 Kid Bam Bam Bigelow Bret Hart DieselDoink the ClownKwang (only 32X Version with a code) Lex LugerLuna Vachon Owen Hart Razor Ramon Shawn Michaels The Undertaker YokozunaGame Gear Version Bam Bam Bigelow Bret HartCrush Diesel Lex Luger Randy Savage Razor Ramon Shawn Michaels The Undertaker YokozunaGame Boy Version Bret Hart DieselDoink the Clown Lex Luger Razor Ramon Shawn Michaels The Undertaker YokozunaCheat: Change wrestlers attributesOn the wrestler select screen, when the indicated wrestler listed below is highlighted, press the select button to see the character's attributes, then press the following button sequence to change their stats:Cheat: Referee leavesKnock the ref down 5-10 times or use yokozunas mega move 5-10 times</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>LJN, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>SJMw9JmqSio</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6363</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588867-wwf-raw</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/wwf-raw-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wwf-raw/3030-4155/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/CjaD8Dn.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/urJaCo1.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/pnT2Ltl.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/aY6eCoV.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/MNwazwx.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/RoaS7zS.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/lELJlOf.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/oaL5fMe.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/kOv2HtI.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/kVJNmMf.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/gV9sac5.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Xab9QeJ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/8mlHAN5.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/WWPzWaT.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/dX6HzOh.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/immkwAV.png</clearlogo1>
</game>