<Game>
	<Name>WWF WrestleMania - The Arcade Game (Japan) (En)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:WWF WrestleMania: The Arcade Game is an exaggerated fighting game that uses digitized sprites of the featured professional wrestlers, similar to Mortal Kombat. Players battle through one-on-one, one-on-two, and one-on-three matches to claim either the Intercontinental Championship or WWF Heavyweight Championship. Vince McMahon and Jerry Lawler provided commentary and the game was later ported to home consoles by Acclaim Studios Salt Lake City, which would make the successor title, WWF in Your House.Playable CharactersThe UndertakerShawn MichaelsBret HartRazor RamonLex LugerBam Bam Bigelow (Not playable in the SNES version)Yokozuna (Not playable in the SNES version)Doink The ClownGameplay:Developed by Midway, WWF Wrestlemania plays similarly to Mortal Kombat, with a few exceptions. Characters can move in somewhat 3-D space, in that you can walk up and down, as well as left and right. Combat features 5 buttons, Light Punch, Power Punch, Light Kick, Power Kick and Block. It is also possible to Run by pressing Light Punch and Light Kick together.The main game consists of the player choosing to go after the Intercontinental title or the World Wrestling Federation Title. In the Intercontinental Title challenge, you'll face 4 opponents via 1-on-1 matches, followed by two 2-on-1 matches, and finally a 3-on-1 match. In the WWF Title Challenge, you'll start out with four 2-on-1 matches, moving on to two 3-on-1 matches, and finally the "Wrestlemania Challenge", a gauntlet match against every wrestler in the game. In the final match, however, only 4 people (including yourself) will be in the ring at once. Once you eliminate an opponent, someone will replace them until you've beaten all eight opponents.Each character has a unique ending.The only known "finishing move", similar to a Fatality, is done by the Undertaker. Originally the game was scheduled to have finishing moves for each character, but the WWF shot down the plan.																	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>Lcdzf-7Pw2Y</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6365</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588870-wwf-wrestlemania-the-arcade-game</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/wwf-wrestlemania-the-arcade-game</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wwf-wrestlemania-the-arcade-game/3030-8027/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/aGSAQUv.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/QW1E73B.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/e6Tekp6.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/V4cQtYH.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/YUHAXI0.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/qqBDbBH.jpg</boxart6>
	<boxart7>http://i.imgur.com/TGL4vJr.jpg</boxart7>
	<boxart8>http://i.imgur.com/PyJckUI.jpg</boxart8>
	<boxart9>http://i.imgur.com/rU9jD3z.jpg</boxart9>
	<boxart10>http://i.imgur.com/xZeqPox.jpg</boxart10>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/RrzpSIy.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/1GcHuvT.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/630mr0s.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/RsL2Sh5.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/iXBeU7i.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/ilKsmPF.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/k7L2k4g.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/1yNjaON.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/AYhdb1k.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/dvmjwkB.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/aGNVNc3.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/TPc1GS1.png</clearlogo1>
</game>