<Game>
	<Name>X Zone (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Set in the bleak future, the defense computers of an entire planet have gone crazy. The player must fight them through seven levels with their trusty Super Scope. They face off against walkers and tanks before eventually taking down the master computer end boss.X-Zone is one of a handful of SNES games that takes advantage of the Super Scope peripheral, which is required to play the game. As with its Super Scope contemporaries Bazooka Blitzkrieg and Battle Clash, the game is a light-gun rail shooter filled with futuristic robots and vehicles to shoot down.Critical ReceptionElectronic Gaming Monthly awarded X-Zone scores of 7,8,8,8 adding, "...the action is non-stop from the start and you really need to keep calm throughout each level. Only patience can win this game, as rockets come at you from every angle!".	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Kemco</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>mxNZ-1tS7Uw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>8184</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588875-x-zone</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/x-zone</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/x-zone/3030-13533/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/nhhU97a.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/X3evzwF.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/P4cHCsZ.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/hBbT9kR.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/uY32Qkb.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/AsBcO1X.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/FuqlMz1.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/9mwAwbO.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/XObweCi.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/tzgaKnP.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/29OuN23.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/qJpMMWu.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/pnr229k.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/BIXPiAz.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5MfIN3H.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/CLoIpSG.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Quick! Get that blaster off your shoulder and zero in on your target with the first Super Scope game using on screen cross hair sights. The nation's main frame bio computer wants to x-terminate Earth. Your mission, should you x-cept it: infiltrate the x-tra defenses, x-plode the overseer's drones and moles that want to make you x-tinct. And x-ray the buggy bio brain with a couple of nuclear weapons. It's an x-plosive situation that only the truly x-cellent can survive.</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b9abd45b-8aba-462c-9ca2-949b4dc22051.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b35e5e0-b913-47d5-9c1b-03983c44ad65.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a206d8e-d4fe-4dc5-8230-1cdd518a626e.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c2db3193-9c60-4554-8a18-23855696850d.png</snapshot12>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Kemco</Publisher>
</game>