<Game>
	<Name>Yoshi no Cookie - Kuruppon Oven de Cookie (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Yoshi no Cookie: Kuruppon Oven de Cookie is a cuisine focused re-release of the original Yoshi's Cookie by Bulletproof Software and National Human Electronics. While the gameplay is identical, the game also adds cooking advice and recipes concerning the Kuruppon Oven from Panasonic. Only 500 copies were released in Japan, and the game was not available in other territories. It currently fetches a very high price on the Japanese retro game market.Yoshi no Cookie: Kuruppon Oven de Cookie is not the first advergame Nintendo signed off on. The thematically similar Motoko-Chan no Wonder Kitchen was released the same year.	</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Bullet Proof Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>2</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/610912-yoshi-no-cookie-kuruppon-oven-de-cookie</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/yoshi-no-cookie-kuruppon-oven-de-cookie-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yoshi-no-cookie-kuruppon-oven-de-cookie/3030-29976/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/d0YeaTt.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/BTQ7DVV.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/mtm9myp.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/0N4YkFt.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/yGqMZo0.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/i4PPrXN.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/i1sFbU2.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/w7x6wRl.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/7xYQeJg.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/9QZCgam.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/3VMWsqA.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>A Japan-only edition of Yoshi's Cookie developed to promote A new Kuruppon oven. Only 500 copies of the game were produced, and are now very expensive collector's items. While an identical copy of the SNES version of Yoshi's Cookie is included, an additional mode is available in which Yoshi moves around on a map similar to Super Mario World's, navigating a small, unknown island. By surveying around and selecting areas, Yoshi is able to cross bridges, hop over blocks, and swim river streams. Along his tour, Yoshi teaches recipe tutorials in the local buildings that players can use to bake real versions of the cookies featured in the game such as Checkerboard Cookies, Heart Cookies, and Flower Cookies.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99cd86a0-56b8-493e-b0fd-9b1077090c9c.png</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>