<Game>
	<Name>Yoshi's Cookie (USA) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Yoshi's Cookie was originally released in April 28, 1992 for the Nintendo Entertainment System. Initially developed by  Nintendo R&amp;D1 and published by  Nintendo, the game has been released in a variety of forms and versions since its original release. The ports of the game include the  Game Boy version (which changes little from the NES version), a  SNES version (which reskinned the game to reference  Super Mario World more frequently), and inclusion in a Japan-only compilation for the  GameCube titled Nintendo Puzzle Collection.The game included on Nintendo Puzzle Collection is technically an enhanced port of Yoshi's Cookie. There are added things, however, such as upgraded graphics and sound. Other than that, the game is completely identical to the  Super Nintendo Entertainment System version of the game).Gameplay:The game is made up of a square grid, broken up into 25 to 49 sections (5 x 5 or 7 x 7) depending on the version. Cookies of various decorations fill in the entire grid. The player manipulates entire rows either horizontally or vertically to try to match cookies that are alike. Once a row is filled with cookies of the same design, their point count increases by one and the row is wiped off of the screen.The multiplayer portion of this game has two of the cookie grids side by side, with a different player controlling each grid while different power-ups cycle on the screen. Once a player correctly aligns a row of cookies, the power up on the screen at that time is put upon the opposing player. This could range from losing five points to scrambling the cookies on their grid.Cheat: Bonus Rounds </plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>85vnsu_NjIw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6368</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588876-yoshis-cookie</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/yoshis-cookie</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yoshis-cookie/3030-16966/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/mtTqfNE.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/sxiGcFC.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/WwtoaZQ.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/B8fNIp1.png</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/rUkb13D.jpg</boxart5>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/iYtsTuv.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/sBkZkSY.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/I2z4Bj4.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Uuesnfv.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/liwy5Uh.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/TQAY1Ae.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/qXEmRj4.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/ybo6prQ.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/rGCDm6W.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/IeD0Zau.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/hcQzphS.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/swXrH9R.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/kMAlA5w.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://i.imgur.com/4ZaJHdk.png</clearlogo2>
</game>