<Game>
	<Name>Yoshi's Safari (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Yoshi's Safari is a 1993 SNES release that was designed for use with the Super Scope accessory. The game plays from the perspective of Mario riding atop Yoshi's back, and he must use the Super Scope to defeat the enemies they encounter along the way and thwart Bowser's latest scheme. Throughout the game, the player encounters numerous foes from the ranks of Mario's traditional enemies such as the Koopa Kids, Big Boo, Big Blooper, and many more. The game's levels feature branching pathways, jumps and other obstacles that must be traversed as the player battles to recollect stolen gems.The game could be played by one player with the Super Scope, or by two players, with the second controlling Yoshi's movement with a controller.Historical NotesYoshi's Safari was the first game released in western territories to refer to Princess Peach by her original name. All prior Mario games released in western territories that featured the princess had her name changed to Princess Toadstool.Critical ReceptionElectronic Gaming Monthly gave the review scores of 6,6,7,7 and 4 out of ten. Mike Weigand, who gave the score of 4 out of ten, wrote, "After playing this for a while you will want to turn the SuperScope on yourself and end it all! Yoshi's Safari suffers from one fatal flaw -- it is way too easy. The scrolling and graphics are excellent, but that is it!".			</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>mFusaFqgP5E</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2088</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588877-yoshis-safari</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/yoshis-safari</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yoshis-safari/3030-3699/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/kKzBJdF.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/FlkAtKu.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/V9JaVtO.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/cKK5fov.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/5yuzYyH.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/IWklva4.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/832gZn7.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/mCreN11.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/9fgImVb.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/8HMvaKc.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/dlQdKo9.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/nsdBWBu.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/iDa140u.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/ath7wll.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8YBi1ea.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ck2WBjE.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Bowser, King of the Koopas, and his evil offspring have invaded yet another kingdom. The Koopalings have seized the Kingdom's precious crystals. It's up to you, armed with your trusty Super Scope, to ride Yoshi to the rescue! Play alone or have a friend join you to guide Yoshi. The unique first-person viewpoint is provided exclusively by the Super NES and its Mode 7 graphics capability. Combined with the pinpoint accuracy of the Super Scope, Yoshi's Safari is sure fire fun!</Notes>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b42f6eb9-6092-423e-8c15-f8dcd9f5a341.jpg</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a6545d4e-892d-4624-8b97-920abc4fc53f.png</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/96ea76c9-700a-4f2e-9ebb-8aba0eb6b7d6.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/12ad8409-8c26-4617-9a01-84f0faf2d7aa.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/91a543ae-38d3-4430-80fe-02bf809d1174.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>