<Game>
	<Name>Ys IV - Mask of the Sun (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ys IV: Mask of the Sun was developed by Tonkin House and was released for the Super Famicom on November 19, 1993. There are two games called Ys IV that were released in 1993: Mask of the Sun and Dawn of Ys by Hudson. Falcom had no hand in the development of either game except that they came up with the basic plot outline that each developer followed. Although Dawn of Ys is a fan favorite, Mask of the Sun is considered to be the "canonical" fourth entry in the Ys franchise since it was released before Dawn of Ys and was published by Falcom. However, a true Falcom developed Ys IV was created decades later for the Playstation Vita in 2012 under the name Ys: Memories of Celceta. Taito Corporation also developed a remake of Mask of the Sun called Ys IV: Mask of the Sun - A New Theory for the PS2 in 2005.A patch was released for Ys IV: Mask of the Sun by Aeon Genesis on February 7, 2005 that translated all of the game's text into English.	</plot>
	<releasedate>19/11/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Tonkinhouse</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>Z6g81zEcQM0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6370</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/564844-ys-iv-mask-of-the-sun</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/ys-iv-mask-of-the-sun</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ys-iv-mask-of-the-sun/3030-11933/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/WvFXYVO.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/QBOVHdT.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/amrTpbW.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/24CWzE2.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/otqRVbM.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/tQT4Vac.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/RRn3G4O.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/LugjRBU.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/qlqkz0p.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/Zvm8cEk.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/3Auc0yW.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/7NRvjBH.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/KCrCEUK.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DNTaxbv.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/cd2hIzE.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>After having defeated the ultimate evil in his previous adventure, the great hero Adol stands on a sea shore, thinking about the fate of the once peaceful Utopian land of Ys, while the wind is blowing through his red hair. Suddenly, Adol notices a bottle, thrown onto the shore. It contains a letter, written in a foreign language, in which an unknown person asks Adol to come to his land and save it from a mysterious evil. Adol decides to accept the offer, and thus his adventure begins again... Ys IV: Mask of the Sun is an action RPG with a combat system like the earlier Ys games. An enemy should be rammed from the sides in order to hurt him. If performed incorrectly, the player will get hurt himself. It's also possible to use magic and position oneself strategically in battle so that the enemy won't be able to inflict any damage.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a6427d7b-befe-43a0-998f-fdcbcccdee07.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2eec0b4f-a9fd-4698-b3f4-57474d682663.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>American Sammy</Publisher>
</game>