<Game>
	<Name>Yu Yu Hakusho - Tokubetsu Hen (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:YuYu Hakusho: Tokubetsu Hen ("YuYu Hakusho: Special Edition") is a fighter game for the Super Famicom. Rather than controlling the character directly with the D-pad and buttons, the players charge attacks and unleash them at the right amount of power. Combat is depicted as a series of dramatic cutaways as each fighter launches their attacks and the other tries to defend or evade them.YuYu Hakusho, an anime series about a teenage delinquent that is recruited by the underworld to fight demons and spirits that have escaped into the normal world, saw multiple adaptations for the Super Famicom and other consoles. Most are straightforward fighter games, though this and its predecessor YuYu Hakusho use this timing-based variant. Cheat: Play as Youko Kurama, Shoujo Genkai and 100% ToguroIn the blank screen after the NAMCO logo, press B, A, B, Y, B, A, B, Y. If you did it right you'll hear a sound. In the character select screen, put the cursor in Kurama, Genkai or Toguro and press L or R to see his/her alternative mode.Cheat: Play as Youko Kurama, Shoujo Genkai and 100% ToguroWhen the screen displays "Namco", press L and R simultaneously and rapidly. It is recommended that you use a controller with the turbo-autofire function. </plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<rating>8.8</rating>
	<VideoURL>dnOaY4S5afo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>25675</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/564158-yuu-yuu-hakusho-tokubetsu-hen</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yuyu-hakusho-tokubetsu-hen/3030-50764/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/Kk4YmEC.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/H5aB9sS.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/fUni1gM.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/rxCgKzW.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/rBV3RL5.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/YEVEwnC.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Jpb6i4V.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/kSB5TkN.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/naldX6o.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/FOHCwFl.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/fX2yZ5y.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Uv7BZ4n.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/RcUswI6.png</clearlogo1>
</game>