<Game>
	<Name>Yu Yu Hakusho (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:YuYu Hakusho is a Super Famicom game based on the horror-themed manga and anime about a belligerent young man who dies unexpectedly from being hit by a car and is revived as a "spirit detective" by the rulers of the afterlife, and it becomes his job to investigate ghostly matters in the mortal world. The game is a series of set-piece battles where two opponents build up gauges using the D-pad and one of the face buttons: each combination leads to a separate attack and requires a different amount of build-up. The player can go through the story mode, which recounts events from the manga, or they can play a "free" mode against opponents of their choice.The game is the first of four YuYu Hakusho games for the Super Famicom, all of which were developed and published by Namco. The second (YuYu Hakusho 2: Kakutou no Sho) and fourth (YuYu Hakusho Final: Makai Saiky&#333; Retsuden) games are standard one-on-one fighter games featuring numerous playable characters from the series. The third game (YuYu Hakusho: Tokubetsu Hen) is a lot like the first, using a similar battle system.Though they have identical names, this particular YuYu Hakusho is not to be confused with the 1993 Game Boy YuYu Hakusho game, nor the 1994 3DO YuYu Hakusho game.	</plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/1993</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>CPIKVBbpWtM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>25676</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/564411-yuu-yuu-hakusho</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yuyu-hakusho/3030-32322/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/DyL89Ra.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/wmHJvpM.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xfHe9tT.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/48Pfd9G.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/595SqUA.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/VdHwlmd.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/EUHvDGI.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/SMKngJh.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/BgRKfxT.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/POMrBFL.jpg</snapshot8>
	<fanart1>http://i.imgur.com/sXOFQ3s.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/FcOHuvq.png</clearlogo1>
</game>