<Game>
	<Name>Yume Meikyu Kigurumi Daiboken</Name>
	<ReleaseDate>1994-04-15T00:00:00-07:00</ReleaseDate>
	<Plot>Yume Meikyu Kigurumi Daiboken (also known as Dream Maze Kigurumi Adventures) is a wacky and cute dungeon crawler published by Hector. The game tells the story of a boy who dreams of the mysterious kingdom of Enderia every night. There, he constantly lives exciting adventures and this time he is on a quest to save this world from destruction. Our hero must explore perilous towers and rescue all the kidnapped princesses from the kingdom. He is, however, not alone and friends (Harumi and Zakkari) will later help him out in his journey. Interestingly, the boy doesn't level up but wears special animal costumes called Kigurumi. Each new costume gives the player a certain number of characteristics and abilities such as better attacks or special magic spells. Some enemies (such as giant sparrows chicken or cows) must be defeated in order to acquire their costumes and abilities. Changing Rooms are scattered throughout the game and allow the boy to equip Kigurumis and Tailors can store them and customize their abilities if needed. Yume Meikyu Kigurumi Daiboken is a classical dungeon crawler but it however features a random and turned based battle system. Our heroes can punch, kick or use special attacks and a grid displayed over the combat screen allows the player to precisely hit his enemies and, in some cases, even find their weak spots. Once the combat is over, the player is awarded with candies than can be used to purchase new items or be eaten to recover some health.</Plot>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxback1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3af48f83-14cf-4f39-955a-2a1cb77c5631.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/59a8b9c1-3c3e-4fef-a873-c976d3d9316a.jpg</boxart1>
	<media1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/44acd2c1-9189-47dd-b776-42dc47ff0dd0.jpg</media1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6a3c1b2a-140a-4544-864b-42f66deb7e49.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e49d7ad4-7875-47e7-bf46-85984ab2c2b7.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2b4abac5-5e08-4ce1-b438-d1272fd76054.png</snapshot3>
	<Genre>Action; Role-Playing</Genre>
	<Developer>Axes Art Amuse</Developer>
	<Publisher>Hect</Publisher>
</game>