<Game>
	<Name>Zan II Spirits (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Zan II: Spirits is the first Super Famicom game in Wolf Team's series of strategy sims set in historical Japan. It was eventually followed up with a sequel, Zan III: Spirits.As with its thematically-similar contemporaries, like Shingen the Ruler or Nobunaga's Ambition, Zan II puts the player in the geta of a Japanese feudal lord, or daimyo, with designs to wrest control over the rest of Japan from the other daimyos. The game is more focused on warfare than day-to-day resource management, with armies of samurai marching across the map to attack fortresses and pagodas that host enemy flags.	</plot>
	<releasedate>29/5/1992</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Wolf Team</Developer>
	<VideoURL>EGulgb2YPnk</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/570842-zan-ii-spirits</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/zan-ii-spirits/3030-44032/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/01wfEZR.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/BOy3r5S.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/gVoWihr.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/gfwqb22.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/wzIMxpO.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/oYnLLFD.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/8XlOSjh.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/jWX8Smb.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/3FUdRtm.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/rkhaP60.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/sPAJDHm.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/cDgKjMV.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>A Super Famicom strategy war sim from Wolf Team. It is set in the Sengoku era of Japanese history. Zan II: Spirits is the first Super Famicom game in Wolf Team's series of strategy sims set in historical Japan. It was eventually followed up with a sequel, Zan III: Spirits. As with its thematically-similar contemporaries, like Shingen the Ruler or Nobunaga's Ambition, Zan II puts the player in the geta of a Japanese feudal lord, or daimyo, with designs to wrest control over the rest of Japan from the other daimyos. The game is more focused on warfare than day-to-day resource management, with armies of samurai marching across the map to attack fortresses and pagodas that host enemy flags.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8d01f315-187f-4c0f-bf83-ab2db39b2191.jpg</boxart3>
</game>