<Game>
	<Name>Zero 4 Champ RR (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Zero-4 Champ RR is a drag-racing game from Media Rings Corporation and the third game in their Zero-4 Champ series. The game features a story mode that has the young protagonist attempting to make a name for themselves in the underworld street racing circuit, specifically the "Zero-4" (or "Zeroyon" - a shortened version of 0-400m, the standard length of the drag races in the game). The game also features a standard racing mode.Zero-4 Champ RR is the first of two Super Famicom games in this series. It was followed by Zero-4 Champ RR-Z in 1995.Cheat: Get the most expensive tunning part Traction C for free!Go to the pit shop. When the keeper greets you a "irasshaimase" (Welcome), hold down X, and press left, up, down, down, up, right, up, down, down, up, right, up, down, and down, and then release X.  You now have the "torakushon C" (Traction C) installed in your car.Cheat: Beyond any cars limit--unlock the jet engine!Start a new game from the very beginning of the story mode. You will have to enter a name for your hero from the bunch of Japanese letters.Cheat: Beyond any cars limit--unlock the jet engine!Now enter the following Japanese hiraganas: MaKeINu. You will now have the jet engine. Select it in your dining room. Later in the races, press L and R at the same time to activate your jet engine. Your car is now ultrafast!Cheat: Beyond any cars limit--unlock the jet engine!By entering the name "Go Ki Bu Ri- Na" in hiragana when the Story mode starts, you can enter the sound test mode. Cheat: Beyond any cars limit--unlock the jet engine!Start a new game with the Story Mode. Enter the name "Me Mo Ri" in katakana and then "Ke Shi Te" in hiragana, that's "MeMoRi(katakana) KeShiTe(hiragana)".Cheat: Beyond any cars limit--unlock the jet engine!Boom! All your game saves are now gone!Cheat: Beyond any cars limit--unlock the jet engine!Start a new game, enter the name "Ra N Ku" in katakana and then "Ke Shi Te" in hiragana, that's "RaNKu(katakana) KeShiTe(hiragana)", which lietrally means "rank erase" or "erase rankings", all of you fastest records will be erased. Cheat: Beyond any cars limit--unlock the jet engine!Start a new game with the story mode and the game will prompt you to enter a name for your hero. Now enter the Japanese hiragana "OKaNeMoChi" which literally means "Money Have". Cheat: Beyond any cars limit--unlock the jet engine!After the cutscenes, you are now in your hero's room. Your revenue has been raised up to 30,000,000 Yen!</plot>
	<releasedate>22/7/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Arcade</genre>
	<Developer>Media Rings</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>W6UpxxYmEpw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26321</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581826-zero-4-champ-rr</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/zero4-champ-rr</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/zero4-champ-rr/3030-49619/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/mtZsq3p.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/tNLCQcv.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/9Hmmt90.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/Xr7C956.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/rb8hCTB.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/dxCbx4q.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/kn5aw5x.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Xf3eLJ8.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/290DgQD.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/9erfwEA.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/GkYpxYD.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/O5mtw8V.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/wQrCscZ.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/ewjDSfu.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Zero4 Champ RR (ゼロヨンチャンプ ダブルアール) is a 1994 racing video game developed by Media Rings for the Super Famicom, about an 18-year-old race car driver who must chase his dreams of drag racing after being turned down for university (and becoming a rōnin due to his joblessness status). Because the game takes place in the "near future" and it was released in the mid-1990s, the game itself is referring the story of the game to the first decade of the 21st century. This game received a sequel in the form of Zero4 Champ RR-Z.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/56da156d-aaf4-4e65-b6cf-32e3fccf550d.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a75c1348-8781-4b78-b7ea-ed44858e4e75.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Media Rings Corporation</Publisher>
</game>