<Game>
	<Name>Zero 4 Champ RR-Z (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Zero-4 Champ RR-Z is a Driving game, published by Media Rings,which was released in Japan in 1995.Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!Start a new game with the STORY mode. Right after the starting scene, you will be in your new dining room where the game gives you options to customize its colors.Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!There are five options for your dining room; they are (in order): Kabe (Wall), Ka-ten (Curtain), Ka-petto (Carpet), Sofa- (Sofa), and Posuta- (Poster). You will have to choose a color for each of them.Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!Choose Wall=kiiro (yellow), Curtain=midoriiro (green), Carpet=kiiro (yellow), Sofa=kiiro(yellow), and Poster=Shu-ru (Surreal).Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!Your money will then be raised to 30 million yen!Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!Start a new game. When the screen prompts you to enter a name for your hero, enter the Japanese hiragana:GoBuRinThen when you enter the combats with your party members, you will never die!Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!Start the story mode of the game. You will have to enter a name for your character. Enter "Do-H-Ga-Me" in Japanese hiragana, which literally means "dumb tortoise".Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!Then when you have control over the character's action in his dining room, choose the option "Dogu o Tsukau", which means "Use an Item". And then choose "Jetoenjin", which is a phonetic borrowing of the words "Jet Engine". Then your car will have excessively strong power on the wet course!Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!Start a new game with the stroy mode. The game will invite you to enter a name for your hero, now enter the Japanese katakana: RonRonRon. Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!When you have control over your hero's action in his dining room, choose the option DouguoTsukau (use an item). You will have all the items that allow you to win automatically in the mahjong contest.Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!Start a new game. When the game prompts you to customize your hero's dining room, enter the following options in order:Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!Kabe (Wall) -- Shiro (White)Kaaten (Curtain) -- Kuro (Black)Kaapetto (Carpet) -- Kuro  (Black)Sofaa (Sofa) -- Aka  (Red)Posutaa (Poster) -- Suupaakaa (Super car)(It matters not if you can\'t read Japanese letters and Chinese characters, you can tell from the picture.)Cheat: Get tons of easy money just by cheating in your dining room!Now you can purchase the hidden car Zero1 in the showroom at any time!  Cheat: The ultimate racer--Fannicar!Reach the very last race against the champion. Lose to the champion 10 times. Go back to the showroom and you can now purchase the ultimate overpowered car--the Fannicar. No car can stand a chance against your Fannicar now!</plot>
	<releasedate>25/11/1995</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Arcade</genre>
	<Developer>Media Rings</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>0nuazLkW8iE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26322</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/581827-zero-4-champ-rr-z</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/zero4-champ-rrz</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/zero4-champ-rr/3030-49619/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/lrtVRi6.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/tNLCQcv.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/9Hmmt90.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/xdu06mV.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/yaaARYB.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/HV8ISfR.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/l4B0f6Z.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/Vagx8uQ.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/GGZC2g5.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/va4srO9.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/D7QGkYt.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/MNqbv3I.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/fwVcYJm.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/K7YmPq6.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Zero4 Champ RR-Z (ゼロヨンチャンプ ダブルアール・ヅィー Double R Dzui Zero Yon Chanpu) is a 1995 racing video game developed by Media Rings for the Super Famicom, and is the sequel to Zero4 Champ RR.</Notes>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/62ab03a4-fa73-49b3-a9c7-491cea583d03.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/edbee4f9-4307-48a0-944b-0b72589f9a01.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Media Rings Corporation</Publisher>
</game>