<Game>
	<Name>Zico Soccer (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Zico Soccer is a 1994 soccer simulation game featuring the likeness of famous mononymmed Brazilian soccer player Zico. Rather than controlling the soccer players directly, the player acts as the lead coach and must direct the soccer players on the field with the mouse cursor. They can tell specific players where to go, when to shoot and to whom to pass. The game uses the SNES Mouse peripheral.The game features international sides, with the single exception of the Japanese league team the Kashima Antlers, for whom Zico was playing at the time. The player can choose to play single exhibition matches or in a cup tournament.The game was a Super Famicom exclusive. Despite the international sports focus, and the likeness of a foreign soccer star, it remained Japan-only. It uses the name of EA Sports, but was actually created by EA Victor: a joint venture between Electronic Arts and the Japanese game company Victor Entertainment.TeamsIt featured the following national teams:Commonwealth of Independent States (CIS) - An international team created for Euro 1992 comprised of former Soviet Union states.DenmarkMoroccoJapanBrazilSpainBelgiumUnited States of AmericaFranceNorwayNigeriaRomaniaNetherlandsCameroonSwitzerlandMexicoArgentinaItalyColombiaGreeceWest GermanySwedenBoliviaSouth KoreaKashima Antlers</plot>
	<releasedate>4/3/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts Victor</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>7hT81wFsNQA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26320</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571045-zico-soccer</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/zico-soccer</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/zico-soccer/3030-37604/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/DZb75a1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/HcDgucW.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/eKkCzL7.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/PBPN5MY.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/Ql0gzt2.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/iz4SiIz.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/flaGcmO.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/PUs5fYG.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/slbLe69.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/MVevSzs.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Qa4RlWp.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/RUvgQig.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WSSKPzH.gif</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>http://i.imgur.com/mQA7u7E.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Zico Soccer (ジーコ サッカー) from Electronic Arts is a Super Famicom football management video game that allows players to become the head coach of an international football team; it was named after the modern-day soccer legend Zico (also known as the White Pelé). The game is mostly in the Japanese language although some words are in the English language.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/43e91438-cd85-4cc9-8590-8d1f8df3c003.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a4f9bce9-a5e0-45de-9b7d-3c58d3263888.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts Victor</Publisher>
</game>