<Game>
	<Name>Zig Zag Cat - Dachou Club mo Oosawagi da (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Restoring the lands from evil, saving the princess, and finding a way back home might not be the most original of goals, but how many games also include the comedy stylings of Japanese performance group Dachou Club? Not many, that's for sure!Zig Zag Cat is an unusual fusion of Breakout and a scrolling shooter. During action stages the player's avatar walks forward while attempting to keep their cat from bouncing off the bottom of the screen. The cat can break most obstacles by hitting them, and all obstacles will be broken if they collide with the avatar. By breaking blocks money and temporary paddle upgrades can be uncovered, such as ones that increase the size or the paddle, let you fire bullets, or allow you to curve the cat while it is moving. Several times during each stage a black octopus block will appear, and it must be destroyed by the cat before the player's avatar will continue moving forward. While the avatar is totally unharmed from walking through any enemies or blocks, some enemies and all bosses have the ability to fire projectiles at him which do cause damage, and if all health is lost from projectiles then a life will be lost just as if the cat had fallen off the screen.In between action stages the player will enter an Inn. At the Inn he can save, talk to the locals, play a bonus board to earn additional money, buy temporary paddle upgrades, and check his progress on his trip around the island.</plot>
	<releasedate>24/6/1994</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Den'Z</Developer>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/571082-zig-zag-cat</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/snes/zig-zag-cat-dach-club-mo-oosawagi-da</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/zig-zag-cat/3030-37540/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4sdlfGN.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/azbD1CD.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://i.imgur.com/p6ZMX9t.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://i.imgur.com/VfgmUYm.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://i.imgur.com/ZlosmwF.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://i.imgur.com/Kj4oqDa.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://i.imgur.com/uIYAneE.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://i.imgur.com/Jnj3kpk.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://i.imgur.com/hv1sjzG.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://i.imgur.com/wj1vm5h.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://i.imgur.com/Ae0839f.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://i.imgur.com/LebYbht.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>A puzzle-action game featuring a young hero and his shapeshifting cat. The gameplay is a mixture of a vertical-scrolling shoot 'em up and Breakout. The player can collect money, which unlocks various bonuses, as well as Arkanoid-style power-ups that include a fireball that will go straight through blocks instead of being deflected. They can also send the bat forward a short distance, which helps to collect items, defeat enemies and hit the ball.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/024abb5a-a56a-4629-87c6-f0c1030f0cf4.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eeff4637-958d-4459-a533-92351a33371b.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fbde5da5-dabb-4467-921a-de92c1adcc8e.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b5f46d32-698e-42e8-8f07-44ad9f6a3c97.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Den'Z</Publisher>
</game>