<Game>
	<Name>90 Minutes - Sega Championship Football (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>A soccer game developed by Smilebit for the Dreamcast.  It was only released in Europe. </plot>
	<releasedate>25/10/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Europe Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>29249</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/90-minutes/3030-45187/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/29249-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/549379-90-minutes-sega-championship-football-dreamcast-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/549386-90-minutes-sega-championship-football-dreamcast-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/549387-90-minutes-sega-championship-football-dreamcast-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/549380-90-minutes-sega-championship-football-dreamcast-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/549381-90-minutes-sega-championship-football-dreamcast-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/549382-90-minutes-sega-championship-football-dreamcast-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/549383-90-minutes-sega-championship-football-dreamcast-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/549384-90-minutes-sega-championship-football-dreamcast-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/549385-90-minutes-sega-championship-football-dreamcast-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Notes>90 minutes is a traditional action football game, featuring 7 leagues (England, France, Germany, Italy, Spain, plus an assortment of clubs from around the world) and national teams. While there are no team licenses, most players feature real names and there's also a player and team editor, allowing to change name and number of players, who's in each national team, as well as creating teams from scratch, including its players. Gameplay follows the norms of the genre - A to pass, B to throw a high lob, X to shoot, Y to change players, with the triggers to perform modifiers (though passes and lob shots) and sprint, although these can all be changed in the options. The player can also assign special tactics to each direction on the d-pad to adapt quickly according to the flow of the game. Game modes include the usual - World Championship (based on the world cup), as well as national leagues and cups (as well as a customizable cup), with secret teams waiting to be unlocked by those who win them, exhibition and training. Options are also the usual on these kind of games - change half lenght (3,5 or 10 minutes), opponent level and game speed. At gametime, players can also choose the weather, time of day, and between 10 cameras. There are six stadiums to choose from, inspired by venues such as the old Wembley Stadium, the Nou Camp or the ArenA in Amsterdam.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/22a27505-4ca7-42f6-9aba-48217157337d.jpg</boxart2>
</game>