<Game>
	<Name>Alienfront Online (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: Alien Front Online was developed by Wow Entertainment and published by Sega. The game was one of the last games released for the Dreamcast. It is notable for being the first console game to utilize voice chat for online play.Story: Aliens have invaded Earth. Kill them, or... play as the enemy. The game allows you to play as either humans protecting Earth or the aliens invading it. The game has little story truth be told, it was largely focused on online deathmatches. There is a single player mode in which you complete missions, however it is more of an afterthought and was meant as practice for the online play.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/9/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>2411</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/alien-front-online/3030-20140/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2411-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/852201-914120_19631_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/47067-alien-front-online-dreamcast-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/47068-alien-front-online-dreamcast-screenshot-tank-selection.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/47069-alien-front-online-dreamcast-screenshot-siberia.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/47070-alien-front-online-dreamcast-screenshot-tokyo.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/47071-alien-front-online-dreamcast-screenshot-in-the-desert-near.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/47072-alien-front-online-dreamcast-screenshot-the-island.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/47073-alien-front-online-dreamcast-screenshot-washington-d-c.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/47074-alien-front-online-dreamcast-screenshot-playing-as-the-aliens.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/221/1364100-afo3.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/221/1364099-afo2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Alien Front Online is a Dreamcast video game originally released for the console in 2001. In the game, players use armored vehicles to fight tense battles staged in large, interactive arenas. Players could choose which side they wished to fight for, the aliens or the human defenders of Earth, and could also choose one of three different vehicles to combat with; each having its own advantages and disadvantages. Although Alien Front was fully playable for one person, it was primarily designed as an online game in which up to 8 players (up to 4 on each side) could battle it out. Players move around the arena attempting to blast each other with their weaponry, while also looking for power-ups that will enhance their ability to wreak massive destruction. Typically, the game was played for a set number of minutes, after which the team with the most kills would be declared the winners. Being killed while playing the game had no serious consequences (you simply respawned in a different part of the area you were in), but it did reflect on your win/loss score.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bbada1dd-b336-4915-a700-ea4b353914f6.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/923462a9-ed86-4b7b-88c6-811be061ccbd.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>