<Game>
	<Name>Armada (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Ten millennia after the initial wave of colonization of the universe, humans have developed into distinct races adapting to their newfound homes. While there is peace between the races, there is no sense of unity. This all changes when, without warning, a bio-mechanical Armada wages war on the whole of humanity. Now as a starship captain representing one of the six main races of humanity, your charge is to take the fight to the Armada and save humanity.Gameplay: consists of commanding a starship as you explore the universe, taking out Armada opposition where you see it. Along the way you can take missions and answer calls for help which will provide you with valuable experience and credits to upgrade your ship. In this way, you can build your strength until you are ready to take on the Armada full force in an attempt to end the threat once and for all.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/11/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Metro3D, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>4+</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3522</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/armada/3030-7164/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3522-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59326-armada-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59328-armada-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/3csbUyQ.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Armada is a video game that was released for the Sega Dreamcast in 1999. Earth has been destroyed by the unfathomable Armada, giant space aliens of unknown origin with unknown purpose. Fleeing in whatever was available, humanity took to the stars in a desperate attempt to survive. Eons later, humans have split into 6 distinct groups who maintain a shaky alliance against the Armada. An Asteroids-like RPG, Armada was a sci-fi shooter that allowed 1-4 players to fly about the universe, fighting the enemy, performing missions and improving their ship. The player would gather credits to buy power-ups for their ship, allowing them to voyage deeper into enemy territory, blow up ever more powerful Armada, and perform missions of increasing importance and danger as the alliance fights not only for answers as to why the Armada attack, but for their very lives.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/209ef0e5-b981-45d1-8f58-d5627600a7b5.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/181b7962-75ba-4703-aac0-530b6c894845.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/47127d14-58bc-4474-bbec-a30267da96c9.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d5062f0-1736-49d2-bc6c-acd068f8611d.png</snapshot2>
	<Publisher>Metro3D, Inc.</Publisher>
</game>