<Game>
	<Name>Army Men - Sarge's Heroes (USA)</Name>
	<plot>One morning Sarge is resting in his cot when the Tan launch a surprise attack on the Green base.  Sarge and the Colonel are forced to retreat just as the base is overrun.  But in the chaos, Sarge's entire team of elite soldiers has been kidnapped by the Tan.  Worse yet, the Tan have made an amazing discovery: blue portals that lead to the real world!  They use these portals to take amazing weapons of war from the real world into the plastic world including magnifying glasses, deadly robot action figures, and fire crackers.  Its up to you, as Sarge, to rescue your team and put an end to the blue portals and Tan's evil schemes.Control Sarge in this Army Man third-person shooter.  You will wage war across Tan-infested territories, both in the real and plastic world. Make Sarge proud as you battle the Tan army across 14 levels, utilizing 13 unique weapons like sky rockets and spray cans. Fight against not only infantrymen, tanks, and helicopters, but also killer toy robots and insects.  This third game in the Army Men series adds several new features, including 3DO's unique Plastosheen lighting effects, which give the army men a real-life plastic shine. Also included is a multiplayer mode.  Choose your character and even your color and duke it out with your friends.  You can choose from many different weapons and battle each other in areas from the game or exclusive multiplayer levels.  Even incorporated is the portal system, where you can enter blue portals and come out anywhere in the level.Relive those childhood fantasies, yet again.  Don't you just love the smell of burnt plastic in the morning?</plot>
	<releasedate>16/11/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Midway Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>8106</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/army-men-sarges-heroes/3030-11157/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8106-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/86329-army-men-sarge-s-heroes-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/86330-army-men-sarge-s-heroes-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/855898-gfs_41716_2_11_mid.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/855897-gfs_41716_2_10_mid.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/855896-gfs_41716_2_9_mid.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/855895-gfs_41716_2_8_mid.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/855894-gfs_41716_2_7_mid.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/855893-gfs_41716_2_6_mid.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/855892-gfs_41716_2_5_mid.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/855891-gfs_41716_2_4_mid.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/855890-gfs_41716_2_3_mid.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/855889-gfs_41716_2_2_mid.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8106-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/HOVb3IL.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Campaign is the main mode of Sarge's Heroes. The player plays as Sarge, the protagonist for many of the Army Men games. The player travels through several missions, completing objectives, killing enemies, destroying vehicles, and rescuing people. The plot starts out as the Tan Army is invading the Green Army base. Sarge rescues Colonel Grimm and they evacuate the base in a helicopter. In the game, Sarge discovers portals that lead from the "plastic world" to the "real world". The Tan Army is getting "Weapons of Mass Destruction" from the "real world" (toys and ordinary objects, i.e. magnifying glass). Throughout the game, Sarge rescues commandos of his own unit, Bravo Company. Sometimes they are in Tan bases, and other times he has to go through portals and save them from the "real world". To avoid the destruction of the Green Army, Sarge must destroy the portals and stop Plastro.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e99c784c-8a87-449b-9c4f-726f9d96f02c.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b891be91-d703-4de2-a94c-301d410f8ed3.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/81f93fc4-7d2b-449f-bfc9-6bd333178987.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>5</rating>
	<Publisher>Midway</Publisher>
</game>