<Game>
	<Name>Atari Anniversary Edition (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The Atari Anniversary Edition features 12 classic Atari games, whereby two versions of this game exits. One for Dreamcast/Windows and the other one for PlayStation.The Dreamcast/Windows version features the following games:1. AsteroidsAsteroids DeluxeBattlezoneCentipedeCrystal CastlesGravitarMillipedeMissile CommandPongSuper BreakoutTempestWarlordsThe PlayStation version features these games:1. AsteroidsAsteroids DeluxeBattlezoneBlack WidowCentipedeGravitarMissile CommandPongSpace DuelSuper BreakoutTempestWarlordsNote: the bold games are those that are just in the one version, but not in the other one.In addition to the pure emulation modes, there is an option to display the cabinet art surrounding the display of each game, intended to give the player a sense of actually playing a stand-up machine. Each game also has a toggle for an "enhanced" graphical mode, which varies from game to game. For instance, "enhanced" asteroids merely has a static backdrop, whereas "enhanced" warlords is a complete graphical overhaul with new colors. It should be noted that the "enhanced" version of Tempest is none other than Tempest Tubes, a modification for Tempest made in 1982 by Duncan Brown.Also included is a gallery of game memorabilia, video clips of an interview with Nolan Bushnell, and desktop themes for Windows.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/6/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing, Simulation, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Infogrames Interactive, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>8108</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/atari-anniversary-edition/3030-14298/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8108-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/61745-atari-anniversary-edition-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/61746-atari-anniversary-edition-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8108-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<Notes>The Dreamcast/Windows version features the following games: •Asteroids  •Asteroids Deluxe  •Battlezone  •Centipede  •Crystal Castles  •Gravitar  •Millipede  •Missile Command  •Pong  •Super Breakout  •Tempest  •Warlords</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/91df1108-190e-467d-ae81-cdf15a7c819b.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Infrogrames</Publisher>
</game>