<Game>
	<Name>Bomberman Online (USA)</Name>
	<plot>GAME MODESSurvival Mode - This mode is your standard bomberman, last one alive wins the matchHyper Bomberman - Collect 3 Target Items then make your way to the gate for the winPanel Paint - Your flames paint the panels with the color of your bomberman, the one with the most panels winsSubmarine - This for 2 teams of 2. The battle field is divided in half, when you lay your bombs on your side, it counts down then is sent like a torpedo to the corresponding sideRing Mode - A small battle field 5 x 7, with no blocks to hide around, no power ups, just one bomb. Bombs also fall from the sky. Set fire to your opponents to score a ring out, the most right outs at the end of the time wins.Other Info1-4 playersOnline Multiplayer/ Modem compatibleVMU compatible: 5 blocksVGA box compatible</plot>
	<releasedate>30/10/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>8109</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bomberman-online/3030-18180/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8109-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/8109-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/21142-bomberman-online-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46517-bomberman-online-dreamcast-screenshot-intro-sequence-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46518-bomberman-online-dreamcast-screenshot-intro-sequence-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46519-bomberman-online-dreamcast-screenshot-intro-sequence-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46520-bomberman-online-dreamcast-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46521-bomberman-online-dreamcast-screenshot-a-step-up-from-the-nes.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46522-bomberman-online-dreamcast-screenshot-all-honest-fun.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46523-bomberman-online-dreamcast-screenshot-victory.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46524-bomberman-online-dreamcast-screenshot-there-are-different-scenarios.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46525-bomberman-online-dreamcast-screenshot-death-is-not-the-end.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14355/2470322-bombo023.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8109-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8je2SJV.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Bomberman Online brings gamers the same addictive battles as in other Bomberman games in the form of online multiplayer puzzles. Players progress through different levels attempting to destroy their opponents by strategically planting bombs and running for cover. Each playing field is constructed out of both destructible and indestructible walls, and it's up to you to position bombs in the right place at the right time. The action gets frantic as alliances and rivalries are made and then broken. Intense battles unfold online when you connect to the Internet and play other Bomberman Online users in Internet battle mode. The new screen-scroll option displays a larger map, making it possible for numerous players to skillfully battle it out at the same time. Five new stages and four new ways to play add to the fun, creating an endless chain reaction of unique and dramatic battles!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b81f68f-4a08-429f-812d-afd65198104d.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9d3bece9-1e24-4176-9cb8-1d90b6c6461b.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>