<Game>
	<Name>Bust-A-Move 4 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The 4th edition of Bust-A-Move adds some great new characters to choose from, as well as a Story mode, where you win Tarrot cards from each puzzle you complete. Player VS. CPU has two different modes: Story mode sees a story unfold as you defeat each CPU character (and changes depending on the character you start with) and Win Contest is a simple "how many games can I win in a row" against the computer. Finally, if you complete the Challenge mode (where you must complete certain puzzels as fast as possible, and get judged on technique, speed etc.) the Edit mode will become available. In here you can put together your own puzzles for you or your friends to complete.</plot>
	<releasedate>6/1/2000</releasedate>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>23234</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bust-a-move-4/3030-1263/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/23234-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/23234-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/152750-bust-a-move-4-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/23234-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/23234-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ckV9FeS.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Puzzle Bobble 4 (also known as Bust-a-Move 4 in North America and Europe) is the third sequel to the video game Puzzle Bobble and is the final appearance of the series on the Arcade, PlayStation and Dreamcast. The game is also the final title to be recognizably similar in presentation to the original. Building upon the success of Puzzle Bobble 3, the game adds a pulley system that requires two sets of bubbles, attached to either side of a rope hanging across two pulleys. The game contains a story mode for single player play.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ecbfbc88-d589-4936-89f1-365b2a26e2fe.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bd6b76fc-bb12-4196-b2d9-e5cf07f49026.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3fc96304-a740-401b-a095-8de91b3a35c5.jpg</snapshot3>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Publisher>Natsume</Publisher>
</game>