<Game>
	<Name>Capcom vs. SNK - Millennium Fight 2000 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Capcom vs. SNK: Millennium Fight 2000 is a 2D fighting game developed and distributed by Capcom for arcades (using the Sega NAOMI hardware) in 2000.Capcom's first offering in their crossover series with SNK, the game pits fighters from both Capcom's Street Fighter series and SNK's King of Fighters series in a massive worldwide martial arts tournament. Building on the team elimination mechanic from King of Fighters, the game introduces the "Ratio" system (in which players form different-sized teams from fighters of different strengths). It also introduces a new "Groove" system (in which players can choose between two different variations of super meters), a "Groove Point System" (a real-time ranking system for single-player mode that raises and lowers as the player fights), and a special "EX" version of most characters (changing their movelists).The game was later ported to the Dreamcast on November 9, 2000, adding color edit support, training mode, a variety of unlockable secret features, and Neo Geo Pocket Color support (allowing players to unlock secrets quicker when paired with SNK vs. Capcom: Match of the Millennium, both versions of SNK vs. Capcom: Card Fighter's Clash, and SNK vs. Capcom: Card Fighters 2 Expand Edition). The arcade version was updated a year later as Capcom vs SNK: Millennium Fight 2000 Pro, making use of the GD-ROM upgrade for the Sega NAOMI while adding two new characters (Dan Hibiki and Joe Higashi) and new moves for existing characters. This version was also ported to both the Dreamcast (in 2001, only in Japan) and the PlayStation (in 2002, as Capcom's final PS1 release).Capcom later developed a sequel, called Capcom vs SNK 2: Mark of the Millennium 2001, which builds upon the "Ratio" and "Groove" systems while adding new characters, 3D backgrounds, and new game mechanics. SNK's main entry in the series, SNK Vs. Capcom: Chaos, was planned to be released at the same time as this game, but was delayed for years after the company went bankrupt.Gameplay:Capcom vs. SNK: Millennium Fight 2000 plays like a traditional Capcom fighting game, using only four buttons (instead of their traditional six button layout): Light Punch, Hard Punch, Light Kick, and Hard Kick.Some of the fighting game mechanics included are rolling (performed by pressing both Light buttons simultaneously, giving the character temporary invincibility), throw escapes (performed by performing a Throw command while being grabbed by normal throws, cancelling the throw), super jumps (performed by tapping Down before jumping, giving the character a faster and higher jump), and dashing (performed by tapping Forward or Back twice, allowing characters to dodge attacks and close the gap between them). In the console versions, players can unlock running forward as a replacement for dashing (allowing players to close the gap quicker).Ratio SystemAn update to the team elimination style of the King of Fighters series (in which players must eliminate all of their opponent team's fighters sequentially, with no health regeneration between rounds), the "Ratio" system gives each player four "Ratio Points" to form their team with. Characters are separated into four strength tiers (Light, Average, Strong, Strongest), which affects both their offensive and defensive power. There are five combinations of teams that can be used:One R-4.One R-3, one R-1.Two R-2's.One R-2, two R-1's.Four R-1's.A hidden mode (unlocked in the console version as "Pair Match Mode") puts all characters in R-2 (changing their strength to match), simplifying the game into 2-on-2 team battles. This mode also allows players to pick the same character for both teammates.Groove SystemBefore selecting their characters, each player picks one of two "Grooves" to fight with. Each Groove changes the way the Super Meter is used during the fight (as well as changing the art style used for character portraits).Capcom Groove - Based on the early Street Fighter Alpha games (as well as A-Ism in Street Fighter Alpha 3), players are given a three-level Super Meter that is slowly replenished by hitting their opponent and performing special moves. They can perform different levels of their Super Moves, as long as they have enough meter to perform, by pressing different buttons for the move (Light for Lv. 1, Hard for Lv. 2, Light+Hard for Lv. 3). Some Super Moves can only be performed at Lv. 3.SNK Groove - Based on the early King of Fighters games (as well as Extra mode in The King of Fighters '97 and The King of Fighters '98: The Slugfest), players are given one large Super Meter that can only be replenished by charging (holding both Hard buttons simultaneously). Once the meter is full, MAX mode activates and the fighter gets increased attack power as the meter slowly depletes. Players can perform their Super Move either during MAX mode (which fully depletes the meter) or when their vitality is low (as shown with a blinking vitality meter). When their vitality is low and MAX mode is active, they can perform a more powerful version of the Super Move (known as MAX Super Move). Some Super Moves can only be performed as MAX Super Moves.Characters:The game includes 28 playable fighters from the start, split up into four tiers of strength. All SNK characters are redrawn to fit Capcom's style, while most of Capcom's characters are based on their Street Fighter Alpha sprites (with the exception of Morrigan, who is based on her Darkstalkers sprites, and  Ryu, Ken, Dan, M. Bison, and Akuma, who are redrawn in the same style as the SNK characters).In addition, the game includes two hidden opponents (fought by reaching the fourth stage with no continues, five or more Super Move finishes, and at least 60 GPS) and one hidden boss (fought by reaching the final stage with no continues, ten or more Super Move finishes, and at least 80 HPS). All three hidden characters, along with more powerful versions of Ryu and Iori, are unlockable for play (by the arcade operators).All characters, with the exception of the hidden characters, Ryu, and Iori, have a special "EX" variant (which can be used by holding Start while selecting that character, must be unlocked in the console versions) which change some of their movelists.The "Pro" update to the game adds two additional characters (Dan and Joe) for play, updating the total roster to 35.CapcomAll characters are from the Street Fighter series (with the exception of hidden character Morrigan from the Darkstalkers series).Ratio 1 (Light)BlankaCammyDan (added in the Pro update)DhalsimSakuraRatio 2 (Average)Balrog (M. Bison in the Japanese version)Chun-LiE. HondaGuileKenMorrigan (hidden opponent)RyuZangiefRatio 3 (Strong)M. Bison (boss, Vega in the Japenese version)SagatVega (M. Bison in the Japanese version)Ratio 4 (Strongest)Akuma (hidden boss)Evil Ryu (hidden)SNKAll characters are from the King of Fighters series (with the exception of Raiden from the Fatal Fury series, and hidden character Nakoruru from the Samurai Shodown series).Ratio 1 (Light)BenimaruJoe (added in the Pro update)KingViceYuriRatio 2 (Average)IoriKimKyoMaiNakoruru (hidden opponent)RaidenRyoTerryRatio 3 (Strong)Geese (boss)RugalYamazakiRatio 4 (Strongest)Wild Iori (hidden)</plot>
	<releasedate>11/9/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>14994</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/capcom-vs-snk-millennium-fight-2000/3030-8768/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/14994-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/29473-capcom-vs-snk-dreamcast-inside-cover.jpg</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/29474-capcom-vs-snk-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/14994-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/14994-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/14994-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/283124-capcom-vs-snk-dreamcast-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/283126-capcom-vs-snk-dreamcast-screenshot-menu-screen.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/283192-capcom-vs-snk-dreamcast-screenshot-character-selection.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/640595-capcom-vs-snk-dreamcast-screenshot-one-of-the-funniest-moments.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2180592-cvs1_1.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2180591-cvs1_3.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2180590-cvs1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/14994-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/14994.png</clearlogo1>
</game>