<Game>
	<Name>Chicken Run (Europe) (Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Chicken Run is a 3D platformer movie tie in to the Chicken Run movie. In keeping with the film's story, the game takes place on a 1950s Yorkshire chicken farm and follows a group of chickens as they try to break out of confinement. Players must help Ginger and her flock make a break for freedom while avoiding the evil Mrs. Tweedy and her husband, who want to turn them into chicken pies.The game is set in a 3-D world that reflects the film's stye and design and the gameplay emphasizes stealthy exploration which also fits in with the film. The aim of the game is to sneak your way around the farm and gather objects that are necessary to your escape plan and features vehicles, weaponary and platforming all linked to the stealth gameplay. Throughout the game, there are opportunities to control different characters who star in the film - Ginger, Rocky, Nick, and Fetcher.</plot>
	<releasedate>14/11/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Eidos Interactive, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>TUb4mN5UOzM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>8114</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/chicken-run/3030-9182/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8114-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8114-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/8114.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Tweedy's Farm is home to a bunch of chickens, who are falling behind on their work load (laying eggs). So Mrs Tweedy decides to go into a new business, Chicken Pie making. The chickens leader, Ginger, is in desperate need of a good escape plan, and when Rocky flys in from the US to lend them a hand, the gang decide that the only way out of the farm is to fly out. But of course, chickens can't fly!! So it is up to you to collect the pieces for the flying machine so you and your fellow chickens can escape.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>TUb4mN5UOzM</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/18debf68-9896-4730-a9fb-f7372b2f82a8.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/35e05927-283d-4d4e-91b6-35ab9111db80.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Eidos</Publisher>
</game>