<Game>
	<Name>Coaster Works (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Coaster Works puts the player in the role of a roller coaster engineer, recently hired to help construct several different roller coasters for different amusement parks.The construction part is set up with a screen divided in four camera angles and a grid based building tool. Using vector pieces, the player has to make a roller coaster that meets the requirements of the specific park. The pieces can be tilted, elevated, lowered and turned to make sure the ride is as exciting as possible.After the roller coaster is done it will be tested with a crash test dummy (who's also able to squeal like an excited kid), to make sure it meets such requirements as safety, speed, excitement etc. This is done in a 1st person view, allowing the player to come along for the ride as well.There are 6 different stages, each with different sizes and limitations.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/4/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Xicat Interactive</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>13042</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/coaster-works/3030-38082/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/13042-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/231316-coaster-works-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/257845-coaster-works-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<Notes>Move over tycoons, the baddest coaster in the land is coming straight for the SEGA Dreamcast. Coaster Works serves up much more than your typical roller coaster game. Build your own death defying tracks, or trade them on-line with friends. No matter how you play, hold on, because Coaster Works will be the most intense ride of your life. Ride your own tracks No other roller coaster simulation lets you actually ride the tracks you have created. Coaster Works lets you climb into the hot seat for all the razor-sharp turns, daredevil drops, and stomach-churning loops you can dish out. You can playback the action from multiple viewpoints as well, giving your coaster a whole new life. The Killer G's are back! Advancing to the next level isn't as simple as building a cool track. Your creations are tested under conditions like top speed, safety level, and of course, how many G's they can pull! Not enough force? How about slipping in some serious drops followed by a killer corkscrew. Watch out for your safety level though, because too much force and you'll derail your coaster!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/969358de-d1ca-4d6d-afe9-ec200a125293.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Xicat Interactive</Publisher>
</game>