<Game>
	<Name>Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX is a bike-riding spin-off the Tony Hawk's Pro-Skater Series. Released in 2000, this game takes place on bikes instead of skateboards throughout various locations around the world with huge ramps and dirt tracks. The game was released for the PlayStation, Dreamcast, Game Boy Color, and PC. The story mode takes players through various levels where completing objectives, tricks, and stunts unlocks a variety of gear for their bike.Gameplay:Players ride around various areas pulling off different tricks. The trick system involves pulling off one base trick, and then adapting other modifier tricks into that one base trick. The game features exaggerated movement and ragdoll physics.Four modes are available: Proquest, Free Ride, Session, and two-player (only available in the PlayStation and Dreamcast versions). Each mode has different events and certain tasks to perform. Players can unlock features by beating the game with various characters. As well as this, players can unlock two secret characters: the Slim Jim mascot and an Armish boy.Soundtrack:59 Times the Pain - Got It All in SightCypress Hill - DustDeftones - Be Quiet and Drive (Far Away)Dropkick Murphys - Never AlonePennywise - GreedPrimer 55 - LooseRancid - Maxwell MurderSocial Distortion - Don't Drag Me DownSublime - What I GotSwingin' Utters - Stupid LullabiesVision - Don't Sound the Alarm</plot>
	<releasedate>21/11/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>23949</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx/3030-9243/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/23949-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/54313-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/54314-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/192314-davemfpc_006_large.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/192313-davemfpc_005_large.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/192311-davemfpc_004_large.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/192306-davemfpc_002_large.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/192304-davemfpc_001_large.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/192301-b_6.jpg</snapshot6>
</game>