<Game>
	<Name>Daytona USA (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The game should not be confused with the recent PSN/XBLA release, which is actually an update of the  original arcade version.CoursesThere are eight courses in Daytona USA, each of which have a mirror, reverse, and mirror reverse version. Five courses return from previous games and three tracks are new for this version.Three Seven Speedway (returning from the  original arcade game)Dinosaur Canyon (returning from the  original arcade game)Sea-Side Street Galaxy (returning from the  original arcade game)National Park Speedway (returning from  Daytona USA: Championship Circuit Edition)Desert City (returning from  Daytona USA: Championship Circuit Edition)Circuit Pixie (exclusive new course)Rin Rin Rink (exclusive new course)Mermaid Lake (exclusive new course)CarsThere was only one car in the original Daytona USA.In  CCE there were nine different cars to choose from, each with different attributes for Grip, Acceleration, and Top Speed. Selectable cars return in this version but with an entirely new cast of ten cars to choose from. Four of the cars are available from the start, and the other six are unlockable through fulfilling certain conditions.Car NameUnlock ConditionsGripAccelerationMax Speed Hornet available from the start707070 Grasshopper available from the start904030 Falcon available from the start805050 Lightning available from the start508080 Unicorn beat championship mode359090 Red Cat win an online race608065 Pywackett Barchetta finish one race with each  original car in single race mode858040   Rule of the 9th beat track records for all mirror reverse tracks in single race mode508585 Javelin accumulate 100 hours of game time20100100 Pywackett Barchetta SuperFinish a race by turning around andgoing backwards with the Pywackett Barchettain single race mode1006045There are several options after selecting a car, including choosing automatic or manual transmission, the level of tire inflation, and car color. There is a separate menu in which 3 different color slots can be edited.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/3/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Corporation</Developer>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>7766</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/daytona-usa/3030-225/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/7766-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/190097-daytona-usa-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/190098-daytona-usa-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46526-daytona-usa-dreamcast-screenshot-intro-attract.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46527-daytona-usa-dreamcast-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46528-daytona-usa-dreamcast-screenshot-in-game-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46529-daytona-usa-dreamcast-screenshot-in-game-2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46530-daytona-usa-dreamcast-screenshot-in-the-pits.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/46531-daytona-usa-dreamcast-screenshot-crash.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/12/125705/1990400-9490620111018_084243_13_big.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/12/125705/1990399-9490620111018_084243_12_big.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/12/125705/1990398-9490620111018_084243_11_big.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/12/125705/1990397-9490620111018_084243_10_big.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/7766-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/2P6PssL.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/7766.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Just like the arcade version, pick one of three tracks (beginner, advanced, or expert) and either automatic or standard transmission. A pounding music soundtrack kicks in as you are slapped into your car to await the green light. The game offers both a traditional arcade mode with checkpoint time splits and a special PC mode that pits you against the other cars over different race distances. The PC mode also offers more car choices, with a variety of speed, acceleration, and grip characteristics. It even rewards successful players (meaning those finishing first, second, or third in the difficult setting) by offering up to ten more upgraded cars to drive. Once underway, the goal is to work from last to first as smoothly and quickly as possible</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8507582f-d112-435e-a81e-512ee3aabb55.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7b34e92a-26e5-4ceb-a610-d138cd180448.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b7412dec-280d-4d9e-9b66-c670bf9038f4.png</clearlogo2>
	<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a48f9f84-5e65-4c6f-bf43-0adc827ce219.png</clearlogo3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/119ed052-2f62-4a18-bede-d7d6fd32cc45.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/db4cfb0b-ce9f-4a65-8ffb-8c894386a98a.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>