<Game>
	<Name>Dead or Alive 2 (Japan) (Shokai Genteiban)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dead or Alive 2 is a fighting game published by      Tecmo and developed by      Team Ninja.  It made its debut in arcades in October 1999 and was released on      Dreamcast in February the following year, followed eight months later by a Playstation 2 launch. In 2004 it would be released for the  Xbox as  Dead or Alive Ultimate, which contained online play, and an upgrade in graphics and additional features.It was very popular and shortly after the release for the      Playstation 2, another version was released, it was called      Dead or Alive 2: Hardcore. Changes would include, added stages, more unlockable outfits, cutscene framerate increased from 30 to 60 Frames Per Second, as well as english voiceovers. A final update titled Dead or Alive 2: Hard*Core was released in Japan only and featured slight gameplay tweaks as well as more costumes.Gameplay: Bashing the opponent against a wall. Dead or Alive 2 followed the first one in terms of dangerzones and the tempo of the gameplay, it remained as fast and as twitchy all while improving graphics as well as character roster, and added character abilities. As well as new moves for the characters and the improved graphics Dead or Alive 2 was the first versus-fighting game to include walls on the various stages. Walls would stop you from knocking your opponent out of the ring (ala      Virtua Fighter), while still confining the fight to a small area. The game continued the      Rock-Paper-Scissors gameplay from the first title to stand out from the rest of the at the time popular fighting games (Tekken and Virtua Fighter). The Rock-Scissors-Paper system is still in use in the fourth release of Dead or Alive ( DOA4) on the      Xbox 360. In Dead or Alive, they introduced Offensive Holds (OH) which LOOKS like a Regular throw, but plays different. Offensive Holds executed when an opponent would strike you with a regular attack, would avoid the opponents attack and throw them, dealing damage in the process. Offensive Holds however, executed when an opponent would initiate a Regular Throw, would lose to the Throw and as a result you would be taking quite a bit of damage from their Throw. Regular Throws executed when an opponent would strike you with a normal attack would be ineffective, and you would take damage from their blow.Quickly described:Offensive Holds &gt; Attacks &gt; ThrowsThrows &gt; Offensive Holds &gt; AttacksAttacks &gt; Throws &gt; Offensive HoldsOther InfoDreamcastPlayers: 1 - 4VMU compatibleJump Pack compatibleArcade Stick compatibleCharacter Roster     Ayane      Bass Armstrong      Bayman (cannot be used in Story Mode)      Ein      Gen Fu      Helena      Jann Lee      Kasumi      Lei Fang      Ryu Hayabusa      Tengu (Final boss, cannot be used in story mode)      Tina Armstrong      Zack </plot>
	<releasedate>29/2/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Tecmo, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>FT8ehr0ynlQ</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2413</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dead-or-alive-2/3030-2045/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2413-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2413-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/zw1ovJo.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/igyVPOP.jpg</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/36959-dead-or-alive-2-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/2413-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/536426-dead-or-alive-2-dreamcast-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/536427-dead-or-alive-2-dreamcast-screenshot-game-modes.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/536428-dead-or-alive-2-dreamcast-screenshot-character-selection.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/536429-dead-or-alive-2-dreamcast-screenshot-loading.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/536430-dead-or-alive-2-dreamcast-screenshot-ko-on-tina.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/536434-dead-or-alive-2-dreamcast-screenshot-winner-lei-fang.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/536437-dead-or-alive-2-dreamcast-screenshot-cut-scenes-between-matches.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/536441-dead-or-alive-2-dreamcast-screenshot-tag-battle-start.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/536442-dead-or-alive-2-dreamcast-screenshot-kasumi-vs-lei-fang.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2413-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2413-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CgVv905.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2413.png</clearlogo1>
</game>