<Game>
	<Name>Deadly Skies (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:AirForce Delta is a flight combat game that was developed by Konami for the Dreamcast. There is also a Game Boy Color version that was developed by The Climax Group and published by Konami.Story:Nine years ago, in the Federated Republic of Zabayral, ethnic tension broke out causing a civil war. Due to the ethnic tension, neighbors began drawing boundaries according to religious faith. However, Zabayral never maintained an army, instead the citizens relied on the nation's rich mineral reserves, because of this, they hired mercenaries to fight for them.Currently, there is a revolution being led by forces seeking unification. This revolution began in a northern country, the Klonne Republic, and has since spread southwards. The unification forces are now approaching the Republic of Laconia. AirForce Delta is the mercenary defense organization employed by the Republic of Laconia, this is who players fly for.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/7/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>23996</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/airforce-delta/3030-7790/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/23996-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/10831/475161-196566_50158_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<Notes>Players take control of a mercenary that has been contracted to complete a number of strategic military missions. Each mission completed earns the player money, and the more money that is accumulated, the more sophisticated aircraft the player can purchase. Players select from a myriad of fighters and take to the skies to defend a newly independent republic from its many enemies—for fame, for glory, and most of all: for a price.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6fa01cf1-a3dd-427b-bd70-aada3713dfc5.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8e612eaa-151e-4c29-a896-d53aece2b2c7.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Developer>KCE Studios</Developer>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>