<Game>
	<Name>Deep Fighter (Europe) (En,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Deep Fighter, a Criterion Studios developed game, puts you in control of a variety of submarines designed for combat. It is considered a first person shooter, despite being vehicular based, drawing inspiration from Wing Commander for the PC. Like its predecessor, you are able to move freely in any direction as the entirety of the game takes place underwater. The game features 24 missions across two discs, and like Wing Commander, makes liberal use of Full Motion Video.Story:The player is put in the role of a new graduated private (callsign MORAY 2) from the Academy, a training institute for submarine pilots. The Academy is a part of a wholly underwater civilization which is under siege by enemy threats (the Shadowkin) and a seemingly natural disintegration of the environment. Ultimately, the goal is to aid the civilization develop a mother ship and then protect it in order to transport the entire society from these threats.Gameplay:As noted, the core mechanic of the game is full 3D motion in a fluid, allowing for control much like Wing Commander and Descent. Throughout the course of the game, you pilot a series of 5 subs and an ROV (Remotely Operated Vehicle) that are suited for a variety of tasks. One of the key gameplay elements is combat, which operates much like dogfights in a flight or space sim, often engaging numerous enemies with the aid of teammates. Battles are broken up by pathfinding, item collection, and puzzle solving, all of which are designed specifically around the idea of full 3D motion.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/8/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Ubi Soft Entertainment Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>8119</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/deep-fighter/3030-206/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8119-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/23987-deep-fighter-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/23988-deep-fighter-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/26220/850602-8952_full.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/26220/850601-8951_full.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/26220/850600-8950_full.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/26220/850599-8949_full.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/26220/850598-8946_full.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/26220/850597-8945_full.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/26220/850596-8944_full.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/26220/850595-8943_full.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/26220/850594-8942_full.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/26220/850593-8953_full.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/y0pwKHZ.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>As a private in the defense force by The General, players take on deadly missions to seek out and destroy enemies, perform reconnaissance into uncharted waters and rescue damaged craft and installations. Meanwhile, droids and drones scuttle around busily, maintaining and repairing the slowly crumbling city. With the ultimate objective of the construction of a giant mothership, the Leviathan, that will transport the entire civilization away from hostile waters. This games combines elements of furious 3-D dogfighting and challenging exploration in true 3-D environments. 3-D worlds actually react and evolve around you as the game's level of difficulty adapts to your skill level. Five life-like and realistic environments, including the Abyss, Atlantis, and Jungle. Dynamic modes of battle include 3-D combat, unique weapons, special attack moves and upgradable fighter submarines.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a26832ed-d1dd-4539-96ec-09336418a41a.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9ec7e97a-d9e3-47ee-b854-9135b77c45b1.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6f1a3edb-0366-400b-a790-4db01c1922f7.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d91fbf19-af66-4566-b204-a8a272edabc1.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>