<Game>
	<Name>Disney-Pixar Toy Story 2 - Buzz Lightyear to the Rescue! (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Toy Story 2: Buzz Lightyear to the Rescue is a game based on the movie of the same name and was developed by Traveller's Tales Ltd. and published by Activision for the Sony PlayStation, Nintendo 64, PC and Sega Dreamcast. A Game Boy Color port of the game was also developed by Tiertex Design Studios and the publishing of the port was handled by THQ.Gameplay:Toy Story 2: Buzz Lightyear to the Rescue is a traditional style 3D platformer in which players take upon control of protagonist Buzz Lightyear as he attempts to rescue his best friend Woody after he is kidnapped by the evil Al McWhiggin.As is typical with the genre players have access to both a single and double jump and have to variations of attack to defeat the various enemies and bosses scattered throughout the game. The first form of attack utilises Buzz's wrist layer and fires a single projectile to damage enemies. This can be done from either the third or first person perspective as the game allows players to make precision shots from a first person viewpoint. The second of Lightyears' attacks is a spin attack to damage enemies with his pop out wings. Both of these attacks may also be charged resulting in a more powerful form of the attack although charging the spin move will leave players vulnerable for a short period of time after its execution. The game also features 5 different power-ups which are needed to help players complete certain tasks and these are permanently unlocked to be used in other levels once players recover one of Mr Potato Head's missing body pieces during the first level of each zone. The five power-ups are:Cosmic Shield - a shield which protects Buzz from damage and hazards in the environment.Disk Launcher - the disk launcher helps to defeat enemies in the harder to reach places.Rocket Boots - these give Buzz a speed boost for a short period of time.Grappling Hook - this allows Buzz to reach high places.Hover Boots - these allow Buzz to hover for a brief moment in order to reach specific platforms.Finally scattered throughout the stages often on harder to reach platforms are limited use upgrades such as a more powerful laser upgrade which increases the damage of the laser attack but comes with a limited amount of potential shots.The game contains 15 levels in total split into 5 zones consisting of 3 levels per zone (which follow the pattern of two objective based levels followed by a boss level). The gameplay centres around collecting Pizza Planet tokens to advance onto further levels in the game and although there contains five tokens per stage only one is required to progress onto the next level in the game and a set number of tokens being required in order to access the boss stage at the end of each zone.The five ways to unlock the Pizza Planet tokens within each stage are:Collecting 50 coins for Hamm.Finding 5 of Bo-Peep's lost sheep.Defeating RC Car in a race or completing Slinky's time trial challenge.Solving a puzzle or reaching a typically hard to reach location.Defeating a mini-boss within the stage.Are we gonna do this all night? My parts are killing me.As previously alluded to on the first level of each zone Mr Potato Head appears requesting Buzz recover a missing body part of his, rewarding the player with one of the five aforementioned possible power-ups for doing so. Obtaining these power-ups are essential to collecting all of the tokens within the game as several of the tokens are only obtainable using specific power-ups.Finally Buzz's dinosaur pal Rex provides advice and hints about the current level and tells players where in the level they can find the mini-boss to defeat in order to obtain the token awarded for doing so.Levels:Example level select screen.Andy's HouseAndy's NeighbourhoodBombs Away! (Boss Level)Construction YardAlleys and GulliesSlime Time! (Boss Level)Al's Toy BarnAl's Space LandToy Barn Encounter! (Boss Level)Elevator HopAl's PenthouseThe Evil Emperor Zurg! (Boss Level)Airport InfiltrationTarmac TroubleProspector Showdown! (Boss Level)Story:It's not flying, its falling with style.The game's plot follows that of the film pretty closely and like the film begins with the kidnapping of Woody by evil collector Al McWhiggin outside of Andy's house. The game then follows Buzz Lightyear and his companions as they set out to rescue the captured cowboy as the traverse the nearby neighbourhood, Al's Toy Barn, Al's penthouse and finally the airport terminal and tarmac at the film's end.Unlike the film however the game closes after Buzz Lightyear defeats Stinky Pete (aided by two henchmen) in a final battle, contrary to the films actual ending. Differences Between VersionsThere are many noticeable differences across the different versions of the game. This includes the game having a different soundtrack across the multiple platforms on which it was released. An example would be the first level of the game (Andy's House) which featured a unique soundtrack in the PS1, Dreamcast and PC release of the game. The N64 release though featured significantly different audio from the other versions of the game most likely due to the hardware differences between the various consoles.</plot>
	<releasedate>17/11/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Activision Publishing, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>8338</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/toy-story-2-buzz-lightyear-to-the-rescue/3030-7301/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8338-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/8338-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/6/62561/1523105-startmenu_n64.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/6/62561/1523104-first_boss.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1109610-psd3d012.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1109609-psd3d011.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1109608-psd3d010.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1109606-psd3d009.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1109605-psd3d008.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1109603-psd3d004.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1109602-psd3d003.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/329/1109601-psd3d002.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8338-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Az2HGMD.jpg</banner1>
</game>