<Game>
	<Name>Dynamite Cop! (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Dynamite Cop (Dynamite Deka 2 in Japan) is a arcade beat'em up released by SEGA in the arcades, under the SEGA Model 2 hardware, in 1998. The game was later ported to the SEGA Dreamcast for Japan, North America, and Europe. Dynamite Cop is a sequel to the Japanese version of Die Hard Arcade which is known as Dynamite Deka. The Japanese version of Die Hard Arcade had nothing to do with the Die Hard series. In the game, a gang of terrorist/pirates have high-jacked a cruise ship that contains the President's daughter. It's up to three heroes to put a stop to the terrorist's evil plan.Gameplay:One of the many levels of the game.The game follows the standard of any beat'em up game, the player defeats a number of enemies and move on to the next area. Other features are introduce in the game, such as "visuals scenes," in other words, Quick Time Events. There are three playable characters, each with their own special movesThe game starts off with the player giving the option (known as "missions" in the game) to pick one of three different ways to infiltrate the cruise ship; it also represent the difficulty of the game. Depending on which mission is chosen will result on certain areas that the player will go through in the game and the length of the play through that's giving. In one mission, the game's levels will only take place on the cruise ship, and in other missions, later levels will take place inside of a mountain which is the headquarters of the terrorists.A visual scene taking placeThe game uses five buttons: punch, kick, grab, and a 360 spin that attacks all surrounding enemies. Combos are the main emphasis of the gameplay; the player can grab an enemy and perform a button combination to activate a string of submission moves.A variety of weapons are available, such as guns, steel pipes, arcade cabinets, a piece of cake, a pepper shaker, hairspray, etc can be used. The player can also use power up items that enemies drop after they're defeated. If the player collects six power ups, or one of the super power ups, the player can temporarily perform a strong combination of attacks.Illustrations are hidden throughout each of the game's levels. Dynamite Cop takes advantage of the VMU hardware. If the player is close to an illustration, the VMU will make a sound indicating that's it's nearby. The illustrations include art work of all the characters."Showdown mode," a harder version of the regular campaign, is featured. Each of the three missions under showdown mode have the player go through the game under certain conditions - one being is the player has to go through the game with one life, others are to try to beat the game without getting hit once, and the last is the player is giving a time limit in each level to defeat every enemy before the time goes out or the game is over. The game also includes a Vs. mode and a survivor mode.Playable CharactersBruno Delinger - The main character of the game. Bruno has a sidekick monkey named Banana and is also known as "Mr. Dynamite." Bruno also has marriage problems.In the American version of Die Hard Arcade (Which was known as Dynamite Deka in Japan), Bruno was actually the character John McClane, the star of the Die Hard series.Jean Ivy - Jean loves anime, long walks on the beach, and cats. She also loves Kung-Fu, Sambo, and beating up evil pirates who want to take over the world. She loves to get her punches in, and she usually aims them at your face!Eddie Brown - Eddie is a former NFL player that was banned for drop kicking a referee for unknown reasons. He likes listening to reggae and is a master at kick boxing.</plot>
	<releasedate>31/10/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>421</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dynamite-cop/3030-1590/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/421-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/421-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/190051-dynamite-cop-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/421-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17339-dynamite-cop-dreamcast-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17340-dynamite-cop-dreamcast-screenshot-punch-enemies-until-they.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17341-dynamite-cop-dreamcast-screenshot-high-kick.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17342-dynamite-cop-dreamcast-screenshot-pile-driver.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17343-dynamite-cop-dreamcast-screenshot-the-president-s-daughter.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17344-dynamite-cop-dreamcast-screenshot-success.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17345-dynamite-cop-dreamcast-screenshot-two-players-at-once.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17346-dynamite-cop-dreamcast-screenshot-pirates.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7395/2554847-3.png</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/421-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/KJ3gPC1.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/421.png</clearlogo1>
</game>