<Game>
	<Name>Evil Dead - Hail to the King (France)</Name>
	<plot>Plot: A few months after the events of Army of Darkness  Ash begins to have nightmares filled with visions of "Deadites" and other beings of the  Necronomicon. Ash and his girlfriend, Jenny, decide to return to the  cabin in the  woods where the whole  Evil Dead ordeal began to try and end the nightmares. Once there Ash runs into his possessed hand that he had previously lobbed off. The hand turns on the  tape recorder with the incantation to make the Deadites rise and all hell breaks loose. Ash must find the  pages of the Necronomicon to send the Deadites back "once-and-for-all".  Gameplay: Evil Dead: Hail to the King plays very much like an early  Resident Evil game with the real-time action happening over pre-rendered and  fixed camera scenes. Ash is controlled much like a  tank with the left and right directions turning him rapidly and the forward and back moving him backwards.  Combat involves the use of melee weapons and ranged weapons to kill the various Deadites that appear. One of the buttons on the controller is reserved for  taunting with Ash's catchphrases such as "Come get some!" You are able to performing finishing blows on enemies, picking up with your chainsaw and using your secondary weapon to deal a fatal blow.The game is additionally notable for Bruce Campbell reprising his role as Ash. Weapons:There are five weapons in the game, four of which can be upgraded. These include the trademark Evil Dead weapons of a chainsaw and a 'boomstick' (a double barrelled shotgun), as well as a pistol, axe and rifle. You always have the chainsaw equipped in one hand, while the other can be switched out for any of the other weapons. However, you need to refuel the chainsaw with gas periodically.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/12/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<ESRB>M - Mature</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>qrzPNd1MxuE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>8126</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/evil-dead-hail-to-the-king/3030-14365/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8126-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/6428-evil-dead-hail-to-the-king-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/261428-evil-dead-hail-to-the-king-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6279/764177-hailtotheking1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8126-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8126-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/gtOHmBW.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/8126.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Ash, the square-jawed, insult-spewing, shotgun-toting, chainsaw-armed hero from the cult classic Evil Dead trilogy is back. Picking up eight years after the last installment of the Evil Dead films, Ash is drawn back to the infamous cabin in the woods only to again face evil forces that have crossed over to our world. Our hero finds himself slicing and dicing carnivorous Kandarian demons, vicious deadites, and other unspeakable atrocities spawned by the notorious Book of the Dead. And in true Evil Dead fashion, Ash must once again attempt to save the world from an appalling and horrific end. Evil Dead: Hail to the King is a survival horror game with over-the-top bloodlust and signature Ash humor--all within the confines of the Evil Dead universe.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>qrzPNd1MxuE</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/93c21af1-86bc-4b06-b478-469d7f31c650.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ad67bd89-3d46-4184-8841-c12dca975233.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>