<Game>
	<Name>Exodus Guilty Neos (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>It is the same place. But it is different time. The events of the past will influence the present and change the future. A mysterious item that was hidden thousand years ago will play an important role in the events of today and tomorrow...1200 BC. Total obedience is what the God demands from the people. Humans have no free will, but they believe that their obedience will bring them reward. Your protagonist in this time period is the "flame priest" Ales who serves the God. 200X AD - many good and evil powers are present in the world of our time, but the treasure hunter Kasumi Shindou is only interested in one thing - to find a treasure and to become rich, and nothing and nobody will stop him! In the future, 13800 AD, the skies have became black, the oceans are red, and the earth is on the verge of a disaster - Sui, the last descendant of a royal dynasty, and her friends decide to undertake something to change the reality. "Exodus Guilty Neos", an enhanced version of the Playstation title "Exodus Guilty", features a "Multitime Zapping System", which allows you to play as Ales, Kasumi, and Sui in their respective time periods, switching between them when necessary. You have to gather various items and to coordinate your actions in the past so that the future will be changed. The gameplay relies largely on dialogues (at certain points you are able to choose one of several available answers). You can also navigate your characters from first-person perspective (pressing arrows that point to different directions). You also have a party - people who join the main protagonists and help them in their quests.</plot>
	<releasedate>31/5/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Abel Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/exodus-guilty-neos/3030-2585/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4647/1030030-581334_22329_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/35951-exodus-guilty-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/35952-exodus-guilty-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/810308-exodus-guilty-playstation-screenshot-makes-me-think-of-chrono.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/810319-exodus-guilty-playstation-screenshot-nice-touch-with-the-english.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/810330-exodus-guilty-playstation-screenshot-you-can-pick-different.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/810341-exodus-guilty-playstation-screenshot-let-s-start-by-going.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/810346-exodus-guilty-playstation-screenshot-post-apocalyptic-city.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/810347-exodus-guilty-playstation-screenshot-yes-we-re-both-hot-and.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/810348-exodus-guilty-playstation-screenshot-ouch-i-m-so-clumsy.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/810349-exodus-guilty-playstation-screenshot-but-you-don-t-care-about.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/810350-exodus-guilty-playstation-screenshot-by-all-means-help-yourself.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/810309-exodus-guilty-playstation-screenshot-no-i-m-not-the-flower.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>