<Game>
	<Name>GigaWing (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Giga Wing is a 1999 vertical shooter originally released in the arcades on Capcom's CPS-2 system and later ported to the  Sega Dreamcast for the home market. It was developed by    Takumi and published by    Capcom. The game is notable for the incredible amount of points that can be obtained (with the world record set at 2,954,296,261,700 on the arcade version, according to the Guinness World Records Gamer's Edition). It has been compared to    Treasure's fast paced shooters as well. The game takes place during a war in a futuristic steampunk setting, and the player takes control of one of several different pilots.Gameplay:Trust me, this is one of the easier momentsGiga Wing is a fast-paced shooter. At points in the game, literally hundreds of bullets and lasers can be onscreen at one time. Because of this, the game utilizes a feature unique to Giga Wing. It is called the Reflect Force; by holding down the A button, the Reflect Force is activated. It makes all of the bullets onscreen go back towards the shooter. The power-up system is also unique. After destroying certain enemies, a P will begin bouncing around the screen. After collecting it, the weapon the player has is upgraded. Up to three can be collected, each making the lasers of the player even more powerful.Bombs can also be collected an then shot (by using the B button). When unleashed, the bomb explodes over a radius of the entire screen, flashing lightning and fire while causing incredible damage to every enemy craft in sight. Each one of the ships starts out with two bombs, and up to seven can be collected at one time.Expansive and difficult bossesThere are four different crafts to choose from, each having a unique shooting pattern. As power-ups are collected, the lasers upgrade in different ways. Each pilot reacts similarly to the scenarios presented in the game, however there are slight differences.The score multiplier is very unique. When an enemy is destroyed, it drops medals of varying size and shape (Strider 2, also by Capcom, also utilizes this medal system). Each medal is worth a certain amount of points, and the points add up as a score multiplier. For example, if the player collects five medals that are worth five points each, then the score multiplier will be at twenty-six. Each medal collected after that will add to that value. The medals come in varying amounts of one, five, ten, twenty, or one-hundred.</plot>
	<releasedate>31/1/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Virgin Interactive Entertainment (Europe) Ltd., Capcom Co., Ltd., Capcom Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>4.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>8132</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/giga-wing/3030-22712/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8132-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/8132-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/137879-giga-wing-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/710828-gigawing34.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/710827-gigawing2.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/710810-gigawing58.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/710809-gigawing52.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/710808-gigawing46.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/710807-gigawing42.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/710806-gigawing37.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/710804-gigawing33.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/710803-gigawing26.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/710802-gigawing14.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6lP5L6X.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/8132.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In the World of Giga Wing, many wars have been fought for the divine stone Medallion. Entire civilizations were destroyed in the struggle for gaining control of the legendary item. Now, in the year 2050, four pilots have set off, each carrying a mysterious stone. The stones are said to be the only way to destroy Medallion once and for all. The player can choose to complete the journey for any of the four pilots. Giga Wing is a vertical scrolling shoot 'em up. Up to two players must steer their planes around enemy bullets and destroy everything in their path with only a limited amount of lives. When tapping the A button, the main gun is fired. Holding the button activates the Reflect Force. The B button fires a bomb from a limited stock to become temporarily invincible. Power-ups can be collected to increase the bomb and life stock or enhance the main gun's fire power. Scoring works by using the Reflect Force to repel enemy shots. Once the shots hit an enemy, medals appear in their place. When these are collected, the score multiplier increases.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/42472fc1-6b45-4f3d-8d26-e647a9462bba.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5daba77b-3511-40bf-872a-2b1d8e2bc25f.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2e060647-92dd-457d-bbef-252b008f6a23.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fe50ed99-d380-47b4-841c-499c77110d09.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb5b8065-ef77-4e6f-ad54-5acb3f00e3a1.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>