<Game>
	<Name>Grandia II (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Grandia II was developed by Game Arts with additional services provided by many companies in specific parts of the game, aka CG production. Additional help was provided by employees of IKUSABUNE, Shirogumi, Xeonix and Studio Deen, for CG animation.Grandia II was released for the Sega Dreamcast on August 3rd, 2000 in Japan. Later releasing on December 6th in the US. It was a traditional Japanese Anime-style RPG. As well as being noted for its then state-of-the-art 3D graphics, Grandia II is perhaps better known for its combat system, as some people claim it was the influence behind Final Fantasy X's own battle system.It was later ported to the PlayStation 2 and PC in 2002. Although the Dreamcast version is considered the better of the two due to technical issues present in the PlayStation 2 port. A Steam version of the game will be released, published by GungHo Online Entertainment. This release will feature both mouse and keyboard and gamepad support as well as Steam achievements and Trading Cards.Gameplay:The gameplay is unique from a typical turn-based RPG. It combines elements of real-time fighting and turn-based attacks. This allows battles to be faster paced while adding another level of complexity to the fight. Grandia II employs a bar to show how long the character has to wait before making an attack, while allowing the player limited movement during the battle.Since there is real-time and turn-based elements in the fighting it also means that there are more stats to grow for the character. For example there are two forms of speed in the game: how fast the character can attack, and physically moving to the enemy and attacking them. The time in which it takes a character friend or foe to perform their attack is called the "act".The ability to cancel an enemy's attack can be used to great advantage, but the key is timing and being able to figure what special attack is about to be done, how long it takes, and if the character can physically make to the enemy and hit them in time.Strategy comes into play as a player has to decide which attack to use to best time his attack hitting the enemy within that short "act" period. By doing so the enemy's attack will be canceled or delayed, allowing more characters to attack the enemy and cause greater damage. Later in the game as players level up their skills, the ability to instantly perform attacks adds greater emphasis on delaying attacks, as most Boss battles become more difficult.MagicSome of the best visuals for its timeMagic in the Grandia series is learned by equipping items called mana eggs. In this game different types of eggs existed usually containing 2 to 3 elemental types per egg. These elemental types determine the magic spell the egg could use. Magic can also be leveled up which allows for faster casting and more damage.Story:Main CharactersRyudo - Geohound (mercenary)Initially rude, with a very sarcastic attitude, he later comes to terms with the causes of his bitter behaviour through the course of the game. He is usually accompanied by his bird, Skye.Elena - Songstress of GranasMild-mannered, polite, and devoted to her faith, but she can also be quite spirited at times. As a result of this, she often clashes with Ryudo.Roan - Prince of CyrumWhile showing an understanding far beyond his years, he still approaches a lot of common things with childish curiosity and surprisingly good manners.Mareg - Beast WarriorA noble beastman on a quest for revenge after his village was attacked by a merciless superhuman.Tio - AutomataCreated during the war of the Gods some 10,000 years ago she is initially an emotionless being only there to serve. Although through her experiences with Mareg she begins to understand the nature of what makes humans, human.PlotRyudo and his pet bird SkyeThe story starts as Ryudo the Geohound (a kind of mercenary), along with his bird, Skye, accepts a mission to accompany Elena, a songstress of Granas, as she heads to Garmia Tower. As luck would have it the mission turns into much more as an accident occurs at the tower which will require Ryudo and Elena to work together.As they travel around the world they struggle to uncover how Valmar, the Dark God, is once again wrecking havoc on the land. You see the pieces of his body have been sealed away using the power of Granas, the Light God, to prevent Valmar from returning again. Soundtrack:Grandia II: Deus (Disc 1)Grandia II ~Deus~01 - Memory of the Gods02 - Opening Act03 - Village of Carbo ~ Pious Adepts04 - A Deus05 - The Ones Hidden Within the Darkness [1]06 - Tower of Garmia07 - Dangerous Zone08 - FIGHT!! Ver.109 - "You Won't Be Able to Kill Me Just Like That!"10 - Come on, Let's Travel11 - Inn Town Ageel ~ Cursed Land12 - The Ones Hidden Within the Darkness [2]13 - Commercial Town Lilig ~ Apparent Prosperity14 - The Broken Seal15 - Purification of Darkness ~ Battle With the Parts16 - Nightmare Village Milm ~ A Good, Unknown Anxiety17 - The Garden of Dreams ~ The Mysterious Girl18 - FIGHT!! Ver.219 - The Country of Laws Santhaim ~ Pious Adepts20 - Out For Lunch21 - Granas Sanctuary22 - Granas SaberGrandia II: Povo (Disc 2)01 - Memory of the Gods (Full Version)02 - The Sairam Kingdom ~ Prosperity and Freedom03 - LIVE! LIVE!! LIVE!!!04 - Sairam Castle05 - Announcement at Sairam Kingdom ~ March06 - Romance at a Windy Isle07 - The Moon of Valmar08 - Have Faith in Yourself09 - Evil Root of Destruction10 - FIGHT!! Ver. 3 ~ Middle Boss Battle11 - "Heh, They Didn't Even Get to Fight Back!"12 - Skye's Reminiscence13 - The Town of Nanan ~ Overwhelming Nature14 - Traditional Song ~ The Villager's Chorus15 - Despair and Hope16 - The Ones Hidden Within the Darkness (Mix Version)17 - Elegy18 - Collapse19 - The Mythical World20 - Valmar21 - A Farewell, and Decision22 - Awakening Ryudo ~ Prayers of the People23 - FIGHT!! Ver. 4 ~ The Final Battle24 - Can&#231;ao Do PovoLimited Edition SoundtrackGrandia II ~Melodia~The Dreamcast had a Limited Edition of Grandia II (Grandia II: Special Package) that came with an audio CD titled "Grandia II: ~Melodia~". It consists of 7 songs not on the original soundtrack:01 - Can&#231;&#227;o do Povo - Little Shelter Mix02 - A Deus - Challenge to the Gods Mix03 - Digital Museum Radiodrama Opening04 - Gadwin's Art of Loving05 - Gadwin's Pad06 - Baal's Diary07 - Sample the TastePC RequirementsWindows 95/98/ME;Pentium II 300 MHz or compatible (Min.), Pentium II 500 MHz or compatible (Rec.);64 MB RAM (Min.), 128 MB (Rec.);16 MB DirectX 8 supported 3D video card (Min.), 32 MB (Rec.);DirectX 8 compatible sound card;8x CD-ROM drive (Min.), 16x (Rec.).</plot>
	<releasedate>12/5/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Ubi Soft Entertainment Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>2415</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/grandia-ii/3030-10129/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2415-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/35179-grandia-ii-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/35181-grandia-ii-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/488793-grandia-ii-dreamcast-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/488794-grandia-ii-dreamcast-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/488795-grandia-ii-dreamcast-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/488796-grandia-ii-dreamcast-screenshot-second-part-of-the-intro-using.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/488797-grandia-ii-dreamcast-screenshot-beginning-of-the-game.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/488798-grandia-ii-dreamcast-screenshot-found-a-treasure-chest.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/488799-grandia-ii-dreamcast-screenshot-fighting-a-spider.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2809295-2015-12-26_00016.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2809294-2015-12-26_00015.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2809293-2015-12-26_00014.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4yDvCgU.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The story focuses on Ryudo the Geohound (a kind of mercenary) and his talking bird, Skye. Together they accept a mission from the town of Carbo's church as bodyguards for Elena, a Songstress of Granas, who is on her way to Garmia Tower. The job turns into something much more after an incident at the tower, and Ryudo and Elena find themselves travelling all over the world, meeting some new friends and some new enemies.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>uLPMdro-j20</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/259349aa-55e3-43f2-9652-4c5f13b3d635.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9b2c2b11-dbad-477f-a9a6-8152bdb6685a.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>