<Game>
	<Name>Grand Theft Auto 2 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The top-down view that GTA was once known for.Grand Theft Auto 2 was the sequel to DMA's " Grand Theft Auto" which was a PC and Playstation title. Grand Theft Auto 2 would have a similar top down style to the original game, but with enhanced game mechanics and graphics. This was the last of the Grand Theft Auto games to use a strict top down camera. The game was first released on the original Playstation in October 22, 1999 and then two days later for PC. Grand Theft Auto 2 was also ported to both Game Boy Color and Dreamcast. There has been some criticisms of all versions that the storyline was lackluster and that the rewards for completing missions was disproportionate to the cost of items in-game.Multiplayer:The PC version of GTA2 included IP to IP multiplayer. This means that there were no server browsers and that most games were privately hosted in an era when broadband connections still had relatively low market penetration. The multiplayer had severe lag due to this networking model and was called "unusable" by most users. It should be noted that once someone is in Multiplayer, the map is drastically reduced, and most AI features are turned off.Soundtrack:Head RadioApostles of Funk - Yellow ButterPussywillows - Real LoveDavidson - All I Wanna DoThe One - SouthparkBula Matari - Taxi DriversFlytronix - PendulumAnna - Do It On Your OwnTesting - My Tiny WorldStikki Fingerz - Holdin' It Out For YouConor &amp; Jay - Vegas RoadTrack 7 - I Wanna PhunkKREZNegro Vs. Conner - Showin' Me LoveE=MC Good Times - Jacking In HilltownFlytronix - Past ArchivesNumb - How It's DoneLo-Fi FMStylus Exodus - Toucan PieBert Reid's Guitar Trio - A Cool Day In DowntownTammy Boness &amp; The Swingin' Mammaries - The DinerCow Tastes Good - Surf CityFuturo FMReed - L.E.D.Davidson - All I Wanna DoZaibatsu PromoSpangly Feet - Dazed &amp; ConfuzedStylus Exodus - Toucan PieFunami FMToys Are Real - FlymuthaFuture Loop - Garage Acid4 How Much 4 - O2NIdo - BallbusterLithium FMTammy Boness &amp; The Swingin' Mammaries - The DinerVoice Box - COMPUTER LUSTRev. Rooney &amp; The Rocksta Choir - God Bless All The UniverseRebel Radio/KINGBula Matari - Taxi Drivers (Must Die)Testing - My Tiny WorldStikki Fingerz - Holdin' It Out For YouSterlin - Standing On My OwnOsmosis RadioDavidson - All I Wanna DoPussywillows - Real LoveAnna - Do It On Your OwnTrack 7 - I Wanna PhunkHeavenly RadioRev. Rooney &amp; The Rocksta Choir - God Bless All The UniverseSterlin - Standing On My OwnZoneboys - Amazing GraceKGBHCow Tastes Good - Surf CitySpangly Feet - Dazed &amp; ConfuzedFree releaseOn December 23rd, 2004, Rockstar announced that it would give away both Grand Theft Auto and Grand Theft Auto 2 as freely downloadable packaged from their website. The core game remains unchanged, but it has been tweaked in order to natively work within Windows XP and Windows Vista. There have been isolated reports that the game intermittently crashes, but many users find it to be fully playable without any issues at all.External LinksRockstar Classics - Link to Rockstar's site, offering free downloadPC System RequirementsOS: MacOS X 10.6.7 or higherProcessor: Core 2 Duo 2.4 GhzMemory: 2GB RAMHard Disk Space: 6GB of free HDD spaceGraphics: SVGA color monitorDirect&#174; X: DirectX 6.1Sound Card: SoundBlaster compatibele sound cardVideo Card: 3D acceleration with 8 Mb RAM</plot>
	<releasedate>30/4/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Rockstar Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>M - Mature</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>8133</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/grand-theft-auto-2/3030-10593/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8133-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/8133-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/7141-grand-theft-auto-2-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112562/1668725-opening_screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112562/1668724-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112562/1668723-end.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112562/1668722-bonus3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112562/1668721-bonus2.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112562/1668720-bonus1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17172/1271355-gta2gbc_015.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17172/1271354-gta2gbc_014.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17172/1271353-gta2gbc_013.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17172/1271352-gta2gbc_012.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/8133.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Lie, cheat, and steal your way through three districts of a huge city in the follow-up to Grand Theft Auto. Earn the respect of 7 different gangs as you demolish the town in your attempt to make lots of cash. The game takes place at an undisclosed time in the near future. Unlike the first game which featured three different cities, Grand Theft Auto 2 only features a single town, but it's divided in three districts which are unlocked one at a time: downtown, residential and industrial. Like in the original the player goes around answering phones to initiate various missions. The game uses an overhead camera in a 3D landscape and allows the player to freely explore the city and steal any vehicle the player sets his or her eyes on. To unlock new districts the player must reach a certain score which is done by committing crimes and finishing missions. Because the game now features multiple criminal gangs, the player must choose allegiances. Performing missions for one gang, will decrease the player's reputation for another. When the player commits crimes he also becomes wanted by the local police, but as more crimes are committed without shaking the police, they will give way for first SWAT Teams, then Special Agents and finally the army. New features include the ability to save at the church, when donating enough money, and various side missions, such as becoming a taxi driver to ear money. There are also many new cars with weapons attached such as a firetruck with a flamethrower and a car with machine guns.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7312e209-3e46-45f4-998f-bc9450b3b1b9.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9f2442b9-86e2-4078-9671-3f1b8fe50989.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/877d1383-84bd-48e9-847e-f3f3784c9540.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/88045b32-b30d-4d80-978c-fd7e2171c74c.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Rockstar</Publisher>
</game>