<Game>
	<Name>MDK2 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Summary:MDK 2 is the sequel to MDK and features the protagonists from the previous game, the six-legged robot dog Max, Doctor Fluke Hawkins and Kurt Hectic (the hero from the first game).Unlike the original MDK, you actually get to play as Max and the doctor as they all have distinct playstyles.Kurt Hectic's is a mix between puzzle-solving, sniping and all-around combat. Max' is the action type, with an unique four-arm setup that allows you to quad-wield any weapons he pick up, and can be equipped however you want: Four uzis, or one pistol, one shotgun and two uzis, and etc.Dr. Fluke Hawkins focuses on puzzle-solving, although there is a lot of combat involved. You have two hands and two inventory spaces, which allows you to merge items, creating solutions to puzzles or inventing new weaponry. The first two basic things you need to combine are toast and a toaster, which you will be able to mix into a weapon later. The game starts off with a level with Kurt, then changes to Max, then to Fluke, and rotates in that order.Story:The game starts directly after MDK ends, with Kurt and the others celebrating for saving the world, when they detect alien movement on the earth's surface, namely Edmonton, Canada. So now the gang must stop another invasion from the ruthless aliens.AvailabilityThe game has been re-released in its original state on digital distribution services like Steam and GOG.com.HD RemakeOn June 28th, 2010, Interplay announced plans to re-release MDK2 in high definition for the Wii and PC. MDK2 HD is currently available on both Beamdog and Steam in addition to the Wii Shop, and was developed by Overhaul Games, a company made up of ex- Bioware employees.System RequirementsOS: WindowsProcessor: Pentium 300MhzMemory: 64MBGraphics: DirectXDirectX&#174;: 7Hard Drive: 650MBSound: DirectSoundHD Version System RequirementsOS:Windows XP / Vista / 7Processor:Core 2 Duo or equivalentMemory:512 MB RAMGraphics:GeFroce 8800GT, OpenGL 3 compatibleDirectX&#174;:9.0cHard Drive:1 GB HD spaceAdditional:Many Intel HD video chipsets do not fully support OpenGL 3 and may prevent the game from running.</plot>
	<releasedate>31/3/2000</releasedate>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mdk-2/3030-1531/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4865/825264-197880_42478_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14912/830625-mdk2_arma_back.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/18205/611844-mdk2dc006.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/18205/611842-mdk2dc004.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/18205/611840-mdk2dc002.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/18205/611839-mdk2dc001.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5479/344322-mdk2_hwtcl.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5479/344304-mdk2pic2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5479/344303-mdk2_d.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5479/344301-mdk2_bemutato_04.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5479/344299-mdk2_b2_screen007.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5237/260718-mdk2_13.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>After Kurt Hectic, the janitor extraordinaire, has bravely ventured into the perilous minecrawlers and averted the alien threat to the Earth, he returns to his friends, the genius scientist Dr. Fluke Hawkins, and his invention, the six-legged robotic dog Max, to celebrate their great victory. However, they find out that one minecrawler in Canada still hasn't been destroyed. Kurt is sent to complete the mission, but as a result gets kidnapped by an alien being known as Shwang Shwing. Doc and Max rush to his rescue, and soon realize that they are up against a much bigger threat, involving an alien empire and galactic conquest. The fate of the Earth is in their hands!</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/35468087-fed2-4e75-a726-3c8041b2c1e1.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/20a1cb17-7745-44c0-b4df-032ed3ca1454.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9b061e45-cf09-40e0-9086-1dacf99b9af8.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/54d4da28-4200-4520-af0e-c97173e5dc75.png</snapshot12>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>BioWare</Developer>
	<Publisher>Interplay</Publisher>
</game>