<Game>
	<Name>Ms. Pac-Man Maze Madness (USA)</Name>
	<plot>A combination of exploration and classic Pac-Man (or in this case, Ms. Pac-Man) action, Ms. Pac-Man Maze Madness has Ms. Pac-Man saving Pac-Land once again, although this in full 3D.The four Wonders, mystical regions separated from the rest of Pac-Land by force fields, contains four Gems of Virtue: Generosity, Truth, Wisdom and Courage, each holding enough power to help keep Pac-Land safe from evil. However, an unknown enemy has transformed the Enchanted Castle into a haunted house, in turn starting a chain reaction of evil all around Pac-Land and the four Wonders. It is up to Ms. Pac-Man to enter the 3D designed worlds of the four Wonders and put the evil to rest for good.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/11/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Hometek Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>8145</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ms-pac-man-maze-madness/3030-3903/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8145-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/8145-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/237441-ms-pac-man-maze-madness-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/239755-ms_pacman_maze_06.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/239751-ms_pacman_maze_05.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/239749-ms_pacman_maze_04.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/239747-ms_pacman_maze_03.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/239746-ms_pacman_maze_02.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1550/239745-ms_pacman_maze_01.jpg</snapshot6>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/IcOi5ep.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Ms. Pac-Man Maze Madness has Ms. Pac-Man saving Pac-Land once again, although this in full 3D. The four Wonders, mystical regions separated from the rest of Pac-Land by force fields, contains four Gems of Virtue: Generosity, Truth, Wisdom and Courage, each holding enough power to help keep Pac-Land safe from evil. However, an unknown enemy has transformed the Enchanted Castle into a haunted house, in turn starting a chain reaction of evil all around Pac-Land and the four Wonders. It is up to Ms. Pac-Man to enter the 3D designed worlds of the four Wonders and put the evil to rest for good.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d50a9f2-b3db-4689-9fc9-00f4b3443da9.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c3ddd4ef-8eca-4c84-a6a3-4d6e5024a1cc.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>