<Game>
	<Name>MSR - Metropolis Street Racer (USA) (Rev. A)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: Metropolis Street Racer, or "MSR" as it was known in the days of the Dreamcast, is seen as the precursor to the now widely popular   Project Gotham Racing franchise. It was the first game to introduce the "  Kudos" system that rewarded drivers for style as well as speed. This gave the game a arcade tilt to the gameplay, and allowed players a new focus during races, instead of soley fighting for points or positions players also competed to complete races with the most "  Kudos" in order to unlock the later races.   Gameplay: Metropolis Street Racer features several standard racing game modes, including a lengthy and unique single player campaign, time trials, and both online and offline multiplayer. The core of the game focuses on the single player campaign, wherein you unlock the cars and tracks for play in the other modes by progressing through a series of 25 sets of challenges. Each set of challenges is called a chapter, and there are several types of challenges, keeping the game feeling fresh. Races take place in different locations around the world, the time of day that the race takes place is calculated using the time set on the internal Dreamcast clock and the location of the player within the world. The types of challenges presented are:One-on-One: A standard single race against a single opponent.Street Race: A standard single race against several opponents.Championship: A series of races against multiple opponents, where score is tallied after each race based on finishing position.Hotlap: A standard single race where you race solo attempting to beat a specified time.Challenge: A challenge with custom rules for completion, such as passing a specified number of cars within the race.Car ListAlfa Romeo156GtvSpiderAudiS3TT CoupeTT RoadsterFiatBarchettaCoupe 20v TurboFordMustang JensenS-V8 MazdaMiataMX-5RoadsterRX7MercedesBenz SL320Benz SLK MGMGFRV8 Mitsubishi3000GTGTOEclipseEclipse 99Eclipse SpiderFTOLancer EVO VINissan300ZXFairlady ZFairlady Z SpiderSilviaSkyline GTRVarieta OPEL / VauxhallASTRA CoupeOPCSpeedsterVX220Peugeot206206 Cabriolet306406 CoupeRenaultClio V6MeganeSpider ToyotaCelicaCelica 99Celica GT-FourMR-3MR2SupraTVRChimaeraUnlockable Cars Unlockable cars are non-traditional "cars" won from Special Events in the single player campaign. They include: London TaxiLondon Double Decker BusSan Franciso Yellow CabSan Franciso City BusTokyo TakusheTokyo BusLawnmowerMusic: The soundtrack was composed primarily by long-time   Sega collaborator   Richard Jacques. It is unique for being one of the first instances where the music is presented with a "radio"-style presentation, with some banter and introduction before and after tracks by fictional radio DJs. The music itself was a mix of original tracks and pop parody, and was generally poorly received by critics.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/1/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd., SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>10589</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/metropolis-street-racer/3030-3027/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/10589-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/15320-metropolis-street-racer-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/63528-metropolis-street-racer-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/10589-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/10589-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/56/234013-302794343_76c266e763_o.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/56/234010-302794342_f182f97d53_o.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/56/234007-302794338_bfc85b57f9_o.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/56/234004-302794334_2cf373b16e_o.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/56/234002-302792749_0e7749b033_o.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/56/234000-302792746_45c012aa04_o.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/56/233999-302792744_8881f47361_o.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/56/233996-302792742_06fda0d01a_o.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/10589-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WktaXY2.png</banner1>
</game>