<Game>
	<Name>NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:NBA Showtime features the same arcade 2 on 2 style of NBA Jam and NBA Hangtime. One of the NBA teams is chosen, then two players from that team are chosen. At half time two different players can be chosen to switch out the current ones. NBA Showtime also features the "on fire" feature. If a player makes 3 consecutive shots they become on fire and can not only make shots at a much higher percentage, the player can also goal tend without penalty. The announcer from NBA Jam ( Tim Kitzrow) returns after an absence from NBA Hangtime. NBA Showtime also features a create a player mode as well as the initials and PIN system for record keeping.Arcade VersionsOne of the Showtime arcade cabinetsNBA Showtime: NBA on NBC featured a four player cabinet. Each player had three buttons to use: Pass/Steal, Shoot/Jump, and Turbo. NBA Showtime uses the same hardware that is used in the NFL Blitz series. In version 1.0 of the game Dennis Rodman was on the Lakers. The player could adjust the color of his hair. After version 1.0 Rodman was no longer with the Lakers and was removed. The Arcade version of the game also included various Universal Monsters such as: Frankenstein's Monster, The Bride of Frankenstein, The Mummy, The Wolf Man, and the Creature From the Black Lagoon.Game Boy Color VersionThe Game Boy Color version of the game features four play modes: Season, Exhibition, Playoffs, and Practice. The Game Boy version also features all 29 teams found in the other versions of the game.RostersTeamsAtlanta HawksDikembe MutomboAlan HendersonLaPhonso EllisBimbo ColesIsiah RiderJim Jackson                        Boston CelticsKenny AndersonAntoine WalkerDana BarrosTony BattiePaul Pierce (Dreamcast Only)Danny FortsonCalbert CheaneyCharlotte HornetsEddie JonesAnthony MasonBobby PhillsDerrick ColemanElden CampbellChicago BullsToni KukocRon HarperAndrew LangKornel DavidB.J. ArmstrongWill PerdueCleveland CavaliersShawn KempBrevin KnightBob SuraZydrunas IlgauskasWesley PersonLamond MurrayDallas MavericksMichael FinleyCedric CeballosShawn BradleySteve NashDenver NuggetsAntonio McDyessNick Van ExelBryant StithChauncey BillupsRon MercerDetroit PistonsGrant HillLindsey HunterChristian LaettnerBison DeleJerry StackhouseJoe DumarsGolden State WarriorsJohn StarksDonyell MarshallErick DampierMuggsy BoguesMookie BlaylockHouston RocketsScottie PippenCharles BarkleyHakeem OlajuwonEddie JohnsonMatt MaloneyTony MassenburgIndiana PacersReggie MillerDale DavisJalen RoseSam PerkinsMark JacksonChris MullinLos Angeles ClippersMaurice TaylorStojko VrankovicJohnny NewmanLamar Odom (N64 Version Only)Los Angeles LakersShaquille O'NealGlen RiceKobe BryantRick FoxTravis KnightA.C. GreenMiami HeatTim HardawayAlonzo MourningVoshon LenardP.J. BrownMilwaukee BucksGlenn RobinsonRay AllenErvin JohnsonSam CassellTim ThomasDanny ManningDale EllisMinnesota TimberwolvesKevin GarnettTerrell BrandonDean GarrettJoe SmithBobby JacksonMalik SealyNew Jersey NetsStephon MarburyKeith Van HornJayson WilliamsKendall GillNew York KnicksPatrick EwingAllan HoustonLatrell SprewellLarry JohnsonCharlie WardMarcus CambyOrlando MagicBo OutlawDarrell ArmstrongDanny SchayesChris GatlingPhiladelphia 76ersAllen IversonTheo RatliffAaron McKieMatt GeigerTyron HillBilly OwensPhoenix SunsJason KiddTom GugliottaRex ChapmanLuc LongleyRodney RogersAnfernee HardawayPortland TrailblazersDamon StoudamireRasheed WallaceArvydas SabonisWalt WilliamsSteve SmithDetlef ShrempfSacramento KingsChris WebberJason WilliamsCorliss WilliamsonVlade DivacLawrence FunderburkeDarrick MartinNick AndersonSan Antonio SpursDavid RobinsonSean ElliottTim DuncanSteve KerrAvery JohnsonTerry PorterSeattle SupersonicsGary PaytonVin BakerHorace GrantBrent BarryToronto RaptorsVince CarterCharles OakleyDoug ChristieTracy McGradyKevin WillisDee BrownDell CurryUtah JazzJohn StocktonKarl MaloneGreg OstertagJeff HornacekBryon RussellVancouver GrizzliesShareef Abdul-RahimBryant ReevesCherokee ParksDoug WestMike BibbyWashington WizardsJuwan HowardRod StricklandMitch RichmondTracy Murray</plot>
	<releasedate>16/4/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Midway Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>19324</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nba-showtime-nba-on-nbc/3030-4632/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/19324-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/233/445538-so_box_usa_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/19324-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2431001-nba+1.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/1681817-nbaonnbc.jpg</snapshot3>
	<Notes>The game features gameplay similar to its predecessors NBA Jam and NBA Hangtime. Rather than typical 5 on 5 action, this game features 2 on 2 play with the ability to pick two players from any NBA team's starting line-up for the first half and can choose again for the second. The game introduces personal fouls for each shove on another player; after a certain number of fouls the opposing team gets a free throw. The game retains the series standard "on fire" feature. After a player makes three consecutive shots he becomes "on fire", which allows him to easily make shots from almost anywhere, as well as goaltend without penalty and push opponents without being charged a foul. Play otherwise is similar to NBA rules.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6abc4eb1-31aa-4493-954d-71ceda702686.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1df40f21-1af5-482d-909b-7b6cafc4e425.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Publisher>Midway</Publisher>
</game>