<Game>
	<Name>NFL Blitz 2000 (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>New edition of Midway's "NFL Jam" action/sports game where the emphasis is on bone-crushing action rather than sport simulation.Additions this year come in the form of a season mode, a simpler passing system based on preset buttons (gone is the "aiming" mechanism) as well as a limited yet functional play-book editor.Also included are new audible calls and voice-overs, smoother animations and new stadiums to play in.Supports multiplayer gameplay of up to 4 players in one single machine! (two on keyboard, two on gamepads).</plot>
	<releasedate>9/9/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Midway Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>21257</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nfl-blitz-2000/3030-2849/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/21257-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/162163-nfl-blitz-2000-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/162176-nfl-blitz-2000-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7784/698927-nfl_blitz_2001.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7784/698925-blitz1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7784/698924-1767_1.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7784/698923-1765_1.png</snapshot4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/eDmIfXZ.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/21257.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>NFL Blitz is a series of American football themed video games by Midway featuring National Football League teams. It began as a 1997 arcade game that was ported to home consoles and spawned several sequels. Rather than being designed as a realistic interpretation of the sport of football, like Madden NFL or NFL 2K, the Blitz series was created as an over-the-top, exaggerated version of the sport, inspired by Midway's own NBA Jam basketball games. In 2005, following the loss of the NFL license, the Blitz series was relaunched as Blitz: The League, featuring fictional players and teams in a fictional league with slightly more realistic (though still exaggerated) on-field play and a focus on the seedy behind-the-scenes lives of the players. The series rebooted January 4, 2012 on PlayStation Network and Xbox Live. The game took the series back to the original style of NFL BLITZ, but removed the late hits due to input by the NFL.[2]</Notes>
	<nPlayers>4</nPlayers>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd93e4b3-3f8a-4a88-a705-7e1264c3159f.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cb6b6daf-c85a-493a-8a35-a716847ae351.png</clearlogo2>
	<rating>5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Midway Home Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>