<Game>
	<Name>NFL 2K1 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:NFL 2K1 is the sequel to the well-received Dreamcast launch title, NFL 2K. Released exclusively on the Dreamcast and developed by Visual Concepts, NFL 2K1 added several gameplay changes, some graphical upgrades, a franchise mode, updatable rosters, and most notably, online play via the Internet. Online Play2K1 was the first home console football game to support online, through the Dreamcast network adapter. In-game chat was also possible with the Dreamcast Keyboard. Players could also download roster updates throughout the season for the first time. There were three regions and each region had 10 to 12 city-specific servers to select from to keep players close to each other and minimize lag.Features:Online multiplayer for up to 8 total players (4 on each console)Enhanced running game with new blocking, juke, and power movesFranchise ModeOver 2,000 motion-captured animationsRealistic team playbooksOnline roster updates</plot>
	<releasedate>9/5/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3955</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nfl-2k1/3030-805/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3955-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3955-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/86016-nfl-2k1-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/196704-nfl-2k1-dreamcast-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/196705-nfl-2k1-dreamcast-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/196706-nfl-2k1-dreamcast-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/196707-nfl-2k1-dreamcast-screenshot-fantasy-team-menus.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/196708-nfl-2k1-dreamcast-screenshot-the-coin-toss.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/196709-nfl-2k1-dreamcast-screenshot-opening-kick.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/196710-nfl-2k1-dreamcast-screenshot-play-selection.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/196711-nfl-2k1-dreamcast-screenshot-time-to-pick-a-receiver.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/196712-nfl-2k1-dreamcast-screenshot-between-plays.jpg</snapshot9>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3955-g.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>NFL 2K is an American football video game series developed by Visual Concepts and published by Sega.[1] Based on the National Football League, the series was originally exclusive to Sega's Dreamcast video game console. As the foremost "2K" title, it marked the beginning of a running athletics series that eventually led to the spinning off of 2K's sports publishing business under the name of 2K Sports. Upon the Dreamcast's discontinuation, the series continued to be published for other sixth generation game systems and became the chief competitor of EA Sports's Madden NFL series. However, after the competitively priced NFL 2K5 significantly reduced sales of that year's Madden release, EA signed an exclusivity deal with the NFL that made Madden NFL the only series allowed to use NFL team and player names. After losing the NFL license, Visual Concepts made a brief return to developing football games with the release of All-Pro Football 2K8, which featured former NFL players.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0f761d9d-169f-4446-9d3e-fced401a35f8.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/941bb673-f387-42e6-980a-6a7743a138b6.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>