<Game>
	<Name>NHL 2K2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:NHL 2K2 was the second game in the series, and featured Chris Drury on the cover. Drury was a key member of the 2001 Stanley Cup Champion Colorado Avalanche team that won the year prior to the game's release. The game was released very late for a hockey title, and was the last Dreamcast title to ever be released in North America.Colorado forward Chris Drury The game was met with a number of positive reviews and currently holds a solid 80 on metacritic, but was not a commercial success due to the state of the Dreamcast console at the time. Game Modes:ExhibitionA quick head to head gameTournamentWill let you set up a custom bracket-style tournament with 4, 8 or 16 teamsPlayoffsSkip the season and jump right into the NHL Playoffs with 16 teams and 7 game series. SeasonSeason allows you to play an entire NHL season. This is a bare bones mode, players can trade and track stats but that's about it.</plot>
	<releasedate>14/2/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>19485</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nhl-2k2/3030-21789/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/19485-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WIHN3VL.png</banner1>
	<Notes>NHL 2K is a series of hockey games by 2K Sports for the Dreamcast, PlayStation 2, Nintendo GameCube, Xbox, iPhone, Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and the Wii. Initially discontinued after the release of NHL 2K11 in 2010, the brand was revived on mobile devices in 2014. The games are officially licensed from the National Hockey League and NHL Players Association. While its games were released on consoles, its main competition was EA Sports' NHL video games.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b5bc0ffd-87da-460b-acef-7542cb5bfa6e.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dee187d4-5875-4179-918c-19d9cc9c1ca9.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
</game>