<Game>
	<Name>Nomad Soul, The (France)</Name>
	<plot>You are the Nomad Soul, a computer game player sucked into another dimension. At first you take on the role of Kay'l, an Omikron police officer. As Kay'l you must figure out what has happened over the past few days due to memory loss. As the game progresses you will find a plot that twists and turns at every corner. For transportation, you use a "Slider" that you can control manually or set to auto-pilot to take you throughout much of Omikron. When given a choice of what to say to a person, your answers will almost always affect your future in the game and how people act towards you. Throughout the course of the game you may take on the role of up to 41 different characters through the use of a "Soul Transfer" spell. In most situations, even if you die, you will be "virtually" reincarnated through the next character that touches you. In your travels you must explore the vast city of Omikron. You may visit anywhere in the city that you wish to, even if it isn't important for finishing the game. An example of this freedom is when in the "red light" district of Omikron, you find a flyer about a "prohibited" concert that you may attend. If you go to the concert, the band will play a full length song for you. Also in this part of Omikron you can attend "peep-shows" and go visit the sex shops. All items are kept inside your SNEAK device on your wrist, 18 items may be carried at once and there is a transfer system set up so items can be stored and retrived at another station. Also, in Omikron, it is important that with each character you take them through combat training so you are at a higher fighting level. Although most of the game takes place in adventure mode there are two other modes available to use at certain points throughtout the game, shooting and fighting. In the fighting mode, your character knows a variety of moves and will have to fight off his opposition. In the shooting mode, you find yourself in a first-person perspective shooting after thugs mostly, although you will run into some more interesting enemies to shoot later in the game. As they say in Omikron, "Who will you be after you die?"</plot>
	<releasedate>21/6/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Eidos, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>5564</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/omikron-the-nomad-soul/3030-18133/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/5564-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/203223-omikron-the-nomad-soul-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/203225-omikron-the-nomad-soul-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/88633/2501297-vlcsnap-2013-06-20-18h29m43s87.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13749/404909-omikron_02.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13749/404846-untitledoz6.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13749/404845-tnscy9.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13749/404830-omikronchick2.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13749/404826-omikronchick1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13749/404823-omikronb.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13749/404821-omikron_screen002.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13749/404818-omikron_3.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13749/404814-omikron_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/eCF3Dte.png</banner1>
</game>