<Game>
	<Name>Prince of Persia - Arabian Nights (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Story:The game's plot revolves around the betrayal of the Sultan of Persia by his brother Assad and the resulting kidnap of the Princess of Persia. The Prince must chase down the evil half-tiger half-man Prince Rugnor who wishes to wed the Princess. The chase takes the Prince through various levels filled with traps and architecturally baffling chasms. During the course of the Prince's journey the main plot is told by cutscenes. In these the player discovers that unsurprisingly the Princess is unwilling to submit to Rugnor. Once the Prince finally chases down Rugnor a climatic final battle ensues in which the Princess is tied to a massive gear heading towards a squishy demise. The Prince must kill Rugnor before the Princess meets her fate.Gameplay:The game takes place on 17 separate levels which involve some 3D platforming and combat. Scattered throughout each level are numerous traps that more often than not result in instant death.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/3/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<thegamesdb_id>8147</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/prince-of-persia-3d/3030-10863/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8147-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/8147-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5911/775415-pop3d2.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5911/775414-pop3d.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3419/617262-foto_prince_of_persia_3d1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3419/617261-foto_prince_of_persia_3d.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7473/213035-prince_of_persia_3d.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7473/213034-pop5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7473/213033-pop3d6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/g3ppZah.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>The Sultan of Persia and his son-in-law are visiting the Sultan's brother, Assan. The friendly family meeting soon turns into a nightmare: Assan kills the young Prince's bodyguards, locks him up in a prison, and captures the Sultan. The reason is a little disagreement between the brothers regarding matrimonial arrangements: it appears that the Sultan had promised his daughter to Assan's son, Rugnor, and later broke his promise by letting her marry the Prince. In the resulting turmoil, the Sultan is killed, and the Princess is kidnapped by Rugnor, a ruthless half-tiger creature. The Prince must figure out a way to find Rugnor, defeat him, and rescue his wife. Prince of Persia 3D is just what its title implies: an action platformer with puzzle-solving elements in the style of the previous Prince of Persia games, but set in a three-dimensional environment. The Prince still has to time his jumps, avoid deadly traps, interact with the environment, and fight Rugnor's minions who will try to stop him.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1eb69429-45eb-45f3-8faa-fab4ac998fd7.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/86a1119f-e960-4ea5-b011-0383894f07e0.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot8>http://images.launchbox-app.com/522a3df9-6b6c-49a9-9ae7-0fa0a84e87df.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/42ec644d-fc70-45bc-8088-a51675d62e49.png</snapshot9>
	<rating>4</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Developer>Red Orb Entertainment</Developer>
	<Publisher>Mattel Interactive</Publisher>
</game>