<Game>
	<Name>Railroad Tycoon II (Europe) (En,Fr,De)</Name>
	<plot>Campaign The campaign consists of six scenarios each of which has three levels of completion and three different options for a starting bonus.  The Iron Seed Objectives: Bronze: Connect Baltimore and Washington and haul as least 4 loads.Silver: Connect to Harpers Ferry and haul at least 8 loads.Gold: Connect to Philadelphia and haul at least 12 loads.Bonuses:  $50,000.10% Lower track building costs.John Bull 2-4-0 available early. Handle on the Bread Basket Objectives: Bronze: Connect New York and Chicago and haul 8 loads.Silver: Your company value must exceed $4,000,000.Gold: Complete by 1858.Bonuses:   $80,000.15% Lower Track Building Cost. 20% Steel Revenue. Bridging a Nation   Objectives: Bonuses are instead objective options for this objective. Complete selected route and haul 6 loads.Have a company equity of $10,000,000 or more.Do it by 1878 and  have a personal net wealth of $8,000,000 or more.Bonuses (Objective choices): St. Louis to Sacramento.St. Paul to Seattle.New Orleans to Los Angeles. Silver Booms and the Market Busts Objectives: Personal net worth of over $5,000,000 by 1905.Personal net worth of over $10,000,000 by 1900.Personal net worth of over 20,000,000 by 1895.Bonuses:  20% Stock Price. 15% Lower track building cost. 20% Security.  10% Steam Engine Speed.2-8-0 Consolidation Available Early.  15% Cattle Revenue. Whistle Stops and Promises Objectives:  Take the President to 13 cities.14 Cities.16 Cities.Bonuses: Use 4-4-2 Atlantic (High top speed, Terrible grade performance).Use 2-6-0 Mogul (Mid-range top speed and grade performance).Use 2-6-0 Camelback (Low top speed, Outstanding grade performance). Crossing the Great Divide Objectives:  Connect Halifax and Vancouver and haul 6 loads.Company worth must exceed $20,000,000.Company worth must exceed $50,000,000.Bonuses: Manager Van Horne. 10% Lower track building costs.2-8-0 Consolidation Early. 10% Increase in engine speed.One Lever improvement in credit rating. 10% Fast station turn around. Cheats To enter cheat codes press [Tab], type the code and then hit enter.    $1,000,000 for Railroad Company  - slush fund  $1,000,000 for Player - cattle futures $100,000,000 for Railroad Company - powerball  $100,000,000 for Player - king of the hillSkip Scenario - bigfoot Win Bronze - bigfootbronze Win Silver - bigfootsilver Win Gold- bigfootgold Lose Scenario - bobo Double Maximum Train Speed - speed racer Double Industrial Center Output - overtime Competitor's Trains Crash - casey jones Cities Grow Faster - viagra All Trains Are Available - show me the trains All Trains Are AMD103 - amd103 Access All Territories - let me in</plot>
	<releasedate>11/3/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Gathering of Developers|Take-Two Interactive Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11105</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/railroad-tycoon-ii/3030-10886/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11105-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11105-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/277360-railroad-tycoon-ii-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/15/155745/2270529-image_017.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/15/155745/2270528-image_016.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/15/155745/2270527-image_015.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/15/155745/2270526-image_014.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/15/155745/2270525-image_013.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/15/155745/2270524-image_012.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/15/155745/2270523-image_011.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/15/155745/2270522-image_010.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/15/155745/2270521-image_009.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/15/155745/2270520-image_008.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/LoEMDc2.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Establish yourself as a mogul to be reckoned with as you work your way up the ranks of the railway industry in this strategy game. Expand your domain across continents and a changing global marketplace. Build the Transcontinental Railway or the Orient Express. Run Steam train through the jungles of Africa, or electric trains through the Swiss Alps. Run your competitors out of town on a rail. An 18 scenario campaign lets you re-create history's greatest railroading feats and failures</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/669fc04c-33c9-4c34-a0e7-a787cd1f0203.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Take Two Interactive</Publisher>
</game>