<Game>
	<Name>Real Sound - Kaze no Regret (Japan) (v1.006)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Contents of the game, including a cloud box overlay and braille card.Real Sound: Kaze no Regret ("The Wind's Regret") is an audio game released for the Sega Saturn by Japanese studio WARP, Inc. and directed and produced by the company's founder Kenji Eno. The game was released on June 15, 1997. The game was re-released for the Dreamcast in 1999 with a visual mode that included pictures and photos to accompany the story, but this version of the game also relies entirely upon sound and audio cues for gameplay.The game came as a result of contact that Eno had with blind and visually impaired fans of WARP games. Eno was fascinated that the visually impaired would be fans of his games. He thought his games were very visually rich. He even went so far as to contact some of these fans to find out how they played his games if they could not see the games. As a result Eno decided to make a game that would be audio only, with no graphics at all.Real Sound: Kaze no Regret was a very large influence on further games from Kenji Eno and WARP, Inc. Games that came afterward from the company would take gameplay elements from Real Sound. Enemy Zero featured invisible enemies that could only be through sound. D2, also from WARP, included parts of the game where the player's character was rendered blind and the player must rely on sound, following a voice to get through the game. D2 also featured a sequence where the character was rendered deaf.Story:Real Sound: Kaze no Regret's story and plot revolve around a love story; the love story between Mizu Sakura and Hiroshi Nonoiti. The two characters meet while still very young in school and fall in love. Mizu and Hiroshi decide to meet one evening to elope. Mizu does not show up at the clock tower where they planned to meet and shortly afterward is transferred to a new school, separated from Hiroshi. The two characters meet coincidentally again. The game continues to follow the characters as Hiroshi is a college student and as Mizu is looking for a job and is starting her career.The game features the voices of Ai Maeda, an anime voice actress, and Miho Kanno, a Japanese actress and idol singer.Gameplay:Real Sound: Kaze no Regret is a completely spoken and audio game, as a result the game's game play elements were unique and different than most games that came before it. The player would listen to the game's story, similar in manner to a radio play, and would be prompted at particular times to make decisions in the branching storyline. These decisions would be prompted by an audible chime. Some have described the game play as almost like an audio "choose your own adventure" game.Soundtrack:Real Sound ~The Wind's Regret~ The MusicThe soundtrack to Kaze no Regret was composed by Keiichi Suzuki, who is most known for his work on the MOTHER series. It was distributed by Pony Canyon and released August 20, 1997. The song 'Takeyama's Wanderings' was written by Kenji Eno.Real Sound ~The Wind's Regret~ The MusicTotal length: 70:55The Wind's Regret Main Theme ~ Piano VersionA New NostalgiaThe Wind's Regret Main Theme ~ Quartet VersionLet's Go by TransportHer Name is IzumiAn Empty PlaceMorning SaxophoneWas It the Same DreamHer Name is AsamiWeather Forecast 1Weather Forecast 2Weather Forecast 3Weather Forecast 4Izumi's Question MarkWhat a Fool I Am (Ambient Version)A Sad and Beautiful TimeThe Wind's Regret Main Theme ~ Piano Version by NanaIzumi's SuspicionNana RunsTakeyama's WanderingsFragments of NostalgiaNostalgic AmbienceCardboard songDriving HighWhat a Fool I AmThe Wind's Regret Main Theme ~ Orchestra VersionRegretTrivia:Real Sound: Kaze no Regret was to be the first game in a three part trilogy of audio only adventure games to be created by WARP. The second game in the series was to be titled Real Sound: Kiri no Orgel ("Mists of the Music Box"). Advertisements even appeared for the game in some Japanese video game magazines. The game was under development by the company but was never completed supposedly due to problems with voice and sound compression. The game was to be a horror game.The third game in the Real Sound trilogy was to be a comedy game, Spy Lunch. The game never made it past the planning stages and development never fully began.Real Sound: Kaze no Regret to this day is still very popular with the visually impaired and the blind as it is one of the few such video(?) games ever released.One branch of the possible storyline for Kaze no Regret was broadcast in its entirety on the radio in Japan.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/7/1997</releasedate>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/real-sound-kaze-no-regret/3030-31199/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2579/1696689-61pef5wgqol.jpg</boxart1>
</game>