<Game>
	<Name>Roadsters (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>Roadsters is a car racing game that features both licensed cars from manufacturers like Mitsubishi, Alfa Romeo, Lotus, etc., and unlicensed cars from imaginary manufacturers that are based and bare great resemblance to their equivalent, real car models. The game has 8 racers and 34 cars from which you can choose from and 4 modes in total:1. Roadster Trophy  The player starts by selecting one of the available racers and is given a sum of money that must be used to acquire a car. There are 3 divisions in which the player can compete on with the 3rd being of the easiest difficulty and requiring less money to participate;  the 1st being the most difficult one and needing a higher amount of money in order to participate. More money can be earned by winning the races and that in turn allows to buy new cars or upgrade the ones that are already in  possession.Multi-Player  Multi-player mode supports up to 2 human players that can compete in any of the available circuits with 4 more CPU controlled racers. The mode allows for either vertical or horizontal split screen. Quick Race  In Quick Race the player can select the racer, car, circuit and weather conditions, and race against 7 more CPU controlled players.Time Trial  Like Quick Race mode, the player can also select here the racer, car, circuit and weather conditions but without the competition of the other modes, the player races against time for as many laps as the player wants.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/4/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Titus Software Corporation</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>29241</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/roadsters/3030-25254/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/29241-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/194746-roadsters-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/194745-roadsters-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/dZcQAD7.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Roadsters is a racing game released by Titus Software in 2000 for the Nintendo 64, PlayStation, Sega Dreamcast and Game Boy Color.[1][2] It is a car racing game that features both licensed cars from manufacturers (e.g. Mitsubishi, Alfa Romeo, Lotus) and unlicensed cars from imaginary manufacturers that are based and bare great resemblance to their equivalent, real car models. The game also includes a multi-player mode supports up to 2 human players that can compete in any of the available circuits with 4 more CPU controlled racers.[3] This was the only game Titus published for the PlayStation.[1] It has met with mixed to negative reviews from critics (with the exception of the N64 version, which received positive reception). Video game developer Player 1 was originally plan to release the game for the PlayStation 2, but it was canceled.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/04d27128-d304-4d3d-aea2-400f6687e9a0.jpg</boxart2>
</game>