<Game>
	<Name>Sega Smash Pack - Volume 1 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Sega Smash Pack: Volume One was the first, and ultimately the only collection of classic Sega games released for the Dreamcast.  It contains only some games in common with the PC Sega Smash Pack and Smash Pack 2 so is an iteration of the concept rather than a port of that collection.This collections features ten emulated Genesis/Mega Drive titles. These games are Altered Beast, Columns, Golden Axe, Phantasy Star II, Shining Force, Vectorman, Revenge of Shinobi, Sonic the Hedgehog, Streets of Rage 2 and Wrestle War. This was the first American release of Wrestle War.It also included two games that had been previous released for Dreamcast: Sega Swirl, which had been given away on various discs and Virtua Cop 2, which had been previously available for Dreamcast only in Japan.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/4/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>11095</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sega-smash-pack-volume-1/3030-10946/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11095-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11095-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/29597-sega-smash-pack-volume-1-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414233-sega-smash-pack-volume-1-dreamcast-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414234-sega-smash-pack-volume-1-dreamcast-screenshot-game-selection.jpg</snapshot2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/axG8V0Q.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Sega Smash Pack Volume 1 was released for the Dreamcast in 2001 in North America only. It featured twelve games: Altered Beast Columns Golden Axe Phantasy Star II The Revenge of Shinobi Sega Swirl Shining Force Sonic the Hedgehog Streets of Rage 2 Vectorman Virtua Cop 2 Wrestle War</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fda523cd-e8b2-47de-9804-cd06a0616440.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>