<Game>
	<Name>Sentimental Graffiti 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Sentimental Graffiti 2 happens some time after the first game, and instead of high-school setting it fast forwards to college setting. However, the protagonist in this game is 2nd year university student, Kouhei Shiina, whereas the original protagonist from the first game had died in an accident and while he is not present in this game, all the heroines he met in the original game are back in this sequel, ready for the new protagonist to meet them for the very first time and start a relationship. Kouhei is a member of a photography club and is looking for someone who will model for his photo exhibition for the upcoming college festival. That's where twelve heroines come in.The game is played in both 1st-person and 3rd-person isometric perspective. While 1st-person perspective is used in communication with other characters and looking at places up close, the isometric view is used while traversing the city which features many locations which can be accessed. Both city and locations are affected by the time of day and will feature different graphics during morning, twilight or night, as well as affecting stores and other locations which may be open or closed at the decided time. The map features 29 locations in total, some of which can be further explored from the inside. Your actions cost time and clock progresses whenever you do something or go someplace. By the end of the day, you return to your dorm and continue the exploration the next day.</plot>
	<genre>Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>NEC Interchannel, Ltd.</Developer>
	<boxart1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/309482-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-front-cover.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/309483-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/309484-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796003-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796004-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-screenshot-enter-your-name.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796006-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-screenshot-game-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796007-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-screenshot-talking-to-takenouchi.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796008-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-screenshot-college-campus.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796010-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-screenshot-running-into-honoka.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796011-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-screenshot-flower-store.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796012-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-screenshot-exploring-the.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796013-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-screenshot-convenience-store.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/796014-sentimental-graffiti-2-dreamcast-screenshot-city-at-night.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>