<Game>
	<Name>Shenmue II (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Shenmue II is the sequel to the acclaimed Shenmue. It took the main character, Ryo Hazuki, to China in order for him to continue his quest to avenge his father's death. The game was released on Dreamcast in Japan and Europe on September 6th, 2001 and November 23rd, 2001 respectively. The North American Dreamcast version was cancelled but released on the Xbox a year later on October 28th. The Xbox port was released in Europe as well on March 23rd, 2003. Despite clear hanging threads, Shenmue 3 was never released and the story never concluded.Story:henmue II, continues the adventure of Ryo Hazuki as he tries to find Lan Di, the man who murdered his father. The game begins as Ryo arrives in Hong Kong and begins his task given to him at the end of the first game - to find Master Lishao Tao - who might be able to point Ryo in the right direction.Shenmue II tells three chapters of the 16-chapter Shenmue story and continues to portray Ryo's journey from adolescence into adulthood. The entire first game is considered chapter one and chapter two is an untold story of the ship ride from Japan to Hong Kong. Chapter three takes place in Hong Kong whilst chapter four concerns Ryo's stay in Kowloon and chapter five is the story of Ryo in Guilin at the end of the game.</plot>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/1/13158/1130264-gb.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/9/93507/1360466-save_2.jpg</boxart2>
	<fanart1>http://img14.deviantart.net/6bc0/i/2012/005/7/5/shenmue_ii_fan_cover_by_ryohazuki68-d4leb60.jpg</fanart1>
	<VideoURL>Ie-gswHz2QY</VideoURL>
	<Notes>"Across the sea, from a distant land in the East, he shall rise appear"...the epic adventure of Shenmue is re-borne once again as Ryo Hazuki arrives in Hong Kong on his continued mission to avenge his father's death and discover the truth behind the Phoenix Mirror. In a world almost three times bigger than the original, you will have to interact with many people and gain the knowledge you need through a variety of experiences, but beware who you trust. Full of emotional encounters, Shenmue II is a compelling and majestic production that will engulf your entire existence...</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL1>NR_LIqh4oeE</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/149e62f2-7ddf-4d3d-9dcf-b8c2f3e71cda.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cd5d54da-885a-407c-bdd1-6c85ed2ef63d.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>4.6458312500000005</rating>
	<genre>Adventure; Role-Playing</genre>
	<Developer>Sega AM2</Developer>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>