<Game>
	<Name>SnoCross Championship Racing (Europe) (En,Fr,De)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Sno-Cross Championship Racing is a snowmobile racing game that was released for the Playstation and Dreamcast in 2000 and 2001. The game was developed by UDS and published by Crave in the US and by Ubisoft in Europe. There are very snowmobile games and this game's closest competition was Polaris SnoCross. The game uses Yamaha snowmobiles exclusively.  Game Modes:Championship Championship mode is the main single player mode. Here you'll races in locales all over the world and must finish in third or better to continue. Earn money for your rankings and spend it on repairs and upgrades. There are three separate classes: 500cc, 600cc and 700cc.Single RaceIn single race mode you can select any track in the game and race either by yourself with computers or against a second player via split-screen multiplayer.Time TrialRace against the clock in time trial mode trying to set the fastest time.Hill Climbing Hill climbing is popular among snowmobile riders and it is in included in this game as an unlockable mode; you can only try this after completing the 500cc championship.Track EditorThe game also comes with a track editor that allows you to create your own tracks. The track editor is divided into two parts: the track piece section and the track edit screen. In the track piece selection you'll pick which piece you'd like to use, be it a straight path, a sharp turn, a jump, etc. Once you have your piece selected you switch over to the track edit screen and place it.</plot>
	<releasedate>22/8/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Crave Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11090</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sno-cross-championship-racing/3030-19890/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11090-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11090-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/239078-sno-cross-championship-racing-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/QwmeYIm.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Strap on your goggles and helmet, choose your favorite Yamaha sled, and hit the courses. Gain experience day and night, sun rain or snow, racing on the icy flats of Vladivostok, the slopes of Aspen, and the tunnels of Nagano.  But, the real challenge starts when you enter the race circuit. Start with the 500cc sleds, win races, upgrade your snowmobile, and unlock higher end sleds and new courses.. And, if you're looking for even more challenges, race head-to-head with your friends, go vertical on hill-climbing tracks, or create your own courses with the included track editor. The PC conversion has a higher polygon count, higher resolution on the textures, and more accurate physics.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d58c3dc5-6d13-46a5-b1f7-5ee930f0709e.jpg</boxart2>
</game>