<Game>
	<Name>Snow Surfers (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>This game, called Rippin' Riders in the US, Snow Surfers in Europe, and Cool Boarders Burrrn (&#12463;&#12540;&#12523;&#12508;&#12540;&#12480;&#12540;&#12474;&#65381;&#12496;&#12540;&#12531;) in Japan, is a 1999 snowboarding game by UEP Systems for the Sega Dreamcast.Grab some serious air and get shredding in the safety of your own home. If you're into extreme sports then take a look at this. Snow Surfers is a joy to look at. It's almost as if you can feel the chill mountain air on your face as you prepare to descend the slopes at high speed. There are so many play modes and options in here it's hard to know where to start. Suffice to say that you'll need the nimblest of fingers to outperform your opponents in competition, and there's a plethora of tricks and manouevres to attempt. This will keep you busy for hours.</plot>
	<releasedate>26/8/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>9974</thegamesdb_id>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/9974-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/9974-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<Notes>This game, called Rippin' Riders in the US, Snow Surfers in Europe, and Cool Boarders Burrrn (クールボーダーズ･バーン) in Japan, is a 1999 snowboarding game by UEP Systems for the Sega Dreamcast. Grab some serious air and get shredding in the safety of your own home. If you're into extreme sports then take a look at this. Snow Surfers is a joy to look at. It's almost as if you can feel the chill mountain air on your face as you prepare to descend the slopes at high speed. There are so many play modes and options in here it's hard to know where to start. Suffice to say that you'll need the nimblest of fingers to outperform your opponents in competition, and there's a plethora of tricks and manouevres to attempt. This will keep you busy for hours.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3f632cda-7c7d-474e-8395-55df86c11dc9.jpg</boxart2>
	<Developer>UEP Systems</Developer>
	<Publisher>Sega (EU), UEP Systems (JP)</Publisher>
</game>