<Game>
	<Name>Spawn - In the Demon's Hand (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Basics:Spawn: In The Demon's Hand is a broad-mapped 3d fighting game. It has a large variety or unlockable characters, many items and weapons to pick up while traversing through the large, unique levels, and multiple modes of play.Single Player is basically battling through levels until the boss arrives (usually on a timer) collecting points and power-ups . Rinse, Wash, and Repeat. The cool thing about this is that almost everything in the game is unlockable, and playing through certain scenarios with different characters will cause different weapons to appear, and more things to unlock. Every character is equipped with a specific set of weapons at the launch of the first level, and opening chests gives you item drops, sometimes based on your equipped weapon, which makes it really hard to get everything in the game.Co-op is similar to Single player, but split screen and has a few different scenarios and unlockables.Multiplayer in this game is really where the game is the strongest. You get to take all the unlocked weapons anf characters, and destroy up to three of your friends in head-to-head body -cutting action. Some of the characters have a hover ability, some can punch people's torso right off their pelvis,. others shoot guns or have fire ball breath. As in the campaign style modes, there is also the abilty to open chests and get upgraded weapons, but it makes it a little more difficult to get open chest while you're getting kicked in the head by an angel with a halberd.There are a few other modes like a tiered team fighting mode, much like Mortal Kombat but with two people.Character ListSpawn: In the Demon's Hand features a total of thirty-seven playable characters, with twelve unlocked right from the beginning. Hidden characters are unlocked by beating the games boss mode with a certain character.Selectable CharactersAl SimmonsBrimstoneClownCogliostroGraceJessicaRedeemerSamSpawnTiffanyTremorTwitchUnlockable CharactersAdmonisher (Beat All Levels on Boss Mode Multiplay Without Continuing -14 Times)Angels E (Finish Boss Mode With Tiffany to Unlock)Angel Teneres (Finish Boss Mode With Soliel to Unlock)Army A (Finish Boss Mode With Overtkill to Unlock)Black Brimstone (Beat All Levels on Boss Mode Multiplay Without Continuing -20 Times) [To Select Hold L &amp; R Triggers and Press A]Cy-Gor (Finish Boss Mode With Tremor to Unlock)Dark Ages Spawn (Beat All Levels on Boss Mode Multiplay Without Continuing -5 Times)Gatekeeper (Finish Boss Mode With Hell Spawn to Unlock)Green Beret A (Finish Boss Mode With Jessica to Unlock)Hell Spawn (Finish Boss Mode With Redeemer to Unlock)Overtkill (Finish Boss Mode With Brimstone to Unlock)Skeleton I (Finish Boss Mode With Al Simmons to Unlock)Soldier I (Finish Boss Mode With Twitch to Unlock)Soliel (Finish Boss Mode With Grace to Unlock)Spawn I (Beat All Levels on Boss Mode Multiplay Without Continuing -1 Time)Spawn IV (Beat All Levels on Boss Mode Multiplay Without Continuing -10 Times)Sub Curse (Finish Boss Mode With The Curse to Unlock)The Curse (Finish Boss Mode With Spawn to Unlock)The Mafia (Finish Boss Mode With Sam to Unlock)Vacillator (Finish Boss Mode With Vindicator to Unlock)Vandalizer (Finish Boss Mode With Cogliostro to Unlock)Vaporizer (Finish Boss Mode With Vandalizer to Unlock)Vindicator (Finish Boss Mode With Clown to Unlock)Wolf I (Finish Boss Mode With Cy-Gor to Unlock)Zombie I (Finish Boss Mode With Gatekeepeer to Unlock)</plot>
	<releasedate>16/4/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>M - Mature</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>HF96Qm2_n9k</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2255</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spawn-in-the-demons-hand/3030-9555/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2255-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2255-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/2255-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2255-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/hPJw6Iw.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2255.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Todd McFarlane's dark comic book anti-hero, Spawn, is ready to give your Dreamcast hell. Play as Spawn (a.k.a. Al Simmons), or any of the anti-heroes or villains from the comics, such as Clown, Twitch, Overtkill, Angel, Redeemer and more in a battle royale blastfest. Not up to killing just anyone? Play Team Battle and join with a friend to blast those other guys! Just do your best to get to the big guy downstairs: Maelebogia, to reclaim your soul and return to life.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>HF96Qm2_n9k</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f24a8ca8-35a0-4cbe-b2aa-9c14425bf414.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8d06705a-3efc-4ebb-8889-7b38150b8951.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5a558ab6-2ee3-47df-aa9c-508e5e13f47c.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4e85ff45-1f82-4a57-b18d-4f0fbb9f88a8.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e1b4925e-fbe6-4e44-8b76-6f166c676b80.png</snapshot3>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>