<Game>
	<Name>Spec Ops II - Omega Squad (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Omega Squad is the only game in the Spec Ops series released on the Dreamcast. Players control a squad of special operations soldiers who must carry out a string of tactical missions across the planet. Unlike previous Spec Ops games, a single soldier is controlled instead of a complete squad. The mission objectives include destroying enemy compounds, recovering military hardware and rescuing hostages. They take place in five different locales: Antarctica, Korea, Pakistan, Thailand, and Germany. Each country has a specific mission that entails promoting the well being of the United States of America - there is no specific storyline but rather a collection of missions to complete. Most of them are based on possible future events in the 21st century, not based on existing, historical conflicts.The success of the mission depends on the preparations (determining the equipment), which weapons are chosen and which soldier is picked. Each soldier has different abilities and some are better suited for specific missions than others. The six classed include infantry, grenadier, machine gunner, sniper, close quarters, and demolition. Each class has a different payload and arsenal to his disposal, including items such as medical kits and optical devices that are restricted to a specific soldier.The game is shown from a first-person perspective, common for the Windows titles in the series, but not the PlayStation console versions.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/4/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ripcord Games</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.1</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11088</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spec-ops-ii-omega-squad/3030-22351/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11088-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11088-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/165706-spec-ops-ii-omega-squad-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ku0pbzW.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Spec Ops is an military video game franchise, created by Zombie Studios. The games have primarily been launched on the PC, PlayStation and Dreamcast systems. The first titles in the series were developed by Zombie Studios, and later titles by Runecraft. The same goes for publishers: initially the games were published by Ripcord Games, and later by Take-Two Interactive. Other developers and publishers have since been brought in for spin-off titles and sequels[1] The Spec Ops franchise was intended to introduce a realistic first/third-person shooter experience and immerse the player in a two-man team gameplay. The first two games were well received; and the PlayStation and Dreamcast sequels, developed by Runecraft, received lower review scores.[2] The latest game in the series, Spec Ops: The Line, was highly acclaimed for its narrative, based on the novel Heart of Darkness.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3169f146-0345-432e-a936-b4c4fcb2bd28.jpg</boxart2>
</game>