<Game>
	<Name>Speed Devils (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>A straightforward racing game. You race for money to upgrade your car and open up new tracks.  Each track can be played at a different time of the day and with different weather conditions.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/4/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Ubi Soft Entertainment Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>S-kwVYSjzzc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>19332</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/speed-devils/3030-5819/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/19332-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/9814-speed-devils-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/91996-speed-devils-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17513-speed-devils-dreamcast-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17514-speed-devils-dreamcast-screenshot-racing-in-the-rain.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17515-speed-devils-dreamcast-screenshot-mexico.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17516-speed-devils-dreamcast-screenshot-in-car-view.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17517-speed-devils-dreamcast-screenshot-nevada.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17518-speed-devils-dreamcast-screenshot-canada.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17519-speed-devils-dreamcast-screenshot-two-player-split-screen.jpg</snapshot7>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/19332.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Speed Devils is a series of video games developed by Ubisoft's Montreal studio for Microsoft Windows in 1998 and Dreamcast in 1999. Both Speed Busters: American Highways (also known as just Speed Busters) and Speed Devils are racing games in which the courses feature hazards such as dinosaurs rolling boulders, and UFOs in exotic locales including Louisiana, Louisiana Tornado, New York City, New York City Winter, Mexico, Nevada, Aspen Summer, Aspen Winter, Canada (Supposedly northern Quebec), Canada Light Winter, Canada Heavy Winter, Montreal Industrial, Hollywood, and Hollywood Disaster. The console version's career mode allowed a player to rise a racer through the ranks of a fictional racing league. Colorful rivals would challenge you to accomplish certain feats during races, making accompanying bets using prize money from competition. Money earned from gambling and performance is used to buy cars, upgrade them, and maintain them. There are 4 classes in the game.Each class had 4 people. Starting in Class D, they are Jack, Ms. Penny Parker, Alfanso, and Luigi. Class C has Vanessa, Blue Bullet, James, and Tex. Class B has Billy-Sue Bayou, Cora and Antonio Martinez, and Jake. The top class, Class A, has Cory, Pat, Yu and Driver X. Then you must beat Driver X, the boss of the game. The game also supports five players on one Dreamcast console.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>S-kwVYSjzzc</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dd34a389-0e4c-4d7e-bed0-f2d20a30e4ce.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/14726814-1f61-44c0-9025-7e3058fb1ecd.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>