<Game>
	<Name>Star Wars - Episode I - Racer (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:Star Wars: Episode I - Racer is a fast paced anti-gravity racing game based on the infamous "Pod Race" from The Phantom Menace movie. The player can reach extremely high speeds and use quick reflexes to dodge oncoming racers and obstacles. The racer begins each of the three lap races with three lives, meaning that in contrast to the film crashing doesn't mean your race is over, but is more of a minor setback. Once the lives are all used up, however, the racer is disqualified. Alongside the home console (of which just the N64 version was published by Nintendo) and computer versions, a port for the Game Boy Color was released with entirely different tracks, but similar core gameplay. Of greater note is Star Wars: Racer Arcade (developed jointly by Sega AM5 [later renamed Sega Rosso] and Lucasarts), which put the public in the seat of Anakin Skywalker's Pod with a cockpit shaped control deck. Two levers were used to control the game, mirroring events in the film. There are only four tracks in the Arcade, many less than the other versions.Characters:Note: While the characters are given individual backstories which show some to be inexperienced or unmotivated to seek victory, the game treats them all as dedicated and talented racers.Anakin SkywalkerA hero from the film which the game is based on. Anakin is a young human, notable for being the only of his race capable of participating in the dangerous game of podracing.SebulbaSebulba, a Dug, is a popular and successful racer who worked his way to the top by cheating. He is the only racer in the game to have a weapon. When using Sebulba's taunt, a flamethrower spouts out sideways.Bozzie BarantaOnce a mechanic for Gasgano, Bozzie chose to become a racer. He was fairly successful in this venture.Aldar BeedoWhile Aldar Beedo is a talented racer, his first priority is his work as a hitman, taking out racers to pave the way to victory for whoever pays for his services.Toy DampnerDampner is a menacing pilot. While he is known to race elsewhere, he prefers the tracks of Oovo IV, where he is a crowd favorite.Dud BoltA racer hired by Sebulba who is paid per race based on how many competing pods he is able to take out.GasganoAn experienced and talented racer who does not hesitate to take out racers who get in his way.Mars GuoA loudmouth braggart with a fondness for gambling and drinking. While he is a competent racer, his tendency to anger other racers often leads to his downfall.Ebe EndocottOnce a daredevil delivery man, Endocott was encouraged by his boss to take up podracing, where his daredevil ways and piloting skills let him achieve some success.Cy YungaA talented racer with an advanced pod. Yunga is only available in-game through a cheat code, causing him to replace "Bullseye" Navior.Ratts TyerellRatts Tyerell is a racer who gained success for his swift reflexes. He owns one of the largest podracers in the circuit.Fud SangA somewhat mediocre and unknown racer, who nevertheless is paranoid of being sabotaged by his opponents.Boles RoorA podracer who also excels at singing, Roor pilots an outdated podracer that nevertheless boasts a high top speed.Ark "Bumpy" RooseRoose is a particularly dim-witted pilot who is known for indiscriminately ramming into opposing racers.Wan SandageSandage is a podracer who gained a great deal of fame on his homeworld of Ord Radama. However, he is less successful on other planets, where he suffers from disorientation.Jinn ReesoLittle is known about Jinn Reeso. He is only available for use through a cheat code, causing him to replace Mars Guo.Ben QuadinarosQuadinaros is an inexperienced racer, racing out of his league with an experimental four-engine pod.Slide ParamitaParamita is an elitist racer who uses a small pod. He disapproves of racers who use bulky podracers.MawhonicA very talented racer who sells parts in his spare time."Bullseye" NaviorNavior is a talented pilot who gained the nickname "Bullseye" for his unique looking eyes.Teemto PagaliesDespite being a drunkard, Pagalies is one of the least corrupt racers in the sport. He is a crowd pleaser, known for performing daring stunts during races.Ody MandrellMandrell is a racer who participates not for money, but for an adrenaline rush. His tough skin lets him survive otherwise deadly crashes.Neva KeeNeva Kee stands out among the other racers for his unique podracer. Its engines are attached directly to the cockpit and jut out behind it. This makes the cockpit the frontmost part of the pod, greatly increasing the risk of death in a crash.Elan MakElan Mak is actually a bounty hunter named Kam Nale. He joined the podracing circuit in order to hunt down Aldar Beedo. When he discovered his talent for the sport, he became involved with it beyond his initial intention to only use it as a front to catch Beedo.Clegg Holdfast A reporter for Podracing Quarterly, Holdfast participates in races primarily in order to get an inside scoop. Despite his ulterior motives, he showed himself to be a talented racer.Modes:N64, Dreamcast, PC and Mac Versions:There are four main modes within the game. The single player story mode, called "Tournament", is a sequence of championships of increasing difficulty composed of several races each in which the player competes for trophies. New tracks, racers and upgrades are unlocked by playing through it and Credits earned by winning races allows you to add new parts to your Pod. The difficulty level in Tournament mode can't be set. Free Race mode is essentially the exhibition mode in which players compete in single races but can't unlock rewards, however the level of the opponents' challenge can be determined. Time Attack is no different to any other mode with this name, as the player attempts to beat a track as quickly as possible. There is also a local two player mode, and the level and number of AI racers can be altered.PlanetsTatooineOnly two of the game's courses are found in Tatooine. The first is the Boonta Training Course, an easy map that acquaints players with the game. The second is the Boonta Classic, which is a relatively faithful recreation of the racetrack from the movie.Mon GazzaMon Gazza is a Mars-like world with vast red deserts, crowded but small cities, and lava pits. Tracks here often involve large open spaces that quickly turn to narrow corridors.Ando PrimeAndo Prime is an ice world. Tracks here take players through numerous caves, and often take them across slick, icy surfaces. Many tracks in this world feature a shortcut that opens up in laps 2 and on, in which the racer may turn left immediately past the finish line and enter a tent that hides a tunnel.AquilarisAquilaris is composed largely of water, and its tracks take place largely in the infrastructure built on the water. Players are taken through underwater tunnels through which massive fish may be seen.MalastareMalastare is a dark world with many sharp turns and visual obstructions such as gas and rocky pillars. Tracks here are narrow and unforgiving.BaroondaBaroonda is a jungle world. Players race through a variety of environments here, including thick rain forests, beaches, and a volcano.Ord IbannaRacetracks on Ord Ibanna are all located on infrastructure floating in a cloudy sky. These tracks often feature elevated shortcuts that are difficult to stay on because they are narrow.Oovo IVOovo IV is a large, asteroid-like world. Players race through open expanses along with urban areas. The highest speeds achievable in the game are found here in anti-gravity tunnels.Track OverviewThere are several tracks on each of the available planets, and every racer has at least one signature track. There are 25 tracks in total, divided into four categories: Amatuer, Semi-Pro, Galactic, and Invitational.Tracks in order of appearance:Boonta Training CoursePlanet - TatooineCircuit - AmateurAdvantage - SebulbaPod Racing!Mon Gazza SpeedwayPlanet - Mon GazzaCircuit - AmateurAdvantage - Teemto PagaliesBeedo's Wild RidePlanet - Ando PrimeCircuit - AmateurAdvantage - Aldar BeedoAquilaris ClassicPlanet - AquilarisCircuit - AmateurAdvantage - Clegg HoldfastMalastare 100Planet - MalastareCircuit - AmateurAdvantage - Dud BoltVengeancePlanet - Oovo IVCircuit - AmateurAdvantage - Fud SangSpice Mine RunPlanet - Mon GazzaCircuit - AmateurAdvantage - Mars Guo / Jinn ReesoSunken CityPlanet - AquilarisCircuit - Semi-ProAdvantage - "Bullseye" Navior / Cy YungaHowler GorgePlanet - Ando PrimeCircuit - Semi-ProAdvantage - Ratts TyerellDug DerbyPlanet - MalastareCircuit - Semi-ProAdvantage - Elan MakMore Pod Racing!Scrapper's RunPlanet - Ord IbannaCircuit - Semi-ProAdvantage - Wan SandageZugga ChallengePlanet - Mon GazzaCircuit - Semi-ProAdvantage - Boles RoorBaroo CoastPlanet - BaroondaCircuit - Semi-ProAdvantage - Neva KeeBumpy's BreakersPlanet - AquilarisCircuit - Semi-ProAdvantage - Ark "Bumpy" RooseExecutionerPlanet - Oovo IVCircuit - GalacticAdvantage - Toy DampnerSebulba's LegacyPlanet - MalastareCircuit - GalacticAdvantage - SebulbaGrabvine GatewayPlanet - BaroondaCircuit - GalacticAdvantage - Anakin SkywalkerAndobi Mountain RunPlanet - Ando PrimeCircuit - GalacticAdvantage - MawhonicDethro's RevengePlanet - Ord IbannaCircuit - GalacticAdvantage - Ody MandrellFire Mountain RallyPlanet - BaroondaCircuit - GalacticAdvantage - Ebe EndocottBoonta ClassicPlanet - TatooineCircuit - GalacticAdvantage - SebulbaAndo Prime CentrumPlanet - Ando PrimeCircuit - InvitationalAdvantage - Slide ParamitaAbyssPlanet - Ord IbannaCircuit - InvitationalAdvantage - Bozzie BarantaThe GauntletPlanet - Oovo IVCircuit - InvitationalAdvantage - GasganoInfernoPlanet - BaroondaCircuit - InvitationalAdvantage - Ben QuadinarosEven though the planets host multiple races, it does not mean that those races are at all similar.Attribute OverviewEach pod has 15 total attributes that determine its racing performance. You can buy parts for them, but you can only affect 7 total attributes by doing so. The others are set in stone for each unique pod.Upgradeable Attributes:Repair Rate - Affects the speed at which the pod repairs its damage.How to Upgrade - Buy some REPAIR parts.Best Part: Cluster 2 Power Plug 7,000Cool Rate - Affects the speed at which the pod cools down just after using your boost.How to Upgrade - Buy some COOLING parts.Best Part: Turbo Coolant Pump 5,400Airbrake Inverse - Affects the speed at which a pod can slow itselfHow to Upgrade - Buy some BRAKING parts.Best Part: Quadrijet Air Brake 14,000Maximum Speed - Affects your top speed.How to Upgrade - Buy some MAX SPEED upgrades.Best Part: Block 6 Thrust Coil 20,000Acceleration - Affects the rate at which a pod can achieve its top speedHow to Upgrade - Buy some ACCELERATION upgrades.Best Part: Mag 6 Injector 14,000Turn Response - Affects the speed at which a pod reacts to steering commands.How to Upgrade - Buy some TURNING upgrades.Best Part: Control Stabilizer 7,500Anti-Skid - Affects the ability of the pod to stay on course during a hazardous race or through a sharp turn.How to Upgrade - Buy some TRACTION upgrades.Best Part: R-600 Repulsorgirp 6,000Non-Upgradeable Attributes:Maximum Turn Rate - How good a pod can turn.Deceleration Inverse - The rate at which a pod will slow down without applying brakes.Boost Thrust - Dictates how fast a pod can go during a boost.Heat Rate - How fast a pod overheats.Hover Height - How high a pod sits in the air whilst idling.Bump Mass - Dictates how much damage your pod deals during a collision.Damage Immunity - Your pod's ability to resist damage during collisions.Intersect Radius - The size of your pod. The larger it is, the more hard it will be to navigate tight spaces.Podracer OverviewSpeeds are in miles per hour (mph).Sebulba's Pod is the fastest pod before upgrades, capable of reaching speeds up to 600 mph without using boost.Ben Quadinaros has the fastest unmodified pod with boost, reaching speeds of over 1000 mph.The highest speed without cheats is in the neighborhood of 1400 mph, during the zero gravity portions of Oovo IV.The highest speed with cheats is reportedly roughly of 3000 mph.The only character with a weapon onboard their Pod is Sebulba, who has hidden flamethrowers on each side that can be activated to damage other racers.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/4/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>11083</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/star-wars-episode-i-racer/3030-13526/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11083-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/54180-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/54181-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17464-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17465-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-racing-demo.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17466-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-tatooine-track.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17467-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-tatooine-finish.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17468-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-ice-planet.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17469-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-crossing-a-bridge.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17470-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-imperial-city.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17471-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-in-an-elevated.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17472-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-anti-gravity.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/17473-star-wars-episode-i-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-two-player-split.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/nHqBE86.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/11083.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>At last! The first Star Wars game for the 128-bit Dreamcast lets you participate in the famous podrace sequence (which was the critical highlight of the 1999 film Star Wars: Episode I, The Phantom Menace). These lightning-quick vehicles are capable of reaching simulated speeds of up to 600 miles per hour, while skimming a mere 4 feet above the ground. You can race alone or against a friend in split-screen mode, on over more than 21 courses among eight worlds. Take the controls as Jedi-to-be Anakin Skywalker, or any one of over 20 podracers, and feel the full-force blast--while avoiding hazards such as methane lakes, meteor showers, and the unfriendly Tusken Raiders.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a3322680-dcaf-45f5-ad27-4acc887abd0e.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/47ce8fa7-7659-4867-8490-518174f669b2.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/84e7d14c-0ea4-4c8e-a246-d6734403842c.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/380cdaf6-b2a1-4124-b914-33e52644ead5.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b04db84c-7b9a-4b7c-97ef-748295d23a28.jpg</snapshot13>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</Publisher>
</game>