<Game>
	<Name>Super Robot Taisen Alpha (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Featured Series A list of the anime series which are featured in the game. Series that premiered in the Super Robot Wars series in this game are marked with "(new)".  Mobile Suit Gundam Mobile Suit Gundam 0080: War in the Pocket Mobile Suit Gundam 0083: Stardust Memory Mobile Suit Zeta Gundam Mobile Suit Gundam ZZ Mobile Suit Gundam: Char's Counterattack Mobile Suit Gundam F90 (units only, new) Mobile Suit Gundam F91 Mobile Suit Victory Gundam New Mobile Report Gundam Wing New Mobile Report Gundam Wing: Endless Waltz Mazinger Z Mazinkaiser (Banpresto Original version) Great Mazinger Getter Robo Getter Robo G Shin Getter Robo (manga version) Super Electromagnetic Robot Combattler V Super Electromagnetic Machine Voltes V Brave Raideen Invincible Steel Man Daitarn 3  Aura Battler Dunbine Super Dimensional Fortress Macross (new) Super Dimensional Fortress Macross: Do You Remember Love? (new) Macross Plus (new) Super Beast Machine God Dancougar Aim for the Top! Gunbuster Giant Robo: The Animation Neon Genesis Evangelion End of Evangelion (new) Banpresto Originals (original characters made for the game)Masoukishin - Lord of Elemental (Banpresto Original storyline) SRX (Banpresto Original storyline)  New FeaturesFull Animation. While every SRW up to this point had robots frozen in a single pose, with effects and weapons pasted on top of them when necessary, Alpha brings to robots to life allowing them to move separate parts of their body. Defend and Attack. Featured only in this game, this option allows you to defend an enemy attack while still using a counterattack. Both the defense and the attack are reduced in effectiveness, however.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/5/2000</releasedate>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-robot-wars-alpha/3030-22661/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/12421/417086-alphafront.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3346/897948-srwa_huckbeinmkiii.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3346/897799-srwa_tittiemissiles.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3346/897711-srwa_dscythehell.jpg</snapshot3>
</game>