<Game>
	<Name>Tennis 2K2 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es) (Rev A)</Name>
	<plot>Sequel to the original game which was released two years prior.The games graphics have been improved, and there is a greater roster of players to choose from. The most noteworthy addition is that of female players, such as Monica Seles and Venus and Serena Williams. You cannot however play as a male against a female.The gameplay is a lot faster than the original. The players you control move a lot faster, as do the AI computer players. Less diving, but more getting at shots that go behind you and over the shoulder shots.The game modes from the original are the same, featuring tournament mode, where you play against the pros; exhibition mode for a one-on-one, best-out-of-three game; and world tour mode which now features the option of creating and customizing your own player. Build you player up, buy equipment and hire pros to play in doubles matches with you.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/11/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ghoi7Awkgng</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>11078</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tennis-2k2/3030-14977/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11078-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11078-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8371/481968-t2k2_2.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8371/481967-t2k2_3.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8371/481966-t2k2_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8371/481964-t2k2_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8371/481859-virtua_tennis_2__11_.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8371/481858-virtua_tennis_2__6_.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8371/481857-virtua_tennis_2__12_.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8371/481855-virtua_tennis_2__1_.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8371/481853-virtua_tennis_2__8_.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8371/481852-virtua_tennis_2__7_.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/iHC4mxD.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The top seed is back. Take to the courts of Virtua Tennis 2 as you compete to become the world No1. Serve, smash and lob your way through 16 internationally top-ranked male and female players as you go head to head in singles matches or compete with up to 4 players in doubles and mixed doubles matches. With revamped Tournament, Exhibition and World Tour modes its game set and match Virtua Tennis 2.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>ghoi7Awkgng</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3eaa95c7-64fa-4f69-b83f-e57cba68788d.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>