<Game>
	<Name>Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The second of the Tokyo Xtreme Racers to appear on the Dreamcast, the game play is identically to the first. Once again, there is no specific start, or finish lines, it all depends on how well you drive, and how fast.This time round, there are more opponents to beat, roughly 120, and plenty of new cars to choose in your quest.For those unfamiliar with the Tokyo Xtreme Racer series, unlike other racing games, TXR 2 (and others in the series) implements a system found most commonly on fighting games, where each player has a life bar and the player with remain life wins the race. Different factors can cause the life bar of a player to deplete, include hitting into object, other cars, or just simply falling behind the lead car.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/4/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Crave Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11071</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tokyo-xtreme-racer-2/3030-5397/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11071-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11071-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/46291-tokyo-xtreme-racer-2-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/795302-tokyo-xtreme-racer-2-dreamcast-screenshot-time-to-personalise.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/795303-tokyo-xtreme-racer-2-dreamcast-screenshot-going-on-a-leisurely.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/795304-tokyo-xtreme-racer-2-dreamcast-screenshot-nice-shot-of-my.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17517/610470-tokyo_xtreme_racer_2.328292.jpg</snapshot4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/NpWVIQ3.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2, known as Shutokō Battle 2 (首都高バトル 2) in Japan and Tokyo Highway Challenge 2 in Europe, is the sequel to Tokyo Xtreme Racer, which is also on the Sega Dreamcast. Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2 has been enhanced with better sound quality and graphics over its predecessor. The game managed to produce two more sequels. It is the last game in the series that was produced for Sega Dreamcast. Some of the game's mechanics were implemented into Daytona USA 2001.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b7fd5980-4c36-42de-93a9-7af55471926e.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Crave Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>