<Game>
	<Name>Tokyo Xtreme Racer (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Tokyo Xtreme Racer was a launch title for the dreamcast and the second release in the Tokyo Highway Battle Series. The game is unlike most racing games in that there are no tracks per say an endless highway to race on. The game features a semi-open world although there are no sidequest and the world is rather limited, still it was two years before GTA 3 and so it felt bigger than it was. During the game the main goal is to win races again a variety of gangs. To do this the player drives up to a gang member's car and then flashes their headlight's initiating a race. During races each car has a life bar, the life bar of each car deteriorates for every few seconds they fall behind, a race is completed once one of the opponents' life bars is totally depleted.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/9/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Crave Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11070</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tokyo-xtreme-racer/3030-7007/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11070-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11070-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/213327-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35231-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35232-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-map-selection.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35233-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-car-selection-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35234-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-car-selection-2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35235-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-car-selection-3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35236-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-racing-1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35237-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-racing-2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35238-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-racing-3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35239-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-replay-1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/35240-tokyo-xtreme-racer-dreamcast-screenshot-replay-2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/NpWVIQ3.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Tokyo Xtreme Racer, known as Shutokō Battle (首都高バトル) in Japan and Tokyo Highway Challenge in Europe, is a racing video game for the Sega Dreamcast. Released in 1999 as one of the console's launch titles, the game was one of the first mission-based racing games. The gameplay involves the player challenging other drivers on the Shuto Expressway in order to gain money to modify and enhance his or her car. The game features a wide variety of Japanese cars and tuning parts to purchase as the player progresses through rivals. When released in Japan, Shutokō Battle was one of the best selling Dreamcast titles at this time. The game is based on illegal highway racing in Tokyo's Wangan highway with custom tuned cars. A such phenomenon is growing popular in Japan since the 90's with its dedicated manga (Shutokō Battle's biggest inspiration being Wangan Midnight), anime series and video games (C1 Circuit, Wangan Trial, Naniwa Wangan Battle).</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c8f8d1d0-c75b-49c2-8493-229019f2147c.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Crave Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>