<Game>
	<Name>Ultimate Fighting Championship (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Roster Tito Ortiz. Mikey Burnett Mark Coleman Gary Goodridge Jeremy Horn Matt Hughes Eugene JacksonTsuyoshi Kohsaka Tim Lajcik Gary Goodridge. Chuck Liddell Guy Mezger Pat Miletich Tito Ortiz Kevin Randleman Marco Ruas Bas Rutten Pedro Rizzo Mikey Burnett. Andre Roberts Frank Shamrock Maurice Smith Evan Tanner Ron Waterman Pete Williams  Gameplay: Won by tapout.Ultimate Fighting Championship uses an 8 directional D-Pad and 4 buttons - each one responsible for the fighter's different limb (LP, RP, LK,RK). The grappling moves, counters and submissions can be executed by pressing 2 specific buttons together. Each fighter has his own selection of moves. The fights can be won by knockout, point advantage or tapout. Apart from acassional spurting bits of blood and painful facial expressions ( and the endurance and stamina meters at the top of the screen) there are no visible indicators of damage taken by the fighters unlike the way damage is perfectly visible in later fighting games e.g. UFC Undisputed 2010, Fight Night Round 4or Mortal Kombat.Game modes A career mode submission type fighter. UFC mode - in this mode 8 fighters compete in order toget the silver belt which - when obtained - enables the player to play in the Champion Road and defend it. When the UFC mode is completed with a particular character his model and style become available in career mode.TournamentChampion Road - a character which previously obtained the Silver Belt has to defend it by fighting 12 challengers. After defeating the last opponent - Ulti Man - player is awarded with a golden belt for his character. Exhibition - a single match.Career mode - the player can choose from several martial arts styles of fighting (submission, sumo, kickboxing etc.), give character a name, slightly customize his appearance, and earn  experience points by winning fights that get gradually tougher. These points can be spent either on upgrading the  stats (endurance, stamina, punch skill, kick skill) or learning new moves. Each of the already beaten opponents can be challenged once again, but the player will earn a smaller sum of experience points. Ulti Man defeated by Tito Ortiz. Training</plot>
	<releasedate>30/8/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Crave Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>7771</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ultimate-fighting-championship/3030-13855/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/7771-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/198846-ultimate-fighting-championship-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/197865-ultimate-fighting-championship-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/7771-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/7771-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/199919-ultimate-fighting-championship-dreamcast-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/199920-ultimate-fighting-championship-dreamcast-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/199921-ultimate-fighting-championship-dreamcast-screenshot-creating.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/199922-ultimate-fighting-championship-dreamcast-screenshot-you-can.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/199923-ultimate-fighting-championship-dreamcast-screenshot-don-t.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/199924-ultimate-fighting-championship-dreamcast-screenshot-there.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/199925-ultimate-fighting-championship-dreamcast-screenshot-you-can.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/199926-ultimate-fighting-championship-dreamcast-screenshot-ufc-mode.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/7771-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/7771-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/VdSUFzl.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Ultimate Fighting Championship is based on the no-holds-barred martial art tournament of the same name. What makes the game (and the real-life counterpart) distinct from wrestling, boxing, and other fights is the variety of fighting styles in use; it is perfectly possible to end up with a judo master facing a kickboxer. The actual gameplay is simple enough. You have various basic moves, combos, holds, and so on. The complications come in the form of the huge list of moves, featuring many different styles. Hit your opponent until he gets knocked out, or force him to tap out early.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1409342b-dca1-4250-9e32-065731cf1167.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0f3ad0e9-19a0-47c2-b9a7-05dc14884bba.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8a2fa6dc-05c6-4825-8801-8aa1b9abadf7.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Crave</Publisher>
</game>