<Game>
	<Name>Urban Chaos (Europe) (En,Fr)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Urban Chaos is a third person action adventure game, that was released on the PC, Sega Dreamcast and Playstation. It was the first game developed by Mucky Foot Productions, and was published by Eidos. the game features both hand-to-hand combat and firearms, as well as large maps that can be freely roamed across.Another game, Urban Chaos: Riot Response, was released by Eidos in 2006, but other than a shared title, the two games are unrelated.It has been re-released digitally on PlayStation Network for PS3, PSP and PS Vita, and PC through Steam and GoG.com.Plot:The plot itself is split into two parts. The player initially takes on the role of police officer D'arci Stern, a new recruit in the Union City Police Department. Throughout the course of the game, Stern butts heads with a criminal gang known as the Wildcats, who are growing in power with disturbing speed. Through her contact with a man who identifies himself only as "Roper", Stern realizes that their eventual goal is to take over Union City. As D'arci makes her way deeper into the criminal underworld and uncovers more information about the Wildcats, she discovers that the gang has connections to mayoral candidate Bane, as part of their overall plans to wage war against the UCPD. As a Wildcat riot breaks out, the UCPD largely manages to bring the city back under control, mostly through D'arci's direct intervention.The second part of the plot deals with a criminal investigation into a brutal murder. D'arci discovers that the murder was carried out by Bane's mysterious bodyguards, the men in black. She also learns that he will stop at nothing to achieve power far beyond that of a city mayor. It turns out that Bane is involved with an ancient evil and preparing to invoke a dark ritual. While the rest of the UCPD is busy quelling the rioting Wildcats, D'arci and Roper must hunt Bane down and stop him before he completes his ritual and brings Hell to Earth.PC RequirementsWindows 95/98/Me/XP/7;Pentium 233 or above;4x CD-ROM drive;32MB RAM (Rec.), 64MB (Rec.);4MB DirectX 6.1 compatible graphics card;DirectX 6.1 compatible sound card;150MB free hard drive space.</plot>
	<releasedate>14/11/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Eidos, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.1</rating>
	<ESRB>M - Mature</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>8339</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/urban-chaos/3030-15032/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8339-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/8339-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/55663-urban-chaos-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/773299-urban-chaos-dreamcast-screenshot-title-screen-that-has-nothing.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/773300-urban-chaos-dreamcast-screenshot-opening-cinematic.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/773301-urban-chaos-dreamcast-screenshot-mission-select.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/773302-urban-chaos-dreamcast-screenshot-mission-briefing.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/773303-urban-chaos-dreamcast-screenshot-loading-screen-with-progress.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/773304-urban-chaos-dreamcast-screenshot-the-chaos-of-falling-leaves.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/773305-urban-chaos-dreamcast-screenshot-the-urban-of-getting-your.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/773306-urban-chaos-dreamcast-screenshot-beating-up-an-offenseless.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/773307-urban-chaos-dreamcast-screenshot-sweet-mother-of-bambi-what.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/773308-urban-chaos-dreamcast-screenshot-the-sirens-give-crooks-a.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/8339-g.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>As the 2nd millennium ends, the cities are over-ran with Apocalyptic violence. Is this down to urban frustrations, or a sinister cult controlling everybody? You are either cop D'Arcy Stern or former soldier Roper McIntyre, and have to find the answers, but more importantly put a stop to the carnage.  This involves a succession of action-packed non-linear missions. The environment incorporates shadows, rain, fog and a day/night cycle. Police cars, motorcycles and ambulances must be controlled during some missions. There are many ways to 'settle' the enemies - car chases, hand-to-hand combats and action movie-style shoot outs for example.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/445473aa-a6b7-48c1-a21f-3ebbde0c9ce7.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/20dff4a1-4494-45d0-8366-4eb521f7930d.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Eidos</Publisher>
</game>