<Game>
	<Name>Virtua Cop 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Justice shot.Sometimes they just get too close.Virtua Cop 2 is a rail shooter dealing with the topic of modern police operating in a giant metropolis called Virtua City. The game can be controlled by the use of various peripherals like the light gun or PC mouse. The player does not manually control camera movement, but has to skilfully shoot the scripted enemies and avoid killing civilians. The player gets rewarded with extra points for disarming opponents by performing 'justice shots' or drowning them with a hail of bullets by performing '3 point shots'. Virtua Cop's sequel provides gamers with two modes - 'arcade' and proving ground. The first one allows players to choose from one of three available stages of various difficulty level in any order. The second one serves as a shooting ground with 3 fields to choose from. After each segment of the game the players can see their statistics which involve: score, the number of killed gangsters and civilians, total number of shots, the number of successful shots and overall accuracy. Apart from killing villains the game features numerous destructible surrounding elements (you can even play drums!), which lower the overall accuracy, but are cool enough, that it is often hard to resist not to shoot 'just one more window'. There are also in-game upgrades that are hidden in these destructible elements. By shooting them the players can gain access to extra lives, magnums, rifles, automatics, shotguns, machine guns and more.Selectable stagesStage select.The game features only three selectable stages, but each of them has alternate routes to follow. Each major stage ends with a boss battle.File 1: Big Chase! (Beginner)- Downtown- Seaside DriveBoss: Bobbie Louise - a muscular gang leader who throws barrels at the player and...he also grabs a truck.File 2: Save the Mayor! (Medium)- On Deck- BridgeBoss: Aero-Divers - five soldiers with jetpacks. They shoot rockets.File 3: Railline Shooutout! (Expert)- Arcade Line- Saturn WayBoss: Garse Bradley - basically it is a general operating a heavily armored tank.After successfully shooting through all three episodes awaits the final battle with 'the Mastermind' - a supervillain wearing a jetpack.</plot>
	<releasedate>3/2/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/virtua-cop-2/3030-9341/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/13692/1233670-virtua_cop_2_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7930/542438-virtua_cop_2__xplosiv__uk_box_art__back_.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/106662/1524224-vc_2_04.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/106662/1524223-vc_2_03.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/106662/1524222-vc_2_02.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/106662/1524221-vc_2_01.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/106662/1523563-vc2_justice_shot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/106662/1523561-vc2_co_civillian.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/106662/1523560-vc2_chapter_select.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/106662/1523559-vc2_title.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6036/324213-vctwo45.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6036/324209-vctwo44.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/xuSwAaD.png</banner1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5668079d-e364-465f-802a-ac86657d7716.png</boxart3>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>