<Game>
	<Name>World Series Baseball 2K2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>World Series Baseball 2K2 features a complete 2002 roster list and various game modes.  You can compete in a standard exhibition game, go for a franchise, skip directly to the playoffs, compete in a home run derby, or play online.2K2 features several new options.  You can take total control of your fielding and lineup positions.  You can create, sign, and trade free agents.  You can manage your batting and pitching rotation.  You can set up a custom batting order and take control of every player on the field.There are many statistics to keep track of, including hot and cold zones for each player, drafts, injuries, trades and fines.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/8/2001</releasedate>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11060</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/world-series-baseball-2k2/3030-17823/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11060-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/231069-world-series-baseball-2k2-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/24301-world-series-baseball-2k2-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7QELVob.png</banner1>
	<Notes>World Series Baseball 2K2, or World Series Baseball as it is known for Xbox, is a sports game developed by Visual Concepts and published by Sega for the Dreamcast and Xbox. It is the first game in the modern series to be featured on the Xbox and the first title in the series developed by Visual Concepts. It is the successor to the World Series Baseball series for the Sega Genesis, Sega Saturn, and Sega Dreamcast. It was released in 2001 to coincide with the beginning of the 2002 baseball season. World Series Baseball consists of many game modes and features. The game modes are Play Now, Season, Franchise, and Create-A-Player. Jason Giambi is on the cover of the game. Some new features updated from the Dreamcast version is in-depth trading and a 15- and 60-day Disabled List. In the new franchise mode there is a Management Draft, Rookie Draft, and a Free Agent Signing Period. Create-A-Player is also highly updated from the last version.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8dc510f5-7dbc-4dc7-96f6-2ecaf5a48935.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bf14c3dc-8b2c-4b52-98ee-eca8ca322a6f.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/10f92367-e496-41b6-a127-a99f047c04cd.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8604f6bd-ca2b-4afb-ac3f-48f9751f92c1.png</snapshot2>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
</game>