<Game>
	<Name>Worms Armageddon (USA) (En,Fr,De,Nl,Sv,No,Da)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Worms Armageddon is a turn-based artillery game created by Team 17. The objective of the game is to kill the other team of worms with a variety of conventional and bizarre weaponry - varying from shotguns to exploding sheep.WeaponryAxe: Takes half of a worm's health off but will not kill a worm unless they are on one HP.Handgun: Only a maximum damage of 30; however, players get Five shots.Uzi: Does a maximum damage of 50.Shotgun: Very effective at close range and can fire more than once in a turn.Minigun: Upgrade to the Uzi and does maximum of 75 damage.Longbow: Can be used to knock opponents off edges. Players get two shots with the longbow.Prod: Does no damage and only moves the enemy a small amount.Suicide Bomber: If used, the worm will blow themselves up. This does a tiny bit of damage but also releases fumes that make the enemy sick.Kamikaze: launch the worm in enemy&#8217;s direction. Does maximum of of 30 damage.Air Strike: Missiles dropped from the air. The angle of the strike can be chosen and each missile does a maximum of 25 damage.Napalm Strike: Napalm missiles dropped from the air which will explode into napalm above the ground coving it in fire. Napalm is affected by the wind.French Sheep Strike: Exploding sheep are dropped over an area and do large amounts of damage.Mine Strike: Drops 5 mines onto the landscape or onto enemies.Bazooka: Shoots a rocket which is affected by the wind. Can use this to hit worms who are in difficult places or behind cover.Homing Missile: A missile that homes onto enemies. Players select the area to be hit, then the power. The missile will automatically home in on this position.Homing Pigeon: Much like the Homing missile but does much more damage.Sheep Launcher: Launches an exploding sheep. They jump around before they explode; they do a maximum of 75 damage.Grenade: The power and length of fuse can be set to ensure maximum damage. Grenades tend to bounce around a lot and are useful for hitting worms hidden in holes.Cluster Bomb: Like the grenade but instead the bomb explodes into smaller cluster bombs which also explode. Only does 15 damage per cluster bomb and is well, pretty useless.Banana Bomb: One of the most powerful weapons in the game! The Banana Bomb is much like the Cluster bomb but it separates into 5 smaller banana bombs on contact. Each of these can do up too 100 damage.Earth Quake: Shakes the ground causing worms to fall off ledges and sometimes into the water.Fire Punch: A massive punch that and is useful for knocking worms off ledges or into explosive objects.Dragon Ball: Very similar to the fire punch but the worm launches it self towards the enemy and therefore does not have to be next to him to make it effective.Dynamite: One of the most likely the most used weapon and it's very simple: Just place the dynamite and run. Does a maximum of 75 damage.Mine: Places a mine on the ground which will be set off by any worm coming close to it. Can also be placed on top of worms to explode instantly (after a small countdown).Sheep: Lets loose a sheep which bounces along the land and can be exploded at any time.Super Sheep: Much like the normal sheep, however the super sheep can be controlled whilst in the air.Aqua Sheep: The same as the super sheep, except this can go underwater.Mortar: This has a huge range but is very inaccurate. Shoots a cluster bomb which explodes into further clusters of bombs doing a maximum of 15 damage each.Mole Bomb: Let loose a mole which borrows into the ground and can be detonated at any time. Useful at creating a quick shelter underground or to flush out worms already below ground.Mail Strike: Drops five letters onto enemies.Mole Squadron: A group of mole bombs dropped from the air, which behave like any other type of strike. However, they can be detonated at will.Blowtorch: Used to dig through the ground to create shelter. Can also be used to attack other worms at close range. Does a maximum of 35 Damage.Pneumatic Drill: Much like the blowtorch but can only dig vertically downwards.Girder: Creates a girder which will protect worms from incoming attack. Can also be used to reach inaccessible areas.Baseball Bat: Can knock worms off cliffs and does a maximum of 30 damage.Ninja Rope: A rope that can be used to swing along the landscape and reach inaccessible areas. Normally has unlimited uses and can be used to escape after a weapon has been places (mostly dynamite). Players can also drop weapons while using the ninja rope.Bungee: Used to bungee down the side of cliffs without taking any damage or ending the turn. Can be used for reaching inaccessible areas.Parachute: Can be used to jump large gaps in the terrain. Weapons can also be dropped while using a parachute. This is heavily affected by the wind.Teleport: Players select a location and then teleport there.Super Banana Bomb: Much like the banana bomb, but more powerful.Holy Hand Grenade: Much like the hand grenade, but does a huge amount of damage and can blow huge holes in the landscape.Flame Thrower: Shoots flames and does a maximum of 125 damage. The flame is affected by the wind.Salvation Army: Releases the forces of the salvation army (characters with drums). They move slowly along the ground and explode on their own after a while. Can also be detonated at will before this.Priceless Ming Vase: Places an ancient vase from the Ming Dynasty on the playing field which explodes.Petrol Bomb: Much like napalm, but on a much smaller scale. Once the petrol bomb explodes it releases fire, which burns the landscape and any worms present.Skunk: Releases a skunk. The skunk runs along the landscape and releases gas. This makes all worms in the area ill, causing them to lose health each turn.Scales of Justice: Redistributes the health of all worms on a team, making them all equal.Carpet Bomb: Releases carpets from the air which behave like any other air strike, but once they hit the ground, they can bounce and explode up to five times.Mad Cow: Launches a cow along the ground, which explodes after a certain amount of time. It does up to 50 damage.Old Woman: Players release and old woman that causes a maximum of 75 damage.Concrete Donkey: Drops a massive concrete donkey from the sky. Once it hits land, it stomps around destroying everything until it reaches the sea.Patsy's Magic Bullet: Fires a silver bullet that functions like the Homing Missile, however, its flight path is extremely accurate and much more sensitive to the contour of the terrain.Indian Nuclear Test: Causes the water to rise and makes everybody on the map sick, losing 2 health after each turn.Armageddon: Destroys nearly everything with a randomized meteorite strikes. Although extremely destructive, it is possible to survive this attack.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/4/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>MicroProse Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>QnNc2KD_PXc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>8342</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/worms-armageddon/3030-17255/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8342-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/8342-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/79309-worms-armageddon-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7025/452644-barrel_11.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7025/452640-bzuqurntnq.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7025/452639-fireguardian5iw.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7025/452633-reviewwormsarmageddon_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7025/452632-screen0133.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7025/452629-screenshot_wine.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7025/452628-sgawd.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7025/452626-shot_5_lrg.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7025/452625-worms2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7025/452624-worms23.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8342-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/IqvP1rM.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/8342.png</clearlogo1>
</game>