<Game>
	<Name>WWF Attitude (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The game was dedicated to the memory of Owen Hart who died performing a ring entrance as the Blue Blazer persona.Attitude would be the last WWE game produced by Accliam, as THQ took over the license.Gameplay:The game retained the controls from WWF Warzone. Taking a more complex route than the WCW world tour series. The control scheme mimicked more of a fighting game, rather than a traditional wrestling game. The game required a button sequence to pull off moves. For example: Undertaker's Tombstone Piledriver required the following button sequence:Down, Up, Down, or Up, Down, Up (depending on location) + C Left on the Nintendo 64.Career ModeUsing any wrestler from the roster you compete in 3 title runs, starting from the European title, Intercontinental title, and the WWF title, going through the list of wrestlers in various matches and different situations. After winning the title, you defend the title against the top 5 wrestlers. Also in the career mode, you can do a tag team career mode with a computer character. By completing the career mode, you can unlock more wrestlers and cheats, which can be accessed in the cheat menu option.Create a WrestlerThe create a wrestler or C.A.W had a robust set of features. The player could choose from a wide range of options including : Gender, Attributes, Moveset, Entrances, and Taunts. Allowing the player to make their own creation, or closely replicate wrestlers not included in the original roster, or from other wrestling organizations. Many fan dedicated CAW sites developed on the internet with formulas for wrestlers, and fictional characters.SoundThe game received positive response for its sound. The game featured specific crowd chants, commentary from Jerry Lawler, and Shane McMahon, and wrestler voices. In IGN's reviewthey claimed "The audio elements of Attitude are outstanding top to bottom. It's not necessarily the quality that got to us, but the variety of bits and depth of the samples that made us take notice."Playable RosterAl SnowBig Boss ManBilly GunnBradshawBrian ChristopherChristianD'Lo BrownDr. DeathDrozEdgeFaarooqGangrelThe GodfatherGoldustHeadbanger MoshHeadbanger ThrasherJeff JarrettKaneKen ShamrockMankindMark HenryOwen HartRoad DoggThe RockSteve AustinSteve BlackmanTriple HThe UndertakerVal VenisX-PacChyna (Secret Character)"Head" (Secret Character)Jacqueline (Secret Character)Jerry "The King" Lawler (Secret Character)Kurrgan (Secret Character)Marc Mero (Secret Character)Paul Bearer (Secret Character)Sable (Secret Character)Sgt. Slaughter (Secret Character)Shawn Michaels (Secret Character)TAKA Michinoku (Secret Character)The Trainer (Secret Character)</plot>
	<releasedate>11/10/1999</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11057</thegamesdb_id>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wwf-attitude/3030-16435/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11057-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/194887-wwf-attitude-dreamcast-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/194732-wwf-attitude-dreamcast-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/140/403752-wwf_attitude.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/140/403751-wwf5.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/140/403749-foto_wwf_attitude.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/140/403748-fjao.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/140/403747-attitude7.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/140/403746-attitude5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/140/403744-attitude2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/140/403742-attitude.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/140/403741-att1.2318437.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/140/403740-a.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/YNIpCbL.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/11057.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>WWF Attitude from Acclaim is the ultimate in wrestling titles for the Dreamcast. Just like its PSX counterpart, the Dreamcast version allows the ultimate wrestling fan to have a plethora of options to choose from to suit his particular wrestling mood. The 128-bit experience is, in itself, amazing. Team that up with good gameplay and a multitude of options makes WWF Attitude for the DC a forerunner in the wrestling ring!</Notes>
	<nPlayers>4</nPlayers>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49d9769d-990f-4c72-9c05-7df9e291414b.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b9938f6-1133-4b86-8868-7d23915d4717.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/06e0c373-14ca-40f1-a784-6801f65043c4.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>