<Game>
<Name>Bounty Bob Strikes Back!</Name>
				<plot>Players control a miner named Bounty Bob that has to claim every square of a mine while pursuing the evil Yukon Yohan.Gameplay:The game, as originally developed on Atari 8-bit platforms, consists of 25 levels where players complete a series of jumping puzzles in order to claim all the land in a mine. Ladders, Slides, and Suction Cups are there to help the player along the way. Land is "claimed" by walking over it, which fills in lines on the various platforms that make up each level. When the entire level is filled in, the level is complete and play proceeds onto the next stage.Bounty Bob will lose a life if he falls down or comes into contact with a mutant. Mutants can be made safe by collecting any of the irradiated objects strewn about the level, which turns the glowing mutants into harmless green creatures for a brief period. The nature of the collectable items and the limited time with which the player can turn the tables on the enemies are reminiscent of elements of Donkey Kong and Pac-Man.The different ports of BBSB! made various changes to "fit" the game onto different hardware. The BBC Micro version, for example, has 20 levels.</plot>
				<releasedate>7/7/1985</releasedate>
				<genre>Action</genre>
				<Developer>Big Five Software</Developer>
				<nplayers>1</nplayers>
				<rating>4.0</rating>
				<thegamesdb_id>5136</thegamesdb_id>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/atari-5200/bounty-bob-strikes-back</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bounty-bob-strikes-back/3030-5532/</giantbomb_url>
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5136-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5136-1.jpg</boxback1>
				<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55851-bounty-bob-strikes-back-atari-5200-screenshot-big-five-software.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55852-bounty-bob-strikes-back-atari-5200-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55853-bounty-bob-strikes-back-atari-5200-screenshot-beginning-the.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55854-bounty-bob-strikes-back-atari-5200-screenshot-use-the-lift.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55855-bounty-bob-strikes-back-atari-5200-screenshot-those-suction.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55856-bounty-bob-strikes-back-atari-5200-screenshot-plenty-of-slides.jpg</snapshot6>
				<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55857-bounty-bob-strikes-back-atari-5200-screenshot-welcome-to-little.jpg</snapshot7>
				<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55858-bounty-bob-strikes-back-atari-5200-screenshot-the-grain-elevator.jpg</snapshot8>
				<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55859-bounty-bob-strikes-back-atari-5200-screenshot-enter-your-name.jpg</snapshot9>
				<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55860-bounty-bob-strikes-back-atari-5200-screenshot-the-high-scores.jpg</snapshot10>
<Notes>Bounty Bob Strikes Back! is the sequel to Miner 2049er and features similar gameplay. As Bounty Bob, your goal is to claim every inch of 25 challenging mines. To do this, you must walk over each segment of the framework in the mines. To reach each segment of framework, you will need to figure out a way to jump, climb, or use one of the many devices occasionally available to get there. To your help you get around (or sometimes hinder progress) are ladders, slides, suction tubes, cannons, transporters, and other devices. Wandering about the mines are many dangerous mutants. If you come in contact with one of these, you will lose a life. Scattered throughout each mine are special food items; collect one of these, and you will temporarily be able to eliminate the mutants by walking into them. You will need to figure out a unique strategy for each level in order to complete it, plus there is a time limit so claim all the territory quickly!</Notes>
<boxart13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6c298d65-188c-445b-9950-aaff88241fe1.jpg<boxart13>
<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f7ae90c9-96cd-4c29-96fa-1cc38d003521.png<clearlogo1>
<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
<Publisher>Big Five Software</Publisher>
</game>
