<Game>
<Name>Countermeasure</Name>
				<plot>Terrorists have seized control of several missile silos and are planning on launching missiles to blow up Washington D.C. Your job is to stop them! From a top down point of view, you control a tank over varied, scrolling terrain. To stop the missiles, you have two options: you can destroy all of the missiles, or attempt to guess the fail safe code. If you try to destroy all the missiles, you must do so in under ten minutes. The missiles silos have many defenses which the terrorists also control; pillboxes, tanks, jeeps, and cruise missiles are all capable of destroying your tank. Should you attempt to guess the fail safe code, clues can be found by docking at supply depots. The code is three letters long, and can consist of any combination of L, E and O. When you enter a war room, you have a very short time to enter the code correctly or the missiles will launch. When the missiles have been stopped (by either means), the level is complete and you continue on to the next, more difficult round.</plot>
				<releasedate>7/7/1982</releasedate>
				<genre>Action</genre>
				<Developer>Midway Games West, Inc.</Developer>
				<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
				<rating>3.2</rating>
				<thegamesdb_id>5148</thegamesdb_id>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/atari-5200/countermeasure</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/countermeasure/3030-13853/</giantbomb_url>
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5148-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5148-1.jpg</boxback1>
<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27664-countermeasure-atari-5200-media.jpg</media1>
				<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55818-countermeasure-atari-5200-screenshot-atari-logo-and-game-title.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55819-countermeasure-atari-5200-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55820-countermeasure-atari-5200-screenshot-beginning-the-game.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55821-countermeasure-atari-5200-screenshot-watch-out-for-those-pillboxes.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55822-countermeasure-atari-5200-screenshot-entering-the-war-room.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55823-countermeasure-atari-5200-screenshot-level-complete-now-on.jpg</snapshot6>
				<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55824-countermeasure-atari-5200-screenshot-defenses-around-this-missile.jpg</snapshot7>
				<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55825-countermeasure-atari-5200-screenshot-a-clue-the-last-letter.jpg</snapshot8>
				<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55826-countermeasure-atari-5200-screenshot-oops-i-didn-t-stop-the.jpg</snapshot9>
				<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/101045/1439864-cm8.png</snapshot10>
				<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/5148-g.jpg</banner1>
<Notes>We've just received word that terrorists have seized one of our missile silo complexes and are threatening to blow up Washington, D.C. These lunatics aren't fooling! They've wired the missiles to a silo computer and started the launch sequence timer. In just 10 minutes the missiles will lift off for Washington... unless YOU stop them. Destroy all the silos in the complex with your long-range turret gun before the timer runs out. If you complete this mission, you'll win the Congressional Medal of Honor... along with 10,000 bonus points and a bonus life. If the timer runs out before you destroy all the silos, you still have a chance to prevent disaster. In the seconds before impact, dock your supertank at a silo, enter the War Room, and guess the fail-safe code that disarms the missiles: The code is some combination of the letters L, E, and O... for example, ELL, OOO, or OLE. Succeed and you win 10,000 bonus points and a bonus life. Fail and... well, you'll find out.</Notes>
<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7300d02b-462a-4fc8-968f-9c07766963ee.jpg<banner2>
<boxart14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/61c546fa-004f-44bf-8346-17e585a71738.jpg<boxart14>
<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bdf338ca-7d5e-46d4-8e44-69decefe868b.png<clearlogo1>
<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dae45f71-047d-47c6-9671-e4a56245ca84.PNG<snapshot1>
<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b53650b0-9118-4177-80d3-14f384a6150f.PNG<snapshot2>
<Publisher>Atari</Publisher>
</game>
