<Game>
<Name>Defender</Name>
				<plot>Overview:Defender is a  side scrolling shoot 'em up, and one one of the first space shooters to feature the freedom to move left or right. GameplayThe player flies left or right looking for UFOs to shoot. An HUD located on the top of the screen indicates where the UFOs are located; the goal is to achieve as many points as possible.Defender has a wrap-around landscape, and that landscape contains as many as ten humanoids. Alien ships called Landers attempt to abduct these humanoids. If a Lander grabs a humanoid and carries it up to the top of the screen, the Lander and humanoid merge into a much more aggressive Mutant ship. If all of the humanoids are killed, the land at the bottom of the screen explodes and the player must fight in empty space. At this point, all the Landers become Mutants. Every fifth wave restores the humanoid count to ten, regenerating the planetary surface, if necessary.Defender had a fairly complicated control scheme for the time, with a lever for moving up and down and buttons for thrust, fire, reverse, smart bomb, and hyperspace. Most ports and even some emulated versions of Defender replace the thrust and reverse buttons in favor of a four-way joystick to control movement and direction.The game was programmed by  Eugene Jarvis and  Larry DeMar, who would later go on to form an external development company known as Vid Kidz.</plot>
				<releasedate>7/7/1982</releasedate>
				<genre>Action</genre>
				<Developer>Atari, Inc.</Developer>
				<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
				<rating>4.1</rating>
				<thegamesdb_id>5151</thegamesdb_id>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/atari-5200/defender</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/defender/3030-5536/</giantbomb_url>
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5151-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5151-1.jpg</boxback1>
<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/28327-defender-atari-5200-media.jpg</media1>
				<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55089-defender-atari-5200-screenshot-atari-logo-and-game-title.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55090-defender-atari-5200-screenshot-title-screen-and-game-options.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55091-defender-atari-5200-screenshot-a-game-in-progress.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55092-defender-atari-5200-screenshot-uh-oh-you-ve-been-hit.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55093-defender-atari-5200-screenshot-attack-wave-complete.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55094-defender-atari-5200-screenshot-shooting-enemies.jpg</snapshot6>
				<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82221/1276317-gfs_38224_2_1.jpg</snapshot7>
				<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82221/1276315-gfs_38224_1_1.jpg</snapshot8>
				<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/15568/496276-defender__1982___atari__3.png</snapshot9>
				<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/15568/496268-defender__1982___atari__1.png</snapshot10>
				<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/5151-g.jpg</banner1>
				<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/5151.png</clearlogo1>
<Notes>Defender is a two-dimensional, side-scrolling shooting game set on the surface of an unnamed planet. The player controls a space ship as it navigates the terrain, flying either to the left or right. A joystick controls the ship's elevation, and five buttons control its horizontal direction and weapons. The object is to destroy alien invaders, while protecting astronauts on the landscape from abduction. Humans that are successfully abducted return as mutants that attack the ship. Defeating the aliens allows the player to progress to the next level. Failing to protect the astronauts, however, causes the planet to explode and the level to become populated with mutants. Surviving the waves of mutants results in the restoration of the planet. Players are allotted three chances (lives) to progress through the game and are able to earn more by reaching certain scoring benchmarks.</Notes>
<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/48437abc-f6f5-4f52-8885-f3a187cf087e.jpg<banner2>
<boxart14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0248bc1e-9e2b-4f9b-85f2-ef4077b9ee4a.jpg<boxart14>
<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8c3100b4-f898-45da-a5d5-3cb5e92c833e.png<clearlogo2>
<Publisher>Atari</Publisher>
</game>
