<Game>
<Name>Dig Dug</Name>
				<plot>Overview:  View zoomed image in  gallery for animation.     You play as Dig Dug (who is also known as    Taizo Hori in other games that he appears in), a  pump wielding spelunker who faces several enemies while he digs    underground. The object of each level (or board) is to clear it of all of the enemies before they kill you by walking to within a set distance and pushing the button to fill the up with air until they explode. Another more strategic way to dispatch your enemies would be to dig underneath    boulders that are located on each level and drop them on to to enemies that are below them. It could be argued that this was one of the first major acts of  violence  in a video game, but due to it's cartoon like nature it was probably overlooked at the time. The original game was released into arcades by Namco in 1982, and contained the standard (at the time) of 256 levels before you reached a    "kill screen" and the game either froze up or  reset itself. Another source of scoring points throughout the game is the inclusion of a fruit or item in the center of the screen that would appear after dropping two of the levels boulders. This mechanic is very similar to another Namco game series,    Pac-Man. The boulders did not have to drop on enemies for the fruits to appear however. The bonus items include :    Carrot,  Turnip, Zucchini (or Cucumber),    Eggplant,  Green Pepper,    Tomato,    Garlic,    Watermelon,    Pineapple, as well as the inclusion of a  Warship from Namco's    Galaxian.     Enemies:PookaPooka: Best described as a round orange ball with aviator goggles, Pooka is the most common enemy that you will  face in the game. Not as overly aggressive as his counter part, he as well as Fygar still has the ability to pass through  the un-dug parts of the dirt in each level to attack you from any angle.  FygarFygar: A dragon-like creature, not only can he pass through the dirt and attack you but also has the ability to breathe fire, making him a decidedly more difficult and deadly enemy.Legacy:Dig-Dug is considered to be a classic and has spawned many    sequels and has appeared on many    compilations and game download services since its initial release. The character of DIg-Dug also has a son named Susumu Hori ( that appears in the    Mr. Driller series), continuing the family legacy of digging to the depths of the earth.  Downloading and playing the demo of the XBLA version unlocks a Gamerpic. Critical ReceptionWhen the Game Boy version was released in 1993 Electronic Gaming Monthly awarded the game scores of 6,6,6, and 5.  They stated, "...the game play is intact and the graphics are decent for GB standards.  A few new features [are] thrown in for a little variety and you have a solid little GB cart that's great for long road trips".</plot>
				<releasedate>7/7/1983</releasedate>
				<genre>Action</genre>
				<Developer>Atari, Inc.</Developer>
				<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
				<rating>3.6</rating>
				<VideoURL>Pd6TTrVdm7s</VideoURL>
				<thegamesdb_id>5153</thegamesdb_id>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/atari-5200/dig-dug</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dig-dug/3030-2587/</giantbomb_url>
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5153-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5153-1.jpg</boxback1>
<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27248-dig-dug-atari-5200-media.jpg</media1>
				<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/5153-1.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54934-dig-dug-atari-5200-screenshot-atari-logo-and-game-title.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54935-dig-dug-atari-5200-screenshot-title-screen-and-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54936-dig-dug-atari-5200-screenshot-beginning-a-game.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54937-dig-dug-atari-5200-screenshot-shooting-a-creature.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54938-dig-dug-atari-5200-screenshot-yikes-i-m-on-the-run.jpg</snapshot6>
				<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2786026-digdug001.jpg</snapshot7>
				<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2786025-dig+dug+%281990%29%28namco+ltd.%29_003.jpg</snapshot8>
				<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2786024-dig+dug+%281990%29%28namco+ltd.%29_002.jpg</snapshot9>
				<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2786023-dig+dug+%281990%29%28namco+ltd.%29_001.jpg</snapshot10>
				<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/5153-1.jpg</fanart1>
				<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/5153-g.jpg</banner1>
				<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/5153.png</clearlogo1>
<Notes>The objective of Dig Dug is to eliminate underground-dwelling monsters by inflating them until they pop, or by dropping rocks on them. There are two kinds of enemies in the game: Pookas - A race of round red monsters (said to be modeled after tomatoes) who wear yellow goggles. Fygars - A race of green dragons who can breathe fire. The player's character is Dig Dug, dressed in white and blue, and able to dig tunnels through destructible environments. Dig Dug is killed if he is caught by either Pooka or Fygar, burned by a Fygar's fire, or crushed by a rock. A partially inflated monster will gradually deflate and recover after a few seconds, during which time the player can pass safely through it. The monsters normally crawl through the tunnels in the dirt but can turn into ghostly eyes and travel slowly through the dirt. The last enemy on a level will try to escape off the top left of the screen. More points are awarded for popping an enemy further down in the dirt (the levels are color-coded). In addition, Fygars are worth double points if exploded horizontally, since they can only breathe fire horizontally in the direction they are facing. Extra points are also awarded for dropping rocks on enemies in order to eliminate them rather than inflating them. If one enemy is killed by the rock, it is worth 1000 points. The next two add 1500 points each, and any after that add 2000. The act of digging is itself worth points, giving 10 points for each block dug, so some players do as much of it as possible in situations where the threat from the remaining monsters is minimal. After the player drops two rocks, fruits and vegetables and other edible bonus items, such as Galaxian flagships appear in the center of the play field, and can be collected for points if the player is able to reach them before they disappear. These edible bonus items will appear even if the rocks fail to hit any enemies. In some versions of the game, the most points attainable from a single bonus fruit is 8,000 from the pineapple.</Notes>
<VideoURL2>Pd6TTrVdm7s</VideoURL2>
<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dbca5f6c-4e32-491b-880d-d3132e8122e5.jpg<banner2>
<boxart14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/549bd4ee-8a78-4213-9bfc-1a753b15f16f.jpg<boxart14>
<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/453fb600-b728-4b33-a1f0-0e381b09bfa2.png<clearlogo2>
<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/49c69007-d49c-46f8-8155-5477663ce026.jpg<snapshot1>
<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
<Publisher>Atari</Publisher>
</game>
