<Game>
<Name>H.E.R.O.</Name>
				<plot>Overview:  H.E.R.O. is a platforming game published and developed by                     Activision in 1984. It was originally developed for the                    Atari 2600 but ported to many other consoles already listed on this page. The name is speculated to mean "Helicopter Emergency Rescue Operation".Gameplay:   The main objective of the game is to rescue trapped miners. You're equipped with a       heli-pack  allowing you to          fly around the level, as well as a               laser-beam to defend yourself from the game's various enemies (             bats,             snakes,            spiders, etc). You're also equipped with           dynamite, which you can use to kill  enemies or to destroy various walls blocking your way. It's possible to use your laser beam to disintegrate the wall as well without the risk of killing yourself, although it takes longer. There are      magma walls later in the game that kill you if you touch them, making it slightly harder to plant dynamite next to, or navigate through the caverns. When you die, you're returned to the same screen as the one you were just on, costing a life. There is a        power meter on the bottom of the screen that slowly drains indicating a time limit, making later levels fairly difficult due to their length. When the power meter is drained, you lose a life. Later levels often feature a raft the player can use to float across the water unharmed.  H.E.R.O. for Xbox 360 Game RoomH.E.R.O. was included in the June 23rd, 2010 Game Pack release of   Game Room for the  Xbox 360.</plot>
				<releasedate>7/7/1984</releasedate>
				<genre>Action</genre>
				<Developer>Activision, Inc.</Developer>
				<nplayers>1</nplayers>
				<rating>4.1</rating>
				<thegamesdb_id>5164</thegamesdb_id>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/atari-5200/hero</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hero/3030-4430/</giantbomb_url>
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5164-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5164-1.jpg</boxback1>
<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/28332-h-e-r-o-atari-5200-media.jpg</media1>
				<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55084-h-e-r-o-atari-5200-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55085-h-e-r-o-atari-5200-screenshot-beginning-a-level.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55086-h-e-r-o-atari-5200-screenshot-blocked-by-a-wall.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55087-h-e-r-o-atari-5200-screenshot-located-one-of-the-trapped-miners.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55088-h-e-r-o-atari-5200-screenshot-hovering-above-some-danger.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/25048/882271-h_e_r_o_.png</snapshot6>
				<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/5164.png</clearlogo1>
<Notes>There is trouble in the mines! Volcanic activity has trapped numerous miners, and it is your job to save them. As Roderick Hero, you need to make your way through the dangerous mineshaft avoiding the dangerous creatures and lava, and find out where the miners are located before you run out of energy. To help on your mission, Roderick Hero has several useful types of equipment. A prop pack will allow you to hover and fly around the mineshaft and (hopefully) avoid the many dangers within. Your helmet features a short range microlaser beam which can be used to destroy the bats, spiders, snakes, and other creatures you'll encounter in the mines. From time to time, your path through the mine may be blocked by stone or lava walls. You begin each mission with six sticks of dynamite which can be used to destroy these obstacles (be careful you don't blow yourself up, though!) If you run out of dynamite, your laser beam can also be used to destroy the walls, though this will take longer and use up more energy. As the levels progress, the mine shaft will become longer and more maze-like, creatures will more frequently block the path, and lava walls and pools will appear which are dangerous to the touch.</Notes>
<boxart10>http://images.launchbox-app.com/72254079-9255-4279-9273-f8f32952ac4e.jpg<boxart10>
<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8885c188-11d3-4085-9b3e-e53ff4bb6c37.png<clearlogo2>
<clearlogo3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f31ee431-6bdc-48aa-b817-9c77d0799ca1.png<clearlogo3>
<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>
