<Game>
<Name>Miner 2049er</Name>
				<plot>You play the part of Bounty Bob, and it is your mission to explore every inch of an abandoned mine. As you walk over floor sections in the mine, the floor will change color. When all of the floor sections have been changed in color, you can move on to the next, more challenging level. To reach all of the floor sections, you will need to figure out how to get there! You can jump (be careful not to fall too far though, or you will be squished), climb up and down ladders, and use different transportation devices that can be found on the levels (such as an elevator, slides, a springboard, or a canon!) Wandering around the mine are numerous radioactive creatures which get in Bounty Bobs way. Also scattered throughout the mines are various artifacts left behind; if Bounty Bob collects one of these, the creatures will temporarily become vulnerable. If Bounty Bob runs into one of the creatures in this state the creature will be destroyed, but if he runs into a creature while it is glowing Bounty Bob will be destroyed! There is a total of ten different levels, and to complete them all you will need quick reflexes as well as figure out a unique strategy for each level.</plot>
				<releasedate>7/7/1983</releasedate>
				<genre>Action</genre>
				<Developer>Big Five Software</Developer>
				<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
				<rating>5.0</rating>
				<thegamesdb_id>5181</thegamesdb_id>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/atari-5200/miner-2049er</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/miner-2049er/3030-14533/</giantbomb_url>
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5181-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5181-1.jpg</boxback1>
<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27605-miner-2049er-atari-5200-media.jpg</media1>
<media2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27606-miner-2049er-atari-5200-media.jpg</media2>
				<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55688-miner-2049er-atari-5200-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55690-miner-2049er-atari-5200-screenshot-prepare-for-station-1.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55691-miner-2049er-atari-5200-screenshot-gameplay-on-the-first-level.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55692-miner-2049er-atari-5200-screenshot-the-second-level-features.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55693-miner-2049er-atari-5200-screenshot-use-the-transporter-to-reach.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55694-miner-2049er-atari-5200-screenshot-lots-of-little-platforms.jpg</snapshot6>
				<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55695-miner-2049er-atari-5200-screenshot-whoa-even-more-little-platforms.jpg</snapshot7>
				<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55696-miner-2049er-atari-5200-screenshot-great-score-now-enter-your.jpg</snapshot8>
				<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55697-miner-2049er-atari-5200-screenshot-a-bunch-of-5-s-circle-the.jpg</snapshot9>
				<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/776389-1106188445_00.png</snapshot10>
				<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/5181.png</clearlogo1>
<Notes>Miner 2049er is a platform video game created by Bill Hogue that was released in 1982 by Big Five Software. It was developed for the Atari 8-bit family and widely ported to other systems. The game was licensed in conjunction with International Computer Group.[citation needed] At the time of its release, Miner 2049er was notable for having ten different screens, which was a large number for a platform game.[1][2] For comparison, the Donkey Kong arcade game had four screens, and many home ports didn't include all of them. The title "Miner 2049er" evoked a 21st-century take on the California Gold Rush of around 1849, in which the gold miners and prospectors were nicknamed "49ers."[3] Unlike most of the home computer versions, Miner 2049er for the Atari 8-bit family was released on 16K ROM cartridge with the high price, for 1982, of US$49.95.[4]</Notes>
<boxart15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a4f1179f-e8bf-401b-a4af-be7e335fd28d.jpg<boxart15>
<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/43b002cb-2006-401b-bd16-caee801f2c9e.png<clearlogo2>
<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9764eb6f-e852-4914-918c-debe047a49b5.png<snapshot1>
<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/81e9b8cc-ec52-43cc-a4f6-ddfb0ef05fef.png<snapshot2>
</game>
