<Game>
<Name>Qix</Name>
				<plot>Overview:In QIX, the objective is to fence in a large majority of the play field and defeat the QIX. Players must close in the large enemy, the QIX, in a closed space without it touching the player or the lines drawn by the player. Every time the player creates a closed space, they are awarded points and the space becomes solid so the QIX can no longer pass through it. Other enemies besides the QIX exist in the form of Sparx. The Sparx moves on the lines that the player draws and can defeat the player in the same way as the QIX.QIX was originally released in arcades in 1981 but Taito ported the game to a large variety of consoles such as the Atari 5200, Atari 400/800, Apple II, Commodore 64, DOS, Amiga (with new graphics), Apple IIGS, NES, and Atari Lynx. Nintendo also developed a Game Boy version that featured Mario, Luigi, and Princess Peach.</plot>
				<releasedate>7/7/1982</releasedate>
				<genre>Action</genre>
				<Developer>Atari, Inc.</Developer>
				<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
				<rating>3.8</rating>
				<thegamesdb_id>5197</thegamesdb_id>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/atari-5200/qix</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/qix/3030-6136/</giantbomb_url>
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5197-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5197-1.jpg</boxback1>
<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27227-qix-atari-5200-media.jpg</media1>
				<snapshot1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/screenshots/5197-1.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54902-qix-atari-5200-screenshot-atari-logo-and-title.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54903-qix-atari-5200-screenshot-title-screen-and-game-demo-mode.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54904-qix-atari-5200-screenshot-a-game-in-progress.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54905-qix-atari-5200-screenshot-slowly-trapping-the-qix.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54906-qix-atari-5200-screenshot-level-complete.jpg</snapshot6>
				<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/54907-qix-atari-5200-screenshot-can-you-split-two-qix.jpg</snapshot7>
				<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/9408/755635-985313440_00.gif</snapshot8>
				<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/9408/755634-985312589_00.gif</snapshot9>
				<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/9408/755633-qix_5.png</snapshot10>
				<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/5197-g.jpg</banner1>
				<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/5197.png</clearlogo1>
<Notes>In this game, you guide a marker which must draw rectangles and other weird objects in order to claim your territory, and you can either draw these rectangles fast or slow. Drawing the rectangles using the "slow" method awards you the most points. Once a rectangle has been made, it will be colored in to show that you have claimed your territory. While drawing the rectangles, you need to watch out for Qix (pronounced "kicks"), a series of colored lines that crawl the screen. In addition to Qix, you also need to avoid the Sparks who travel around the border, as well as any lines that you have made, as well as The Fuse, who travels along the line that you are drawing. Once you have claimed enough territory, you proceed to the next level.</Notes>
<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9cd2de0f-eae8-4c84-a8c2-0a6468bf3cf8.jpg<banner2>
<boxart14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/77bbaa7e-7d04-46c8-b136-98068c9d4c26.jpg<boxart14>
<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0a75e14a-729f-49a5-b28c-69afd1130527.png<clearlogo2>
<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b334e541-6156-4aad-b8a6-b05e91152f9a.jpg<snapshot1>
<Publisher>Atari</Publisher>
</game>
