<Game>
<Name>Quest for Quintana Roo</Name>
				<plot>You are Yucatan Sam on a quest to explore the temple of Quintana Roo. Your goal is to find the vault which is hidden somewhere within and return with the treasure that is inside. You begin your quest outside the temple; climb your way up the side of the temple in order to get inside. Poisonous snakes and deadly lightning bolts will block your progress here. Once inside the temple, you have a limited air supply so you need to explore quickly. Hidden in various rooms of the temple are numerous keys which are needed to unlock the vault. The keys and some other useful items are hidden in secret rooms which you need to locate by using your trusty pick axe or the flasks of acid you carry. To help figure out which rooms may contain hidden objects, you carry a geiger counter with you;  the higher the reading, the closer you are to something of interest! The rooms you'll be exploring are guarded by snakes, spiders, and even mummies! To deal with these enemies you carry a gun, and you can also use the acid flasks against them (ammo is limited, so use it wisely). If you are successful in your mission, you may receive a secret code which can be used to begin the game at later levels. Good luck!</plot>
				<releasedate>7/7/1984</releasedate>
				<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
				<Developer>Sunrise Software, Inc.</Developer>
				<nplayers>1</nplayers>
				<rating>2.5</rating>
				<thegamesdb_id>5198</thegamesdb_id>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/atari-5200/quest-for-quintana-roo</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/quest-for-quintana-roo/3030-1841/</giantbomb_url>
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5198-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5198-1.jpg</boxback1>
<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/30749-quest-for-quintana-roo-atari-5200-media.jpg</media1>
				<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63494-quest-for-quintana-roo-atari-5200-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63495-quest-for-quintana-roo-atari-5200-screenshot-press-start-or.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63496-quest-for-quintana-roo-atari-5200-screenshot-outside-the-temple.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63497-quest-for-quintana-roo-atari-5200-screenshot-sliding-down-a.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63498-quest-for-quintana-roo-atari-5200-screenshot-exploring-a-room.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63499-quest-for-quintana-roo-atari-5200-screenshot-found-a-secret.jpg</snapshot6>
				<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14975/1342650-quest3.png</snapshot7>
				<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14975/1342649-quest2.png</snapshot8>
				<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14975/1342648-quest1.png</snapshot9>
				<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/5198-g.jpg</banner1>
				<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/5198.png</clearlogo1>
<Notes>Help Yucatan Sam explore the dozens of terror filled chambers that create the mystical temple of the Mayan god Quintana Roo. You must use your supplies as well as your cat-like reactions to avoid the sleeping snakes, overcome the mummy's curse, and eliminate the other adversaries while attempting to solve the mystery that will deliver the hidden treasure to you and Yucatan Sam. Since a different solution is required each time the game is started, you will be assured hours of mind-challenging, reflex-testing entertainment.</Notes>
<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/23b5e5a6-05ea-44ac-9846-a712c6c167cf.jpg<banner2>
<boxart13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/15a1686f-90f8-40d3-90c0-f6d7e8d928a4.jpg<boxart13>
<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6979f460-eff8-45ae-9751-272ec24f2c93.png<clearlogo2>
<Publisher>Sunrise Software</Publisher>
</game>
