<Game>
<Name>Space Shuttle - A Journey Into Space</Name>
				<plot>Space Shuttle is a simulation game where you are the pilot of space shuttle Discovery. Your goal is to launch the Discovery, establish an orbit around the Earth, open the cargo bay doors and recover a satellite to perform repairs, and finally land the Discovery successfully, all while using as little fuel as possible. Each time the complete mission is accomplished, it will then repeat at a higher difficulty level (in the higher difficulty levels the satellite has a more erratic flight path). The game is played from a first person perspective in the space shuttle cockpit where you can control everything from the shuttles engines to cargo bay doors. When the game is over you will be given a ranking which is based on the number of successful dockings and the amount of fuel that was used. In addition to the full flight mode, two easier game variations (autosimulator and simulator mode) are included. The autosimulator mode is the easiest; the computer will control the flight (you can take over at any point you wish) and the controls are simplified. The simulation mode is closer to the full game, however you have an unlimited amount of fuel so there is no time pressure, and the computer will help compensate for inaccurate maneuvering.</plot>
				<releasedate>7/7/1983</releasedate>
				<genre>Simulation</genre>
				<Developer>Activision, Inc.</Developer>
				<nplayers>1</nplayers>
				<thegamesdb_id>5215</thegamesdb_id>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/atari-5200/space-shuttle-a-journey-into-space</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/space-shuttle-a-journey-into-space/3030-11469/</giantbomb_url>
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/5215-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/5215-1.jpg</boxback1>
<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/29686-space-shuttle-a-journey-into-space-atari-5200-media.jpg</media1>
				<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60659-space-shuttle-a-journey-into-space-atari-5200-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60660-space-shuttle-a-journey-into-space-atari-5200-screenshot-t.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60661-space-shuttle-a-journey-into-space-atari-5200-screenshot-here.jpg</snapshot3>
				<banner1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/5215-g.jpg</banner1>
<Notes>In Space Shuttle, you're the entire crew of America's pride and joy, the shuttle Orbiter. Climb into the cockpit, wait for the countdown, and follow the flight path precisely when you launch (and don't forget to separate the solid booster rockets and external tank on your way to orbit). Locate and rendezvous with a satellite in need of repair and re-launch it to the correct orbit, then make a fiery reentry through the atmosphere to return safely to Earth.  Originally released for the Atari 2600, Activision's intricate Space Shuttle simulator fares much better on the Atari 5200 for one simple reason: the controller keypad. The 2600 edition required players to memorize a bewildering array of alternate uses for every switch and toggle on the console except the power switch, whereas those functions -- although still cryptically named in NASA-speak -- are much easier to access with the keypad and overlay.</Notes>
<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/964df739-0dd0-447f-8012-c11a9d6080cc.jpg<banner2>
<boxart7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99252140-065c-49bd-8c61-1745002140fe.jpg<boxart7>
<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f510f9bd-8d8f-4128-94be-6eb613515aa1.png<clearlogo1>
<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>
