<Game>
<Name>Star Wars - Return of the Jedi - Death Star Battle</Name>
				<plot>Overview:Star Wars: Return of the Jedi - Death Star Battle released in 1983 by Parker Brothers put you at the helm of the Millennium Falcon on a quest to destroy the Galactic Empires battle station.  The game was based on two different scenarios.  In the first sequence you fought through swarms of Tie-fighters and worked to lower the force field surrounding the Death Star.  As you battled the force field would lower giving you a few moments to scramble through the opening to begin sequence two.  In sequence two, you are faced with more Tie-fighters and the "under construction" Death Star itself.  During the second sequence, the Death Star is constantly having more portions put together to complete its construction and thus making the powerful world destroying super laser operational.  The game charges you with keeping Tie-fighters at bay while successfully chipping away at the outer layers of the Death Star, exposing the laser.  Once you destroy the laser, and Death Star, you complete the level and basically replay the game at higher difficulty.Gameplay:   The Atari 2600 version of the game uses the familiar joystick that controls the Falcon in all directions.  The red button fires lasers from the ship. </plot>
				<releasedate>7/7/1983</releasedate>
				<genre>Action</genre>
				<Developer>Parker Brothers</Developer>
				<nplayers>1</nplayers>
				<rating>1.6</rating>
				<thegamesdb_id>35937</thegamesdb_id>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/atari-5200/star-wars-return-of-the-jedi-death-star-battle</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/star-wars-return-of-the-jedi-death-star-battle/3030-19947/</giantbomb_url>
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/35937-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27412-star-wars-return-of-the-jedi-death-star-battle-atari-5200-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
<media1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27413-star-wars-return-of-the-jedi-death-star-battle-atari-5200-media.jpg</media1>
				<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55512-star-wars-return-of-the-jedi-death-star-battle-atari-5200-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55513-star-wars-return-of-the-jedi-death-star-battle-atari-5200-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55514-star-wars-return-of-the-jedi-death-star-battle-atari-5200-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/55515-star-wars-return-of-the-jedi-death-star-battle-atari-5200-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/12459/445727-star_wars__death_star_battle.png</snapshot5>
<Notes>Death Star Battle is loosely based on the events of the film Star Wars Episode VI: Return of the Jedi. Your task is to destroy the Death Star before its construction is finished. You start the task outside the shield perimeter of the Death Star. There you'll have to combat different imperial vessels and avoid the death ray while waiting for an opportunity to slip through one of the random openings in the energy shield. After reaching the Death Star you must reduce its structure up to the point where you can hit the core. In the following destruction of the station you must avoid collision with Death Star debris.</Notes>
<boxart9>http://images.launchbox-app.com/06a5f8c5-619f-4d9f-ab91-28af5d4450e7.jpg<boxart9>
<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d21bc7c-54fc-48b3-9c04-70d33398b988.png<clearlogo1>
<snapshot1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aa1b97a3-a60d-41d5-bd14-6c6e718641e5.png<snapshot1>
<snapshot2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2852525a-6236-467f-9293-0b4e4d9e59ca.png<snapshot2>
<Publisher>Parker Brothers</Publisher>
</game>
