<Game>
	<Name>007 - Everything or Nothing (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The game was noted for its 3rd Person view and unique story.This was the second James Bond game to feature in a third-person perspective, and the very first Bond game to feature a cooperative mode. Everything or Nothing also marked Pierce Brosnan's last performance as James Bond in film and in video games.This version of Bond lacked an actual deathmatch unlike its previous installments, which had become standard after GoldenEye's success in 1997. Jaws from the classic Bond films reprises his role as the giant, silver-teethed villain for the first time with a different Bond actor. This installment includes 29 missions and 4 unlockable ones. It also brings back the Aston Martin V12 Vanquish, which was featured in the Bond film Die Another Day.Gameplay: consists of a mix of third person gunplay, vehicular combat and stealth segments. The player has access to an assortment of weapons (pistols, shotguns, assault rifles) which will be displayed on Bond depending on the most recent weapons of choice. Bond also has access to a variety of gadgets including coin grenades.Bond MomentsA predominant feature throughout the levels in Everything or Nothing focus on "Bond Moments". While venturing, players will come across certain objects that can be interacted with in a unique way that James Bond would actually do in order to trump the bad guys. A prime example is how Bond will fly a helicopter through a canyon to escape, and there will be bad guys on a rope-and-wood bridge firing weapons at him.Players could use their turret gun to try and kill them all and just fly past them, or they could use a Bond moment that would shoot the bridge out. Another memorable Bond moment from the game involves sliding the motorcycle under the trailer of an 18-wheeler. The majority of these moments are noted with a special crosshair indicator and, in some cases, a context sensitive button press.VehiclesA handful of levels in Everything or Nothing feature vehicle chases. A variety of cars, motorcycles, and other vehicles make up the majority of these levels. Some use a slightly open-ended approach, while others offer a very linear pathway to move along.Chimera MotorcyclePorsche Cayenne Turbo (Also as RC)Triumph Daytona 600Peruvian TankVolotech TruckAston Martin V12 Vanquish (Also as RC)LimousineRally CarPlatinum TankWeapons:The bulk of the gameplay consists of third person combat, and these are the weapons players will come across in the game. (Note: the last weapons used by players will be displayed on Bond, with a two handed weapon on his back and pistols in his holster).Walther P99 (silenced or unsilenced)Desert EagleGolden Gun (unlockable by a cheat code)Platinum Gun (unlockable by a cheat code)SPAS-12Heckler &amp; Koch MP5KSIG 552AK-74 (The AK-74 is the 5.45mm version of the AK versus 7.62mm of the original AK-47) Although the game calls it an AK-74, the weapon model is actually that of the AK-47/AKM.Dragunov Sniper Rifle (A sniper variant of the AKM)AT-420 (Actually is a M202 FLASH(supporting weapon)GadgetsGadgets given to Bond for use in his missions. Some are only available for certain missions, others are more common use (such as the grenade coin).Fragmentation Grenade (disguised as coin)ThermovisionStrobe Grenade (disguised as coin)EMP Grenade (disguised as coin)Q-Spider (remote controlled robot)Dart gunNano Suit (invisibility)Network Tap</plot>
	<releasedate>17/11/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>Cfxfl8X-RFI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>25838</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/914854-007-everything-or-nothing</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/007-everything-or-nothing</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/007-everything-or-nothing/3030-6530/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1841792-box_eon.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/40793-007-everything-or-nothing-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/40794-007-everything-or-nothing-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/88365-007-everything-or-nothing-game-boy-advance-screenshot-bond.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/88366-007-everything-or-nothing-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-fight.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98055-007-everything-or-nothing-game-boy-advance-screenshot-bond.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98056-007-everything-or-nothing-game-boy-advance-screenshot-007-races.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98057-007-everything-or-nothing-game-boy-advance-screenshot-jaws.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98058-007-everything-or-nothing-game-boy-advance-screenshot-action.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/98059-007-everything-or-nothing-game-boy-advance-screenshot-mission.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17172/1367567-007everythingnothing_010804_49.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17172/1367565-007everythingnothing_010804_46.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17172/1367564-007everythingnothing_010804_40.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/tLgDBZR.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Think like Bond, act like Bond, and experience an entirely new Bond adventure. James Bond, the world's greatest secret agent, returns in Everything or Nothing with new guns and gadgets, combat skills, and clever tricks--and it's up to you to put them to good use. Travel through four exciting continents including the Valley of the Kings in Egypt and the French Quarter in New Orleans. The game also features two-player co-op missions and four-player multiplayer arena modes.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>Cfxfl8X-RFI</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e768bf3a-5d32-4752-a774-2cbb536e05a2.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/73e54675-382f-4e2e-9ddf-e2b1a65eef2f.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>EA Games</Publisher>
	<crc32>caf2e99f</crc32>
 	<snapshot11>http://thumbnails.libretro.com/Nintendo - Game Boy Advance/Named_Titles/007 - Everything or Nothing (Japan).png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://thumbnails.libretro.com/Nintendo - Game Boy Advance/Named_Snaps/007 - Everything or Nothing (Japan).png</snapshot12>
</game>