<Game>
	<Name>2 Games in 1 - Sonic Battle + ChuChu Rocket! (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It+En,Ja,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Double Pack: Sonic Advance &amp; ChuChu Rocket! is a Miscellaneous game, developed by Sega and published by THQ,which was released in Europe in 2005.Cheat: Complete the following to unlock new modes:Cheat: Every time you visit the Help section (which is the ChuChu Rocket! ''Homepage''), more of the Help section becomes revealed. 1st Visit: Various Modes 2nd Visit: Make your own puzzles! 3rd Visit: Battle technique 4th Visit: Download corner 5th Visit: Puzzle technique The Download corner is the most intersting. You can download three different Mice-types and Cats-types, so instead of you using the basic ChuChus and KapuKapus, you use Cows and UFOs, for instance. 1 : Mice-Cow     Cats-UFO 2 : Mice-Balloon Cats-Pin 3 : Mice-Snow    Cats-FireCheat: When you're on a credits screen (i.e. after completing a series of 25 puzzles in Puzzle 1P mode), hold B and the credits will scroll a little faster.Cheat: Go to game start on the main menu, and select Sonic (don't press A, just make sure he is on your screen.)  When you do this, do the following: Cheat: up, right, down, right, L, right, R right, A  Cheat: You should hear a chime like you just collected a ring letting you know the code was right.  Select a course (if you have that option) and have fun.  Cheat: Oh, by the way, the computer Tails isn't very smart, but it can be helpful.  (He doesn't Die.)Cheat: You must have a GBA, GBA to GCN link cable, two memory card with Chao garden saves, and this game. Send the Chao you want to duplicate to the GBA. It should say it's making a copy. Once you have the copy go to move. Move the duplicated Chao to the Garden in slot two. Now take the Chao out of the garden and put it in slot 1. Now take the other Chao from slot 2 and transfer it to slot 1. You now have two of the same Chao.Cheat: Run up to the first yellow spring in the level (Just as the ground turns to pavement and grass) and jump to the right side of it. Push yourself against it, face right, and do a spin dash. Release to send Sonic/Tails/Knuckles spinning forward, while holding Right on the control pad, and hold it. You'll go through the two loops, but as you go downhill, your character will fly far right and off the screen. Keep holding Right untill the camera catches up with your character.Cheat: During the chao memory game press the A button as your chao moves a card and it'll trip up. This can stop it from moving the card.Cheat: Normally the sound test has 39 songs on it.  If you can beat (not just make it to) The Moon Zone, then the Sound Test will Have songs 40 (The Moon Zone), 41 (Sonic has cleared EXTRA), and 42 (Super Sonic Ending).</plot>
	<releasedate>11/11/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>Sega</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/943937-double-pack-sonic-advance-and-chuchu-rocket</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/6/7/92667_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/6/6/92666_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/9/1/gfs_121072_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/4/1/gfs_121072_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/f/1/gfs_121072_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/e/1/gfs_121072_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/5/1/gfs_121072_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
</game>