<Game>
	<Name>2 Games in 1 - Scooby-Doo! - Mystery Mayhem + Scooby-Doo and the Cyber Chase (USA) (En,Fr,De+En)</Name>
	<plot>Whether you're in the mood to solve a supernatural mystery or chase down the creator of the Phantom Virus, you'll find plenty to do in the Scooby-Doo Two Games in 1 Double Pack. The compilation includes two games based on the animated series: Scooby-Doo Mystery Mayhem and Scooby-Doo and the Cyber Chase. This is your chance to help Scooby and his friends gather clues, solve puzzles, and defeat various enemies.Cheat: Scooby-Doo and the Cyber Chase: Cheat mode.On the password screen enter CHTMD2 as a password. This will unlock cheat mode. During game-play hold down the required buttons to unlock special abilities. Cheat: Scooby-Doo and the Cyber Chase: Cheat mode.Enter these passwords at the password Menu.Cheat: At the password screen, enter CHTMD2 to unlock the following abilities duiring game playCheat: Enter the passwordsCheat: At the main menu, go to &amp;quot;Password&amp;quot; and enter the following codes to unlock the different levels:Cheat: The following passwords are for each stage on difficult.Cheat: Enter VRSN2 as a password. The build date can be found in the options menu.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/3/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>Various</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/926257-2-games-in-1-double-pack-scooby-doo-and-the-cyber</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/4/9/1/65491_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/4/9/1/65491_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/1/a/gfs_62492_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/c/a/gfs_62492_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/7/a/gfs_62492_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/6/a/gfs_62492_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/d/a/gfs_62492_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/yNwLd8C.png</banner1>
</game>