<Game>
	<Name>2 Games in 1 - Dragon Ball Z - The Legacy of Goku I & II (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Embark on an incredible journey to protect the Universe from evil. Guide the fate of the mightiest warrior known - GOKU&amp;reg; - from the Saiyan Saga to the Cell Games. Use combat strategies to defeat arch enemies, including Frieza, the Androids and Perfect Cell!Cheat: Immortality in LoG 1During the opening of LoG 1, hit: Up, Down, Left, Right, B, A to gain immortality throughout the game. If done correctly, a sound will confirm it. Enemies will not be able to hurt you, but you still get hurt if you touch the edges on Snake Way!Cheat: Alternate ending in LoG IITo unlock the alternate ending, get Mr. Satan (Hercule) to level 50. the go to the News station and break open the door. Walk in and the ending will start.Cheat: Alternate ending in LoG IITo unlock Mr. Satan get every character to level 50 then get all of their trophies. A screen will come up saying Mr. Satan has been unlocked.Cheat: Alternate ending in LoG IITo get these trophies you need to level everyone, except for Goku, up to level 50. The trophies are located behind everyone's level 50 door. So break down the door after your character is at level 50, then make it to the end of the area inside the door, then collect your trophy!Cheat: In the options menu, highlight "Text Speed", hold L+R+Up (thus now highlighting "Exit"), and press A to access a debug menu containing a level select, sound test, sprite viewer, and photo gallery.Cheat: During the intro movie, press the following buttons. If done right, a sound effect will confirm your entry. Start a new game or continue a saved game, and when an enemy attacks, you will not receive any damage.Cheat: Fly away from the boss until he's about 1.5 - 2 screens away from Goku. You can keep shooting the boss with Ki Blasts from there and the boss won't move. You can find a place to shoot by firing Ki Blasts in the boss's direction and moving side to side until it makes the sound that it makes when you hit an enemy with a ki blast. Once you find the place where you hit the boss, stay there and keep firing Ki Blasts. It works because bosses don't move when you are a certain distance away from them. For some bosses, after you fire ki blasts for a long time, you might need to go up to the boss and punch him/her because there are some bosses where you need to be on the same screen as the boss.Cheat: When an enemy attacks you with an energy attack just hit the R button to fly, when you get hit by the blast Goku will land but your flight meter will still show. This allows you to have Infinite Health. You can deactivate the glitch by pressing the R button again to fly and hit it again to land.  Though you can not see it your Ki will go down when you shoot it.Cheat: If you are wandering around in an area and are low on health, you can try this (not-so-secret) trick to recover quickly.  Save your game, then shut off the game and turn it back on again.  When you appear back where you left off, you'll be back at full health/Ki without even using items!Cheat: While playing as Vegeta charge up the big bang attack as soon as you start charging pause the game and Let go of the charge button then unpause the game and it will charge automaticallyCheat: After you find all 7 Nameks take them home and Cooler will be waiting to fight you. The dialogue before the battle will be different if you use Trunks or Goku.Cheat: To see the other ''special'' ending to the game, unlock Mr. Satan and get him to Level 50. Then, go to West City and break down the Level 50 door to ZZTV and you'll see a different ending to the game.Cheat: In the Capsule Corparation, go to Level 2. There, talk to Mrs. Briefs. She will give you a cookie. Continue talking to her, and she will never stop giving you cookies. These restore a small amount of HP every time you eat one.Cheat: To get Gohan's Trophy , simply get to Level 50 with Gohan then go to the ''50'' gate outside Gingertown to collect the  trophy.Cheat: To get Goku's Trophy , simply finish the game.Cheat: To get Piccolo's Trophy , simply get to Level 50 with Piccolo then go to the ''50'' gate at Namek planet to collect the trophy.Cheat: To play as Hercule , simply collect all 5 trophies.Cheat: To get Trunks' Trophy , simply get to Level 50 with Trunks then go to the ''50'' gate at West City to collect the trophy.Cheat: To get Vegeta's Trophy , simply get to Level 50 with Vegeta then go to the ''50'' gate at Northern Mountains to collect the trophy.Cheat: When you can get to the part where the old man steals the key from the mayor, you have to chase him back to his house. When you go inside his house you'll see a blue punching bag. If you continuously hit it you will slowly gain experience.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/12/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>Webfoot Technologies</Developer>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3458</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/930385-dragon-ball-z-the-legacy-of-goku-i-and-ii</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/dragon-ball-z-the-legacy-of-goku-i-ii</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dragon-ball-z-the-legacy-of-goku-ii/3030-11173/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1814881-box_dbztlog2.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/7/1/71971_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464311-dragon-ball-z-the-legacy-of-goku-i-ii-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6246/427231-goku21.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6246/427230-goku20.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6246/427228-goku19.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6246/427227-goku18.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6246/427226-goku17.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6246/427223-goku16.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6246/427222-goku15.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6246/427221-goku14.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6246/427220-goku13.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/BsWStz8.jpg</banner1>
</game>