<Game>
	<Name>2 Games in 1! - Dragon Ball Z - Buu's Fury + Dragon Ball GT - Transformation (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Dragon Ball Z: Buu's Fury / Dragon Ball GT: Transformation is a Miscellaneous game, developed by Webfoot Technologies and published by Atari,which was released in 2006.Cheat: Perfect Fusion In Buus FuryWhile performing the Fusion Dance, hit these buttons to complete a Perfect Fusion every time.Cheat: 255 Senzu BeansDuring the World Tournament Saga, after Videl's fight, Gohan asks Goku to get a Senzu Bean from Korin's Tower and get a bean from Yajirobe. When you get the Senzu Bean, eat it. When you go back Goku will still give Gohan a Senzu and when you look in your invintory, you will see that you have 255 senzu beans.Cheat: Unlock Gogeta In Buus FuryTo unlock the Fusion Dance for Goku and Vegeta, you must collect all of the Z Exhibits and Hercule Exhibits and return them to their places. Once all Exhibits are returned, the man at the counter that takes up the Exhibits will tell you that you can use the Fusion Dance with Goku and Vegeta!Cheat: Unlock Gogeta In Buus FuryMost of these modes and characters can be purchased in the 'Secrets' section of the main menu. But the Single Player Mode has to be unlocked by completing the Story Mode.Cheat: Enter any of the following to time during gameplay(while Not Pause). You'll hear a small chime to comfirm each code:Cheat: Enter these codes at anytime during gameplay.Cheat: You can unlock characters by pressing some buttons!!:PCheat: Note: Press it on the main menu(when you press the code for the character the character you press before that will gone)Cheat: Perform the task in order to unlock the thing specified after it.Cheat: Play through Rudeeze until you reach the boss.  After you destroy his stinger, he will be unable to attack you from a distance.  At this point, simply charge your ki meter and fire a special attack at him.  It won't cause any damage, but you should get about 30,000 points or so for doing this.  Continue doing so and you should quickly gain a large amount of points, and in turn, zenie.Cheat: During the World Tournament Saga, when Gohan asks Goku to get a Senzu Bean, fly to Korin's Tower and get a bean from Yajirobe. Instead of giving it to Gohan, eat it. When you return, Goku will still give a Senzu bean to Gohan even though he does not have any. When you look in your invintory, you will see that you have 255 senzu beans.Cheat: first, Equip Goku/Goten or Vegeta/Trunks (remove all unneeded equips before) and do the Fusion Dance. As Gogeta/Gotenks, remove the equipment from the equipped character. The Fusion will keep the equips but you'll be able to re-use the equips on another character. This will keep working untill you run out of Fusion timeCheat: Lure an enemy onto a Save Point with a strong character. Punch the enemy and kill it. Before you earn any experience from the downed enemy, the "Switch Character" menu will come up. Switch to a weak character. The character you switched to will gain the experience.Cheat: When these exhibits are found, take them to the Hercule Cafe in Hercule City to view them.Cheat: Everytime you get one of those, they are unlocked for the capsule corp museum, letting you see a specific item from the DBZ series.Cheat: To access a store containing some of the best items in the game, visit the Kai's planet once you beat Buu and work your way to the right-most map and break through the crack in the wall. In here you'll find great items for levelling up, such as the Kiloton Gloves/Boots, and great armor with super high endurance.Cheat: While a conversasion press the L or R button and the talking screen will go up and down.Cheat: While preforming the Fusion Dance with Either Goku/Vegeta or Goten/Trunks, if you ignore the buttons it tells you to press, and instead press Up, B, Left, Down, A, you will successfully fuse every time.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/3/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>Webfoot Technologies</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/931746-dragon-ball-z-buus-fury-dragon-ball-gt</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/5/0/1/73501_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/5/0/1/73501_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/f/b/gfs_73261_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/2/b/gfs_73261_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/9/b/gfs_73261_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/8/b/gfs_73261_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/3/b/gfs_73261_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7577671-72e6-4ab1-823a-85e4ce705f7c.jpg</banner1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/366e080d-ea72-41cb-b695-0f1721a3a27c.png</boxart3>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9fa37b14-3bc0-4d68-9a28-4dfa81ecd148.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://images.launchbox-app.com/915a4ec5-505e-42e1-9f98-d4279f834d12.png</snapshot7>
</game>