<Game>
	<Name>Advance Wars (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Basic GameplayBasic Advance Wars gameplay consists of players taking turns moving various combats units across a map in order to engage in combat with an opposing unit, with infantry units able to claim or capture cities, production bases and headquarters.Advance Wars is balanced using a rock/paper/scissors methodology, wherein each unit possesses strengths and weakness in comparison to other units. For example, a Medium Tank can easily destroy most ground-based vehicles in direct combat, but can't fire upon most aircraft, some of which--in turn--can destroy it with relative ease. Anti-Air units, meanwhile, are weak-to-middling against other ground units but can swiftly take out all aircraft.Victory can usually be attained one of two ways: either by wiping out all the enemy units on the map, or capturing the enemy HQ. A scant few story missions change it up, requiring you to protect a certain unit for a period of time, or putting you in a race to be the first to claim a certain number of cities and bases.Advanced GameplayTerrainJust as important as any unit or structure in the game is the battlefield itself. Certain terrain types can afford advantages while others can penalize to an extent. For example, while moving infantry into mountains, their movement range is cut, but it affords excellent cover and also visibility during Fog of War. Others are more obvious, such as tanks being restricted to land movement, but able to attack an adjacent boat unit on shoal. Air units are pretty much free to move wherever.Fog of WarFog of War is a battle situation wherein visibility across the map is obscured and limited to an individual unit's range of vision. Ground units can remain hidden when moved into woodland areas and mountain terrain can afford infantry units high degrees of visibility, while boat units can hide among reefs. This makes movement quite tricky as moving directly in the path of an unseen enemy unit can cause your unit to be trapped and helpless until your next turn. Air units are also very valuable here for their high degree of mobility but are just as at risk.COsAt the outset of each mission, the player chooses a CO and acts as adviser to the CO. Different COs have different abilities, strengths, and weaknesses and affect the battlefield in different ways. Each CO has a CO Power that can be used once its respective meter has been filled during battle, by taking and dealing out damage and securing structures. For example, Andy, the first CO the player meets, retains balanced "all-around" traits. His CO Power is Hyper Repair, which restores 2 hit-points to all units immediately upon use. Max, another CO, is particularly powerful in direct combat where he deals much more damage with any unit that can attack an enemy in an adjacent square. Meanwhile, his ranged, indirect units (rockets, artillery) are less effective and have a shorter firing range than is considered normal.The StoryIn Advance Wars, the player is cast as a military adviser for the Orange Star forces. Throughout the story campaign, players battle across 4 different countries, fighting a war against 4 other armies.The Countries of Wars WorldBlack HoleBlue MoonGreen EarthOrange StarYellow CometCheat: Data ClearIf you would like to erase data, press L, Select, and right on the D-Pad immediately after turning the Gameboy Advance on. The delete data option will appear, and if you want to begin again, you can.Cheat: Field Training Glitch - Unlimited Map EditingWith this glitch you can edit Campaign and War Room maps. The changes are saved only in the in-game (during battle) save, not permanently in the cartridge. - Go to Field Training and play the Naval Forces mission. - Lose by letting Olaf destroy either your T-Copter or your Lander. - Go to the Design Maps, deploy an Orange Star unit and destroy it. - Your screen will be glitched now. You can go to a saved Campaign or War Room map and edit it. Don't forget to save the changed maps using the in-game save, not the Design Maps save. - To return to normal, just turn on/off the GBA.Cheat: Gold Menu IconsTo change certain icons in the main menu screen from their original color to a flashing gold, you must complete the condition listed next to them: Records: Complete all 20 war room maps, regardless of rank. Rank: Obtain the final rank, rank 1. Stats: Get both rank and records gold, and this'll turn gold too. Field Training: Get an A-Rank in all 14 training missions. Campaign: Complete the Advance Campaign, regardless of rank. War Room: Get an S-Rank in all 20 war room maps. Battle Maps: You have to unlock and buy every CO, and buy all the maps. Design Maps, Vs. Mode, and the Multiplayer menu cannot be turned gold. Note: The gold menus do nothing for you; they're just there for pride. Cheat: Skip field trainingIf you want to skip field training and get into the war campaign, map maker or etc., instead of winning every battle in field training, just go to the last one and beat it. It'll save time, and you can always go back to play it any time on the main menu.Cheat: Easier final battle against SturmTo make the final mission a lot easier, allow Sturm to capture the Airport just north of the Orange Star base, and make sure you have Missiles in range of the Airport panel. Sturm will spend 22000 per turn building a Bomber that you can immediately destroy before use, making him much less of a threat.With Sturm wasting 22k per day making Bombers, his army is much weaker and easier to manage, no matter which allies you end up having in this battle.</plot>
	<releasedate>10/9/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>4+</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>d6XZF1YT78Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2495</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/471043-advance-wars</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/advance-wars</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/advance-wars/3030-12719/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1841697-box_awars.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/u2MRgny.jpg</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/27680-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24672-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24673-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-screenshot-mission-briefing.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24670-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-screenshot-battlefield.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24671-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-screenshot-get-ready-to-move.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24674-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24675-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-screenshot-artillery-infromation.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/537911-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-screenshot-deployable-air-units.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/537912-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-screenshot-deployable-ground.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/537913-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-screenshot-deployable-sea-units.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/537914-advance-wars-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-tutorial-doubles.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2495-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2495-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2495-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/yyKYV5P.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2495.png</clearlogo1>
</game>