<Game>
	<Name>Aggressive Inline (Europe) (En,Fr,De)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Released in 2002 by Z-Axis and Full Fat, and published by Acclaim, Aggressive Inline is similar in style to the Tony Hawk Franchise. The game features real life inline skaters Chris Edwards, Franky Morales, Jaren Grob and Taig Khris. The game also featured a soundtrack with a slight Third-Wave Ska leaning.Gameplay:Essentially, Aggressive Inline is extremely similar to Tony Hawks games, especially Tony Hawks Pro Skater 4. The player takes control of an inline skater in a small, but open, level, and can complete missions for various eccentric characters to not only increase game progression, but to increase the stats of the chosen skater. Some missions stick to generic Skating Game ideas, such as tasking the player with pulling off a high scoring trick, or racing somewhere in a particular time. However, some missions are decidedly crazier, such as helping a mad scientists achieve his ostensibly evil goals by performing sick-ass tricks. The game also featured a leveling system not unlike that seen in Final Fantasy 2, where the more a skater performs a particular style of trick, the more experience they get in that area, allowing them to perform better or longer (or more insane) tricks in that style.Reception:The game received high praise from many critics, mostly for it's easy-to-pick-up control scheme, wide open levels and an innovative style of gameplay. Scores averaged at about 85%. It was considered to be a very strong contender to the Tony Hawk franchise, but a sequel was never released.Soundtrack:Student Rick - Falling For YouHoobastank - Crawling In The DarkDJ Eric B &amp; Rakim - Don't Sweat the TechniqueThe Ataris - Song 13The Pharcyde - Passin' Me ByThe Vandals - An Idea for a MovieStudent Rick - Monday MorningP.O.D. - Youth of The NationReel Big Fish - Sell OutSublime - Wrong WayBoy Hits Car - I'm a CloudBlack Sheep - The Choice Is YoursSaliva - Your DiseaseCheat: CodesAt the code selection screen enter the following:</plot>
	<releasedate>27/8/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>CEvhX42BzQM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3307</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/914495-aggressive-inline</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/aggressive-inline_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/aggressive-inline/3030-2570/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2133335-box_ainline.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3307-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/205350-aggressive-inline-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/205351-aggressive-inline-game-boy-advance-screenshot-menu-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/205352-aggressive-inline-game-boy-advance-screenshot-character-selection.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/599051-aggressive-inline-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-small-bit.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/599052-aggressive-inline-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-are-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/599054-aggressive-inline-game-boy-advance-screenshot-racing-around.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/599055-aggressive-inline-game-boy-advance-screenshot-and-performing.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/599057-aggressive-inline-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-the-freeskate.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/599056-aggressive-inline-game-boy-advance-screenshot-however-some.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/13/131146/2123675-ai_screenshot__44_.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3307-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3307-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/sjzlh43.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3307.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In Aggressive Inline the player takes the role of one of nine real-life skaters with one specific goal: receiving as much points as possible by performing spectacular stunts. Every of the 13 courses also has various special challenges, e.g. collecting or smashing certain items, which need to be performed to beat it. In contrast to the open areas of the console versions this one features more linear levels and tight time limits.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2368a5dc-751c-4043-bde3-f61bb6bd61a6.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8aab2df9-7d9c-43af-b189-9defc5e63cf8.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Acclaim</Publisher>
</game>