<Game>
	<Name>Asterix & Obelix - Bash Them All! (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>Asterix &amp; Obelix: Bash Them All! is a 2D side-scrolling platform game based on the French comic series Astrix. It is a collection of two games. One old, namely a port of the SNES game Asterix and Obelix. The other game is called Asterix &amp; Cleopatra, based on the comic and animated movie of the same name. In Asterix and Cleopatra, Asterix has to help a Egyptian architect Artifis to build his pyramid for Cleopatra. You play typical platform levels where you jump around obstacles and walk towards the right of the screen. Many enemies such as fake building contractors and Roman soldiers (sent by a jealous Caesar), and pirates have to be bashed into the sky. Each level is concluded with a mini-game. The game closely follows the events of the comic.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Infogrames Europe SA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>19121</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920113-asterix-and-obelix-xxl</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/asterix-obelix-bash-them-all</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/19121-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349935-asterix-obelix-bash-them-all-game-boy-advance-screenshot-loading.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349936-asterix-obelix-bash-them-all-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349937-asterix-obelix-bash-them-all-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349947-asterix-obelix-bash-them-all-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349939-asterix-obelix-bash-them-all-game-boy-advance-screenshot-1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349940-asterix-obelix-bash-them-all-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349941-asterix-obelix-bash-them-all-game-boy-advance-screenshot-who.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349942-asterix-obelix-bash-them-all-game-boy-advance-screenshot-opening.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349943-asterix-obelix-bash-them-all-game-boy-advance-screenshot-starting.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349944-asterix-obelix-bash-them-all-game-boy-advance-screenshot-paf.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>What could be better than an Asterix game? Two Asterix games, of course! Indeed, this extraordinary cartridge designed for GameBoy Advance offers the lucky player two games for the price of one. Allow us to introduce the one on the right, inspired by Asterix and Cleopatra. Your mission, as you control our two heroes, is to help Edifis with the construction of a palace for Cleopatra. Mainly, you'll be defending him from the vile stratagems of his rival Artifis and Caesar's watchful legions. In the game on my left, "Asterix and Obelix," the idea is to bring souvenirs from every country in the Roman Empire to Julius Caesar, who deluded himself into thinking he could confine our indomitable Gauls to their village. Hang onto your helmet as your package tour, eventful as ever, takes you to see the wonders of (Great) Brittany, Helvetia, Greece, Mesopotamia, and Spain.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3084d9f1-0928-4f8b-8e39-a35d5f762d77.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0ecb83b5-3ce2-44a5-851c-8c376bcd97f0.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0977483-aebd-4fe8-873f-2d44a33472ee.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Bit Managers</Publisher>
</game>