<Game>
	<Name>Atomic Betty (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>It's tough being an intergalactic superhero when you've got to finish your homework and make it in time to the basketball finals - but that's just what Atomic Betty, defender of the cosmos, has to do!  Take care of the spoiled Penelope with the help of your friends while you're on earth, then blast off into space and combat the villainous genius, Maximus I.Q. (Evil Master Mind).Atomic Betty is a mix of the platform and puzzle genres, and plays very similarly to The Lost Vikings, in that you control three different characters simultaneously, each with varying abilities.  However, because Atomic Betty is aimed at a younger audience, there are two notable differences: first, it is a lot more difficult to die, and second, the player only needs to get one character to the exit to successfully finish the level.When on Earth, the player controls one character that can finish the homework, one that can push or pull objects, and the last that can slide under narrow gaps.  In Space, one character can repeatedly attack and use special gadgets, one can use a jetpack for a very high jump, and the last can grab items and enemies.  In addition to the main levels, the game also features levels where the player must control the spaceship as it zooms through asteroid belts and high-speed space warps.Cheat: Level PasswordsEnter the following passwords under "Continue" under "Play" at the Main Menu screen:Cheat: Level PasswordsUse the password at the Password screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/10/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Hometek Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>4vN6DR_ocpM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18439</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/927682-atomic-betty</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/atomic-betty</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/atomic-betty/3030-7832/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/18439-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/57348-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/57349-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150272-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150273-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150274-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-screenshot-tutorial.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150275-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-screenshot-opening-story.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150276-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-screenshot-controls-for-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150277-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-have-to-navigate.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150278-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-screenshot-help-betty-make-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150279-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-screenshot-success.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150280-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-map-of-the-current.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150281-atomic-betty-game-boy-advance-screenshot-an-example-of-using.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/18439.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Betty has a lot more to handle than most little girls. To her friends and family, she is your average, girl-next-door, but when the galaxy beckons, she becomes Atomic Betty, Galactic Guardian and Defender of the Cosmos. With the help of her trusty sidekicks, Sparky and X-5, Betty must save the galaxy from the evil Maximus I.Q., while at the same time saving her reputation on Earth from the scheming of her archrival, Penelope. "Atomic Betty's" five playable characters, rocket ship travel, selectable gadgets and weapons, and fast-paced story bring the cartoon hit to life.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/88141d92-0987-4bdf-8bc1-0d698733ab84.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/daa92c64-291e-4ba2-9cb3-376c33d4b022.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>