<Game>
	<Name>B-Densetsu! Battle B-Daman - Moero! B-Damashii!! (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Battle B-Daman 1 takes the action and adventure of the popular animated program 'Battle B-Daman' &amp; brings it to your Game Boy Advance. B-Daman is the ancient sport of the B-DaWorld, and Yamato Delgado dreams of playing it. His dream comes true when he's chosen to wield Cobalt Blade, the most powerful B-Daman ever. Use Cobalt Blade to compete in B-Daman tournaments and defeat the evil B-Daplayers of the Shadow Alliance, who will stop at nothing to take over the B-DaWorld.Cheat: Bronze Pass Zero Codes (US)In the Part Shops you can select the Input Zero Codes option to go and use these passwords.Cheat: Bronze Pass Zero Codes (US)(There is still probably more of these but I haven't found/tested those yet)Cheat: Bronze Pass Zero Codes (US)This is a password you could use when you get the gold passCheat: Bronze Pass Zero Codes (US)Enter these codes at the Parts Shop once you have gained the Bronze Pass. (Note: Each letter set represents the corresponding katakana symbol.  Lowercase letters mean the small version of the symbol, and "-" means the long line that represents a held vowel)Cheat: Bronze Pass Zero Codes (US)Enter these codes at the Parts Shop once you have gained the Gold Pass. (Note: Each letter set represents the corresponding katakana symbol.  Lowercase letters mean the small version of the symbol, and "-" means the long line that represents a held vowel)Cheat: Bronze Pass Zero Codes (US)Enter these codes at the Parts Shop once you have gained the Gold Pass.Cheat: Bronze Pass Zero Codes (US)Enter these codes at the Parts Shop once you have gained the Silver Pass. (Note: Each letter set represents the corresponding katakana symbol.  Lowercase letters mean the small version of the symbol, and "-" means the long line that represents a held vowel)Cheat: Costume ChangeUnder B-Dabattle, if you press the R button on the character select screen, you may change your current character's costume, for certain characters only.</plot>
	<releasedate>26/7/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>ATLUS</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/921230-battle-b-daman</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/battle-b-daman/3030-22494/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/16/164924/2360090-921230_74655_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/2/1/61221_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3699/415078-64768_16_2.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3699/415076-64768_15_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3699/415071-64768_14_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3699/415070-64768_13_2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3699/415067-64768_12_2.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3699/415063-64768_11_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3699/415060-64768_10_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3699/415056-64768_9_2.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3699/415050-64768_8_2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3699/415049-64768_7_2.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>