<Game>
	<Name>Backyard Sports - Baseball 2007 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Create your own team, and control every wacky pitch, clutch hit, and sprint for home. With players like Alex "A-Rod" Rodriguez, secret pros to unlock and amazing power-ups, kids can play big-league ball right in their own backyard. An all-star MLB lineup: Carlos Delgado, Alfonso Soriano, Nomar Garciaparra, Alex Rodriguez, Ichiro, Albert Pujols, Eric Gagne, Pedro Martinez, Ivan Rodriguez and Vladamir Guerrero.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/932373.htmlCheat: Unlimited TurboEnter the combination at the match up Screen.Cheat: Unlimited TurboType Grand Slam as a code to unlock Paul Konerko.Cheat: Area 51Make it to the World SeriesCheat: Area 51Play a season, don't need to complete it in order to unlock character</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Atari</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22235</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/932373-backyard-sports-baseball-2007</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22235-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/3/8/gfs_74254_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/e/8/gfs_74254_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/5/8/gfs_74254_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/4/8/gfs_74254_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/f/8/gfs_74254_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/v2gz9dr.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Backyard Baseball 2007 is the fifth iteration of the best selling youth baseball video game of all time and the only kid's game to hold the coveted Major League Baseball (MLB) and Major League Baseball Players Association (MLBPA) licenses. Backyard Baseball 2007 features a roster full of top MLB pros as kids and includes all 30 MLB teams, uniforms, and logos. In addition, the game's kid-friendly, non-violent format, and high level of diversity makes it especially popular with parents.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3d402e05-afc5-424d-acfc-dbc737a7c8cd.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7819a090-c4ab-4ac4-9473-5febe38d954b.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Atari</Publisher>
</game>