<Game>
	<Name>Barbie - The Princess and the Pauper (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>In her new adventure, Barbie takes on two roles--Erika and Princess Anneliese. Based on the classic story The Prince and the Pauper, this game follows Erika as she tries to prove that she's worthy to be crowned queen. With the help of Princess Anneliese, you must help Erika move through the game's unique environments and settings--the village, castle, and forest--so that she is fully prepared for the coronation ceremony and her role as queen. Showcase Erika's best qualities by helping villagers, solving puzzles, and completing creative tasks.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/920218.htmlCheat: All level passwordsEnter any of these passwords at the password screen to go to any part of the game you desire:Cheat: All level passwordsEnter these on the password screen</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>VU Games</Developer>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>27925</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920218-barbie-as-the-princess-and-the-pauper</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/27925-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/4/6/gfs_58443_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/9/6/gfs_58443_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/2/6/gfs_58443_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/3/6/gfs_58443_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/8/6/gfs_58443_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Barbie as the Princess and the Pauper is based on Barbie's home video take on the favorite fable. Erika are Anneliese beauties from two different worlds -- one a girl about town, the other a princess high in the land. When trouble starts in the kingdom, the two will have to solve puzzles and jump across dangers in 20 stages of adventure. Barbie as the Princess and the Pauper features two-player minigames and the ability to play as Erika, Anneliese, and even the royal cats Wolfie and Serafina!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d6b2e843-aa03-4246-b138-a6afe7465aa8.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>VU Games</Publisher>
</game>