<Game>
	<Name>Batman - Rise of Sin Tzu (USA) (En,Fr,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:A new supervillain tries his hand at conquering Gotham City.Batman: Rise of Sin Tzu is a 3D brawler developed by Ubisoft Montreal and published by Ubisoft for the PlayStation 2 (on October 16, 2003), Xbox (also on October 16, 2003), and GameCube (on November 11, 2003). The fourth and last Batman game to be based on the animated TV series The New Batman Adventures, up to two players can play as either Batman, Batgirl, Robin, or Nightwing, as they team up to take down four of Batman's supervillains: master of fear Scarecrow, shapeshifter Clayface, juiced-up warrior Bane, and a brand new adversary (warlord of Asia, Sin Tzu).Plot:Batman goes around the streets getting rid of the thugs in Gotham City. Afterwards, he gets a news that Commissioner Gordon is in trouble by the hands of Scarecrow, and proceeds to save him. While doing so, he is in contact with Scarecrow about trying to spread his fear gas throughout Gotham.By the time Batman goes to the museum, he finds Gordon affected by the fear gas and confronts Scarecrow. He defeats him and punches him, sending Scarecrow struggling to be hanged, but Batman saves him and arrests him.Batman goes to the Axis Chemicals factory to be confronted by clay-like henchmen. He is in contact with Clayface telling him that he plans to spread his chemical through all of Gotham, turning everyone into like him.After getting through Clayface's henchmen, Batman confronts him in the rooftop. After defeating him, Clayface tells Batman that there is someone who will take over Gotham. When Batman demands to know who is this person, Clayface faints.Batman gets into contact with Sin Tzu, the warlord of Asia. He tells him that he will stop his plot, if only Batman knows where Sin Tzu is hiding.He goes to the docks to stop Sin Tzu's weapon. By the time he gets into the Batcave, the weapon is revealed to be Bane. He says that he is the weapon of mass destruction. After being defeated, Batman has Bane knocking him out, but not before telling that by the time he woke up, he will forget where the Batcave is.Just then, Sin Tzu calls Batman about their battle. The latter figures out that the former is hiding in Arkham Asylum. Batman goes to the sewers in order to gain entry.While searching for Sin Tzu, Gordon calls Batman to tell him about Sin Tzu's ability, Yanjin, a mind control devise and that is how he has Scarecrow, Clayface, and Bane into his side. Gordon warns Batman that Sin Tzu's thugs would try to use the power on him, but Batman reassures that there will be no effect to him.Batman gets to Sin Tzu and defeats him.Cheat: CodesEnter the following codes at the Main Menu while holding L + RCheat: CodesHighlight Continue and enter the code below:Cheat: Fighting Bosses.Highlight Continue and enter the passwords below:Cheat: Fighting Bosses.Choose "Continue" from the main menu and the following passwords:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Beat-Em-Up</genre>
	<Developer>Ubisoft</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3328</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/914732-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/batman-rise-of-sin-tzu_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/batman-rise-of-sin-tzu/3030-17844/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3328-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3328-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/730628-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/730627-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu-game-boy-advance-screenshot-languages.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/633666-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu-game-boy-advance-screenshot-jump-on.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/633674-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu-game-boy-advance-screenshot-life-lost.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/633675-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu-game-boy-advance-screenshot-fight.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/633678-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu-game-boy-advance-screenshot-comics.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/633680-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu-game-boy-advance-screenshot-use-a-box.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/633689-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu-game-boy-advance-screenshot-password.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/633684-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu-game-boy-advance-screenshot-map.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/633687-batman-rise-of-sin-tzu-game-boy-advance-screenshot-video-conference.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3328-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3328-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3328.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In Batman: Rise of Sin Tzu, Batman faces a new enemy unlike any he has ever faced before. The faceless foe plunges Gotham City into chaos on the night of the anniversary of Bruce Wayne's parents' murder. Who is responsible for unleashing havoc on Gotham City? The truth will be revealed after you battle evil forces and super-villains, including Bane, Clayface, Scarecrow, and the new formidable foe--Sin Tzu. In addition to Batman's martial arts attacks, Batman has an arsenal including the Batarang, Grappling Hook, and Smoke Bomb.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/861837cd-e03a-4cfc-9107-2aaac2664de8.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bcda255e-e45d-4e0c-ba0e-e7c6f11f69d1.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8b6d046b-14d3-4b31-91f5-cab1687bc3ac.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>