<Game>
	<Name>Battle Network Rockman EXE 3 - Black (Japan) (Promo)</Name>
	<plot>Join Mega Mega.EXE, his pal Lan and friends as they keep the net safe from cyber mayhem in the most expansive battle network adventure yet. Together with the White version, find all of Mega Man's battle style changes, 'Giga Class' Chips, enemies and discover more surprises just for you!Cheat: CodesIf you attempt to use a Program of a color your current style does not support,you will get an error and be unable to boot up MegaMan until the problem is fixed.Cheat: CodesYou can bypass these errors once you have purchased the ModTools at Beach Street.When the error number appears,press Select and input the code to counter.Cheat: CodesThese codes can be entered after you buy the Mod Tools on Beach St. In the Navi Customizer, press select after loading your programs. This allows you to input codes. (Note: 1,2, and 3 correspond to the symbols.) Cheat: CodesIn the Navi Customizer Screen, move the highlight over the name of the program that you want to shrink (and has not been shrunk yet). Hold the 'Select' button, and key in the corresponding code.Cheat: CodesNOTE: 1,2, and 3 stand for the 3 weird characters, the first of which is 1, second is 2, and third is 3.Cheat: CodesWhen using the VarSwords, hold down the A button and enter the following quickly before the VarSword attacks and the VarSword's attack range will change to the following effect.Cheat: Numberman passwordsNumberman passwordsIn Higby's shop, you'll see Numberman who'll give you chips and other goodies if you enter the right passwords.Cheat: 11th Chip TrickThis trick will allow you to use the 2nd chip in your folder at any point in battle. First, you need Custom Style to fully level up, then get another Custom Style and begin leveling it up. You need enough Custom+ NaviCust programs to total Custom+5. Install said NaviCust parts. Now, in battle, load up any chip, then hover the cursor over the 10th chip and press right. The picture will show an ''11th'' chip. Now, there are two ways to go from here. If the 11th chip can normally be selected with the chip you've currently got selected, you can select it now and the chip in your first slot will become the second chip in your folder (the second chip in the list when viewing the full contents of your folder). If the 11th chip does NOT match, you can also deselect the selected chip(s) and select the 11th chip. Instead of getting the 11th chip in battle, you will get the 2nd chip in your folder! Really useful with the 2nd chip being a ProtomanV5 chip, etc.Cheat: 11th Chip TrickIn 2-player versus, the game can be fooled into copying wagered chip data, allowing players to duplicate chips. This glitch works in both versions.Cheat: 11th Chip TrickFirst, start up the game and begin a Real match, in which the winner gets a chip from the loser's pack. Once the battle is over and the Battle Result screen appears, the winner must press A once to reveal the chip he just won. Once the chip is revealed, the loser must turn off his game without pressing any buttons. This will let the loser keep his otherwise lost chip while still putting it in the winner's chip pack, duplicating the chip.Cheat: 11th Chip TrickMake certain that the loser is the one to turn off his game; if the winner turns off his game, the winner will not keep the chip while the loser still loses it, destroying the chip.Cheat: 11th Chip TrickIn Secret Area 2, near a warp point where the Time Trial Navi is standing facing diagonally down to the left, you can go into the corner behind him. If you press down at the right spot, you should walk through him.Cheat: 7 StarsThere are 7 stars you can get, which will appear next to the main title screen once you satisfy the objectives.Cheat: 7 StarsTo obtain a good number of these battle chips, you will need to use the Omega Navis Code. The ones that need this code to be active will be marked (SP).Cheat: 7 StarsTo Unlock the Secret Boss of the Secret Area Net, You need to gather all 200 standard chips. Then the Door of Honor will open, and you will be allowed to fight Serenade.Cheat: 7 StarsAfter you beat Alpha, secret bosses will be available to you.Cheat: 300,000 ZennyAfter obtaining all three Tomes in the "Legendary Tomes" job, don't head back to the Ghost Navi just yet. Instead, go to the strange-looking statue in the teacher's lounge at ACDC school. Examine the statue to find 300,000 Zenny.Cheat: 300,000 ZennyAfter you complete the Secret Area by defeating Serenade, use the 10-bug bug Trader 30 times, trading in a total of 300 bugs.  Then leave the secret area, (leave the internet and go back in). When your return to the Bug Trader, Bass will appear, fused with Gospel, and attack you. If you defeat him, you will get the Bass chip.</plot>
	<releasedate>24/6/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>4B_dzjfjV6Q</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6927</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/915457-mega-man-battle-network-3-blue</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6927-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6927-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/a/1/gfs_27076_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/5/e/gfs_50739_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/8/e/gfs_50739_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/3/e/gfs_50739_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/c/3/gfs_50739_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/6927-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/6927.png</clearlogo1>
</game>