<Game>
	<Name>Battle Network Rockman EXE 2 (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Enter the futuristic universe of Mega Man.EXE in this new adventure in the Battle Network series. Join him in his battle to fight cyber crimes in this mega role playing adventure. Now, there's a new net crime organization in town and its computer hacking has created a virus that's quickly gaining momentum. It's up to Mega Man.EXE, his pal Lan and friends to join the Net-Battlers and win this new cyber battle. Stop it before it spreads!Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.When fighting Thunderman, when one of the clouds is about to move on a pannel near you (when it's about half way on), move onto the same pannel. The game recognizes it as hit, but you don't take damage. If done right, you should have the Invis chip effect for about 1/4 of normal time. This is a useful trick for S ranking him.Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.Requirements:2 GBA/SP2 MMBN2 game paks.Link cableCheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.This glitch allows you to duplicate your lost chipdata in a netbattle against your oppenant, do not worry about it damaging your gamesave, I have done this hundreds of times and my gamesave has not suffered.Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.You and your friend (or just you on your own, still possible to do) must go into network and compete in a real netbattle against eachother, and one must win without flaw, when the battle is over, as soon as the chip datas name is shown, the LOSER must reset his game. (A+B+Start+Select), as a result, where the winners data is saved and the losers is not, the losers chip data is not lost and the winners is still saved resulting in a duplication of the chip.Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.WARNING: If the winner resets, instead of duplication you will simply DESTROY the chip, because the loser still loses and the winner doesn't save the fact it was won.Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.What are the benefits to this? Well in short, imagine how easy it'll be to duplicate and share your secret chips, Bass V3s, Lifeaur3s and other rare only get one of me chip data. You can even duplicate the final chip data, Sanctuary. Of course the better the busting level, the better the chip you'll duplicate.Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.Put a ZeusHammer into your folder. Go into battle and take damage on purpose till you have 200HP or less. Then kill the virus or escape. Now, find a Mole2 Virus in WWW Area 3. (This can be done with Mole1, too, but it's harder.) Attack the virus till it has 200HP or less. Then use your ZeusHammer. The Mole2 is deleted and you take 200 damage. Your HP is reduced to zero but you still win the battle. Now you can walk around the net with zero HP. Note: Have a healing subchip or you'll get deleted when next battle starts.Cheat: 5 StarsYou can get up to 5 stars, which will help allow you to unlock Hard Mode.Cheat: 5 StarsAfter you beat Gospel, secret Navis are fightable to you, if you meet the requirements.Cheat: Gamecube LogoAt the end of ShadowMan's level (the Mother Computer), on the right there is the Gamecube Logo.Cheat: Unlock HubstyleTo unlock this special style, you must defeat all V3 navis (excluding Bass) with an S-rank. Then, the next time a style change occurs, you will get Hubstyle.Hubstyle is a unique style that is non-elemental, and combines the benefits of every other style in the game. It will halve your max HP though.This style will only show up once per game, so if you skip or erase it, it will be gone for good.To confirm this unlockable, talk to the girl in ACDC Town behind the trees near the park. She will tell you which V3 navis you have defeated with an S-rank, and say that she sees all the available "ghosts" if you have defeated them all.</plot>
	<releasedate>17/6/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<rating>9.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>oGzwNcvDYeU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6926</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561218-mega-man-battle-network-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6926-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6926-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/1/9/gfs_1997_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/9/b/gfs_44978_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/4/b/gfs_44978_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/f/b/gfs_44978_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/e/b/gfs_44978_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/6926-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/6926.png</clearlogo1>
</game>