<Game>
	<Name>BattleBots - Design & Destroy (USA)</Name>
	<plot>BattleBots: Design and Destroy lets you create the robot warrior of your dreams and challenge 16 actual bots from the TV show.  Equip them with weapons and armor of your choice and challenge your friends to system link play with up to four players.  Play solo against three bots simultaneously in Tournament or Brawl mode.  Combat takes place in five different hazard filled arenas including the famed BattleBox.  BattleBots: Design &amp; Destroy captures the action and excitement of the TV show that started the robot combat craze.Cheat: Airplane Graveyard LevelWin the lightweight division to unlock the Airplane Grave Yard.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Majesco Sales, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>20857</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/918795-battlebots-design-and-destroy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/battlebots-design-destroy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/battlebots-design-destroy/3030-7572/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/20857-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/b/d/gfs_48994_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/6/d/gfs_48994_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/d/d/gfs_48994_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/c/d/gfs_48994_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/7/d/gfs_48994_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Enter the robotic mayhem of BattleBots: Design &amp; Destroy, developed exclusively for the Game Boy Advance. Based on the TV show of the same name, BattleBots the game puts you in control of your favorite robotic vehicles, including Overkill, Tazbot, Diesector, Minion, and more. You can play as one of the combatants in the TV show or build your own BattleBot from six categories of parts and weapons. See how well your machine performs against up to four BattleBots.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/71fd3180-fb21-425c-9e9d-85d1b129388d.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/18c73d78-e1c0-403b-9032-1e0dbcdfba91.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Majesco Games</Publisher>
</game>