<Game>
	<Name>Battle Network Rockman EXE 3 (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Join Mega Mega.EXE, his pal Lan and friends as they keep the net safe from viruses and cyber menaces. You'll travel through new virtual and real worlds, fight-off new bosses, interact with new characters and even find new Battle Chips. It's cyber mayhem at it's best!Cheat: Error CodesIf you attempt to use a Program of a color your current style does not support,you will get an error and be unable to boot up MegaMan until the problem is fixed.You can bypass these errors once you have purchased the ModTools at Beach Street.When the error number appears,press Select and input the code to counter.Cheat: Error CodesIf you have the ModTools and there are no Errors in the NaviCust, extra codes can be entered to give MegaMan a power boost. To enter these, press the 'Select' button after 'Running' the NaviCust program and then enter the code.Note: 1 = first strange symbol, 2 = second strange symbol, 3 = third strange symbol.Cheat: Error CodesIn the Navi Customizer Screen, move the highlight over the name of the program that you want to shrink (and has not been shrunk yet). Hold the 'Select' button, and key in the corresponding code.Cheat: Error CodesNOTE: 1,2, and 3 stand for the 3 weird characters, the first of which is 1, second is 2, and third is 3.Cheat: Error CodesWhen having the VarSword chip in battle hold down A button and enter these codes quickly.Cheat: Numberman passwordsIn Higby's shop, you'll see Numberman who'll give you chips and other goodies if you enter the right passwords.Cheat: 11th chip trickThis trick will allow you to use the 2nd chip in your folder at any point in battle. First, you need Custom Style to fully level up, then get another Custom Style and begin leveling it up. You need enough Custom+ NaviCust programs to total Custom+5. Install said NaviCust parts. Now, in battle, load up any chip, then hover the cursor over the 10th chip and press right. The picture will show an ''11th'' chip. Now, there are two ways to go from here. If the 11th chip can normally be selected with the chip you've currently got selected, you can select it now and the chip in your first slot will become the second chip in your folder (the second chip in the list when viewing the full contents of your folder). If the 11th chip does NOT match, you can also deselect the selected chip(s) and select the 11th chip. Instead of getting the 11th chip in battle, you will get the 2nd chip in your folder! Really useful with the 2nd chip being a ProtomanV5 chip, etc.Cheat: 11th chip trickIn 2-player versus, the game can be fooled into copying wagered chip data, allowing players to duplicate chips. This glitch works in both versions.Cheat: 11th chip trickFirst, start up the game and begin a Real match, in which the winner gets a chip from the loser's pack. Once the battle is over and the Battle Result screen appears, the winner must press A once to reveal the chip he just won. Once the chip is revealed, the loser must turn off his game without pressing any buttons. This will let the loser keep his otherwise lost chip while still putting it in the winner's chip pack, duplicating the chip.Cheat: 11th chip trickMake certain that the loser is the one to turn off his game; if the winner turns off his game, the winner will not keep the chip while the loser still loses it, destroying the chip.Cheat: 7 StarsThere are 7 stars you can get, which will appear next to the main title screen once you satisfy the objectives.Cheat: 7 StarsFor most of these Giga-Class chips, you'll need to have traded and unlocked the SP mode.Cheat: 7 StarsAfter you beat Alpha, secret bosses will be available to you.Cheat: 300000 Easy ZennyFirst do the job &amp;quot;Legendary Tomes&amp;quot;. Once you have the tomes don't go back to the Navi, instead go to the teachers lounge. Look at the back shelf and examine the strange orange statue. Theres a code in the statue that matches with the tomes and the data is 300000 zenny.Cheat: 300000 Easy ZennyOnce you complete the game by defeating the final boss, wait until the credits roll and the title screen appears. There should be a star next to 'continue'. When you continue the game, it will continue from the spot where you last saved as usual, but you will now be allowed access to the Secret Area, which is located in the Ura-Internet square. You can only get there by pluuging into the computer under the hot springs. You will need 100 standard chip entries in your library to enter.Cheat: 300000 Easy ZennyAfter you complete the Secret Area by defeating Serenade, put at least 300 BugFrags in the Trader, then leave the internet. When your return to the Bug Trader, Forte will appear, fused with Gospel, and attack you. If you defeat him, you will get the Forte chip.</plot>
	<releasedate>24/6/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<rating>8.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>6928</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/562255-mega-man-battle-network-3-white</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6928-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6928-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/e/2/gfs_27077_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/1/7/gfs_45233_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/c/7/gfs_45233_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/7/7/gfs_45233_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/6/7/gfs_45233_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/6928-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/6928.png</clearlogo1>
</game>