<Game>
	<Name>Black Matrix Zero (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>This installment of the Black/Matrix series is set in the same universe, a world which is populated by angels with white bird-like wings, demons with black bat-like wings, and wingless humans. For many years, the war between angels and demons has been going on. You control an ordinary boy named Cain. You live on a secluded island as a servant of a woman named Matia, far away and seemingly safe from the battle areas. But as both demons and angels seem to be interested in Matia and she gets kidnapped eventually, Cain realizes he must do everything to save her, and becomes involved in the great struggle.This is a strategy RPG with turn-based combat, in which you navigate your party members on the isometric battle screen and attack or use magic spells when the enemy is in range. Story sequences occur between battles which take up most of the gameplay.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/8/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>NEC Interchannel, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.3</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>30554</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/580564-black-matrix-zero</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/blackmatrix-zero</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/blackmatrix-zero/3030-7917/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/30554-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464071-black-matrix-zero-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464072-black-matrix-zero-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464073-black-matrix-zero-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464074-black-matrix-zero-game-boy-advance-screenshot-character-overview.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464075-black-matrix-zero-game-boy-advance-screenshot-first-battle.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464076-black-matrix-zero-game-boy-advance-screenshot-about-to-be.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2508/586409-bmz_05.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2508/586408-bmz_04.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2508/586407-bmz_03.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2508/586406-bmz_02.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Black Matrix Zero combines standard tactical RPG gameplay with a pastiche of Judeo-Christian religious themes, particularly concerning the nature of good and evil and the interplay between Heaven, Hell, and Earth and the denizens thereof. The game is set in the same fictional world as the original Black/Matrix game, though hundreds of years prior. Three divisions of humankind share the same world - white-winged people who are called angels, black-winged people who are called devils, and wingless people. Those who have wings have great powers and pay little mind to the wingless ones. The angels rule the world via a religious organization called the Prodevon Church, which ensures both the cooperation and ignorance of the wingless people.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9a6ba6b2-b64f-41a5-b2d0-6b3157fd04c1.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Interchannel</Publisher>
</game>