<Game>
	<Name>Blades of Thunder (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The war on terrorism is at large. Terrorist organisations have spread worldwide and the leaders of the free world have decided to form a global anti-terror task force to strike with extreme measures at the sign of terrorist threats. You are the primary weapon of this force and your mission is to hunt down, attack and destroy the threats to America and the rest of the free world, utilizing the best of strategic air combat.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/925884.htmlCheat: PasswordsThe following are entered in the passwords menu.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<Developer>Summitsoft Entertainment</Developer>
	<rating>2.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>25874</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/925884-blades-of-thunder</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/25874-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/25874-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/1/a/gfs_61985_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/c/a/gfs_61985_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/7/a/gfs_61985_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/6/a/gfs_61985_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/d/a/gfs_61985_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>A U.S. recon team reports a terrorist cell is planning a major attack in the Middle East, hoping to overrun the oil refineries of the Gulf States to fuel worldwide terror. To secure our freedom you must hunt down and destroy this threat before it strikes. Take command of a deadly gunship to deal America's wraith in the steel jacketed fury of today's deadliest weapon systems. The game features 10 operation levels with air, land and sea missions, topped by elaborate boss fights. Your gunship's tactical weapon systems include machine guns, hydra rockets and homing missiles. There are also weapon and armor power-ups found throughout the game. Use radar to keep on top of targets and enjoye the real-time 3D graphics packed with realistic visual effects. Features multiple difficulty levels.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7f4961c9-b56a-4294-9bf9-000eb6ec6e36.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Summitsoft</Publisher>
</game>