<Game>
	<Name>Board Game Classics (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Board Game Classics includes the games Chess, Checkers, and Backgammon. In each of these games, you can either face the computer, on one of three difficulty levels, play against your friends, watch the computer play itself, or set up a tournament against the computer. You can choose an avatar, piece set, and board as well.Optional variant rules include forcing jumps in checkers, castling and en passant in chess, and backgammon scoring and automatic doubling in backgammon.Cheat: Password - Unlocking themesTo unlock fantasy and atlantis theme (along with characters like Glorp, Telem, Chomp and Bubbles), type in the following password.Cheat: Unlockable - Characters and themesTo unlock these characters and themes win the tournament for Chess or Checkers.Cheat: Unlockable - Characters and themesTo unlock these characters simply finish the tournament mode for Chess or Checkers.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Destination Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>7H1ZCKwI3Mc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22341</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929030-board-game-classics</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/board-game-classics</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/board-game-classics/3030-34683/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/12/125537/1750464-giant_bomb_sub_2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/189074-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/189075-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/443787-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/443788-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/443789-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-screenshot-game-parameters.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/443790-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-variant.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/443791-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-your.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/443792-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-screenshot-ready-to-start.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/443793-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-screenshot-white-bishop.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/443794-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-screenshot-white-king.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/443795-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-screenshot-white-king.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/443796-board-game-classics-game-boy-advance-screenshot-playing-with.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>DSI Games has gathered together some of the greatest board games of all times in its BOARD GAME CLASSICS compilation game for the Game Boy Advance. The compilation includes CHESS, CHECKERS, and BACKGAMMON. Each game has several different options for players. In CHESS, for example, gamers can watch fantasy and sci-fi pieces battle it out each time a piece is taken. CHECKERS, too, has several different themed boards, including space and Atlantis, that can change the look and feel of the game. All three games have different difficulty settings for players. Variants on the traditional rules are also available for each game. In addition to challenging the AI to a match or playing through a tournament, players can also use the GBA link to challenge friends to any of the three games using any of the rule variations and settings. Gamers who love these three classic games are sure to enjoy their GBA incarnations, and the ability to challenge others to a match adds to the fun and replayability.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/354f07d1-7013-46dd-8eab-8d4c71e22bd7.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d0dbf475-05e6-4078-9a23-c2af7adfa8c4.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>DSI Games</Publisher>
</game>