<Game>
	<Name>Boktai 2 - Solar Boy Django (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Boktai 2: Solar Boy Django is the second installment in the Boktai video game series, and the sequel of Boktai: The Sun is in Your Hand. It introduced a number of gameplay modifications, notably switching its focus from the stealth aspect of its predecessor to a more action-oriented game.   Plot:Following the first game of the series, Django returns to the city of San Miguel, only to have his Solar Gun stolen by a mysterious vampire and find that the city has been overrun by the Undead. Using San Miguel as a central hub, he proceeds through several dungeons as an attempt to stop the Undead from invading the city of the Sun.  Gameplay:As opposed to the stealth-oriented Boktai: The Sun is in Your Hand, Boktai 2 is more of an action RPG, allowing the main character to upgrade his stats by leveling up in battle. A wider assortment of weapons is also available, while the previous game only allowed the player to carry a customisable gun. The new weapons were divided into different categories, including swords, lances and hammers. In addition, the new Solar Forging feature allows two weapons to be crafted together in order to form a new, more powerful one. Despite all these changes, however, the main feature of the series, the solar sensor, remains. It is necessary during boss "purifications", and greatly helps the player by uncovering hidden secrets and recharging his or her character's "solar gauge".Cheat: Crossover Battle CodeEnter the password in the links section.Cheat: Forging at night or in low sunlightIf you go into the smithy, you can forge without any sunlight at all.  Simply get in talking position so you can talk to Smith. Then, use the Rising Sun magic, and quickly talk to Smith before the shot explodes. Proceed with the forging. Afterwards, if you did it correctly, you will have the same amount of energy you started with. This way, at night, if you want to forge more than once, you no longer need to buy Solar Nuts to restore  lost energy.Cheat: BlindboxesBlindboxes are sold to you by ??? (Solid Snake) after rescuing him from the House of Time.  He sells blindboxes in the mall, which contain a random item.  They start off at level 1, and contain regular Items.  By upgrading the blindboxes, the items inside them will improve/Cheat: BlindboxesEmblems are items that enhance your weaponry.  They either bestow new power on your weapons or allow you to forge stronger than normal weapons.Cheat: BlindboxesComplete the task in order to win the specified bonusCheat: BlindboxesFinish Spiral Tower to get Sabata.Cheat: BlindboxesThe Solar Tree requires a certain amount of Sol to be collected for its growth. To check the amount of Sol you have collected, you must complete the game once and speak to the librarian.At a certain point of the tree's growth, you receive armour.Cheat: BlindboxesAll you really need is to have beaten the cathedral and saved Smith so you can forge. Then get some sunlight and any 2 spears to start with.Cheat: BlindboxesAll you really need is to have beaten the cathedral and saved Smith so you can forge. Then get some sunlight and any 2 swords to start with. Cheat: BlindboxesBeat the game once and in the library press A in front of the shelf closest to the right of the lady to view the titles.Cheat: BlindboxesShops are unlocked as follows.Cheat: Smiths Quality RatingsWhen you forge somthing, Smith will say one of these 3 thing: (Next to them is what advantages/disadvantages you can get from them.)"Tsh. Not great, eh?" - Highest:-1  Lowest: -10"Oooh, fine job." - Highest: +10  Lowest: +1"Wow! Superb workmanship!" - SP (Highest rank)</plot>
	<releasedate>19/10/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3334</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920413-boktai-2-solar-boy-django</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/boktai-2-solar-boy-django</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/boktai-2-solar-boy-django/3030-14556/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/27442/953741-boktai2gba_1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3334-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/56795-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464260-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-screenshot-language.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464261-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464262-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-screenshot-entering.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464263-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464264-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-screenshot-start.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464266-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-screenshot-there.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464267-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-screenshot-spiders.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464268-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-screenshot-map.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464269-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-screenshot-player.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464270-boktai-2-solar-boy-django-game-boy-advance-screenshot-inventory.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3334-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3334-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/xdQCYWv.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3334.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Boktai 2 continues the adventures of Django the Solar Boy as he sets out to rid the world of evil vampires and demons. The second installment in the franchise brings back the solar sensor technology, which incorporates natural sunlight into gameplay. Take advantage of natural sunlight through the built-in solar sensor on the Game Boy Advance cartridge to power up and fuse more than 60 weapons and items. Now you can head outdoors and battle enemies with more weapons, new characters, and a larger game environment.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aefc4441-eb42-4133-9277-14acd43e96eb.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b386d818-f9ca-4c9b-8cbf-54224d431050.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/239a43a3-9dd9-489b-bf34-8224e7ce4695.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d507329e-eea1-4464-bc4c-82dbb705df17.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e573902a-467b-42c0-916f-0769857c63ad.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>