<Game>
	<Name>Bokura no Taiyou - Taiyou Action RPG (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Boktai: The Sun Is in Your Hand is the first Game Boy Advance game that uses sunlight to influence gameplay. In the game, you'll follow the adventures of Django, a young vampire hunter on a quest to rid the world of evil. As Django, you must overcome traps, defeat enemies, and fight through the deepest parts of dungeons. Watch out for the amount of sunlight--Django is stronger by day, while the vampires are stronger by night. The game features a solar sensor on the cartridge and a real-time clock system.Cheat: Easy Life FruitIn a room in the Abyss, enter the following:Cheat: Infinite Sunlight1. Get a tonniar rm. You can get one from the Count by burning him with a skylight. 2. Observe what time the sun rises in your game (by going into an Immortal dungeon at night), then save in the area with the solar tree 3. Set the time in the main menu ''Options'' screen to one minute before your sunrise (such as 5:59) 4. Hurry and get under the solar tree. At the crack of dawn, dew will fall and convert your tonniar into a Mr. RainNot. 5. Walk east one screen and use Mr. RainNot. You now have two bars of sunlight at all times until the next sundown. Now, to keep your sunlight permanently, each time you play boktai set the clock to daytime of the day you used the Rainnot. With this method you will have sunlight, day or night, every time you play boktai!Cheat: Dark Gun PiecesComplete the following tasks to unlock the 3 pieces for the dark gun (all 3 must be acquired in order to use them)Cheat: Dark Gun PiecesEmblems allow you to open locked doors in Asure Sky Tower.  All are needed to fight the secret boss of the tower, the Silvery White KnightCheat: Dark Gun PiecesTo gain the ability to carry more grenades, obtain 9999 points in Link Battle mode.Cheat: Dark Gun PiecesThis is by far the hardest to get. It's too tedious for most people.Cheat: Dark Gun PiecesComplete the game at least once, making sure to save after completing the game. Start a New Game+ on this file (automatically done when selecting a completed game file). Upon reaching the Solar Tree, a warp will be next to the little hill going up to the raised area. Access this warp to be teleported to a small room with five Hint Blocks, which contain bits of information about your game data.Cheat: Dark Gun PiecesTo get the Pink Solar Tree, gather at least 1500 Sols. The Pink Solar Tree lets you get the Chaos Battery, and Astro Battery.Cheat: Change OtenkoWhen Otenko is following you around, there a a few, useless, fun things you can do with him. Fire a Rising Sun Grenade and Otenko will grow larger. Shoot him with the Sol Lens and will glow red. Shoot Otenko with a Flame or Frost Lens and he will glow white.Cheat: Change OtenkoOn the main title screen, you will see a sun. The sun's rays move at different speeds depending on how much sunlight is striking the sensor. The rays move faster if there is more sunlight hitting the sensor.Cheat: More Sensitive Solar SensorWhen the game asks to cover the Solar Sensor with your hand, do this in as dark a place as possible. If done right, the Solar Sensor will be extra sensitive.Cheat: More Sensitive Solar SensorAny of the Undead sleep when they have \"Zzz\" over there head. These are the times of their sleeping. A Ghoul (Bok) sleeps from 6-6:30 AM. A Mummy sleeps from 9-9:30 AM. A Golem sleeps from 3-3:30 AM. And a Cockatrice sleeps from 12 PM-12:30 PM.Cheat: More Sensitive Solar Sensor</plot>
	<releasedate>16/9/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
	<Developer>KCEJ</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3333</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589655-boktai-the-sun-is-in-your-hand</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3333-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3333-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/1/2/gfs_47258_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/c/2/gfs_47258_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/7/2/gfs_47258_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/6/2/gfs_47258_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/8/f/gfs_47258_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3333-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3333-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3333.png</clearlogo1>
</game>