<Game>
	<Name>Bomberman Tournament (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Bomberman Tournament is an action/role-playing game developed by Hudson Entertainment and published by Activision for the Game Boy Advance.Story:Bomberman just landed on PhantarionThe 5 Dastardly Bombers (from  Super Bomberman 2 and  3) Land on Planet Phantarion. A Large Fortress erects and the land around the fortress began to freeze over. The inhabitants of Phantarion send out a distress call, and Bomberman Max goes off to investigate. Soon enough he has disappeared, and  Bomberman himself goes to investigate.Gameplay:Game Modes:There are two gameplay modes to choose from in Bomberman Tournament.Quest modeQuest mode involves a single player story with the standard Bomberman gameplay, with added RPGelements including Suit upgrades and new items.Battle modeBattle Mode is a standard Bomberman Multiplayer that has been featured in the franchise over the years.KarabonsStarting a Karabon BattleIn Bomberman Tournament there are small creatures called Karabons that can be collected and battled with, similar to Pokemon. Karabons are a major part of the quest mode.Karabon battles are pre-determined at the beginning of a match due to the Karabons stats and pre-set attacks.Some Karabons can be fused into a single Karabon that has 2 attributes.There are 25 Karabons to collect.ElementsThere are four possible elements that a Karabon can possess:Fire, AKA DragonWater, AKA FishElectric, AKA PommyEarth, AKA BeastThese elements are strong or weak to another element. Water beats fire, fire beats earth, earth beats electricity, and electricity beats water.AttributesEach type of Karabon has an attribute which can help it in battle. For example Electric, or Pommy can use teleport to a town that has been previously visited.Powering UpWhile walking around in the world, Bomberman can bomb the various bushes. Inside some of these bushes are panels. These panels are represented by:Sword - Swords are used to upgrade a Karabons attack.Shield - Shields are used to upgrade a Karabons defense.Star - Stars are used to upgrade a Karabons special attack.Cheat: use elekong in muiltiplayer modeYou must have elekong to do this. Go into a base and equip elekong. Then, save. Next, kill yourself and when the game asks you if you want to continue, quit. Go into muiltiplayer mode and play. You will be able to walk through blocks if you did this correctly.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/6/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Activision Publishing, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>8TKYjpvG72w</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3338</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/477602-bomberman-tournament</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/bomberman-tournament</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/bomberman-tournament/3030-9113/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3338-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3338-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/119832-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/18045-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-piece-of.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/18046-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-doc-will.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/18047-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/18048-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-screenshot-loading-a.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/18049-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-screenshot-your-ship.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/18050-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-screenshot-and-this-is.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/18051-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-screenshot-karabons-a.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/18052-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-only-need.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/18053-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-screenshot-and-let-the.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/18054-bomberman-tournament-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-this-game.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3338-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3338-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Awpoa3i.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3338.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>An S.O.S. from the cosmos signals that planet Phantarion is in trouble! Grab your arsenal and get ready for non-stop action as you blast your way through interactive battlefields and take on up to 4 real-time players. Battle opponents through 8 interactive battlefield mazes! Take on up to 4 players in multi-player blastfests! Fast, furious, explosive bombing adventure!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3753431c-e4e7-4707-b890-823a46b3015e.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c3d29ada-7c00-42bc-b7fb-302f38645b9c.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8670392d-34a3-4be2-a54f-e1e70b19a8de.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>