<Game>
	<Name>Broken Circle (Europe) (En,It) (Proto)</Name>
	<plot>This game is canceled, and should not have a release date or be attached to any concept, object, location, or character except the Canceled Games page. See the page for details.Overview:Broken Circle was a turn-based RPG by 7 Raven Studios for the Game Boy Advance. The developers had difficulty finding an interested publisher, partially because the game's 256MB size would require expensive cartridges. By the time 7 Raven finally managed to reduce the game to 56MB, the GBA was at the end of its life and no longer an attractive platform for publishers. Thus Broken Circle never officially came out; however, 7 Raven later released the last version of the game in ROM form as a free download.</plot>
	<releasedate>Unreleased</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Unpublished</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/932098-broken-circle</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/broken-circle/3030-25333/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890421-front.gif</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890432-screen011.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890431-screen010.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890430-screen009.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890429-screen008.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890428-screen007.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890427-screen006.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890426-screen005.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890425-screen004.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890424-screen003.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/890423-screen002.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>The tale tells the story of the land of Midgard; it was never a quiet land of peace as many wars have raged in the land. In recent months violence of both man and monster has escalated, monsters have become far more dangerous. Earthquakes began to shake the land. Prophets have claims that this is the sign of Ragnarok, the day where man and monster alike will die in the end. Friends and foes alike will cross your path, will you survive your journey to do battle and vanquish Hagen the wizard necromancer the apparent cause of the disruption in Midgard? Or will the Hunter beast from Hell that is stalking you stop you in your travels?</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>lQzH0OHk0SM</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f8eae58f-fec8-413e-a1e8-136ac6ab7ae2.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/77c1b2e9-5fcd-4098-b61d-95def4bade8f.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Piko Interactive</Publisher>
</game>