<Game>
	<Name>Bura Bura Donkey (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The normally quiet jungle is abuzz with excitement, because it's time for the ceremony to choose the king of the jungle! Or at least it would be if King K. Rool hadn't stolen the special medallion meant for the winner. Donkey Kong and his friends must swing their way through the jungle to get the medallion back and, along the way, rescue Diddy, Dixie, and Funky Kong from King K. Rool's minions. A unique control system lets you swing through the trees and spin to build up momentum for a mighty leap. Innovative level design combines elements of platform and puzzle games: Grab gears and spin to crank doors open. Watch out for bolts that loosen as you spin, or you might find yourself falling flat. You'll need steady hands to make the leap-of-faith that takes you to the treetops.Cheat: Secret Jungle Jam EventOn the title screen, press up, L, A, and B at the same time to go to a password screen.Cheat: UnlockablesTo unlock these modes or characters complete the stated requirements, a message should be displayed if you did it correctly.</plot>
	<releasedate>19/9/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Paon Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>7.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3452</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920791-dk-king-of-swing</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3452-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3452-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/6/d/gfs_55622_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/b/d/gfs_55622_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/0/d/gfs_55622_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/1/d/gfs_55622_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/a/d/gfs_55622_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3452-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3452.png</clearlogo1>
</game>