<Game>
	<Name>Cars - Mater-National Championship (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>Cars Mater-National features an all-new international group of racers vying for their chance to compete against Lightning McQueen in the First Annual Mater-National Race Festival, hosted by Lightning's best friend, Mater. Explore the new and improved open world of Radiator Springs, play in the all-new Monster Mode, jump into the fast lane with six new International racing competitors, burn rubber on new tracks, and twist and turn your way through new mini-games like Ramone's Rhythmic Rumble and Fillmore's Fuel Frenzy.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/938975.html</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2007</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>THQ</Developer>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/938975-cars-mater-national-championship</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/6/9/84969_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/2/e/gfs_86426_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/f/e/gfs_86426_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/4/e/gfs_86426_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/5/e/gfs_86426_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/e/e/gfs_86426_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Disney/Pixar Cars: Mater-National Championship is an arcade style racing game based on the continuing story of Lightning McQueen from the feature film Cars. It features 13 characters in total, 3 areas and the following modes: Story Mode Play as one of 10 playable characters in the world of Radiator Springs, Ornament Valley, and Cadillac Range. Challenge 5 international bosses and all the residences of Radiator Springs in 17 races across 14 unique tracks. Challenge Mode Challenge mode includes trophy hunt, elimination, and beat the clock. Two challenge mode events are unlocked every time you process to a new track in the story mode. Multiplayer Includes 4 player single- and multi-cart modes of multiplayer. The player may race in single events or four race cup events. The game includes Cinematic Gameplay Scenarios (or CGS). CGS are cinematic pieces of gameplay where the camera moves to a position to better show the player character, while creating gameplay complementary to the new camera angle/perspective. These exist to make gameplay feel varied and cinematic, to give the player a sense that they are playing a piece of the movie.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/544c06ba-f5eb-4a7e-9d18-127c469ef245.png</boxart2>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>