<Game>
	<Name>Castlevania - Circle of the Moon (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Nathan Graves, the game's main protagonistCastlevania: Circle of the Moon (known in Europe as simply Castlevania and in Japan as Devil's Castle Dracula: Circle of the Moon) is a 2D action-adventure horror platformer developed by KCE Kobe and published by Konami for the Game Boy Advance (as a launch title) on June 8, 2001.Following up on the "Metroidvania" style of Castlevania: Symphony of the Night (where the game's platforming progression structure is based on free-roaming exploration), Castlevania: Circle of the Moon is the first Castlevania installment for the Game Boy Advance.The game takes place in an old Austrian castle in 1830, where Camilla, a female vampire, begins the ritual to ressurect her lord, Dracula. Sensing this, master vampire hunter Morris Baldwin rushes to the castle along with his son Hugh and disciple Nathan Graves. However, they arrived too late, and the risen Dracula imprisons Morris while casting Nathan and Hugh down into a graveyard underneath the castle. Players control Nathan, heir to the Hunter Whip (unknown if it's another name for the Vampire Killer whip), as he explores the large castle to rescue his master and defeat Dracula.Castlevania: Circle of the Moon features a unique magic ability system known as Dual Set-up System (DSS), where players find special Action Cards and Attribute Cards dropped by certain enemies and combine them to produce one of 100 temporary magic effects (such as improving the functionality of the Hunter's Whip and changing the player's stats).It is currently unclear whether the story is canonical to the main Castlevania chronology. At first, it was retroactively redacted by Koji Igarashi, one of the series' producers. However, the game was included in a timeline included with the pre-order bundle of the North America release of Castlevania: Portrait of Ruin.Gameplay:You play as Nathan with his Hunter's Whip, an item handed down through the generations of vampire hunters, as you must search the castle, finding all the enemies and bosses that, upon their defeats, will aid in your journey to get to Dracula and save your master. As you finish each boss, you get a certain Key Item/Ability, that will give Nathan a new ability to use to get to new areas of the castle. This is generally called the "Metroidvania" pattern.Abilities are:Double - allows character to jump a second time in mid-air. After defeating Cerberus.Dash Boots - allows the character to run faster. In Earth Demon room.Tackle - allows the character to take down brittle stone barricades. After defeating Necromancer.Kick Boots - allows character to jump off of walls for an extra boost. After defeating Iron Golem.Heavy Ring - allows the character to push heavy crates out of the way. After defeating Twin Dragons.Cleansing - allows character to walk through the tainted waters in the Underground Waterway. After defeating Death.Roc Wing - allows character to fly upwards a hefty distance. After defeating Camilla.The Last Key - allows character entry to Dracula's chamber. After defeating Hugh.This game features an interesting way of character enhancing, called DSS. It's a card system, with two sets of cards. Creature cards (mythical beasts really) and God cards (Roman Gods specifically). By pairing up a God card with a creature card, you can get various enhancements for Nathan, ranging from a flaming whip to summoning powerful creatures. Be warned that using the cards' abilities drains MP. Luckily, Save Points refill your MP. Getting the cards requires defeating the right enemies. Some cards are more common, and can be found from multiple enemies, whereas some are so hard to find, only 1 enemy will drop them. Note, however, that cards won't be a guaranteed drop from the enemy, and it may take several attempts at killing the foe before they drop the card.Cards Include:Salamander - power of fire.Serpent - power of ice.Mandragora - power of plants.Golem - power of earth.Cockatrice - power of stone.Manticore - power of poison.Griffin - power of wind.Thunderbird - power of electricity.Unicorn - power of healing.Black Dog - power of darkness.Mercury - potential of strength.Venus - potential of enchantment.Mars - potential of change.Jupiter - potential of defense.Diana - potential of creation.Apollo - potential of explosives.Saturn - potential of familiars.Neptune - potential of healing.Uranus - potential of summoning.Pluto - potential of special.Circle of the Moon also features "sub-weapons", little projectiles that can help damage difficult or hard-to-hit enemies. Sub-weapons are found in candles scattered all over the map, with the more powerful ones being harder to find. With the Shooter mode, Nathan has certain enhancements to his sub-weapons (including a Homing Dagger that follows the enemy for a guaranteed hit). They, however, cost the character Hearts. Hearts are easily regained by defeating some enemies who drop them, or taking out candles (which can be found everywhere). Hearts are the only stats that don't get replenished when you use a Save Point.Sub-Weapons include:Dagger - hurl a dagger forward at an enemy.Axe - throw an axe in an arc at enemies.Holy Water - creates a temporary fire on the ground, hurting all enemies who cross over it.Cross - throws a cross forward, it will then reach it point where it will travel in the opposite direction, whether or not the player is there to catch it.Clock - slows down all enemies in the room, while the character is still in normal motion.There is also a DSS combination with Pluto and Salamander that results in a Super Powered Sub-Weapon attack. Activated by a button sequence. Costs 4 MP per use.Dagger - fires rapidly like a machine gunAxe - fires in a spiral motion from center to off-screenHoly Water - it rains down on the enemiesCross - large crosses spiral from the bottom to the top of the screenClock - four clocks appear instead of one (longer effect)Another combination, Pluto and Serpent, fires off two sub-weapons, with the Hearts used being the same (except for the Cross and Clock)The last aspect of Castlevania: Circle of the Moon is it's various modes. Like how many games feature multiple difficulties, it features multiple "scenarios" for Nathan.Vampire Killer -starting character; basic, well-rounded stats.Magician - beat Vampire Killer mode and enter "Fireball" as the file name; high INT, all DSS cards, and high MP, but low STR and DEF.Fighter - beat Magician mode and enter "Gradius" as the file name; high STR and DEF, but no DSS cards.Shooter - beat Fighter mode and enter "Crossbow" as the file name; upgraded sub-weapons (stronger, cost less hearts), high starting amount of Hearts, relatively low stats, and at each level you will gain 10 hearts instead of two.Thief - beat Shooter mode and enter "Dagger" as the file name; extremely high Luck, otherwise very low stats.Final Battle:The final battle against Dracula is divided into 2 parts. The first is the humanoid form of Dracula. He merely attacks (all of which are easily avoidable) and teleports to a different location in the room. This portion of the battle is easy, however, the second portion is rather difficult. Dracula has obtained his full-powered-form, and now you must face it.In a much larger expansive room, Dracula's giant new form fights with several different attacks. One is his eye laser, which fires from his eye in his chest and creates an explosion. Another is his extremely deadly charge attack. This attack has Dracula start glowing, and he'll rush Nathan 3-5 times. The best way to avoid this is to repeatedly use the Roc Wing ability (he can't reach that high). The only way to hurt Dracula in this form is to deal damage to his eye in his chest. In the beginning, it isn't so hard, but halfway through, when he begins his charging attacks, he'll turn into a flying eyeball surrounded by bats. You must still hit the eyeball, though it is much harder to both avoid its attacks, the bats, and still get in that hit.In the end, Nathan defeats Dracula, causing his vast castle to crumble. Nathan, Hugh, and Morris all escape harm. Morris congratulates Nathan, and Hugh learns his lesson and becomes friends with Nathan once more. Peace is restored...for now.Cheat: 99990 attack power1) Equip items with a combined strength penalty that is equal to or greater than your strength. While the game will indicate that you have 1 strength, actually having 1 strength is not enough to activate this glitch. 2) Activate the DSS card combo of your choice. Doesn't matter what it is - any DSS card combo will activate the glitch. Once both conditions are met, attack power will instantly be raised to 99990 while both conditions hold true. While the game says that attack power is 9999, spinning the whip, which normally does 1/10th as much damage as striking with it, will also do 9999 damage when it hits, as if attack power was 99990 or higher. Unfortunately, actually using this glitch is basically impossible, due to the first requirement. The maximum attack power that you can have and still perform this trick is 210 (2 bear rings + dark armor), and, by the time you get these items, attack power will probably be far higher. Still, if you can pull it off, it's quite usefulCheat: 99990 attack power You must have the Black Dog and Jupiter cards. When you are poisoned or cursed activate the Black Dog and Jupiter DSS combo. As soon as you activate it, deactivate it. You will now be poison or curse free.Cheat: 99990 attack powerThis trick works best if you are over level 50, and have at least 10-15 Mind Highs or better. 1. Enter the Battle Arena with a Summon Combo equipped on your DSS button (Uranus + Cocatrice works best). 2. When you want to use your DSS cards, go to ''Items'' on the Pause Menu. Use a Mind High (or better, if you have it). 3. IMMEDIATLY after exiting the Pause Menu, hit the DSS button to prepare, and then quickly hit the Summon Combo off (down, forward, up, attack). You'll have used a Summon inside the Battle Arena! Cheat: 99990 attack powerWhen at the end of the Batlle Arena, where you get the Shinning Armor, Keep distance from the left wall and slide through the gap from a distance that you gon't fall out of it. You'll be at the entrance of the BA. Turn right and slide back in. The doors will be open. Keep killing until your health is low. You should gain a lot of exp. from the BA devil!Cheat: 99990 attack powerThis glitch makes Nathan go into [I]Negative[/I] magic. To do this: 1. Perform the trick to activate a DSS combo that is missing one or two cards (Activate a combo you already have, then while Nathan flashes during activation, goto the DSS screen and pick any combination you desire). 2. Make sure the incomplete combo you use works on use, NOT time (Like a summon, or whip). 3. Use the combo until you run out of magic. If you did it right, and you had few enough ''excess'' magic left after you used the combo and ran out of magic, you should go into negative MP. You know for sure you did this right when you can goto the status screen and see that your MP is replaced with non-numerical characters (Like parenthesis, and , 's). Also, what this does is make you have to wait like normal until you go into positive MP, before you can activate any DSS combo again.Cheat: 99990 attack powerNormally when you finish the Battle Arena, you can play through again by going to the front door. However, there is a way to play the arena [I]in reverse[/I]!&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; After you've beaten Battle Arena Devil, just stand halfway towards the exit in the "Shinning" Armor room. Slide out just enough to where you switch screens, but not far enough to exit the crawlspace. Slide back into the Arena and you'll find all the doors will be open again! Not only can you defeat the Devil again, but you can also run the entire Arena in reverse!&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; Note: Doing this glitch causes the Battle Arena doors to remain open, letting you skip rooms if you so desire. If you move forward however, the doors will close behind you again.Cheat: 99990 attack powerThis powerup works best on a summon, but you can also do it on whips, swords, etc... Summon for example thunderbird. When you fly in the air, pause and switch to Mars+Black Dog (gives the best strength). The summon will be way more powerful! Good for killing hard enemies (Mimic Candle, Lilith, etc...)Cheat: 99990 attack power1. Activate a shield (one using the Jupiter DSS card).2. Enter a save location, and save your game, not turning off your shield.3. Exit the save location, and your shield should still be going, with no consumption of your MP!Cheat: 99990 attack power1.) Select a DSS combo that you have. 2.) Activate it. 3.) As Nathan begins to glow, quickly pause. 4.) Now select any DSS combo, choosing cards from empty slots. 5.) Now instead of the DSS combo you first activated, you will get the new one you chose.Cheat: Magician, Fighter, Shooter and Thief ModesTo play the game in the various modes with different attributes follow the method listed belowCheat: Secret Item CrushTo use this special Item Crush, you must satisfy the following requirements: 1. Have 100 Hearts (NOT Heart Items) or more. 2. Do NOT have ANY subweapons at all! *IMPORTANT* 3*. Have the Pluto and Salamander DSS cards. *If you know how to perform the DSS trick, then disregard requirement #3.* Once these requirements are satisfied, activate the Item Crush DSS (Pluto + Salamander), then, perform the actions needed to use it (Down, Forward, Up). Nathan will then unleash a barrage of homing stars that cause considerable damage against enemies, depending on his Strength level, so to strengthen it, use Strength-increasing items (this can also be done once this Item Crush is activated).</plot>
	<releasedate>11/6/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>lfopPvUP_FI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3350</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/449471-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/castlevania-circle-of-the-moon</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/castlevania-circle-of-the-moon/3030-13197/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3350-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3350-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/pnj1wxz.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/HjvyQj1.jpg</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59658-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3350-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3350-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24680-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24681-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24682-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24683-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24684-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24685-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24686-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24687-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3350-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3350-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/kkcHoho.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3350.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Count Dracula has been resurrected and evil will reign supreme unless he is stopped. As Nathan Graves, you'll hunt down the count and use your whip and a variety of special items to destroy his minions. Battle your way through Dracula's castle and rid the world of evil once and for all!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>hj6RSfzA-OY</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d07912e8-299f-43d1-87cc-34ad1fc5e058.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/37da154c-5c5c-47f7-af39-ce32a5c0867d.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/42c53f78-a9c7-4d9c-bcca-efaaa9ae565e.png</boxart5>
	<boxart6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/12742094-af53-4710-9c15-4c062c049093.jpg</boxart6>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8cb4e1ff-e01a-4753-b477-082a8053e3eb.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4e99e7c0-9c3a-4586-b33d-bbbc2297685c.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3117e688-2522-49a6-80c7-a284e5ad2893.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>