<Game>
	<Name>Castlevania (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Simon Belmont, the game's protagonist, standing at the bloody gates of Dracula's CastleCastlevania (known in Japan as Devil's Castle Dracula) is a 2D action horror platformer developed and published by Konami for the Nintendo Entertainment System on May 1, 1987.Originally released for the Famicom Disk System in Japan on September 26, 1986, Castlevania is the first installment of the long-standing Castlevania franchise (it is often incorrectly assumed that the MSX2 version, named Vampire Killer, is the first due to it being the first Castlevania game released outside of Japan).The player takes control of heroic vampire hunter Simon Belmont, heir to the mighty Vampire Killer whip, who must travel through a dark, unholy castle in the year 1691 to search and destroy the evil Count Dracula. The story of the Belmont clan, the Vampire Killer whip, and the countless resurrections of Dracula had grown with subsequent additions to the franchise.Gameplay:Simon's primary weapon is his Vampire Killer whip, which starts as a short-ranged leather whip but extends to a morning star ball-and-chain by collecting two power-ups. Simon can only crack the whip straight ahead of him.By collecting hearts in single and quintuple increments, Simon can use one of five subweapons that he can find from candles or enemy drops. The Dagger is extremely weak, slow, and is more of a hindrance than a help. The Axe is thrown in an upward arc, useful for taking out enemies hiding or flying above Simon. The Holy Water is a short-range "firebomb" that can stop enemies in their tracks while doing constant damage. The Cross is a boomerang that covers the entire distance of the screen when thrown. Lastly, the Stopwatch stops all regular enemies in their tracks at a cost of five hearts. All the weapons but the Stopwatch can also be upgraded to a double and triple shot, allowing multiple uses of the weapon at the same time. This initial incarnation of Simon also set the standard for unagile Castlevania protagonists. He moves at a single slow-but-steady pace, cannot change direction mid-air after a jump, and suddenly wears cement blocks on his feet while on stairs. There is a slight delay during jumps between the button press and the on-screen action. The delay forces the player to be very deliberate while jumping, because it requires a particular timing. This sort of movement changed in Super Castlevania IV, where the player could alter the direction of the jump to the left or right while in the air. They'll never be lacking for something to whip, as enemies will continually respawn as long as they stay on the same screen.Ports, Re-Releases, and RecreationsThe IBM-PC port (running with CGA graphics)The original NES Castlevania had many ports and re-releases to various computer systems, game consoles, mobile devices, and arcade hardware. Shortly after the NES release, the game was adapted for use in Nintendo's PlayChoice-10 and Vs. arcade systems, with the latter including multiplayer (where players alternate after each life). The NES release was also ported to the Game Boy Advance by Nintendo on October 25, 2004 as part of the Classic NES Series, released on the PC in November 15, 2002 as a compilation of NES Castlevania and Contra games (dubbed Konami Collector's Series: Castlevania &amp; Contra ), and released on the Wii as a downloadable Wii Virtual Console title on April 30, 2007 for 500 Wii Points ($5).In the early 1990s, Castlevania was ported to the PC, the Commodore 64 (both by Unlimited Software) and the Commodore Amiga (by Novotrade). In February 5, 1993, the NES version was released in Japan (prior to that, it had only been released on the FDS), sacrificing the saving and name registration for a new "Easy" mode, which gives Simon more time, damage protection, lives, and knockback protection from being damaged. The game was ported to mobile phones three times, each with improved graphics (one in 2002, one in 2004, and one in 2005).Castlevania, along with having many ports and re-releases, has also had many recreations spanning a variety of game consoles. While they share the same story (as well as some content), they are considered completely different games due to their inclusion of a variety of new gameplay elements and content.Vampire Killer (released for the MSX2 for Japan, Europe, and Brazil shortly after the original FDS version)Haunted Castle (released for the Arcades on September 22, 1988)Super Castlevania IV (released for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System on December 1991)Castlevania Chronicles (originally released on the Sharp X68000 in Japan on 1993, subsequently released on the Sony PlayStation worldwide on October 8, 2001)Cheat: 99990 attack power1) Equip items with a combined strength penalty that is equal to or greater than your strength. While the game will indicate that you have 1 strength, actually having 1 strength is not enough to activate this glitch. 2) Activate the DSS card combo of your choice. Doesn't matter what it is - any DSS card combo will activate the glitch. Once both conditions are met, attack power will instantly be raised to 99990 while both conditions hold true. While the game says that attack power is 9999, spinning the whip, which normally does 1/10th as much damage as striking with it, will also do 9999 damage when it hits, as if attack power was 99990 or higher. Unfortunately, actually using this glitch is basically impossible, due to the first requirement. The maximum attack power that you can have and still perform this trick is 210 (2 bear rings + dark armor), and, by the time you get these items, attack power will probably be far higher. Still, if you can pull it off, it's quite usefulCheat: 99990 attack power You must have the Black Dog and Jupiter cards. When you are poisoned or cursed activate the Black Dog and Jupiter DSS combo. As soon as you activate it, deactivate it. You will now be poison or curse free.Cheat: 99990 attack powerThis trick works best if you are over level 50, and have at least 10-15 Mind Highs or better. 1. Enter the Battle Arena with a Summon Combo equipped on your DSS button (Uranus + Cocatrice works best). 2. When you want to use your DSS cards, go to ''Items'' on the Pause Menu. Use a Mind High (or better, if you have it). 3. IMMEDIATLY after exiting the Pause Menu, hit the DSS button to prepare, and then quickly hit the Summon Combo off (down, forward, up, attack). You'll have used a Summon inside the Battle Arena! Cheat: 99990 attack powerWhen at the end of the Batlle Arena, where you get the Shinning Armor, Keep distance from the left wall and slide through the gap from a distance that you gon't fall out of it. You'll be at the entrance of the BA. Turn right and slide back in. The doors will be open. Keep killing until your health is low. You should gain a lot of exp. from the BA devil!Cheat: 99990 attack powerThis glitch makes Nathan go into [I]Negative[/I] magic. To do this: 1. Perform the trick to activate a DSS combo that is missing one or two cards (Activate a combo you already have, then while Nathan flashes during activation, goto the DSS screen and pick any combination you desire). 2. Make sure the incomplete combo you use works on use, NOT time (Like a summon, or whip). 3. Use the combo until you run out of magic. If you did it right, and you had few enough ''excess'' magic left after you used the combo and ran out of magic, you should go into negative MP. You know for sure you did this right when you can goto the status screen and see that your MP is replaced with non-numerical characters (Like parenthesis, and , 's). Also, what this does is make you have to wait like normal until you go into positive MP, before you can activate any DSS combo again.Cheat: 99990 attack powerNormally when you finish the Battle Arena, you can play through again by going to the front door. However, there is a way to play the arena [I]in reverse[/I]!&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; After you've beaten Battle Arena Devil, just stand halfway towards the exit in the "Shinning" Armor room. Slide out just enough to where you switch screens, but not far enough to exit the crawlspace. Slide back into the Arena and you'll find all the doors will be open again! Not only can you defeat the Devil again, but you can also run the entire Arena in reverse!&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; Note: Doing this glitch causes the Battle Arena doors to remain open, letting you skip rooms if you so desire. If you move forward however, the doors will close behind you again.Cheat: 99990 attack powerThis powerup works best on a summon, but you can also do it on whips, swords, etc... Summon for example thunderbird. When you fly in the air, pause and switch to Mars+Black Dog (gives the best strength). The summon will be way more powerful! Good for killing hard enemies (Mimic Candle, Lilith, etc...)Cheat: 99990 attack power1. Activate a shield (one using the Jupiter DSS card).2. Enter a save location, and save your game, not turning off your shield.3. Exit the save location, and your shield should still be going, with no consumption of your MP!Cheat: 99990 attack power1.) Select a DSS combo that you have. 2.) Activate it. 3.) As Nathan begins to glow, quickly pause. 4.) Now select any DSS combo, choosing cards from empty slots. 5.) Now instead of the DSS combo you first activated, you will get the new one you chose.Cheat: Magician, Fighter, Shooter and Thief ModesTo play the game in the various modes with different attributes follow the method listed belowCheat: Secret Item CrushTo use this special Item Crush, you must satisfy the following requirements: 1. Have 100 Hearts (NOT Heart Items) or more. 2. Do NOT have ANY subweapons at all! *IMPORTANT* 3*. Have the Pluto and Salamander DSS cards. *If you know how to perform the DSS trick, then disregard requirement #3.* Once these requirements are satisfied, activate the Item Crush DSS (Pluto + Salamander), then, perform the actions needed to use it (Down, Forward, Up). Nathan will then unleash a barrage of homing stars that cause considerable damage against enemies, depending on his Strength level, so to strengthen it, use Strength-increasing items (this can also be done once this Item Crush is activated).</plot>
	<releasedate>26/10/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>lfopPvUP_FI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18984</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/449471-castlevania-circle-of-the-moon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/castlevania</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/castlevania/3030-6673/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2361205-nes_castlevania.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59660-castlevania-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59661-castlevania-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464186-castlevania-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4231/968429-29.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4231/968428-28.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4231/968427-27.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4231/968426-26.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4231/968425-25.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4231/968424-24.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4231/968423-23.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4231/968422-22.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4231/968421-21.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>If you think it's scary on the outside, wait'll you see the basement! You're in for the longest night of your life. Ghosts, goblins, demons, wolves, bats - creatures lurking around every corner. As you descend deeper and deeper, they get thicker and thicker. Better stick close to the cavern floor - it's your only chance of finding a weapon or two. You're gonna need 'em. Because when you finally meet the Count, you know he'll be going for the jugular. So keep your courage up and your stake sharp. And say your prayers!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2027040e-f0d5-4eba-a868-a25cc31108ef.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab51db23-38a9-49bb-b5b6-6878a7e1ae08.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>