<Game>
	<Name>Castlevania Double Pack (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Castlevania Doublepack is a compilation of the two previous Game Boy Advance Castlevania titles--Castevania: Harmony of Dissonance and Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow. The games are included in their complete form, giving players the ability to act as either Juste Belmont or Soma Cruz, depending on which story and game they wish to tackle. Both games feature a number of weapons and enemies as you make your way through the castle to combat Dracula in 2D combat.Cheat: Play as 8-Bit Simon and Maxim in Boss Rush Mode (HoD)After you've beaten the game and obtained Boss Rush Mode, input the Konami Code (up up down down left right left right B A) while the Konami logo is being shown. Enter Boss Rush mode and Simon will be automatically selected.To play as Maxim in Boss Rush mode, press and hold the L and R buttons down when in the Boss Rush menu, and hold them down until you enter the difficulty. You can now play as Maxim in Boss Rush.Cheat: Hard Mode (HoD)When selecting your name, make it "HARDGAME." This will enable you to play a harder version of the original game.Cheat: Hard Mode (HoD)To play the game using no spellbooks, enter ''NOMAGIC'' as your name when you start a new game.Cheat: Hard Mode (HoD)When starting a new game, type in NOSOUL as your name to use no souls in the game, and type in NOUSE to use no items. This makes the game much harder.Cheat: Hard Mode (HoD)After getting the good ending(beat chaos) enter the name Julius in a new game as your name and youll play as juliusCheat: AOS- Extended storyBefore you fight Graham, equip the Flame Demon, Succubus, and Giant Bat souls. After killing Graham, the story will continue.Cheat: AOS- Extended storyBeat the GameCheat: AOS- Extended storyTo obtain Boss Rush Mode in either game, simply beat them with a good ending or better.Cheat: AOS- Extended storyTo unlock sound mode in the games simply beat the game you want the sound mode for with the good ending.Cheat: When starting a new game, type in NOSOUL to use no souls in the game.  And type in NOUSE to use no items.Cheat: First do the trick for 100.1% map completion. Continue on with the story except when you get the [I]Undine[/I] soul do not go to the Top Floor area. Go back through the Inner Quarters and Dance Hall. Then go to the Floating Garden. Proceed to the room that connects with the Clock Tower. Go to the upper right corner of the room. Use the [I]Curly[/I] soul and you will be transported outside of the castle again. This time stand on the left side of the 2nd spike from the right. Jump and if you did it right you will be transported to The Arena and then the Top Floor and your map will be 100.2% completed.Cheat: Ok, first you need to do the 100.2% map glitch, have the [I]Giant Bat[/I] and [I]Curly[/I] souls, and have not gone to the Chaos Realm Enter the long verticle room connected to the frist save room of the Chapel. Stand on the platform that is just above the door leading out (not the stone on, you have to be under the stone one). Face right and press R to use the [I]Curly[/I] soul. When Soma turns a strange color pause the game and switch [I]Curly[/I] soul with the [I]Giant Bat[/I] soul. Unpause and hold right and change into the bat. You should end up in the ceiling of the Save Room. Fly just above the statue on the right side and change back into Soma. You should end up in the Underground Reservoir, in the middle of a wall. When you very close to the top of the room hold right and press R to change into the bat. Change back into Soma when you reach the gap in the ceiling of that room. If you did the whole thing right you will fly up through several rooms and end up in the Chaotic Realm. The room of the Chaotic Realm is a tower/observatory room with a space background, if your not halfway off the screen the glitch won't work and you have to try again. Eventually you will be able to move again and your map percentage will now be 100.3%!Cheat: This glitch will make Soma glow for as long as you want. It does nothing else (as far as I know, I could be wrong) but it does make him really easy to see. First of all, you need either the Manticore, Devil, or Curly spirits. Next, make your way to the corridor in the Dance Hall (the one that leads up to the top level of the Dance Hall). Drop down from said top level, make your way to the last door (in the background) without killing anything, face left, and press R to transform. Keep holding it until you're just over the hole in the floor, and when the game starts to change you back, let go of the R button and do a slide. Voila! The game thinks that you fell through while you were changing back, so it replaces Soma's regular image with the really bright one. He'll stay this way until you use Devil, Manticore, or Curly again.Cheat: Using a fast swinging weapon (like the Claimh Solias) will allow you to do a second swing. While jumping, use your swinging weapon. As you hit the ground, use it again and it will allow you to swing again instantly. It's not very much of use, but it is still fun to test out.Cheat: First beat the game with 100% map completed, and a [I]Curly[/I] soul, and start a new game +. Make your way to the chapel and head up the stairs in the room with all of the ghosts. make your way to the top left cornor of the room and stand under the platform that the Axe Armor was on. Next face to the right and back dash until your against the wall. Then use the [I] Curly [/I] soul and you will be warped outside of the castle. Drop down the left side until you land on a platform and jump off the screen to the left. You will be transported to the Study and your map will be 100.1% completed.Cheat: Complete the game to unlock the following:Cheat: If 100% of the souls are collected, additional dialogue appers in the game's ending. Soma and Mina talk about how the experience changed Soma.Cheat: Before fighting Graham, equip the Flame Demon, Succubus and Giant Bat souls. After you defeat him, You'll able to enter the black mist door and will fight two more bosses. Beat both to receive the best ending. Unlocks Sound Mode and Boss Rush Mode.  Before fighting Graham, equip the Flame Demon, Succubus and Giant Bat souls. After you defeat him, You'll able to enter the black mist door and will fight two more bosses. Beat the first one, but lose to the second, you should then get the good ending. Unlocks Boss Rush Mode.  Defeat Graham, but don't collect or equip the Flame demon, Succubus and Giant Bat souls. You'll get the bad ending. Lose to Chaos to get the worst ending. Cheat: Finish boss rush with the following times to unveil secret items. -Over 6 minutes- Potion -Between 5 and 6 minutes- Excalibur -Between 4 and 5 minutes- Positron Rifle -Under 4 minutes- ValmanwayCheat: Ok, before you get excited, there is one requirement to do this.  The Sherman Ring.  It gives you experience points as you walk.  This ring can be found in the dance hall (you must have some way to get up through holes in the ceiling such asgiant bat soul or super jump ability).  I'll leave finding that to you.  On to the trick.1.  Equip the Sherman Ring.2.  Find a safe spot with no monsters.&lt;br/&gt;3.  Pin down the duck button, and either the move left or move right directional button.&lt;br/&gt;4.  Voila.  You have fooled the game into thinking you are walking, when you are just sitting in one spot safe and sound.  Now go to sleep or something and let the experience roll in. Why do it this way?  Because if you just try to hold the run button down against a wall, you will not get experience points even though Soma is running.  Cheat: Go to the teleport room right next to the arena, then head left, go up as soon as possible(on your map it will be two blocks left of the teleport room).  After you go up, go left as soon as possible(it will be two blocks above where you just went up.Cheat: Now you will be three blocks left and two blocks up of the teleport room.  This hall contains two red minotaurs, a werejaguar, and a killer mantle.  Go back and forth across the hall until you get a killer mantle soul.  Equip it, it will kill red minotaurs in a single strike, and they give 1000 exp per kill. I can rack up over 6000 exp a minute doing this.Cheat: Once you get to the Floating Garden, you can use the Gorgons to reach the Arena instantly. First, go up the first elevator you see. Then, head up all the way until you see the Red Crow sitting on the staircase--there should be a Gorgon to the right of it. Stand on the very back of the Gorgon and have it walk towards the pillar. Once it hits the pillar and starts turning, run towards the pillar and, if you did it right, you should see Soma crouched in the wall and rapidly moving upwards. You should land in a room of The Arena right under a Dead Crusader.Cheat: Note: This glitch also works with any other Gorgon or Catoblepas if they run into a wall at some point and turn around.Cheat: After you've beaten the game and obtained Boss Rush Mode, input the Konami Code (up up down down left right left right B A) while the Konami logo is being shown. Enter Boss Rush mode and Simon will be automatically selected.Cheat: To play as Maxim in Boss Rush mode, press and hold the L and R buttons down when in the Boss Rush menu, and hold them down until you enter the difficulty. You can now play as Maxim in Boss Rush. Cheat: Just enter HARDGAME as your name, you will hear sound when you success.Cheat: To play the game using no spellbooks, enter ''NO MAGIC'' as your name when you start a new game. Cheat: After you beat the game, enter MAXIM as your name in a new game and you will start the game as him.Cheat: This glitch will let you, with proper timing, get to some ledges that are just out of your reach. First, get the Ice Fist (Ice book + Sacred Fist) magic, and then go to the ledge you want to get on. At the peak of your jump, activate the Ice Fist, and, if timed properly, it should get you on top. This can be used to get Dracula's ring and Logoth's ring early, and after you get the double jump, you can get the platinum tip early too.Cheat: To unlock the Boss Rush mode, where you play every single boss again, one after another, simply beat the game.Cheat: There are 2 options in the Secret Info menu in the game that you can unlock: Encyclopedia: A list of every monster you've defeated, along with stats on them.  Unlock by collecting the Monster Tome relic. Collectibles: A list of all the collectible items you picked up (used to decorate Juste's Room).  Unlock by simply picking up a collectible for the first time.Cheat: To unlock Sound Mode, where you can listen to all the music from the game- You must have all Dracula parts and you must wear Juste's and Maxim's ring when fighting Maxim in Castle B.  Afterwards, the final boss will show up.  Defeat him to get Sound Mode, which you can select at the main menu.Cheat: Whenever you defeat a boss (Either in the normal game or during Boss Rush) you can go for a Pose Bonus using Juste or Maxim. These bonuses don't actually do anything, they're simply there to see how well you can time a pose.Cheat: To get a Pose Bonus, grab the orb that appears after killing a boss while in the last frame of Juste or Maxim's attack (IE, when Juste's whip is fully extended, or Maxim's sword is completely out). If done successfully, you'll see a Pose Bonus message like 'GREAT!' appear over your character.Cheat: The higher in the air you are when you do this, the better your Pose Bonus.Cheat: Defeat the final boss in Castle B and wear the JB and MK bracelets. You will then fight the true boss and will recive the best ending. Unlocks Boss Rush Mode and Sound Mode. Defeat the final boss in Castle A. You will recive the ok ending. Unlocks Boss Rush Mode. Defeat the final boss in Castle B, but don't wear any of the bracelets. You will recive the bad ending. Unlocks Boss Rush Mode.  </plot>
	<releasedate>10/1/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3443</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/930975-castlevania-double-pack</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/castlevania-double-pack</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/castlevania-double-pack/3030-47975/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/VNkHaFz.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/57450-castlevania-double-pack-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/57451-castlevania-double-pack-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401932-castlevania-double-pack-game-boy-advance-screenshot-game-selection.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/6/c/gfs_71954_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/b/c/gfs_71954_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/0/c/gfs_71954_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/1/c/gfs_71954_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/a/c/gfs_71954_1_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/o08k19x.jpg</banner1>
</game>