<Game>
	<Name>Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (Europe) (En,Fr,Es,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>Step inside the magical world of Willy Wonka's famous chocolate factory. Based on the Warner Bros. film and the classic novel by Roald Dahl, Charlie and the Chocolate Factory lets you delve deep inside the factory to relive the classic story as Charlie Bucket. Find a golden ticket and, along with four other children, win a personal tour of Willy Wonka's factory as guided by the notorious and reclusive candy maker himself. Discover what happens after the other children, greed-driven and unrestrained, wreak havoc throughout the factory.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/926602.htmlCheat: Unlocks all levels and mini games.Go to the select game menu and press- left, right, L, R, START, SELECT. You should hear a noise. Highlight the following and press SELECT to unlock...</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Global Star Software</Developer>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>25881</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/926602-charlie-and-the-chocolate-factory</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/charlie-and-the-chocolate-factory/3030-853/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2285632-box_catcf.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/3/5/65935_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14097/547338-05.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14097/547337-06.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14097/547335-04.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14097/547334-03.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/14097/547333-02.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Developed by High Voltage Software and licensed by Warner Bros., Charlie and the Chocolate Factory puts players right into the world of the film. You'll find the factory rampaged by the other children, who are running amok with greed and impishness. Use your special candy powers and the assistance of the Oompa-Loompas to restore order to Willy Wonka's sugary establishment. Beyond this, Charlie will have to use a variety of candy to overcome obstacles and potential enemies. Everlasting Gobstoppers, for instance, are basically rocks that Charlie can throw around. The game features celebrity voice talent and the likeness of Johnny Depp as Wonka.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67a48159-9baa-425d-b881-c9a3df2af348.jpg</boxart3>
	<Publisher>Global Star</Publisher>
</game>