<Game>
	<Name>Chinmoku no Iseki - Estpolis Gaiden (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>This exciting new chapter in the Lufia saga follows the adventures of Eldin, Torma, and Rami, a group of friends and would-be hunters as they set out in search of treasure, only to discover that fate has much more in store for them! Will they be able to solve the mysteries of the ancient ruins and stop the power-hungry leader Ragule from resurrecting the ancient beast, or will Ragules ambitions be realized at the expense of mankind? Prepare for the Adventure of a Lifetime!Cheat: Infinite NectarGo to the blacksmith in Gruberik. Make sure you have the ingredients for a Nectar (and found the alchemist). Make a Nectar. The blacksmith will make the item like normal, but you won't lose the ingredients! You can get infinite Nectars at no cost.Cheat: Infinite NectarSacrifice kills the enemy and the user. However, there is a glitch. If you use Sacrifice on yourself, you heal 999 HPCheat: Easy Gold in OrdensOnce you reach the town of Ordens go to the item shop and buy as many Blue Teas as possible for 100 gold each. Then you can sell them back for 150 gold each. You can make between 50 and 4450 gold each time. </plot>
	<releasedate>6/5/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Taito Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>6.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>wdPfgEYTmfg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>11196</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589582-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11196-3.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11196-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/4/5/gfs_47255_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/9/5/gfs_47255_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/2/5/gfs_47255_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/3/5/gfs_47255_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/8/5/gfs_47255_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
</game>