<Game>
	<Name>Codename - Kids Next Door - Operation S.O.D.A. (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Codename: Kids Next Door: Operation S.O.D.A. is a platforming game developed by Vicarious Visions and published by Global Star Software for the Game Boy Advance platform.The StoryThe SCB have pass what is called the Soda Control Act which states that no children under the age of 13 are allowed to consume soda. The Kids Next Door have decided to fight against this act by bringing soda to children around the world.Gameplay:In Operation S.O.D.A each of the five main characters can be selected. Each of the characters has a different mission to complete with different settings and objectives. Once a characters mission has been completed, they will be checked off the list and a password will be given.Each operation is split into three smaller stages. Each of these stages are platforming or flying levels with items along the way and henchmen to avoid.Once all the starting operations are played through some of the Kids Next Door get captured and it is up to the others to rescue them in another series of operations.ItemsItemDescriptionBottle CapBottle CapsScattered throughout each mission are collectible bottle caps. If 50 of these bottle caps are collected the player earns an extra life.Rainbow MonkeyRainbow Monkey CheckpointsAt the mid point in a level there will be a rainbow monkey which will allow the player to restart at that location if a life is lost. These rainbow monkeys will only activate if the player touches them.Chocolate BarCandyThroughout the various stages in the game are different kinds of candy. These pieces of candy, such as a chocolate bar or chewing gum will refill some of the players health when collected.Password Monkey Password MonkeyThe password monkeys located in the stages will give the player a password to write down so that the game can be continued from that location.Extra Life Extra LifeIn each stage an item can be found which will give the player an extra life. It look like the floating head of whichever character is currently being played.Super Sour Candy Super Sour CandyThe super sour candy will give the player temporary invulnerability which will allow the player to walk through enemies without taking damage. Characters/MissionsCharacterMissionNumbah OneOperation B.I.R.T.H.D.A.YOperation B.I.R.T.H.D.A.Y stands for bring important rather thirst-halting delivery away yonder. In this mission Numbah One gets the Z.A.P.P.A.H weapon.Numbah One is informed by KND Global Command that a birthday party across town needs some orange soda. Numbah One must deliver the supplies to the party.Numbah TwoOperation C.A.M.P.O.U.TOperation C.A.M.P.O.U.T stands for cruising agent must put out unquenchable thirst. In this mission Numbah Two gets the G.L.O.P weapon.A group of children are having a camp-out and need some root beer. Numbah Two uses his jet pack and G.L.O.P gun to defeat the henchmen along the way to deliver the root beer.Numbah ThreeOperation P.I.C.N.I.COperation P.I.C.N.I.C stands for pop is clearly needed in countryside. In this mission Numbah Three gets the T.H.U.M.P.E.R weapon.Some kids are having a picnic but seem to be missing the lemon lime soda. Numbah Three is tasked with delivering the lemon lime soda to the picnic.Numbah FourOperation S.K.A.T.E.R.SOperation stand for skateboarding kids are totally excellently requiring soda. In this mission Numbah Four gets the S.L.U.G.L.O.V.E weapon.Numbah Four gets a call from a group of skateboarders who are requesting that he bring them some grape soda.Numbah FiveOperation S.L.U.M.B.U.HOperation stands for soda-lugging undercover mission brings unbelievable heroics. In this mission Numbah Five gets the S.N.E.E.D.L.E.S weapon.A slumber party is severely lacking in double-caffeinated cola. Numbah Five needs to deliver it to them so that they can stay up late and tell ghost stories.Cheat: PasswordsThese are the passwords for the levels, input them in the password menu in the main screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Global Star Software</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3356</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/924940-codename-kids-next-door-operation-soda</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/codename-kids-next-door-operation-s-o-d-a/3030-44077/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3356-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3356-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/0/2/gfs_60555_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/d/2/gfs_60555_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/6/2/gfs_60555_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/7/2/gfs_60555_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/c/2/gfs_60555_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3356-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3356.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>With the unanimous passing of the Soda Control Act by the Completely Unbiased We Don't Like Kids Adult Senate, the drinking age of soda has been raised to 13 years and older. Now, you can join the Kids Next Door as they fight for children's soda-drinking rights. Based on the animated show on Cartoon Network, this game lets you play as all five Kids Next Door operatives, each of whom has unique abilities. As you embark on this new adventure, you can use ordinary junk to create weapons and vehicles for your party.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7bc88009-c6c9-469c-b722-54bab90f8d34.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b5d154ad-aaa9-4bac-bc22-d083170d3d3c.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6560dc70-5011-434c-ba99-c3cdbfd503d8.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Globar Star</Publisher>
</game>