<Game>
	<Name>Crash Bandicoot Bakusou Nitro Cart (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Crash hits the track in his fastest adventure yet--Crash Nitro Kart.Kidnapped by the ruthless Emperor Velo and forced to race in his galactic coliseum, Crash must race his way to victory in order to save the Earth from destruction--but it won't be easy, as he must compete against foes both old and new before a final showdown with Velo himself.Crash Nitro Kart mixes 18 rollercoaster raceways, devastating weapons, a variety modes and maps, challenging arenas, and a cast of unique characters into a game that showcases kart-racing at its best.Cheat: GameCube linkTo alternately unlock the following, connect CNK for GBA to CNK for GameCube via the link cable.  Choose the respective link options on each game to successfully unlock these cheats and characters.Cheat: GameCube linkHold down L or R when starting your gba to access the mini game Crash Party USACheat: GameCube linkTo play as the bosses of the game you must beat them at their domainsCheat: GameCube linkTo unlock cheats in the option menu , simply do the following tasks:Cheat: GameCube linkTo Unlock them you must Cheat: Unlock Fake CrashIn Arcade or Time Trial mode, go to the level Out of Time. Head through the race until you get to the bottom right hand corner of the map. Stick to your left and you will come across a break in the barrier where there is a flower instead of a rock. Run over the flower and you will find yourself in the middle of the desert. Turn right and drive towards the starting part of the race, its a red line on the map. Within the u-shaped area that you are driving in, you will find a big patch of light sand. There is a small one and a big one, Fake Crash is standing in the middle of the big one. He will give you a little speech and be unlocked in Arcade and Time Trial modes.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/11/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Vicarious Visions</Developer>
	<rating>7.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3363</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/915605-crash-nitro-kart</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3363-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3363-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/e/d/gfs_52017_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/3/d/gfs_52017_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/8/d/gfs_52017_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/9/d/gfs_52017_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/7/0/gfs_52017_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3363-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3363.png</clearlogo1>
</game>