<Game>
	<Name>Crash Nitro Kart (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Sequel to Crash Team Racing on the original PlayStation, Crash Nitro Kart was released on all major console at the time including Xbox, PlayStation 2, Gamecube, Gameboy Advance, and N-Gage. The series continues on the iPhone.Story:Crash Bandicoot, Crunch Bandicoot, Coco Bandicoot, and Aku Aku are once again chilling at home. Crash sleeps lazily as Crunch and Aku Aku discuss the latest diets, and Coco works on Crash's ride. A bright light suddenly shines down on their home. Seconds later it is raised into the sky and disappears. Their mortal enemies Dr. Neo Cortex, Dr. N. Gin, Tiny, and Dingodile are working in their own lair, planning on how to take Crash out, when the same beam of light shines into their castle. Both groups of characters are transported to a galaxy far away ruled by the evil Emperor Velo XXVII. He demands they race for their freedom and if they don't comply he will destroy planet earth. Completing the game with different teams characters gets you access to different endings.Multiple Endings: Team CrashTeam Crash walks into Emperor Velo's Colosseum as he's fuming over his loss. Fuming too hard as a matter of fact when he suddenly explodes. Its a Wizard of Oz moment as its revealed that he is only a few feet tall alien that was wearing a huge, frightening robotic suit that wasn't strong enough to withstand its controller's anger. As the little alien crawls out of the wreckage, Crash and friends walk over and pick up the scepter that Velo carried. Crash dreams of turning Velo's planet, that happens to be shaped like Velo's face, into a stunning image of his own mug. When Crash snaps back he instead hands the scepter back to Velo and Crash's friends ask to be taken home. We then find Crash and team relaxing on the beach, soaking up the sun.Team CortexTeam Cortex walks into Emperor Velo's Colosseum as he's fuming over his loss. Fuming too hard as a matter of fact when he suddenly explodes. Its a Wizard of Oz moment as its revealed that he is only a few feet tall alien that was wearing a huge, frightening, robotic suit that wasn't strong enough to withstand its controller's anger. As the little alien crawls out of the wreckage, Cortex walks up to the wreckage and pulls out the scepter that was used by Velo. He laughs menacling feeling the power in his hands. The real Velo suddenly jumps out of the robotic wreckage straight at Cortex, knocking him over, and trying to yank the scepter from his hands. Tiny plucks the wimpy emperor off of Cortex then tries to reach for the scepter. Cortex denies him as he strains to lift the scepter above his head and says "On to earth". The end suddenly falls aff the scepter and they are warped to strange aztec looking ruins in the middle of a jungle. Dr. N. Gin, being happy to be back on earth, starts kissing the ground. Cortex looks into the sky and seeing multiple moons notices something... their not on earth. Natives appear walking menacing out from the woods. As this happens Tiny picks up the scepter, puts the end back on, and raises it up. The natives stop and bow down to Tiny, their new ruler. We're left with Cortex yelling "TINY!!! You buffoon!"Playable CharactersCrash BandicootCoco BandicootCrunch BandicootDr. Neo CortexN. GinTiny TigerN. TropyPuraDingodilePolarN. TranceNitrous OxideZemZamVeloFake CrashSpyro the Dragon (GBA version only)Cheat: GameCube linkTo alternately unlock the following, connect CNK for GBA to CNK for GameCube via the link cable.  Choose the respective link options on each game to successfully unlock these cheats and characters.Cheat: GameCube linkHold down L or R when starting your gba to access the mini game Crash Party USACheat: GameCube linkTo play as the bosses of the game you must beat them at their domainsCheat: GameCube linkTo unlock cheats in the option menu , simply do the following tasks:Cheat: GameCube linkTo Unlock them you must Cheat: Unlock Fake CrashIn Arcade or Time Trial mode, go to the level Out of Time. Head through the race until you get to the bottom right hand corner of the map. Stick to your left and you will come across a break in the barrier where there is a flower instead of a rock. Run over the flower and you will find yourself in the middle of the desert. Turn right and drive towards the starting part of the race, its a red line on the map. Within the u-shaped area that you are driving in, you will find a big patch of light sand. There is a small one and a big one, Fake Crash is standing in the middle of the big one. He will give you a little speech and be unlocked in Arcade and Time Trial modes.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/11/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Vivendi Universal Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3363</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/915605-crash-nitro-kart</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/crash-nitro-kart</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/crash-nitro-kart/3030-2278/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1881066-box_crashnk.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/IwmaH9P.png</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116298-crash-nitro-kart-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116295-crash-nitro-kart-game-boy-advance-screenshot-browsing-in-the.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116296-crash-nitro-kart-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-adventure.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116308-crash-nitro-kart-game-boy-advance-screenshot-each-team-has.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116297-crash-nitro-kart-game-boy-advance-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116309-crash-nitro-kart-game-boy-advance-screenshot-depending-of.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116374-crash-nitro-kart-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-race-will.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116369-crash-nitro-kart-game-boy-advance-screenshot-when-the-victim.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116375-crash-nitro-kart-game-boy-advance-screenshot-race-results.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116371-crash-nitro-kart-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-podium-shows.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/C6wo6Xk.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3363.png</clearlogo1>
</game>