<Game>
	<Name>Crash Superpack (USA)</Name>
	<plot>A compilation featuring both Crash Bandicoot 2: N-Tranced and Crash Nitro Kart in a single cartridge.Cheat: You have to beat N-Tranced and finish the game to unlock the extra level. Collect all blue, red, and green gems (there are 4 of each of them) which are scattered (and well hidden) all over the stages. They will open up new levels. Beat all the extra levels and N. Tropy to get the real ending.Cheat: To alternately unlock the following, connect CNK for GBA to CNK for GameCube via the link cable.  Choose the respective link options on each game to successfully unlock these cheats and characters.Cheat: Hold down L or R when starting your gba to access the mini game Crash Party USACheat: To play as the bosses of the game you must beat them at their domainsCheat: To unlock cheats in the option menu , simply do the following tasks:Cheat: To Unlock them you must Cheat: In Arcade or Time Trial mode, go to the level Out of Time. Head through the race until you get to the bottom right hand corner of the map. Stick to your left and you will come across a break in the barrier where there is a flower instead of a rock. Run over the flower and you will find yourself in the middle of the desert. Turn right and drive towards the starting part of the race, its a red line on the map. Within the u-shaped area that you are driving in, you will find a big patch of light sand. There is a small one and a big one, Fake Crash is standing in the middle of the big one. He will give you a little speech and be unlocked in Arcade and Time Trial modes.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/10/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Sierra Entertainment, Inc., Universal Interactive Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>25885</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/954987-crash-superpack-crash-bandicoot-2-crash-nitro-kart</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/crash-superpack</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/crash-superpack/3030-19795/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/1765901-954987_115134_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188488-crash-superpack-game-boy-advance-screenshot-game-selection.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188489-crash-superpack-game-boy-advance-screenshot-game-selection.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/1765898-gfs_115134_2_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/1765897-gfs_115134_2_2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/1/0/gfs_115134_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/c/0/gfs_115134_1_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/7/0/gfs_115134_1_3.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/6/0/gfs_115134_1_4.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/d/0/gfs_115134_1_5.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Notes>The Crash Super Pack brings together two of the best kart racing games available for your GBA -- both of which happen to have Crash Bandicoot, one of the wildest characters in gaming! With Crash Nitro Kart you'll race against Cortex and his minions in hopped-up kart racing action. In Crash: N-Hanced you'll reach incredible speeds and face the wildest obstacles on the fastest tracks.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ba0dee8e-8e8b-4f05-9911-c68914955f3b.jpg</boxart2>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Vivendi Universal Games Sierra Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>