<Game>
	<Name>Crazy Frog Racer (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>This racing game is based on the Crazy Frog license, a character used in the marketing of a ring tone, originally designed by Erik Wernquist. The GBA version was licensed separately, and only the characters remind of the Crazy Frog world. The typical music and soundbites are not present.Only singleplayer is available, and no story at all. The main game modes are Grand Prix, two modes based on checkpoints (alone or against opponents), and Last Man Standing where the last one drops after each lap. Grand Prix consists of three classes based on different speed, with three cups each, and and extra cup. Controls allow for speeding up, braking, using items to hinder your opponents (mines, nails, boxing gloves...), and there is a button to drift through the corners. Record times can be saved on the Battery Backed RAM.Cheat: Extra TracksTo unlock the extra tracks in the Checkpoint Rallye, Checkpoint Madness, and Last Man Standing modes, win the Silver and Gold cups.</plot>
	<releasedate>5/12/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>dtp entertainment AG</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>sAt9T_k6BsI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>29263</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/930690-crazy-frog-racer</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/crazy-frog-racer_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/crazy-frog-racer/3030-5236/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/29263-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/173902-crazy-frog-racer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/173904-crazy-frog-racer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu-includes.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/173905-crazy-frog-racer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose-from-crazy.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/173886-crazy-frog-racer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-the-class.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/173887-crazy-frog-racer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-game-is-shown.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/173888-crazy-frog-racer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-racing-against.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/173889-crazy-frog-racer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-finished.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/173890-crazy-frog-racer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-after-each-race.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/173891-crazy-frog-racer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-get-ready.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/173892-crazy-frog-racer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-it-s-very-easy.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Based on the ludicrously popular animated short and cellphone annoyance, this videogame features the frog-like critter that goes something like, "A'ding ding ding ding ding d-d-ding-ding ding bing BPHACH! B'omm bdom bom d'dom dom bom d'dom bay bom b'dom bom bom b'b'bom bom booooooohm boohm bom, d'dom bomb ahem bom b'dom bom bom b'dom b'dom d'dhom-d'dhom-d'dhom-b'd'd'd'd'd brrhhhh'd'd'd'd'dd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd bhrrem'd'd'd'd'd'd'dd'd'd'd bhrim'd'd'd'd'd'd'dd'd'd bhran'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'dd'd'd'd bhram'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd'd bom-bom-bom-bom bom Bom Booohm BOOOOHM BOOOOOOOHHHHHHHHM WHEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE!!!!!!!" Crazy Frog Racer is a high-speed, high-octane wacky racer. Players can either choose to play as 'The Annoying Thing' and D'Ding Ding their way to victory or play as one of eight other characters on 12 racetracks in single and multiplayer racing.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>sAt9T_k6BsI</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e92cb790-599c-4256-b83a-1dfbb285512f.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>