<Game>
	<Name>Crushed Baseball (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Crushed Baseball 2004 will offer completely original fully-interactive ballparks, where a key interactive feature will reward the player with additional Mojo abilities if they perform a certain task. For example, in a stadium with a stained glass window in the centerfield wall, if a player hits a ball that smashes through the window, they will be rewarded with additional Mojo abilities. In the Karate Dojo stadium, decorated in the traditional Japanese style, players can hit the gong to gain more Mojo abilities.   The game offers players the ability to set the time of day, weather effects and type of turf they play on. Players can choose to play a night game in the rain on a dirt surface, a day game in the wind on AstroTurf or real grass and more. In addition, Crushed Baseball 2004 will be the first baseball game to offer five fully playable female players and 10 original team mascots including a ram, an eagle and a bear.</plot>
	<releasedate>31/8/2004</releasedate>
	<Developer>Summitsoft Entertainment</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>25886</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/562423-crushed-baseball</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/crushed-baseball</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/crushed-baseball/3030-19446/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/25886-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/3/6/3/19363_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/169217-crushed-baseball-game-boy-advance-screenshot-1st-inning.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/169218-crushed-baseball-game-boy-advance-screenshot-hit.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/169219-crushed-baseball-game-boy-advance-screenshot-batter-up.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/169220-crushed-baseball-game-boy-advance-screenshot-home-run.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/169221-crushed-baseball-game-boy-advance-screenshot-league.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/169222-crushed-baseball-game-boy-advance-screenshot-2nd-playing-field.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/169223-crushed-baseball-game-boy-advance-screenshot-right-field.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/169224-crushed-baseball-game-boy-advance-screenshot-strike.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/169225-crushed-baseball-game-boy-advance-screenshot-swing.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/169226-crushed-baseball-game-boy-advance-screenshot-1st-playing-field.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>With its unique comic-book inspired art style, Crushed Baseball 2004 will offer fast-paced arcade gameplay that will appeal to both sports and non-sports gaming fans. With its over-the-top style, players will be able to power-up characters and give them superhuman abilities and special powers called "Mojo" abilities. For example, a pitcher might throw a pitch that acts as a buzz-saw and slices through the hitter's bat; a batter may hit a ground ball that lodges itself in the field so it can't be picked up, and a fielder might use their suction glove ability to suction the ball into their glove to record an out.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/56bb19db-d916-4bbd-a3d3-3e9261a82ac3.jpg</boxart3>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Publisher>Summitsoft</Publisher>
</game>