<Game>
	<Name>Curious George (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Sv,Da)</Name>
	<plot>When a curious monkey with a habit of accidentally causing mischief encounters a man dressed in yellow exploring the jungle, he follows him and stows away on his ship.  Now, the monkey, George, is stuck in the city and needs to find his way back home!  Help George find Ted, the Man in the Yellow Hat.Curious George is a platform game based on the movie of the same name.  In it, you play as the monkey, George, as he jumps, climbs and swings his way through the jungle, a ship, a city and more.  Throughout each level are fireflies, scattered to lead you in the right direction.  For every 50 George collects, he earns an extra life.  Due to his inquisitive nature, George likes to touch objects.  By pressing "R", George will interact with any nearby object with an exclamation mark next to it - and usually cause it to break.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Hometek Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>25887</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/930402-curious-george</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/curious-george</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/curious-george/3030-24914/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/25887-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/171824-curious-george-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/171825-curious-george-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401646-curious-george-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401647-curious-george-game-boy-advance-screenshot-our-story-begins.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401648-curious-george-game-boy-advance-screenshot-george-can-cling.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401649-curious-george-game-boy-advance-screenshot-grab-50-fireflies.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401650-curious-george-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-yellow-hat.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401651-curious-george-game-boy-advance-screenshot-like-any-monkey.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401652-curious-george-game-boy-advance-screenshot-george-climbs-through.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401653-curious-george-game-boy-advance-screenshot-george-heads-give.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401654-curious-george-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-world-map-finish.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/401655-curious-george-game-boy-advance-screenshot-george-mistakes.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Meet and greet your favorite movie characters in this adventure game based on the Universal Pictures and Imagine Entertainment animated feature film, Curious George. When the Man with the Yellow Hat travels to Africa in search of a lost artifact, he returns with some unexpected cargo -- a curious little primate named George. Guide George as he runs, jumps, climbs and swings his way through a variety of adventure-packed levels from the jungle to the Big City, where his spunky and fun-loving nature endears him to new friends and lands him in a series of mis-adventures. Make monkey business as you help George and his friends discover the one item special enough to save the museum from the bulldozer. Loads of bonus content and challenging mini-games keep players busy long after the main story is done.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/69b8cd05-e890-441a-b57d-421a224b6278.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a9348012-0657-4b35-91df-1da3084dbc5c.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>