<Game>
	<Name>Dark Arena (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>You are the leader of the special operations, and it is up to you to find your way out of a very sticky situation - a genetics lab overrun by monsters of every shape and size. Using your advance suit and weapons, you must shoot your way through the lab, destroying the evil creations and saving the lab, and the rest of the world, from total destruction.This 1st person shooter combines the many well known elements of previous games in the genre with an all out blast fest. A 4 player multiplayer deathmatch option is also on offer.Cheat: Version NumberAt the Press Start screen, hold L or R as you press Start. The version number of your cartridge will be displayed in the lower-right corner.Cheat: PasswordsEasy Mode Passwords: CRSDRPLS - Level 2 TKMWTHYB - Level 3 TTLLSFRT - Level 4 STCRSTRD - Level 5 NTLVMLNW - Level 6 NTTRDTNY - Level 7 RQSTMWTN - Level 8 GTSTNDBY - Level 9 YRSDTFGH - Level 10 TWTHYVRS - Level 11 THYRCLLN - Level 12 GHVTBTHR - Level 13 HLYLNDHS - Level 14 TBFRFGHT - Level 15 GDFGHTBL - View End Credits Medium Mode Passwords: VWHTSRGH - Level 2 TCRSDRLR - Level 3 DFRLMWTH - Level 4 LLYRMGHT - Level 5 WRMRCHNG - Level 6 TLNDFRFR - Level 7 MHMNNCNS - Level 8 YWHLLRTR - Level 9 NFRCHRSN - Level 10 DMSSKWLL - Level 11 TKRRVNGN - Level 12 PGNFRMTF - Level 13 STWCHRST - Level 14 NSRCMNGW - Level 15 THSWRDSH - View End Credits Hard Mode Passwords: LDNHGHNT - Level 2 DBYFTHND - Level 3 CSSRCNHT - Level 4 HNSWLLSN - Level 5 TSTRSTLR - Level 6 STNDRDSW - Level 7 LLRSCRSS - Level 8 LNDTBTTL - Level 9 SRCNHRDS - Level 10 WFLLWRWR - Level 11 RRKNGNWR - Level 12 DNTFGHTW - Level 13 CRRYSGNF - Level 14 CRSSWRLR - Level 15 DSFNGLND - View End Credits Special Passwords: KNGHTSFR - All Keys LMSPLLNG - All Maps THRBLDNS - All Weapons NDCRSDRT - Infinite Ammo HLGNDSBR - Infinite Health NFTRWLLH - Level Skip (Go to Map Screen, and push Select to skip the current level) NRYRDDS - Cheat Mode (Disables Special Passwords) CRSDR - Sound FX Test (In Game Options menu, turn Sound FX OFF, then back ON to hear a random sound) S X N - God Mode (Infinite Health, All Weapons, All Keys, Infinie Ammo, All Maps, And Level Skip) Cheat Mode Passwords (Must enter Cheat Mode to use these): KEYS - All Keys MAPS - All Maps WEAPONS - All Weapons AMMO - Infinite Ammo HEALTH - Infinite Health SKIP - Level Skip (Go to Map Screen, and push Select to skip the current level) PWORD - Disable Cheat Mode (Enables Special Passwords) SFX TEST - Sound FX Test (In Game Options menu, turn Sound FX OFF, then back ON to hear a random sound) ALL - God Mode (Infinite Health, All Weapons, All Keys, Infinie Ammo, All Maps, And Level Skip) Level Select Passwords (Must enter Cheat Mode to use these): A - Level 2, Easy Mode B - Level 3, Easy Mode C - Level 4, Easy Mode D - Level 5, Easy Mode E - Level 6, Easy Mode F - Level 7, Easy Mode G - Level 8, Easy Mode H - Level 9, Easy Mode I - Level 10, Easy Mode J - Level 11, Easy Mode K - Level 12, Easy Mode L - Level 13, Easy Mode M - Level 14, Easy Mode N - Level 15, Easy Mode O - View End Credits, Easy Mode AA - Level 2, Medium Mode BB - Level 3, Medium Mode CC - Level 4, Medium Mode DD - Level 5, Medium Mode EE - Level 6, Medium Mode FF - Level 7, Medium Mode GG - Level 8, Medium Mode HH - Level 9, Medium Mode II - Level 10, Medium Mode JJ - Level 11, Medium Mode KK - Level 12, Medium Mode LL - Level 13, Medium Mode MM - Level 14, Medium Mode NN - Level 15, Medium Mode OO - View End Credits, Medium Mode AAA - Level 2, Hard Mode BBB - Level 3, Hard Mode CCC - Level 4, Hard Mode DDD - Level 5, Hard Mode EEE - Level 6, Hard Mode FFF - Level 7, Hard Mode GGG - Level 8, Hard Mode HHH - Level 9, Hard Mode III - Level 10, Hard Mode JJJ - Level 11, Hard Mode KKK - Level 12, Hard Mode LLL - Level 13, Hard Mode MMM - Level 14, Hard Mode NNN - Level 15, Hard Mode OOO - View End Credits, Hard Mode</plot>
	<releasedate>19/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Majesco Sales, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>UOPhvImVywo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3373</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/473427-dark-arena</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/dark-arena</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dark-arena/3030-14972/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3373-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3373-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/103563-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177784-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177785-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-screenshot-using-the-hand-laser.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177787-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-screenshot-i-got-the-bolt-gun.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177789-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-pain-hybrid-shoots.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177791-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-screenshot-long-distance-shoot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177792-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-screenshot-map-view.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177793-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-combat-rifle-in.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177794-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-screenshot-luckily-those-stripey.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177795-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-screenshot-despite-its-name-dark.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177796-dark-arena-game-boy-advance-screenshot-some-cool-architecture.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3373-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3373.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dark Arena is 20 levels of terrifying, non-stop action. You play the role of Angela Bradshaw, a special forces agent who is trapped in the bowels of a deadly labyrinth of maze-like passages crawling with bloodthirsty, genetic horrors. Armed with a deadly array of futuristic weaponry and your wits, you must make your escape.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/69182dbe-b80f-4bee-805b-d9840da8e076.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/affb5fe8-ffbb-4d03-beb0-36662884cfeb.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/26ee2548-f850-49f7-9052-c0821efb145b.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Majesco</Publisher>
</game>