<Game>
	<Name>Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX 2 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:This game is basically Tony Hawk on bikes, there are various levels that you can free roam around in, as well as other famous BMX riders that give you various missions. Doing this missions you will unlock different bikes and other goodies.ProquestA player chooses who they want to play as, and on each map they get 3 minute runs every time they start to break the records and accomplish goals like grinding a certain distance, or doing a certain amount of jumps or tricks.Free rideYou chose a rider and just ride around, you can do anything, no time limit, but nothing counts for your career.Park EditorUse this to create your own unique parks, you can set it up for crazy long grinds and tricks, or just weird stuff and try to make your guy crash.Multiplayer2 players compete in various ways, such as HORSE. One person does a trick ,then the other person has to do one that is the same or of equal or better points value. Also there is a crashing game, when you do a crash you get points, person with the most points win. There is also 2 player free ride mode as well.RidersJohn "Luc-E" EnglebertJoey GarciaKenan HarkinMike LairdTodd LyonsTroy McMurrayColin MackayDave MirraTim MirraRick MoliternoRyan NyquistLeigh RamsdellZach ShawScott WirchAmish Boy (Unlockable)Mike Diaz (Unlockable)Slim Jim Guy (Unlockable)Levels:Slim JimWoodward CampTrainyardsSwamp TrailsCommercial DistrictGalloon Water ParkHWY 47 CloverleafDevil's PeakAirport GarageVenice*Greenville**Gamecube and Xbox versions only.Soundtrack:Rage Against the Machine - Wake UpOzzy Osbourne - ParanoidSublime - Doin TimeSum 41 - Makes no DifferenceThe Cult - She Sells SanctuaryA Tribe Called Quest - Buggin OutMethods of Mayhem - HypocriticalGodsmack - Keep AwayFenix TX - All My FaultGang Starr - Moment of TruthVersion DifferencesThe Gamecube and Xbox releases have higher resolution textures than the Playstation 2 version. They also contain 2 additional levels: Venice and Greenville.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3374</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/541079-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2/3030-10174/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2133345-box_dmfsbmx2.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3374-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/174175-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31469-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-screenshot-opening-video.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31467-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31465-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-screenshot-double-backflip.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31466-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-screenshot-greenville-nc.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31468-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-screenshot-tailwhip-over.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31470-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-screenshot-the-trainyards.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31471-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-screenshot-woodward-camp.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/31464-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-screenshot-watch-out-for.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83660-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-screenshot-rider-selection.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/83661-dave-mirra-freestyle-bmx-2-gamecube-screenshot-180-turndown.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ho7o2Nd.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3374.png</clearlogo1>
</game>