<Game>
	<Name>Donkey Kong Country (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The title screenThe first in the Donkey Kong Country series of video games, Donkey Kong Country is a classic side-scrolling platformer featuring Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong. Among the first games to fully utilize pre-rendered 3D graphics for its sprite-based system, this game, and its sequels, was notable both for its particular brand of action platforming and its impressive, lush visuals. Donkey kong Country was developed by Rare and published by Nintendo.A version called "Donkey Kong Country: Competition Cartridge" was released within the same year as the original game's release. This was a very limited release for certain video game competitions during the 1990s such as the Blockbuster Video World Championship II in 1995.This version of the game is quite different from the original as it is only playable for five minutes. Within that time limit, the player must gain as many points as possible. There is no title screen, save files, or world map in the game; the player instantly starts on the first level when the cartridge is inserted into the console. When one level is completed, the next level starts. The following levels that the game goes through is Jungle Hijinx, Reptile Rumble, Ropey Rampage, Coral Capers, Winky's Walkway, Bouncy Bonanza, Orang-Utan Gang, and Snow Barrel Blast. At the end of the 5 minutes, the game freezes at its current state in order to allow time for the referee of the competition to take note of the points.A screenshot from the Game Boy Color versionA Game Boy Color port was released on November 4th, 2000. This is essentially the same game, except with some mini-games thrown in. Naturally, the graphics aren't as impressive as the SNES version and the game would begin to slow down to a crawl when there were more than a few sprites on screen at once, but was still considered a technological marvel being able to port a SNES game to Game Boy Color, with the core concepts being intact. There are a few other differences in the game, for example, only one character is onscreen at a time. Also, when an animal character is gained, Diddy or Donkey Kong will leave and the player gets to play as the animal as opposed to Diddy or Donkey Kong. The Game Boy Color version's music was mostly ported over from the eight bit soundtrack of Donkey Kong Land, although certain tracks had been switched around, such as DKL's water level music now being used for an ice cavern level.The game featured an additional cave level in the Chimp Caverns world, Necky Nutmare. It also featured a scrapbook which the player could fill up by finding extra hidden items in the adventure before printing out the pages, as well as a few minigames: a fishing game with Funky Kong, a barrel- Kremling coconut-shooter with Cranky, as well as some small bonus games with Candy Kong since her save room was unnecessary now that the game autosaved after each level was completed.Released on June 9th, 2003, Donkey Kong Country on the Game Boy Advance is a very faithful remake of the original. In this game the same various extras of the Game Boy Color version were added; the mini-games and scrapbook where the player had to find hidden scrapbook pieces throughout the game to unlock concept art. The player was also allowed to save after every level, and was able to see their progress on each individual level as well (if they had found the KONG letters, bonus levels, and scrapbook pieces.) A "Hero" mode could also be unlocked by achieving at least a 90% completion rate. This was essentially a hard mode, where the player could only play as Diddy Kong in a yellow color swap suit. There were no D.K. barrels in this mode. The graphics in the Game Boy Advance version are a lot closer to the original than the Game Boy Color adaption, although some of the parralax backgrounds, map details and sprite resolutions have been downgraded, and the weather effects present in some levels from the original were taken out.The Wii Virtual Console version of Donkey Kong Country is an emulated port of the original game; version 1.3 for NTSC gamers and 1.1 for PAL gamers. As such some players may notice slight differences to their cartridge copy, but otherwise the game is a faithful port. It was released in the U.S. on February 19th, 2007.Plot:The game's storyline was characteristically sparse, in keeping with most games of the time period. Essentially, Donkey Kong's banana hoard has been stolen by King K. Rool, who has appeared on a ship with his reptilian Kremling crew. Along with Diddy Kong, Donkey Kong must fight through several worlds to King K. Rool's ship to fight him and recover his bananas. Other Kong members also help Donkey and Diddy along the way by either offering tips, saving their game or flying the Kongs back to previously visited areas.Gameplay:Donkey Kong riding on Rambi the RhinoCompared to Mario's arsenal, Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong have rather few moves available to them at the core. They are capable simply of walking, running, performing a rolling attack, and jumping. However, Donkey Kong Country featured a strong level of interaction with the environment, which greatly multiplied the gameplay possibilities in the game: ropes could be swung on, bouncy tires could be rolled or jumped on, and a vast array of various barrels could be picked up, thrown, or busted on enemies' heads. Still other barrels, called barrel cannons or blast barrels, floated in midair and could be leapt into, upon which depending on the type of barrel, either pressing a button or immediately upon entry, the player is blasted out of the end of the barrel. Often times, these barrels moved or rotated along paths, creating timing exercises which must be mastered to progress in the game.The primary method for dispatching enemies is to jump on them, or to toss barrels into them. Most enemies may also be put out of commission with a rolling attack as well, but some have defenses in this direction. While both Diddy Kong and Donkey Kong may appear on the screen at the same time, only one is actually controlled by the player; should the active character be injured, the inactive character will become playable. Should there be no inactive player, the player loses a life and must start the level over, either from the beginning or the midway checkpoint. Falling into pits results in instant death.There are also animal buddies in the game, which are found in crates and which the active character may ride to gain access to special abilities. These animal buddies and their abilities are listed below in the characters section.There are many secret areas in Donkey Kong Country, which may be found by blasting away walls with tough blows from barrels and rhinoceros horns, or jumping in spots above or below the screen to hidden barrels. These secret areas usually contain a chance to earn either extra lives or animal buddy tokens. Collecting three of the same type of animal buddy token will allow the player to play a different sort of bonus level, in which there is a set amount of time to gather as many tokens as the player can while playing as the animal buddy in question--every 100 tokens collected results in one extra life earned. There are also hidden giant tokens in these levels which, upon collection, will split into many smaller tokens to be collected as well as doubling the player's current token score.Characters:The KongsCharacterDescriptionDonkey KongOne of the two primary protagonists, Donkey Kong is a large gorilla who is ideal for tackling larger enemies due to his greater mass and strength. In addition to his rolling attack, he also has an additional special attack if the player holds down on the directional pad and then press the attack button.Diddy KongThe other primary playable character, Diddy Kong is faster and more agile than Donkey Kong. His special attack is a cartwheel which can knock down bigger enemies where jumping on them does no harm.Cranky KongCranky Kong provides "advice" throughout the game to the player and the two younger Kongs. According to the story, Cranky Kong was actually Donkey Kong in the original arcade version of Donkey Kong. This would mean that the Donkey Kong the player controls now is essentially Donkey Kong Jr. from the original arcade games.Candy KongCandy Kong may be visited to save the game, and in the Game Boy Color version, provides Mini Games to obtain tokens.She serves as Donkey Kong's love interest.Funky KongFunky Kong allows the player to transfer between the worlds in the game.The Good GuysCharacterDescriptionEnguarde the SwordfishA fish who can swim underwater, Enguarde enables the Kongs to kill fish and bash into walls through a charging attack.Expresso the OstrichExpresso runs extremely fast, and can sustain limited flight, allowing the Kongs to glide much further through the air than they could do on their own. his tall legs allow him to run over small enemies without being hurt.Rambi the RhinoRambi is large and heavy, making him unwieldy for platforming, but excellent for bowling over foes. He also has a charge attack.SquawksSquawks the Parrot may not provide transportation for the Kongs as in later games; instead, the parrot holds a flashlight to illuminate the way for the player in dark levels.WinkyWinky is capable of jumping extremely high. However, his awkward motion makes him rather imprecise for difficult platforming.The Bad GuysArmyGnawtyManky KongMini-NeckyNeckySlippaZingerThe Aquatic Bad GuysBitesizeChompsChomps Jr.ClamboCroctopusSquidgeThe KremlingsKlaptrapKlumpKrashKritterKrushaRockkrocThe BossesVery GnawtyMaster NeckyQueen B.Really GnawtyDumb DrumMaster Necky Snr.King K. RoolWorlds and LevelsDKC has a total of 7 worlds and 40 levels. Listed below are the world names, with the level names indented underneath.Kongo JungleWorld MapJungle HijinxRopey RampageReptile RumbleCoral CapersBarrel Cannon CanyonVery Gnawty's LairMonkey MinesWinky's WalkwayMine Cart CarnageBouncy BonanzaStop &amp; Go StationMillstone MayhemNecky's NutsVine ValleyVulture CultureTree Top TownForest FrenzyTemple TempestOrang-Utan GangClam CityBumble B. RumbleGorilla GlacierSnow Barrel BlastSlip Slide RideIce Age AlleyCroctopus ChaseTorchlight TroubleRope Bridge RumbleReally Gnawty RampageKremkroc Industries Inc.Oil Drum AlleyTrick Track TrekElevator AnticsPoison PondMine Cart MadnessBlackout BasementBoss Dumb DrumChimp CavernsTanked Up TroubleManic MincersMisty MineNecky Nutmare (only in the Gameboy version!)Loopy LightsPlatform PerilsNecky's RevengeGangplank GalleonGangplank Galleon (K. Rool Battle)DK JamzThe musical score for Donkey Kong Country was very popular and was known for being one of the most sophisticated soundtracks at the time. Nintendo later released a soundtrack for the game under the name of "DK Jamz."TracksDK JamzThemeSimian SegueDK Island SwingCranky's ThemeJungle GrooveCave Dweller ConcertBonus Room BlitzAquatic AmbianceCandy's Love SongBad Boss BoogieMine Cart MadnessLife in the MinesVoices of the TempleForest FrenzyTreetop RockFunky's FugueMisty MenaceNorthern HemispheresIce Cave ChantFear FactoryGang-Plank GalleonK-Rool's CacophonyThe Credits ConcertoLoseWinCheat: Bonus StageTo see the sound test menu and listen to music from the game, at the start screen, hold select button, then press B,A,L,L,A, Down. Now, youll see the Sound player.Cheat: Bonus StageAt the file select screen, go down to the erase command at the bottom of the screen. Hold select, and input the following buttons. Diddy will say ''Not Bad''. Now, load any of the three game files, and you will automatically start with 50 lives. You do not have to input this code again as long as you save.Cheat: Alternate DK Attack BackgroundUnlock photos in the picture album by finding the camera pieces in the various levels.Cheat: Exit Previously Beaten LevelsOnce you've beaten a level you can press Start and then Select in the level to exit it.Cheat: Exit Previously Beaten LevelsRight after the part where you get the frog, drop down to the ledge on the right. You will be back in the same room and you can collect the +5 multiplier again. Rinse and Repeat for as big of a time bonus as you want!</plot>
	<releasedate>9/6/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>PeVJq3phR6w</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3391</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589452-donkey-kong-country</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/donkey-kong-country</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/donkey-kong-country/3030-15738/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2363725-snes_donkeykongcountry.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3391-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/55401-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101534-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/544874-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-japanese-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101536-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101523-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-visit-funky.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101527-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-be-the-biggest.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101524-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-cranky-gives.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101522-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-jump-in-candy.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101529-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-with-the-help.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101530-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-this-version.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101531-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-mine-cart.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3391-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/XlcQXdE.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3391.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Welcome to Donkey Kong Country, a place where ostriches wear running shoes, apes wear neckties, and rhinoceros gracefully leap across gaping canyons with a style and flair that would make the great Evel Knievel envious. This remake of the SNES classic revamps the Donkey Kong Country gameplay with new minigames, a new Attack mode, and the ability to save your progress anywhere. Whether you're looking for a nostalgic stroll through the jungle or you're new to the Donkey Kong world, Donkey Kong Country keeps you on your toes with platform challenges, dance minigames, and unique enemies.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/243f30cd-e9da-4267-90b1-358c73b7c652.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/790aa5cd-8973-4f01-8bf2-363461839463.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a38cb78e-5d45-43b4-a2d4-ee0863dc0921.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>