<Game>
	<Name>Donkey Kong Country 3 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>In a world where ostriches wear tennis shoes and the Kongs clamber through exotic island adventures, KAOS is on the rampage and you must use Dixie's skills to save the day. Dixie and Kiddy Kong take a run through the jungle to rescue Diddy and Donkey Kong! Baron K. Roolenstein, the leader of the Kremlings, kidnapped Donkey and Diddy, and Dixie and Kiddy must run, roll, hop, and swing across enemy-infested stages. Let the Kremling-crushin' commence with all-new minigames, nine worlds to journey through, more than 50 levels and two-player mode. The beloved side-scrollin' sequel to Donkey Kong Country 1 &amp; 2 is now in the palm of your hands! Use Kiddy Kong's and Dixie Kong's unique abilities like the water skip and helicopter spin to go ape on the baddies. A ninth world, Pacifica, has been added to the original eight worlds. It includes six all-new levels - set from the deepest drain pipes to the tallest treetops - and adds two to three hours of brand-new gameplay. Play all-new mini-games to earn money and items. Compete in a series of boat races in Funky's Challenge, use a shield to block an onslaught of spiked creatures in Cranky's Dojo, or race through tunnels collecting stars in Swanky's Dash. Check back for more information on this game as the release date approaches, and be on the lookout for 'Where is Donkey Kong?' Help us find DK in a charity benefit for all his real-life animal friends.Cheat: Cheat Menu CheatsEnter these into the 'Enter Cheat' screen found in the 'Options' menu.Cheat: Unlimited Bear CoinsGo to the Sunken Spruce level in Pacifica. After you get to the second Bonus level (the one near the rope), go up and get the Bear Coin that's by the Buzz, then go into the Bonus level. Either win or lose, and you'll end up by the rope, with the Bear Coin still there. Repeat this to get unlimited Bear Coins.Cheat: Best endingTo obtain the best ending in the game, you must collect every Bonus Coin in the game, every DK Coin, and every Banana Bird, and defeat the last boss in Krematoa.Cheat: Best endingTo reach Krematoa (the Lost World), go to the four rocks east (left) of Mekanos.  Stay on the rocks as you circle around it clockwise about four times and the volcano will replace the rocks.Cheat: Best endingTo reach the new exclusive to this game Oceanic based world, when you get the jetski use your turbo up the waterfall right where you started the game. Go up the waterfall after that and swim to the very hidden world marked by a K Rool Flag</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>7.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3455</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/928294-donkey-kong-country-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/donkey-kong-country</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/donkey-kong-country/3030-15738/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3455-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3455-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/55401-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101534-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/544874-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-japanese-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101536-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101523-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-visit-funky.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101527-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-be-the-biggest.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101524-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-cranky-gives.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101522-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-jump-in-candy.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101529-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-with-the-help.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101530-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-this-version.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/101531-donkey-kong-country-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-mine-cart.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3455-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/XAEvV4T.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3455.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Revisit Donkey Kong Island and join the Kong family for their latest adventure. The Kremlings have a mysterious new leader named KAOS and are up to their usual mischief, even capturing Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong. Now it's up to Dixie Kong and the newest Kong, a giant infant named Kiddy, to rescue the two missing apes.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a87512df-857d-417f-8c5f-9c0b9de2f4c6.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ce248c08-5d40-4a12-a952-2b1912d8c293.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5a755d6f-2033-4ede-950e-97392db8109b.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>