<Game>
	<Name>Dora the Explorer - Super Spies (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Senor Tucan, a master super spy, has a special mission for super spies Dora and Boots: Race to Tico's workshop to warn him of Swiper's plan to swipe his new rocket car. In this dangerous adventure, Dora and Boots need help from their friends, Backpack and Map, and you. To help them, you must find spy briefcases that contain special spy gadgets, such as spy glasses, rocket sneakers, a rope launcher, and more. You'll need these items to explore levels ranging from a rainforest and a garden to a desert and a cavern.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/915383.htmlCheat: Rain forest 2 codeUse the password function and put in the following code.Cheat: Dora The Explorer - Super Spies For GBAPunch these in on the contiune screen.  These Passwords Have Been confirmed to make sure they are what the game gives you and confirmed to make sure they actually work. However some of them DO NOT work when punched in, they are marked as so.Cheat: Dora The Explorer - Super Spies For GBALegend:^ = Up Arrow-&amp;gt; = Right Arrow&amp;lt;- = Left ArrowDown Arrow = Down ArrowFunny Square =The Square with the Spiral in it+ = Plus Sign:) = Happy Face:( = Frown Face:,  = The Last Face (Not Smiling)Heart = HeartStar = StarCircle = CircleSquare = SquareSun = Circle with little things around it looking like the sun</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Gotham Games</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3396</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/915383-dora-the-explorer-super-spies</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dora-the-explorer-super-spies/3030-41511/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3396-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3396-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7489/2428466-dora.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/2/d/gfs_59223_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/f/d/gfs_59223_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/4/d/gfs_59223_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/5/d/gfs_59223_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/e/d/gfs_59223_1_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3396-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3396.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Seor Tucn, a master super spy, has a special mission for super spies Dora and Boots: Race to Tico's workshop to warn him of Swiper's plan to swipe his new rocket car. In this dangerous adventure, Dora and Boots need help from their friends, Backpack and Map, and you. To help them, you must find spy briefcases that contain special spy gadgets, such as spy glasses, rocket sneakers, a rope launcher, and more. You'll need these items to explore levels ranging from a rainforest and a garden to a desert and a cavern.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a458d507-723d-4b79-9ddd-25d41f3c2251.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4aaae5a9-3229-4d6e-b3aa-5461f4e10253.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c424c716-18a0-4b22-9f15-d4398ddab94f.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Gotham Games</Publisher>
</game>