<Game>
	<Name>Downforce (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>A new extreme anything goes racing league of racecars thrust to EXTREME SPEEDS by super-exotic technologies such as Heavy Element Drive Engines, Directional Thrusters, Vectored Jet Engines, and Electro Magnetic Brakes. Racing on street courses with high-speed straight-aways, sweeping curves and hairpin turns, extreme speed and challenging courses combine to create THRILLING RACES and SPECTACULAR CRASHES.THE ULTIMATE ARCADE RACING EXPERIENCE, Downforce delivers the brutally intense essence of racing action as you battle opponents in an absolute duel for victory! This is what racing is all about-NO RULES, JUST SPEED, FUN, AND CRASHES!Cheat: Continue Codes - Unlocked via Natural ProgressionFrom the Main Menu, select ''Continue'' and input the following code:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Titus Software</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>24658</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561106-downforce</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/downforce/3030-29362/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/24658-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/b/d/gfs_7496_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/6/d/gfs_7496_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/d/d/gfs_7496_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/c/d/gfs_7496_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/7/d/gfs_7496_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>A group of drivers and teams have split from the Formula 1 Championship, after being held back by rules and regulations for too long. Races have become boring with overtaking and pure racing at an all-time low. The new racing league has been condemned as too dangerous and banned from using circuits around the world. The races instead take place in and around major cities. The cars use all the technology available today, to increase speed and `downforce?. With less stringent rules, teams have worked in different directions creating a wide variety of enhanced super cars.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7be61f62-b0f6-4a16-b2a1-4c6e6c1e9590.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ba025077-d155-4bea-9a8d-90ba601be23b.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Titus</Publisher>
</game>