<Game>
	<Name>Downtown - Nekketsu Monogatari EX (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The classic NES game returns with improved graphics and even more role-playing action. As in the original game, River City Ransom for the Game Boy Advance blends action, fighting, and role-playing elements into one game. You'll play one of two young heroes who must battle their way past city gangs and then defeat the gang lord to free the students of River City High. More than just a side-scrolling fighting game, River City Ransom EX features a character-building system and customization options.Cheat: Name CodesEnter these codes in the change name screen under the Status menu. The names are case sensitive.Cheat: Fight Slick with ZombiesUsually Slick will instantly kill any Zombies in your gang, claiming that it's "not their fight." As soon as he kills them, leave the screen and come back, they will reappear in your gang and you can have the extra support in beating Slick!Cheat: Fight Slick with ZombiesAt the left corner of Reihou's Roof, if you're carrying someone and they jump off straight down then they will fall down through an invisible hole and dies. (Works even on Slick)Cheat: Easy Reputation Increase. To quickly and easily increase your rep, simply run into a wall. Every time you do this, the game will give you +1 to your rep.Cheat: Easy Reputation Increase.To find the game's Hidden Shop, go inside the Armstrong Thru-Way and press Up when you are standing between the fourth light and the fifth light (make sure you are against the wall). The shop sells many useful items, including some that can boost your stats.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/5/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Beat-Em-Up</genre>
	<Developer>Million</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.4</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>2939</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/915026-river-city-ransom-ex</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2939-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2939-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/3/1/gfs_26936_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/f/1/gfs_47620_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/2/1/gfs_47620_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/9/1/gfs_47620_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/8/1/gfs_47620_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/2939-g.jpg</banner1>
	<banner2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/2939-g2.png</banner2>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2939.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Kunio's greatest adventure with enhanced graphics and new gameplay! Brothers Ryuichi and Ryuji arrive at the Reihou Academy, located near Nekketsu High. After a short amount of time, nearby schools have begun fallen under the control of Ryuichi and Ryuji, who rumor has it have dubbed themselves the Double Dragons. Riki Samejima of Hanazono High has never seen eye to eye with Kunio, and in fact, they seem to always compete to be the best. But one day, Mami Shimada, Riki's girlfriend, is kidnapped and held at Reihou Academy. The issue is challenged to Riki, come save your girlfriend! Riki's heart is burning with fury, and he flies out of the gates and seeks out his rival Kunio to help take on all opposing gangs. But one man awaits them at Reihou Academy that will shock Kunio!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1eb6c1e5-d8f3-4e4e-8e5c-a842bc78d0d0.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
</game>