<Game>
	<Name>Dragon Ball GT - Transformation (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This release of the Dragon Ball saga is a side-scrolling combat game that allows you to play missions or arcade games with 9 characters of the TV series, though in story mode you have to unlock some characters to be able to use them. There are single and multiplayer modes. In the single player mode you can use multiple characters in your adventures and switch between them, using their special skills when in difficult situations. You can also play in multiplayer mode with the Link system.Each character has his/her special moves and abilities, and the various environments in the planets are also quite accomplished. The game modes are: Story, Standard, Endurance, Boss Endurance, Robot Swarm and Piccolo.In the Story mode, Goku is accidentally turned into a child, and in order to become an adult again, he has to recover all the Dragon Balls which are scattered in different planets. While you battle your way through each planet, you will control 3 characters which represent the lives you have. Though they can expand their stamina, and recover their energy while not used. At the end of each planet you will have to defeat the corresponding boss, and the story finishes with a battle with an evil enemy well known to all Dragon Ball fans...Cheat: Cheat CodesEnter any of the following to time during gameplay(while Not Pause). You'll hear a small chime to comfirm each code:Cheat: Cheat CodesEnter these codes at anytime during gameplay.Cheat: Cheat CodesYou can unlock characters by pressing some buttons!!:PCheat: Cheat CodesNote: Press it on the main menu(when you press the code for the character the character you press before that will gone)Cheat: UnlockablesPerform the task in order to unlock the thing specified after it.Cheat: Easy ZeniePlay through Rudeeze until you reach the boss.  After you destroy his stinger, he will be unable to attack you from a distance.  At this point, simply charge your ki meter and fire a special attack at him.  It won't cause any damage, but you should get about 30,000 points or so for doing this.  Continue doing so and you should quickly gain a large amount of points, and in turn, zenie.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/8/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Atari, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3457</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/921892-dragon-ball-gt-transformation</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/dragon-ball-gt-transformation</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dragon-ball-gt-transformation/3030-15454/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3457-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3457-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/166421-dragon-ball-gt-transformation-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267886-dragon-ball-gt-transformation-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267887-dragon-ball-gt-transformation-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267888-dragon-ball-gt-transformation-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267889-dragon-ball-gt-transformation-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267890-dragon-ball-gt-transformation-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267891-dragon-ball-gt-transformation-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267892-dragon-ball-gt-transformation-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267893-dragon-ball-gt-transformation-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267894-dragon-ball-gt-transformation-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3457-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3457.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dragon Ball GT: Transformation is a Game Boy Advance action game based on the Japanese cartoon Dragon Ball GT. Transformation follows the Dragon Ball GT storyline from the Child Goku Saga to the Baby Saga. You can create three-man teams from seven playable characters--such as Goku, Trunks, and Uub--and choose who you control in the middle of a battle.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c1113114-590d-48a7-9492-fa415e2f5b9d.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4b56b754-473c-451e-a8fd-5493377e0dc4.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dbedef04-26b1-48c6-8432-ac24a858536e.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Atari</Publisher>
</game>