<Game>
	<Name>Dragon Ball Z - Buu's Fury (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The third and final game that re-tells the Dragon Ball Z story on the Game Boy Advance, Buu's Fury picks up after the events of the Android/Cell Saga. Taking place during the events of the Buu saga, Gohan is now all grown up, and also has a new younger brother, Goten. A brand new evil appears that is named Bibidi, who's trying to revive a powerful warrior to take control of so he can take over the universe. Gameplay: Buu's Fury is a beat-em-up with RPG elements at its core. Characters level up and gain more stat points to use. Leveling up also gives characters the ability to break down numbered barriers in order to progress in the story. Legacy of Goku 3 also incorporated equipment and food to both strengthen your character and restore health respectively. The game has a total of five standard characters and 3 fusion characters. By leveling up and completing more of the story, these characters gain access to higher-powered versions of their normal powers and the ability to go into different levels of Super Saiyan, ranging from Super Saiyan 1-3.  Characters: As mentioned earlier, Buu's Fury has 5 total characters and 3 different fusion forms. Two of the fusion forms can be used as powers, while one is only used in some story boss fights. The characters are also given many different costumes throughout the day, and at some points in the story you can use other side characters.Normal Characters        Teen Gohan           Goku          Goten         Trunks        Vegeta Fusion Characters       Gotenks     Gogeta    Vegito* *Only usable in certain story mission.  Temporary Playable Characters   Videl  HerculeCheat: 255 Senzu BeansDuring the World Tournament Saga, when Gohan asks Goku to get a Senzu Bean, fly to Korin's Tower and get a bean from Yajirobe. Instead of giving it to Gohan, eat it. When you return, Goku will still give a Senzu bean to Gohan even though he does not have any. When you look in your invintory, you will see that you have 255 senzu beans.Cheat: 255 Senzu Beansfirst, Equip Goku/Goten or Vegeta/Trunks (remove all unneeded equips before) and do the Fusion Dance. As Gogeta/Gotenks, remove the equipment from the equipped character. The Fusion will keep the equips but you'll be able to re-use the equips on another character. This will keep working untill you run out of Fusion timeCheat: 255 Senzu BeansLure an enemy onto a Save Point with a strong character. Punch the enemy and kill it. Before you earn any experience from the downed enemy, the "Switch Character" menu will come up. Switch to a weak character. The character you switched to will gain the experience.Cheat: Hercule Museum ExhibitsWhen these exhibits are found, take them to the Hercule Cafe in Hercule City to view them.Cheat: Hercule Museum ExhibitsEverytime you get one of those, they are unlocked for the capsule corp museum, letting you see a specific item from the DBZ series.Cheat: Kai StoreTo access a store containing some of the best items in the game, visit the Kai's planet once you beat Buu and work your way to the right-most map and break through the crack in the wall. In here you'll find great items for levelling up, such as the Kiloton Gloves/Boots, and great armor with super high endurance.Cheat: Kai StoreWhile a conversasion press the L or R button and the talking screen will go up and down.Cheat: Kai StoreWhile preforming the Fusion Dance with Either Goku/Vegeta or Goten/Trunks, if you ignore the buttons it tells you to press, and instead press Up, B, Left, Down, A, you will successfully fuse every time.</plot>
	<releasedate>14/9/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Atari, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>OguO8Wo2Kf8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3399</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920530-dragon-ball-z-buus-fury</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/dragon-ball-z-buus-fury</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/dragon-ball-z-buus-fury/3030-5355/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3399-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3399-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/279852-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/160777-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264830-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-screenshot-goku.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264831-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-second.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264832-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-screenshot-gohan.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264833-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-screenshot-flying.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264834-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-screenshot-status.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264835-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-screenshot-trunks.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264836-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-number.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264837-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-screenshot-vegeta.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264838-dragon-ball-z-buu-s-fury-game-boy-advance-screenshot-goku.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3399-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CtFHd9C.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3399.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dragon Ball Z: Buu's Fury begins with the Other World Tournament Saga and continues through the Kid Buu Saga, the final chapter in the Dragon Ball Z story. In a game that combines action and role-playing game elements with exploration, enemies, boss enemies, puzzles, and quests, your ultimate goal is to defeat Buu. Choose the best character--Goku, Vegeta, Gohan, Goten, or Trunks--for each mission, create fusion characters whenever necessary, and unleash powerful attack combos and super moves.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c3a3612f-c331-47d7-861d-56b5a64771ce.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/be305110-cff8-4f11-abf8-cb153716dc4c.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7b3287e8-5828-4b31-848b-8df4aa007611.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Atari</Publisher>
</game>