<Game>
	<Name>Drill Dozer (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Drill Dozer is a 2D platforming adventure game developed by Game Freak for the Gameboy Advance.  In addition to its colorful graphics and fleshed out drill-based game mechanics, it also noteworthy for including a rumble pack in the game cartridge itself to provide players with tactile feedback similar to that of a modern console controller.Gameplay:As Jill, the pink-haired pilot of a mechanical exo-suit called a Drill Dozer, players navigate through seventeen adventure levels filled with enemies, platform-style puzzles, and encounters with boss characters at the end of every stage.  "Chips" collected by defeating enemies, opening treasure chests, and discovering hidden areas can be used between levels to purchase better equipment for the Drill Dozer, such as stronger drill bits for penetrating tougher materials and energy tanks to extend Jill's life bar.The Drill Dozer can jump and scoot through narrow openings to explore the level, but the game's primary drilling mechanic has been woven into every facet of the game.  In addition to defeating enemies and demolishing barriers, revving the drill in the proper direction can deflect incoming projectiles, spin turbines, release screws, propel the dozer through special vents, and even to swim and fly.  The start of each new level restricts the drill to spinning only for a few brief moments, but by locating the gear boxes hidden in each area, Jill can increase its power and duration to the point where it can run indefinitely.  However, since the Dozer's movement is restricted while the drill is running at full power, players will still need to time its use carefully.When the drill is activated, an RPM meter appears on the screen to show how long it can run for.  Once the Dozer has additional gears installed, players can shift up by releasing the button and quickly repressing it again with the right timing.  This means the Dozer needs a little time to reach higher drill speeds which can be vital for breaching certain barriers, and though the timing required is fairly simple, it keeps the player more actively involved than simply holding down a lone button.  Additionally, spinning the drill clockwise or counter-clockwise can have different effects based on the situation, so players will need to correctly switch between using the R or L shoulder buttons on the GBA to succeed.Similar to games in the Metroid series, some areas in Drill Dozer cannot be explored when they are first encountered, but can be revisited later once the Dozer has been enhanced with stronger drill bits.  This backtracking element is not necessary to complete the main game, but is required for players who wish to collect all of the hidden treasures and unlock the game's secret features.Story:When Jill's father Doug is attacked and robbed of a precious family heirloom by a rival bandit game called the Skullkers, Jill sets out to take back the stolen treasure and defeat their wicked plans in the process.  Along the way, she'll also battle crooked cops, quirky crooks, and unite five diamonds with mystic powers.Trivia:Although Drill Dozer enjoyed largely positive reviews, it suffered from poor sales in North America and Japan (where it was released under the title Screw Breaker). Jill and her Drill Dozer appear in the Wii game Super Smash Brothers Brawl as a collectible trophy, as well as one of the in-game assist trophies.  When unleashed, Jill drills furiously towards the nearest enemies and attempts to ram them off the edge of the stage. In the game there are unlockable costumes, some of which reference to other Nintendo and Game Freak games, such as Mario's red shirt and blue overalls, the female Pok&#233;mon trainer's clothes from Pok&#233;mon FireRed/LeafGreen, and even Pulseman's costume. Cheat: Full GearboxOnce you have unlocked the Full Gearbox using the secret room in the tutorial level, you are able to replay any world with all three gears by using its effect.  To activate it, hold R and press Select while on the world select screen.  The Screw Bit will turn yellow to indicate that you have activated the Full Gearbox.Cheat: Full GearboxOnce you have the Proof of Mastery item, you can select Hard mode on the file select screen by holding down L+R before you hit the Start button.Cheat: Secret Password Effect CodesOnce an Unlock Code has been entered in the secret room in the tutorial level, you may enter one or more Effect Codes of equal or lower level. These codes may be entered freely and without any specific method - there is no need to reset the combination lock at any time unless you need to enter another Unlock Code.Cheat: Secret Password Effect CodesEntering in a correct Effect Code will cause a chest to appear from the purple brick pipe in the room. Simply walk into the chest to claim the prize. Certain chests (the wallpapers, for example) may be collected multiple times to alter the current effect. In particular and as an example, the Standard Wallpaper chest will not appear until you have changed the current message border to something else.Cheat: Secret Password Effect CodesNote that these codes will not work until the correct Unlock Code has been entered since entering the secret room.  The Master Seal and Full Gearbox enable certain key combinations on particular screens for extra effects, detailed in the code section.  The Soundstone opens up a Music/SFX Player in Gearmo's Save Menu at the Trailer.  The Wallpapers change the border around messages and the inside of the Red Dozers' Trailer.  And the Costumes allow you to change Jill's appearance by highlighting her in the trailer and pressing either the L or R buttons.Cheat: Secret Password Effect CodesFinally, two Effect Codes have further requirements before they will work.  The Soundstone chest will not appear until you have found the Soundstone treasure in Area 1-2, and the Full Gearbox chest will not appear until you have collected all 31 treasures, earning the highest rank: Crime Boss.Cheat: Secret Password Effect CodesOnce you have earned the Mega Bit by buying it from the shop after it becomes available, you will have access to a secret room in the tutorial world (Red Dozers' Training Course). This room contains a 4-digit combination lock.Cheat: Secret Password Effect CodesBefore you can properly use this room to enter in secret passwords, you must first enter an unlock code. There are 3 levels of Unlock Codes, each unlocking more passwords than the previous.Cheat: Secret Password Effect CodesTo enter an Unlock Code, you must first reset the combination lock by selecting one of the digits and hitting start while the drill is inserted - this will reset the code back to 9999. Once this is done, you must set each of the digits of the Unlock Code to their correct number in the correct order. If you change one of the numbers out of order, or if you connect to and alter the same number twice before completing the unlock code, then the code will not work and you will have to reset the combination again by pressing Start.Cheat: Secret Password Effect CodesOnce the fourth number is correctly set, the combination lock will auto-reset to show that you have entered the code correctly. You may then either enter another Unlock Code, or enter an Effect Code of equal or lower level.Cheat: Secret Password Effect CodesUnlock Codes stay in effect until you leave the room. If you re-enter the room at a later time, you must input the Unlock Code again to use more Effect Codes.</plot>
	<releasedate>6/2/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>6Jg_UoFwTbk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3459</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/928398-drill-dozer</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/drill-dozer</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/drill-dozer/3030-17537/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3459-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3459-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59249-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154471-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/154472-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro-story.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/180301-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-can-scope-out.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/180302-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-press-select-to-access.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/180303-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-ll-need-another.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/180304-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-found-your-second.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/180305-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-now-you-can-gear-up.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/180306-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-skull-rollers-occasionally.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/180307-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-your-drill-can-bite.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/180308-drill-dozer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-these-items-are-chips.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3459-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3459-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3459-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3459-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/i4U2LR4.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3459.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In the platformer Drill Dozer, you can take the roll of Jill, the daughter of a crime boss who is set on revenge. When a rival gang steals away her family's heirloom, Jill gives chase in her Drill Dozer, an upgradeable piece of power armor equipped with a large drill. This piece of equipment will help you navigate through six different areas, where you will encounter varied enemies and bosses.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>UN0Qi-PAo2U</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/569af861-6288-4c8f-b754-98449fa739e4.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b388ab54-022f-4722-ae21-f2c34b4e93e2.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/73d7edcd-19d6-49ed-bec5-41bafa693775.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fafdd84b-aeb4-4060-94d8-d121ed276b9a.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/edf82532-90d3-46db-a474-ee7d1c55b856.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>