<Game>
	<Name>Driver 2 Advance (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>You are an undercover driver, trying to survive amidst an international war between American and Brazilian gangs. The action takes you to Chicago, Las Vegas, Rio and Havana, all of which are depicted in detail, with curved roads added from the first game.As before, you have full control over the car as it storms around the streets. A new feature is the ability to get out of the car, and carjack others. This is especially useful when you have fallen victim to the advanced damage modeling.There is a full sequence of missions to complete, as well as some pre-set challenges and a Free Driving mode allowing you to explore at your leisure.http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/driver-2Cheat: Pass Through CarsAs you walk into a car, press Up + B. If you did this right, the car you walked into will shake, and you'll go through it.Cheat: Change Police Cars ColorWhile driving on the sand in the Rio stage, if there is a police car behind you, press L + R to change its color.Cheat: Change Police Cars ColorIt's possible to ''win'' Survival Mode if you can evade the law for ten minutes. Normally this is almost impossible, but there is an easy way to do it in Rio de Janeiro. Look on the map for a road that seemingly leads to nowhere just north of Lagua Rodrigo de Freitas. This road leads to a path not on the map, which leads to Vasquez's mansion. There is no traffic on the mansion grounds, so no police cars will spawn there. Making it to the path isn't easy, but once you do, you're home free. Just sit tight until the clock reaches ten minutes, and you'll get a ''You Win!'' message and be returned to the Driving Games menu with a literally unbeatable high score!</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Atari</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.2</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3408</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/554414-driver-2-advance</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/driver-2-advance</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3408-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3408-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/424877-driver-2-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-at-the-red-river.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/424878-driver-2-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-meet-pink-lenny.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/424879-driver-2-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/424880-driver-2-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/424881-driver-2-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-your-mission.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/424882-driver-2-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-first-get-in.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/424883-driver-2-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-running-to-your.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/424884-driver-2-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-driving-your.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742649-driver-2-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-off-to-your-next.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742650-driver-2-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-taking-a-bend.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3408-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/DmUXsnG.jpg</banner1>
</game>