<Game>
	<Name>Ecks vs Sever (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ecks vs. Sever was meant to be an adaptation of the film Ballistic: Ecks vs. Sever starring Antonio Banderas and Lucy Liu. Publisher BAM! Entertainment optioned the game rights to the barely in production film and sent developer Crawfish Interactive to work, basing the game on a very early version the film's script. Though the film was delayed and radically altered from the original script, BAM! and Crawfish nevertheless proceeded with the original design and released the game--with no mention of the movie upon which it was based--on November 27, 2001, ten months before the film would debut. A version for PlayStation 2 and Xbox was also in production at Zombie Studios, but it was cancelled.Ecks vs. Sever would be followed by Ballistic: Ecks vs. Sever, another FPS for GBA that was released in tandem with, and more closely followed the plot of, the final film and was positioned as a sequel to this game. Both Ecks vs. Sever games are widely considered to be superior to the film upon which they were based, which was ranked the "Worst-Reviewed Film of All Time" in 2007 by film review aggregator Rotten Tomatoes.Cheat: 3 Multiplayer PasswordsVULNERABLE VORACIOUS VENDETTA* *by chago_85Cheat: 3 Multiplayer PasswordsVULNERABLE  VORACIOUS  VENDETTA VIOLATECheat: 3 Multiplayer PasswordsVINDICATE VESUVIUSCheat: 3 Multiplayer PasswordsLevel-02: EXTREME Level-03: EXCITE Level-04: EXCAVATE Level-05: EXCALIBUR Level-06: EXTORT Level-07: EXPIRE Level-08: EXACT Level-09: EXHALE Level-10: EXHUME Level-11: EXONERATE Level-12: EXPELCheat: 3 Multiplayer PasswordsLevel-02: SEVERE Level-03: SURVIVE Level-04: SAVANT Level-05: SUFFER Level-06: SULPHER Level-07: SERVE Level-08: SEETHE Level-09: SEVERAL Level-10: SEVERANCE Level-11: SAVAGE Level-12: SACROSANCTCheat: Special Character ViewsWhen you select ''start game'', you see an option to play as either Ecks or Sever. While their characters are displayed press either the ''L'' or the ''R'' button to rotate these models. Also press ''up'' or ''down'' to view their actions such as shooting, running, dying, crouching and shoot while crouching.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/11/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>BAM! Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3415</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/537159-ecks-vs-sever</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/ecks-vs-sever</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ecks-vs-sever/3030-15516/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2285647-box_evs.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3415-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/116530-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/252094-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-start-up-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/252095-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/252096-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose-your-character.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/252097-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-objectives-are-explained.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/252098-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-defeat-enemy-agents.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/252099-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-crawling-through.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/252100-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-mopping-up-with.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/252101-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-new-weapons-in-each.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/252102-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-everyone-loves-explosives.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/252103-ecks-vs-sever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-need-hi-tech.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Hmyij0n.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>An FBI agent and a rogue NSA agent are pitted against each other in a deadly game of cat and mouse. Both skilled assassins bent on personal revenge, each must terminate the other in order to survive. But unknown to each other, they are both pawns in a much larger conspiracy. Now the as the hunters become the hunted, they must both determine who the real enemy is.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0a30d152-5d58-40e6-9149-424916a42330.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f6e40f64-bb50-4624-a6c4-c5dd6472b852.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/72f4a4bc-16f1-497c-bba7-a60cb9d86544.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/75be18a9-a889-4678-b56c-ce227efca015.png</boxart4>
	<Publisher>BAM!</Publisher>
</game>