<Game>
	<Name>F-Zero - Climax (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:F-Zero Climax is the third game in the series for the Game Boy Advance and is, to date, the most recent F-Zero game. Like its predecessor, GP Legend, Climax was co-developed by Nintendo and SUZAK and is based on the anime of the same name.Gameplay:The core gameplay is identical to that of the other 2D F-Zero games.Like other F-Zero games, the player's booster unlocks at the start of the second lap. However, in Climax, the player also receives a "Super Boost" stock at the end of each lap. By pressing the booster button twice in succession, the machine gains an even stronger boost of speed at the cost of one stock.The player can slide into turns or quickly shift to a side by using the shoulder buttons. Pressing L and R together executes a spin attack; the booster can be used to enhance this attack, as well.Modes:Grand PrixThe main mode of the game. Players compete in five- or eight-track sets and attempt to place 1st.SurvivalThe player take on a sequence of challenges, such as competing in a one lap race or staying above a certain speed limit. It consists of Tour, Challenge, and Battle.Time AttackThe player can select a track from Grand Prix and race for the best time. It also includes the Zero Test, which challenges the player to complete a portion of track within a time limit.EditThis mode allows the player to create a track. The track can then be traded to friends using either the Link Cable or a password feature.CommunicationThis allows up to four players to compete against each other.OptionsThis mode lets players change the controls, and includes two galleries: one features the profile for racers and their machines, and the other contains episode summaries for the anime series.RacersIn addition to featuring the entire cast of F-Zero X, this game adds characters based on the anime. The player starts with the four original F-Zero machines and Ryu Suzaku/Dragon Bird, and unlocks the rest by completing Grand Prix.CharacterVehicle / PodWeight (kg)BodyBoostGripCaptain FalconBlue Falcon1260BCBDr. StewartGolden Fox1420DADPicoWild Goose1620ABCSamurai GorohFire Stingray1960ADBJody SummerWhite Cat1150CCAMighty GazelleRed Gazelle1330EACBabaIron Tiger1780BDAOctomanDeep Claw990BBCDr. ClashCrazy Bear2220ABEMr. EadGreat Star1870EADBio RexBig Fang1520BDABillyMad Wolf1490BBCSilver NeelsenNight Thunder1530BAEGomar &amp; ShiohTwin Norita780EACJohn TanakaWonder Wasp900DADMrs. ArrowQueen Meteor1140EBBBlood FalconBlood Hawk1170BAEJack LevinAstro Robin1050BDAJames McCloudLittle Wyvern1390EBBZodaDeath Anchor1620EACMichael ChainWild Boar2110ACCSuper ArrowKing Meteor860EBBKate AllenSuper Piranha1010BCBRoger BusterMighty Hurricane1780EBBLeonSpace Angler910CCADraqMighty Typhoon950CADBeastmanHyper Speeder1460CCAAntonio GusterGreen Panther2060ABDBlack ShadowBlack Bull2340AEAThe SkullSonic Phantom1010CADRyu Suzaku (Rick Wheeler)Dragon Bird1850BBBLucy LibertyElegance Liberty1000BCALisa BrilliantPanzer Emerald1900ADBMiss Killer (Luna Ryder)Moon Shadow1110BCBDark SoldierSoldier Anchor1620EAC"New" Captain FalconBlue Falcon GT1380BBCBerserkerRed Bull2200ACBClank HughesDragon Bird EX1880BACHyper ZodaHyper Death Anchor1670CADCheat: Character ProfilesTo unlock the character profiles for all characters, complete the 'Challenge' option in Survival mode with your desired character.Cheat: Character ProfilesDo the following tasks to unlock game modes, cups, hidden pilots and machines.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>OYUZBxuWaaE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26658</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/922026-f-zero-climax</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/f-zero-climax</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/f-zero-climax/3030-21252/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/26658-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/5/8/61758_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/14/142788/2443148-preview_titlescreen.gif</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/14/142788/2443147-preview_timetrial.gif</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/14/142788/2443146-preview_survivalmode.gif</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/14/142788/2443145-preview_superboost.gif</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/14/142788/2443144-preview_spinattack.gif</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/14/142788/2443143-preview_shipselect.gif</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/14/142788/2443142-preview_mainmenu.gif</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/14/142788/2443141-preview_courseedit.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/841243-f_zero___climax01.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/b/c/gfs_57144_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/mLno5Ma.png</banner1>
	<Notes>F-Zero Climax is the sixth installment in the F-Zero series and the third to be released for the Game Boy Advance. This is the first F-Zero game to have a built-in track editor without the need for an expansion or add-on. Custom tracks can be saved to one of thirty slots for future use and they can be exchanged with other players via link cable. If memory becomes full or link cable connection cannot be done, the game can generate a password for the track; when it is input on any F-Zero Climax cartridge, the password will generate the track instantly.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/650de421-db90-4402-a420-a2c1b8d3a707.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c083febc-561d-4bb5-96d1-b560146c76b4.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>Not Rated</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>