<Game>
	<Name>F-Zero - GP Legend (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:F-Zero GP Legend is the seventh installment of the F-Zero franchise, developed by Suzak Inc. and published by Nintendo. GP Legend includes characters and a story mode that recounts the events from the anime of the same name, which had 51 episodes and broadcast on Japanese and North American television networks from 2003 to 2004. The game contains five game modes, 34 total drivers, and numerous race tracks over four cups.Gameplay: and Game ModesGameplay:F-Zero GP Legend retains the gameplay mechanics of the F-Zero franchise. The player can maneuver, accelerate, brake, boost, and attack with their vehicle while racing on course.Game ModesStoryThe game's story mode features eight characters that recounts their account of events of the F-Zero GP Legend story. Each character has five total missions that the player must accomplish in order to advance the character's story. GP Legend's missions offers different challenges for the player to complete outside of finishing first in a race, such as following a machine to a destination or destroy a specific machine within a number of laps in a race.Grand PrixGrand Prix mode is F-Zero's classic race mode that pits the player against 29 other racers over five race courses in a cup (Platinum Cup has eight races). GP Legend features three difficulty levels (novice, standard, expert) and four cups (bronze, silver, gold, platinum). Platinum cup is unlocked once the player completes all cups on novice and standard difficulties.Expert difficulty presents the "second" versions of each track for bronze, silver, and gold cups. Each track under those three cups feature course changes that provide a tougher challenge.Time AttackTime Attack gives the player five laps to post the fastest lap and total times on a race course.TrainingTraining mode allows the player to simulate racing conditions by choosing the number of computer racers and their difficulty level over a desired number of laps on a race course.Zero TestZero Test mode challenges the player's skill by having the player complete a section of a race course with a designated machine under a targeted time. Players can earn a gold, silver, or bronze trophies if they complete the challenge under the trophy's target time.Race CoursesBronze CupMute City - Tradition ParkRed Canyon - JunctionMist Flow - Clip OvalLightning - VoluteFire Field - Blast TrackSilver CupSilence - Box RinkSand Ocean - CaterpillarMute City - Expansion ParkBig Blue - Slip HighwayMist Flow - Front &amp; BackGold CupPort Town - Forked RoadSilence - Honeycomb RinkWhite Land - FlowerFire Field - Wreckage CircuitRed Canyon - Peak JumpIllusion - Abyss Drop (appears in place of Red Canyon in standard and expert difficulties)Platinum CupMute City - Mute City IBig Blue - Big BlueSilence - SilencePort Town - Port Town IIRed Canyon - Red CanyonSand Ocean - Sand OceanWhite Land - White Land IIFire Field - Fire FieldChampionshipMute City - Championship (This track is only playable in Time Attack mode, and is unlocked when the player completes all cups on all difficulties.)</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/2004</releasedate>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>VQMOXF8O6vY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2331</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919100-f-zero-gp-legend</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/f-zero-gp-legend</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/f-zero-gp-legend/3030-13882/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1805108-box_fzgpl.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/uH6T2O7.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/llIlqgG.png</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59931-f-zero-gp-legend-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/312963-f-zero-gp-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/312964-f-zero-gp-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-go.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/312965-f-zero-gp-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-winner.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/312966-f-zero-gp-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-results.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/841244-f_zero___gp_legend02.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/15744/463915-bluefalcon.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/15744/460645-superpiranha.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7697/397613-gplegend_7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7697/397612-gplegend_6.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7697/397611-gplegend_5.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2331-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6kax1kd.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2331.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The F-Zero series grows with new racing circuits, an intense storyline, and multiplayer modes. F-Zero GP Legend lets you take control of one of eight characters, including Captain Falcon, racing star Rick Wheeler, the evil lord Black Shadow, and more. Guide your character through various Grand Prix cups, time trials, and challenges that span multiple planets. In addition to conquering single-player challenges, you can challenge up to three of your friends in multiplayer competitions.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/10ea1335-20d3-483f-a741-af882d67579c.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9aacfef-5934-470e-a5c6-2bba9e91cc32.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a6242440-4ddf-4c89-a665-60b3bb4d5486.png</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/50577f71-a386-4bc8-bdf1-d357377fcbdd.png</clearlogo2>
	<genre>Racing</genre>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>