<Game>
	<Name>F-Zero - Maximum Velocity (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Maximum Velocity was developed Nd Cube as a launch title for the Game Boy Advance. Maximum Velocity and the original F-Zero have much in common, because each were launch titles for their respective systems as a show piece for the systems capabilities. Maximum Velocity has a very similar graphical style as the original F-Zero using the Mode 7 to simulate 3D graphics. Maximum Velocity is the only F-Zero title to not feature Captain Falcon or other racers from the original F-Zero.Gameplay:The game's art style is very similar to the original F-ZeroThe gameplay in Maximum Velocity is extremely similar to all the previous F-Zero games, but is most similar to the original F-Zero. In Maximum Velocity there are a series of Grand Prixs each with five tracks to race. The game involves piloting futuristic racing crafts through tracks with the main objective being to come in first by the end of the race. As each lap is completed the player must be in at a high enough ranking in the race otherwise they are eliminated. With each set of grand prixs the tracks will gradually get harder. There's also a choice of difficulty to choose from for each grand prix, and this will change the skill of the computer opponents in a race. There are four different grand prixs in the game- Pawn Series, Knight Series, Bishop Series and Queen Series.There was also a multiplayer component to Maximum Velocity. It is up to four other players with a Game Boy link cable, and there the option of using either a multi card option or single card option. There are more features when using a multi card play, and can play an entire series of tracks against other players. Whereas with the single card play it was limited to only one track to race on.VehiclesThere are four vehicles to choose from at the very start of Maximum Velocity, and there are six unlockable vehicles. The four available vehicles are:Hot VioletFireballJ.B. CrystalWind WalkerThe six other vehicles that are unlockable upong winning challenges areSly JokerSting RaySilver ThunderFalcon MK-IIFighting CometJet VermilionEach car has its own specific statistics usually involved with speed, handling and boost power. The statistics affect each race greatly, and the player would have to find and option they are most comfortable with.Cheat: Access Password ScreenAt the machine selection screen in grand prix mode, press L, R, Start, R, L, Select. Cheat: Access Password ScreenTo view the game demo, press the select button at the title screen.Cheat: Unlock Jet VermilionCreate a new file with the name "T&amp;T" (without quotes) and select it. Select Grand Prix and on the F-Zero selection screen, enter the following code to access the password menu: "L, R, Start, R, L, Select". Enter the following password to unlock:Cheat: Master Difficulty LevelIf you win the Pawn series, Bishop series, or Knight series on the Expert difficulty level.  If you beat one of these series in Grand Prix Mode while on the Expert difficulty level, the Master difficulty level will unlock for whatever series you beat it with.Cheat: Master Difficulty LevelDirty Joker - Clear Pawn, Knight and Bishop series with Standard Class difficulty. The Stingray - Clear Pawn, Knight and Bishop series with Expert Class difficulty. Silver Thunder - Clear Queen series with Expert Class difficulty. Falcon Mk.II - Clear any one series with Master Class difficulty. Fighting Comet - Clear Pawn, Knight, Bishop and Queen series with Master Class difficulty. Cheat: Master Difficulty LevelFirst, unlock every other craft and the Championship Circuit. Once you've done that, complete every series with every machine in Master class OR by completing the championship 255 times.Cheat: Master Difficulty LevelBeat Pawn, Knight, Bishop all on expert with any car. After that you will unlock a new series called Queen.Cheat: Master Difficulty LevelPlay a vs. game with another GBA, but with only one game pak.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/6/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>JVU7E-GdUpE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2332</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/468549-f-zero-maximum-velocity</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/f-zero-maximum-velocity</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/f-zero-maximum-velocity/3030-46/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2332-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2332-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/cg2Udjj.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/209847-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102005-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102008-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102009-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-screenshot-selecting.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102006-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-machine.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102007-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-pole.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102002-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-screenshot-there.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102011-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-screenshot-do-not.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102001-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-screenshot-since.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102003-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-screenshot-if-you.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/102004-f-zero-maximum-velocity-game-boy-advance-screenshot-if-you.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2332-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2332-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CoAaBLh.png</banner1>
	<banner2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/2332-g2.jpg</banner2>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2332.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>All galactic speed limits are about to be broken! F-Zero® Maximum Velocity has arrived, and the future of racing has never looked so sweet. Brand-new vehicles and Game Boy Advance original tracks await, so whether you're a Super NES® veteran or a race rookies, you'll need some practice laps. And even if you do master the Grand Prix circuit, you'll still have to beat your friends to the finish line. That's right, race fans--with the Game Boy Advance Game Link® cable you can take on up to three rival racers, so put the pedal to the metal and get busy boosting, bumping and jumping your way to intergalactic glory!</Notes>
	<banner3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/501b8843-f45a-4ff5-8ddb-764613320096.jpg</banner3>
	<banner4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/79a5b06d-0c8b-48d7-8050-e66b97fc6345.jpg</banner4>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5dd7bf7d-6f37-4f7e-80ac-bf161bdbd424.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4cda5911-7dce-45a4-b4a4-15bbfe93d773.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c192fea2-b821-4430-9f1f-427aaa056d00.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>