<Game>
	<Name>F-Zero - Falcon Densetsu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The F-Zero series grows with new racing circuits, an intense storyline, and multiplayer modes. F-Zero GP Legend lets you take control of one of eight characters, including Captain Falcon, racing star Rick Wheeler, the evil lord Black Shadow, and more. Guide your character through various Grand Prix cups, time trials, and challenges that span multiple planets. In addition to conquering single-player challenges, you can challenge up to three of your friends in multiplayer competitions.Cheat: Easy Gold Cup on Zero Test Class B Test 04WARNING: Do NOT attempt this glitch if you have already attainted a gold cup on this test. This glitch will reset your best time to 16''00. There is a nasty (or helpful, depending on your perspective of view) bug in Zero Test Class B Test 04 that will allow anyone to instantly get a Gold Cup. When you hit the jump plate, turn LEFT and land on the piece of land that has a green recovery zone (basically you jump and return to the starting point).  Now continue driving for a while, the game should congratulate you on getting the first place instead of letting the timer go on until you hit the finish line. Also, your time on the screen will be set to 0'00''00.  When you return to the screen where you can select different tests, you will be awarded a Gold Cup, but your time is reset to 16''00. Cheat: Easy Gold Cup on Zero Test Class B Test 04When you start there is a jump at front of you, take it and turn left hard to cut the loop and then if you turned hard enough(bit over 90 degrees left) you should land where the recovery zone(the green zone) ends, now take the jump that should be in front of you, (if you did everything as it should be done) and land a bit before the finish line, (dont jump over it because it screws the trick) you know if it worked if you cross finish line and nothing happens, keep driving and you finish in somewhere right part of track. This is much like the glitch in class B test 04 this also resets your best time to a different time: 11,50 and gets you the gold cupCheat: Hidden TracksThere are 2 ''hidden'' tracks in the game, and unlocking thme is all up to chance. Play Gold Cup on Standard difficulty in Grand Prix mode, when you you reach the last race (race #5), you have a chance of getting either an Illusion track or a Red Canyon track, with the latter appearing more frequently. Play through Grand Prix a few times and you will acquire both tracks. Likewise, play Gold Cup on Expert difficulty in Grand Prix mode a few times and you should acquire the version II (more difficult version) of both tracks. Cheat: The DemosWhen at the main screen (the screen where the F-Zero Logo appears), press R shoulder buttons to watch the in game demos.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Suzak</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>VQMOXF8O6vY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2331</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919100-f-zero-gp-legend</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2331-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2331-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/d/c/gfs_52901_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/0/c/gfs_52901_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/b/c/gfs_52901_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/4/e/gfs_53821_1_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/6/9/gfs_55643_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2331-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/2331-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2331.png</clearlogo1>
</game>