<Game>
	<Name>F1 2002 (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>The Teams and DriversThe game features all 25 drivers and 11 teams that took part in the 2002 season.   Scuderia Ferrari  Marlboro:  Micheal Schumacher - GermanyRubens Barrichello - Brazil West Mclaren Mercedes: David Coulthard  - ScotlandKimi Raikkonen - Finland BMW Williams F1:   Ralf Schumacher - GermanyJaun Pablo Montoya - Colombia  Sauber Petronas:  Felipe Massa - BrazilNick Heidfeld - Germany    DHL Jordan Honda:  Giancarlo Fisichella  - ItalyTakuma Sato  - Japan BAR Honda:  Jacques Villeneuve  - CanadaOlivier Panis - France Renault F1 Team:   Jarno Trulli - Italy Jenson Button - England  Jaguar Racing:  Eddie Irvine - EnglandPedro de la Rosa - Spain Orange Arrows:  Heinz-Harald Frentzen  - Germany   Enrique Bernoldi  - Brazil  Minardi Asiatech:  Alex Yoong - MalaysiaMark Webber - Australia Panasonic Toyota Racing :  Mika Salo - Finland  Allan McNish - Scotland   The Circuits The game featured all 17 tracks from the 2002 racing calender, with the option of varying number of laps upto the real life amount.    Australian Grand Prix - Melbourne - 58 Laps Malaysian Grand Prix - Sepang - 56 Laps Brazilian Grand Prix - Interlagos - 71 Laps San Marino Grand Prix - Imola - 62 Laps Spanish Grand Prix - Catalunya - 65 Laps Austrian Grand Prix - A1-Ring - 69 Laps Monaco Grand Prix - Monaco - 78 Laps Canadian Grand Prix - Circuit Gilles Villeneuve - 70 Laps European Grand Prix - N&#252;rburgring - 62 Laps  British Grand Prix - Silverstone - 60 Laps French Grand Prix - Magny-Cours - 70 Laps German Grand Prix - Hockenheimring - 60 Laps Hungarian Grand Prix - Hungaroring - 70 Laps Belgian Grand Prix - Spa-Francorchamps - 44 Laps Italian Grand Prix - Monza - 53 Laps United States Grand Prix - Indianapolis - 73 Laps Japanese Grand Prix - Suzuka - 53 Laps</plot>
	<releasedate>7/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>FeL8SVR_fcM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22628</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/583419-f1-2002</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/f1-2002</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/f1-2002/3030-11485/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22628-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/149917-f1-2002-gamecube-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/149918-f1-2002-gamecube-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/22628-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36756-f1-2002-windows-screenshot-brakes-i-forgot-to-brake.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36758-f1-2002-windows-screenshot-grid-girl-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36760-f1-2002-windows-screenshot-grid-girl-2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36762-f1-2002-windows-screenshot-bonus-car.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36763-f1-2002-windows-screenshot-williams-cockpit.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36764-f1-2002-windows-screenshot-ferrari-cockpit.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36765-f1-2002-windows-screenshot-yes-green-light.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/36766-f1-2002-windows-screenshot-3d-pit-crew-but-no-tobacco-and-alcohol.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/404022-f1-2002-xbox-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>