<Game>
	<Name>Fairly OddParents!, The - Shadow Showdown (USA)</Name>
	<plot>An unbelievable phenomenon is rattling kids all across Dimmsdale--there's no TV reception! When prevented from watching the season finale of Crash Nebula, Timmy and his Fairy Godparents embark on a journey that they soon find goes beyond simple TV static. An evil force plans to take over the world, and now Timmy must use wishes to unmask the evil force known only as The Shadow. New wish inventions include the Suit Spray, Repair-o-Tron, Pogo Stick of Justice, and more.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/920629.htmlCheat: Access Level 7Select Password on the main menu and enter the following password to enter LEvel 7Cheat: Access Level 7Select Password on the main menu and type in one of the following passwords.Codes from level 1 not included as Level 1 (Emergency) is a tutorial.Cheat: Access Level 7THe following are all on Easy mode.Cheat: Access Level 7Select password on the main menu and type in one of the following easy mode passwords for Level 3Cheat: Access Level 7a Door is any door you go through by pressing the control pad UP causing Timmy to appear in a different area without disappearing in a puff of smoke.Cheat: Access Level 7Select Password on the main menu and enter one of the following Easy mode cheats.Cheat: Access Level 7A Door is any door entered by pressing the control pad UP that relocates Timmy without a puff of smoke.Cheat: Access Level 7Select Password on the main menu and enter one of the Easy Mode passwords below.Cheat: Access Level 7A Door is any door accessed by pressing the Control Pad UP that relocates Timmy Turner to a diffrent area without a puff of smoke, triggering a password change.Cheat: Access Level 7Select Password on the main menu and enter one of the following easy mode passwords.Cheat: Access Level 7A Door is any door opened by pressing Control Pad UP that relocates Timmy to another area without a puff of smoke, triggering a password changeCheat: Access Level 7Enter the following at the password screen:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3421</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920629-the-fairly-oddparents-shadow-showdown</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-fairly-oddparents-shadow-showdown/3030-21265/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3421-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3421-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/2/a/gfs_56604_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/f/a/gfs_56604_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/4/a/gfs_56604_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/5/a/gfs_56604_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/e/a/gfs_56604_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3421-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3421.png</clearlogo1>
</game>