<Game>
	<Name>FIFA Soccer 2004 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>FIFA Football 2004 (also known as FIFA Soccer 2004 and commonly abbreviated to FIFA 04) is a video game developed by EA Canada and published by Electronic Arts based around the game of football (soccer). It was released in October 2003 with the tagline "Create Brilliance". FIFA Football 2004 is the eleventh game in the     FIFA Series and the eighth to be in     3D. While not adding much to the engine used in FIFA Football 2003 (except some fluidity), the biggest inclusion were secondary divisions, which allowed the player to take lower ranked teams into the top leagues and European matches. Gameplay had a new feature dubbed Off the ball, which required the player to control two players at the same time to execute some plays. The online mode was boasted as the main feature. Another key feature was the Football Fusion, which allowed owners of both FIFA 2004 and TCM 2004 to actually play games from the management sim'. The title sequence was filmed in St James' Park, the home of Newcastle United, with the opening song being Kings of Leon's European hit "Red Morning Light". The cover featured     Alessandro Del Piero in     Juventus colours,     Thierry Henry wearing his     Arsenal shirt and     Ronaldinho dressed in     Brazil's kit.The teams with names in italic appear in the game with their licensed kits.    Leagues The game covers some of the world major club football leagues including:    Rest of World  GBA exclusive team.   Game features Groundbreaking Gameplay: FIFA 2004 offers a fine-tuned game engine, and new animations dramatically enhance the smoothness in player movement through organic motion. Off the Ball Control: Take command of players not in possession of the ball. Call in tackles, jostle for space, lose your marker, and send players on runs at the touch of a button. Expanded Database and Controls: Enjoy richer depth to team AI, attributes, tactics, playing styles, and individual player personalities. Be the Ultimate Player Manager: Be your own player manager with FIFA's deep Career Mode. Build your franchise and guide your club to the Championship by making calculated front-office decisions. In-game Management: Prove your tactical genius on the fly, by making adjustments mid-game and calling plays in real time via D-pad. Immersive Environments: More than 300 new crowd chants at an ever-growing list of officially licensed stadiums help put you in the best seat in the house. Play With The Best: More than 500 official licenses, including 18 leagues, 500 teams and 10,000 players are available. EA SPORTS Bio: Memory card based tracking/rating system recognizes and rewards gamers for playing multiple EA SPORTS titles.    Game Soundtrack FIFA Football 2004 features a wide variety of world music on its sound track, using the EA Sports Trax feature. The songs included are as follows: 1 - Dandy Warhols - We Used to Be Friends   2 - Junior Senior - Rhythm Bandits  3 - Cassius - Under Influence  4 - Outlandish - Aicha (Mintman Remix)  5 - Kasabian - LS7 (JFL Remix)  6 - Cooper Temple Clause - Promises Promises   7 - Kane - Rain Down on Me (Tiesto Remix)  8 - Suburbia - Always  9 - Kings of Leon - Red Morning Light  10 - Tribalistas - Ja Sei Namorar  11 - Radiohead - Myxomatosis  12 - Stone Roses - Fools Gold  13 - Caesars - Jerk It Out  14 - Wir Sind Helden - Guten Tag  15 - Timo Maas - Unite  16 - Tosca - Gute Loune  17 - Soffet - Gamushara Deko Boko Dai Race!?   19 - Lost Prophets - Burn Burn  20 - Babamania - Wanna Rock   21 - DJ Sensei- Musica Grande  22 - The Ravonettes - That Great Love Sound  23 - Goldfrapp - Train  24 - Cafe Tacuba - EO (El Sonidero)   25 - Cabas - Juancho  26 - Zeca Pagodinho - Deixa a Vida Me Levar   27 - Asian Dub Foundation - Rise To the Challenge  28 - Paul Van Dyk - Nothing But You  29 - Seamonator - Japanese Title  30 - The Individuals - Take a Ride  31 - The Jam - Town Called Malice   32 - Underworld - Two Months Off  33 - Clones - Crazy Boys  34 - Dawholeenchilada - Espiral      Reviews Reviews of the game were mostly positive. Official U.S. PlayStation Magazine awarded the game 5/5 whilst Official UK Playstation Magazine scored the game 8/10.</plot>
	<releasedate>4/11/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3423</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589751-fifa-soccer-2004</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/fifa-soccer-2004</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fifa-soccer-2004/3030-9214/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3423-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3423-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463756-fifa-soccer-2004-game-boy-advance-screenshot-language-selection.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463757-fifa-soccer-2004-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463758-fifa-soccer-2004-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463759-fifa-soccer-2004-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choosing-a-team.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463760-fifa-soccer-2004-game-boy-advance-screenshot-selecting-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463761-fifa-soccer-2004-game-boy-advance-screenshot-tactics-formation.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463762-fifa-soccer-2004-game-boy-advance-screenshot-controls.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463763-fifa-soccer-2004-game-boy-advance-screenshot-players-enter.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463764-fifa-soccer-2004-game-boy-advance-screenshot-kick-off.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463765-fifa-soccer-2004-game-boy-advance-screenshot-throw-in.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3423-g.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>FIFA Soccer kicks its game up a few notches with new installment, FIFA Soccer 2004. This year's action features more advanced levels of player detail and responsiveness. Play as one of the best players from 16 leagues and 350 teams, from Europe's super leagues to the Americas. Plus, a new Career Mode gives you the chance to take a team from the lower divisions, battle through ranks, sign new players, and turn them into champions. With immersive atmospheres, total realism with the world's premier clubs, and improved gameplay, FIFA Soccer 2004 looks to reach the goals of soccer fans.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e05fde06-b4a4-4efd-a675-00aa0d39232e.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3632ad9d-934c-47c3-9324-606bcc829b3a.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/af9cd9ef-cc28-49f0-9d9a-7fad7992178e.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>EA Sports</Publisher>
</game>