<Game>
	<Name>FIFA Soccer 2005 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>Fifa Socccer 2005 holds the distinction of being the very last  PlayStation title released in the United States. Soundtrack  Air  Surfing on a Rocket  France  Brothers  Dieci Cento Mille  Italy  Debi Nova  One Rhythm (Da Yard Riddim Mix)  Costa Rica  Emma Warren  She Wants You Back  England  Faithless  No Roots  England  Ferry Corsten  Rock Your Body, Rock  Netherlands  Flogging Molly  To Youth (My Sweet Roisin Dubh)  Ireland  Franz Ferdinand  Tell Her Tonight  Scotland  Future Funk Squad  Sorcerary  England  Gusanito  Vive La Vida  Spain  Head Automatica  Brooklyn is Burning  United States  Inverga   Num Kebra  Eu Perdi Voce  Brazil  Ivete Sangalo  Sorte Grande  Brazil  INXS  What You Need (Coldcut Force Mix 13 Edit)* Australia  Jose  A Necessidade  France  Los Amigos Invisibles  Esto Es Lo Que Hay (Reggaeton Remix)  Venezuela  Mala Rodriguez  Jugadoras, Jugadores  Spain  Manana  Miss Evening  Switzerland  Marcelo D2  Profissao MC  Brazil  Miss J  Follow Me  Denmark  Morrissey  Irish Blood, English Heart  England  Nachlader  An die Wand  Germany  New Order  Blue Monday* England  Clorofila of Nortec Collective  Almada  Mexico  Oomph!  Augen Auf!  Germany  Paul Oakenfold  EA SPORTS Football Theme  England  Sandro Bit  Ciao Sono Io  Italy  Sarah McLachlan  World on Fire/Junkie XL Remix  Canada  Scissor Sisters  Take Your Mama  United States  Seeed  Release  Germany  Sneak Attack Tigers  The End of All Good  Scotland  Sober  Cientos de Preguntas  Spain  Soul'dOut  1,000,000 Monsters Attack  Japan  The Sounds  Seven Days a Week  Sweden  The Soundtrack of our Lives  Karmageddon  Sweden  The Streets  Fit But You Know It  England  Wayne Marshall  Hot In The Club  Jamaica  Zion y Lennox  Ahora  Puerto Rico  </plot>
	<releasedate>12/10/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3424</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920613-fifa-soccer-2005</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/fifa-soccer-2005</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fifa-soccer-2005/3030-18564/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3424-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3424-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104244-fifa-soccer-2005-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104243-fifa-soccer-2005-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104237-fifa-soccer-2005-game-boy-advance-screenshot-challenges.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104245-fifa-soccer-2005-game-boy-advance-screenshot-season.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104246-fifa-soccer-2005-game-boy-advance-screenshot-tactics.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104247-fifa-soccer-2005-game-boy-advance-screenshot-kick-off.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104248-fifa-soccer-2005-game-boy-advance-screenshot-having-the-ball.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104249-fifa-soccer-2005-game-boy-advance-screenshot-he-is-through.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104250-fifa-soccer-2005-game-boy-advance-screenshot-could-be-a-good.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104238-fifa-soccer-2005-game-boy-advance-screenshot-goal-celebration.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3424-g.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Released only a few months after Euro 2004, FIFA 2005 brings several features to the franchise, such as the return of a player creation tool, where a player can be created from scratch from customizing the face (while it's not possible to define the texture like in previous EA Sports games such as NHL 2000, the player can customize the facial features such as shape of the eyes or the cheeks, in a way similar to RPGs such as Neverwinter Nights), accessories and playing abilities. It's also possible to create all kinds of competitions. The Career mode was also extended, allowing now up to 15 seasons, and giving the player the chance to turn the tide of a simulated match anytime. This mode is a "light" managerial mode, where the player not only plays, but also signs new players and increase the clubs abilities in trainers, medical staff and other club staff).</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/39eafc17-0c70-4ca7-84b2-4ad2a73aff56.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/51e9a37c-9baa-445b-88d6-1332e65b07a4.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>