<Game>
	<Name>FIFA Soccer 07 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:England Premiership Considered by many to be the last FIFA game to be truly "arcade". Undoubtedly, however, this was the FIFA to play the fastest, control the easiest and feature the heaviest use of the skill stick, while it's successor slowed the game down by reportedly 40% and put a heavier emphasis on passing. This was also the first, and last FIFA to make managerial mode tiered, requiring the player to manage lowly clubs, building a reputation, and slowly moving up to the cream of the crop, so to speak.  Game Modes   Manager Mode- Manager Mode allows you to take on the role of manager and lead your club to victory in the league. This is the main single player mode of the game though it can also be played with multiple people.  List of teams on PS2, Xbox and PC:English PremiershipArsenalAston VillaBlackburnBoltonCharltonChelseaEvertonFulhamLiverpoolMan CityMan UnitedMiddlesboroughNewcastlePortsmouthReading CitySheffield UnitedTottenhamWatfordWest HamWigan England ChampionshipBarnsleyBirminghamBurnleyCardiffColchesterCoventry CityCrystal PalaceDerby CountyHull CityIpswich TownLeeds UnitedLeicesterLuton TownNorwichPlymouth ArgylePreston North EndQueens Park RangersSheffield WednesdayShouthend UnitedSouthamptonStoke CitySunderlandWest Bromwich AlbionWolverhampton Wanderers England League 1BournemouthBlackpoolBradford CityBrentfordBrighton &amp; Hove AlbionBristol CityCarlisle UnitedCheltenham TownChesterfieldCrewe AlexandraDoncaster RoversGillinghamHuddersfield TownLeyton OrientMillwallNorthampton TownNottingham ForrestOldhamPort ValeRotherham UnitedScunthorpeSwanseaTranmere RoversYeovil Town England League 2Accrington StanleyBarnetBoston UnitedBristol RoversBuryChester CityExeterGrimsby TownHartlepool UnitedHereford UnitedLincolnMacclesfieldMansfield Town townMK DonsNotts CountyPeterboroughRochdaleShrewsbury TownStockport CountySwindonTorquayWalsallWrexhamWycome Wanderers Italy Serie AAC MilanAscoliAtlantaCagliariCataniaChievoEmpoliFiorentinaInter MilanLazioLivornoMessinaPalermoParmaRegginaRomaSampdoriaSienaTorinaUdinese Italy Serie BAlbinoleffiArezzoBariBolognaBresciaCesenaCrotoneFrosinoneGenoaJuventus LecceMantovaModenaNapoliPescaraPiacenzaRiminiSpeziaTrevisoTriestinaHellas VeronaVicenza Spain Primera DivisionAthletic BilbaoAthletico MadridBarcelonaCelta VigoDeportivo la CorunaEspanyolGetafeGimnasticLevanteMallorcaOsasunaRacing SatanterReal BetisReal MadridReal SociedadRecreativoSevillaValenciaVillarrealZaragoza Spain SegundaAlcoronAthletico Madrid (B)Celta Vigo (B)CobenaFuenlabradaLanzaroteLeganesLugoMaritimaOurensePajara PlayasPontevedraPuertollanoRacing FerrolRacing Satanter (B TEAM)RayoSS ReyesTalaveraTorrelavegaUniversidad Las Palmas Turkey S&#252;per LigAnkaragucuAnkarasporAntalayasporBesiktasBurasporDenizlisporEricy&#233;ssporFenerbahceGalatasarayGaziantepsporGenclerbirligiKayseriesporKonyasporManisasporRizesporSakaryasporSivassporTrabonzonspor South Korea K-LeagueBusanChonbukChunnamDeajuDaejeonGwangjuIncheonJejuKyungnamPohangSeongnamSeoulSuwonUlsan Austria BundesligaAltachGrazer AKMattersburgPaschingRapid WienSalzburgSturmSV RiedTirolWien Belgium Jupiler LeagueAnderlechtAntwerpBeverenBruggeBrusselsCercle BruggeCharleroiExcelsiorGentLierseLokerenMons - BergenRacing GenkRoeselareSint TruidenStandard de LiegeWesterloZulte Waregem Brazil CampeonatoAtl&#233;tico ParanaenseBotafogoCorinthiansCruzeiroFigueirenseFlamengoFluminenseFortalezaGoi&#225;sGr&#234;mioInternacionalJuventudePalmeirasParan&#225;Ponte PretaSanta CruzSantosS&#227;o CaetanoS&#227;o PauloVasco da Gama Denmark SuperLigaenAalborgBrondbyEsbjergHorsensKobenhavnMidtjyllandNordsjaellandOdenseRandersSilkeborgVejleViborg France Ligue 1AuxerreBordeauxLe MansLensLilleLorientLyonMarseilleMonacoNanceNantesNicePSGRennesSaint EtienneSedanSochauxToulouseTroyesValenciennes France Ligue 2AjaccioAmiensBastiaCaenChateaurouxCreteilDijonGrenoble FootGueugnonGuingampIstresLe HavreLibourneMetzMontpellierNiortReimsStade BrestoisStrasbourgTours Germany BundesligaAachenArminia BielefeildBayer LaverkusenBayern MunchenBochumBorussia DortmundBorussia MonchengladbakCottbusFrankfurtHannover 96Hertha BSCHSVMainz 05NurnbergSchalke 04StuttgartWeder BremenWolfsburg Germany Bundesliga 21860 MunchenAugsburgBraunschweigBurghausenCarl Zeiss JenaErzgebirgeFC KaiserslauternFC KolnFreiburgGreuther FurthHasna RostockKarlsruheKoblenzMSV DuisburgOffenbachPaderbornRSW EssenUnterhaching Holland EredivisieAdo den HaagAjaxAz alkmaarExcelsiorFC GroningenFC TwenteFC UltrechtFeyenoordHeerenveenHeraclesNACNECPSV EindhovenRKC WaalwijkRoda JCSparta RotterdamVitesseWillem II Mexico PrimeraAmericaAtlanteAtlasAzul CruzGuadalajaraJaguares ChiapesMonarcasMonterreyNecaxaPachucaQueretaroSan LuisSantos LagunaTiburonesTigresTolucaUAGUNAM Poland EkstraklasaArkaBelchatowCracoviaGornik LecznaGornik ZabrzeGroclinKoronaLechLegiaLodzOdra Wodzislaw SlaskiPogonWidzewWisla KrakowWisla PlockZaglebie Portugal Liga BwinAcademicaAvesBeira MarBelenenseBenficaBoa VistaEstrela AmadoraFC PortoMaritmoNacionalNavalPacos FerreiraSetubalSporting BragaSporting LisbonUniao Leiria Scotland Premier LeagueAberdeenCelticDundeeDunfermlineFalkirkHeartsHibernianInverness Caledonian ThistleKilmarnockMotherwellRangersSt Mirren Sweden AllsvenskanAIKDjurgardenElfsborgGaisGefleGoteborgHackenHalmstadHammarbyHelsingborgKalmarMalmoOrgryteOster Swiss Super LeagueAarauBSC Young BoysFC BaselFC ThunGrasshoppersLuzernSchaffhausenSionSt GallenZurich  USA MLSChicago FireChivasColorado RapidsColumbus CrewDallasDC UnitedHouston DynamoKansas CityLA GalaxyNew England RevolutionNY Red BullsReal Salt Lake Special TeamsClassic XIWorld XIMLS Allstars Xbox 360 leagues and teamsThe Xbox 360 version only has 6 leagues: LeaguesEngland PremiershipItaly Serie ASpain PrimeraFrance Ligue 1Germany BundesligaMexico Primera Special TeamsJuventusClassic XIWorld XI   Soundtrack      Artist                                                                                                 Song                                                                                Country    Ang&#233;lique Kidjo  Wele Wele Benin  Belasco Chloroform UK  Bersuit Vergarabat O Vas a Misa&#8230; Argentina  Bitman &amp; Roban Get On The Floor Chile  Blasted Mechanism Blasted Empire Portugal  Boy Kill Boy Civil Sin UK  caBas La Cadena de Oro Colombia  Carlos Jean Get Down Spain  d.o.c.h.! Was in der Zertung Steht Germany  Elefant Uh-oh Hello USA  Epik High Fly Korea  Fertig, los! Sie ist in mich verliebt Germany  Infadels Can&#8217;t Get Enough (Mekon Remix) UK  Keane Nothing In My Way UK  Malibu Stacy Los Angeles Belgium  Mellowdrone Oh My USA  Mobile New York Minute Canada  Morning Runner Gone Up In Flames UK  Muse Supermassive Black Hole UK  Nightmare Of You Dear Scene, I Wish I Were Deaf USA  Outlandish Kom Igen Denmark  Paul Oakenfold Beatiful Goal UK  Persephone's Bees Muzika Dlya Fil'ma USA/Russia  Plastilina Mosh  Peligroso Pop Mexico  Polysics Tei! Tei! Tei! Japan  The Prototypes Kaleidoscope UK  Ralph Myerz and The Jack Herren Band Deepest Red Norway  Seu Jorge Tive Raz&#227;o Brazil  Shiny Toy Guns You Are The One USA  Stijn Gasoline &amp; Matches Belgium  Suferosa  Royal Uniform Norway  Tahiti 80 Big Day France  The Feeling Sewn UK  The Pinker Tones TMCr Grand Finale Spain  The Sheer Understand Holland  The Young Punx You've Got To&#8230; UK  Tigarah Girl Fight Japan  Trash Inc. Punk Rock Chick Lebanon  Us3 Kick This UK  Young Love Discotech USA</plot>
	<releasedate>3/10/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts</Developer>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>DLSKpd0jzCg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>28148</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929312-fifa-soccer-06</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fifa-soccer-07/3030-37/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/28148-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/5/2/67852_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5234/1655203-87100227_3.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5234/1655202-87100220_3.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5234/1655201-85063128_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5234/1655200-84736199_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5234/1655199-84736185_3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5234/1655198-84730442_3.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5234/1655197-84730436_3.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5234/1655196-84181454_3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5234/1655195-84181450_3.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5234/1655194-83291666_3.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/28148.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>FIFA 07 throws you into the rollercoaster ride of a football season. Employ real world tactics, make realistic decisions, and think like a player in order to win matches.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/091dc686-2522-4e95-97c5-3351fcb1c0e8.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/47c05d5e-546d-40fc-9b70-1bca130d7aa4.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>EA Sports</Publisher>
</game>