<Game>
	<Name>FIFA Soccer 06 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>Game Modes:Road to FIFA World Cup:Pick Your Favorite National Team and start from beginning to end qualify and playing in the World Cup.Choose the teams you face in qualify rounds.Following your ranking in real time.Manage Your Team with substitutions, team formations, and other various tactics.Various unlockable items and teams are available by collecting 'Road Points' during games.Create Tournament:Pick one or several teams and compete in a group, knock out or pure knockout tournament.Control one or several teams in a single tournament.Practice Mode:Practice a certain type of play (free kick, penalty, corner) until its perfected.Set various numbers of players to practice odd-man chances or hone your defensive skills.Online PlayCompete against others either using PSN or Xbox Live online services.Compete in either Ranked or Unranked matches.Meet other FIFA fans and players in the Lobby, you can chat and set up matches.Check the Leaderboards to see what place in the world you stand.NEW features to the gameThere is a budget in manager mode.        Manual set pieces.    Online play.   tricks.  Soundtrack    Artist                                               Song                                                                                                                                                               Country 3D Voz  Fiesta Spain     AK4711  Rock Germany     ATHENA   Tam Zamani Simdi  Turkey     Bloc Party  Helicopter UK     Blues Brother Castro  Flirt Netherlands     boTECOeletro   Coco Nutz Mass   Brazil      Boy   Same Old Song   Canada      Carlinhos Brown &amp; DJ Dero   Nabika   Brazil/Argentina      Damian "Jr. Gong" Marley   Welcome To Jamrock   Jamaica     Dogs   London Bridge  UK    Doves   Black and White Town  UK    Duels   Potential Futures  UK    Embrace  Ashes UK    Hard-Fi   Gotta Reason  UK    Jamiroquai   Feels Just Like it Should  UK    Kaos   Now and Forever  Germany    Kinky  Coqueta Mexico    K'naan   Soobax   Somalia     KYO   Contact   France     LCD Soundsystem   Daft Punk Is Playing At My House   UK     Linea 77   Inno All'Odio   Italy     Mando Diao   God Knows   Sweden     maNga   Bir Kadin Cizeceksin   Turkey     Marcelinho da Lua   Tranq&#252;ilo   Brazil     Nine Black Alps   Cosmopolitan  UK    Oasis  Lyla UK    Paul Oakenfold   Beautiful Goal  UK    R&#246;yksopp   Follow My Ruin   Norway     Selasee  Run  Ghana     SoShy   The Way I   France     Subsonica   Corpo a Corpo   Italy     Teddybears Sthlm   Cobrastyle   Sweden     The Departure   Be My Enemy  UK    The Film   Can You Touch Me   France     The Gift   11.33   Portugal     The Gipsys   La Discoteca   France     The Rakes   Strasbourg  UK    Vitalic   My Friend Dario  France    Yerba Buena   Cityzen Citysoy   USA   </plot>
	<releasedate>11/10/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts</Developer>
	<rating>8.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>DLSKpd0jzCg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>25925</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929312-fifa-soccer-06</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fifa-soccer-06/3030-9171/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/25925-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/5/2/67852_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5892/272468-928333_20051108_screen004.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5892/272465-928333_20051005_screen001.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5892/272463-928333_20051108_screen003.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5892/272460-928333_20051004_screen002.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5892/272458-928333_20051004_screen001.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/9/f/gfs_68989_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/4/f/gfs_68989_1_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/f/f/gfs_68989_1_3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/e/f/gfs_68989_1_4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/9/2/gfs_69490_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/25925.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>EA Sports takes players back to the field with FIFA SOCCER 06 for the Game Boy Advance. Featuring nearly ever soccer team in existence and hundred of players, plus tweaks in game play and several new additions. Gamers will first notice the slight changes in controlling their teams. The passing and dribbling controls have been fine-tuned, allowing gamers to control nearly every aspect of the game. Each player has a strength rating that comes into effect when passing, as does the amount of weight players put behind the kick. A new shooting method, called the Optimized Shot Meter, requires more control and attention, as well. All of these realistic details make gamers feel like they're actually in the game and in control of everything. Manager mode now requires players to keep their club's budgets and handle purchases. Players have to decide how much to spend on staff, recruiting, stadium expenses, and other items. Then gamers have to decide if they want to sign with a sponsor to bring in extra income. All of this adds up to create a game that requires managers to really manage their team. FIFA SOCCER 06 contains all of the modes that made the previous FIFA SOCCER games great, including season, tournament, shoot-out, and verses modes. Soccer fans will enjoy playing against all of today's best soccer clubs throughout the season as they recruit, train, and guide their team to victory in FIFA SOCCER 06.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>DLSKpd0jzCg</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1cba03a0-28d8-4e77-8784-12f5da5b20bd.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fb254573-4b5a-422f-a511-7bfa07de5b45.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>