<Game>
	<Name>FightBox (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>PremiseThe TV show and subsequently the videogame where designed to try and replace Robot Wars which was lost to a rival channel. Contestants design their humanoid fighters and sit in pods to control them virtually. In the game, players are tasked with completing a number of rounds which can be against AI fighters from the series or other players in  split-screen multiplayer and then a final round which is a boss fight of sorts against one of the shows "Sentients" which were the supposedly the strongest fighters.  Gameplay:The game suffered from terrible design and as such the controls were a total disaster. Whilst the challenges were reasonably well designed and a good representation of the TV show, the controls let the experience down. You controlled your fighter in a similar way to many other third person games, face buttons being attacks or jumps and sticks for movement. The game was slow and unresponsive at the best of times.   The SentientsVesuvius The Sentients were the shows boss fighters or Robot Wars' "House Robots" in other words. Six fighters who had apparently become self aware and no longer needed their contestants to fight.   Vesuvius was the largest and most powerful.  </plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>BBC Multimedia</Developer>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>25930</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919548-fightbox</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fightbox/3030-18703/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/25930-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/25930-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/5/9/gfs_52600_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/8/9/gfs_52600_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/3/9/gfs_52600_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/2/9/gfs_52600_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/c/4/gfs_52600_2_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>An interactive fighting game that allows players to design, create, and train their own humanoid warriors, FightBox is essentially a game show utility that allows players to compete in a BBC television show of the same name. It was created exclusively for the British videogame market and is not available anywhere else. FightBox is the tournament for the new millennium. Artificial Warriors pit their strengths against each other in a bid to be the champion of FightBox. Created from the elements, the Warriors' Components are assembled, forged and moulded to create a being that will attempt to win the FightBox contest and the ultimate prize of immortality.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/18f2232b-6b1a-4833-95ae-ba769e9380dd.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/39855a8a-e686-4cf3-bae0-028924f769fb.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>BBC Multimedia</Publisher>
</game>