<Game>
	<Name>Final Fantasy I & II - Dawn of Souls (USA, Australia)</Name>
	<plot>The two titles that began the Final Fantasy Adventure return in an updated and improved portable form. Both titles feature updated visuals from their original NES origins and an improved translation of the story, filling in certain plot holes previously untold in other re-releases.  Both games have also been rebalanced to require less "grinding," and feature gameplay fixes such as party members re-targeting a new enemy if the one they currently are targeting dies.  Players are also able to save at any point outside of combat (including dungeons) and return upon loading.As with other Final Fantasy titles, players take on the role of a group of four heroes out to save the world. Using a vast collection of spells, weapons, and potions, players will travel across the kingdom fighting a range of evil characters and gaining experience to increase strength and magic abilities. Final Fantasy I allows players to build their party out of six possible classes, with varying spells and stats.  Final Fantasy II brings more characterization to the party members, and builds their stats exclusively by constant use in battle.Both games get additional content in this version.  Final Fantasy I features four "Soul of Chaos" dungeons, unlocked during the course of the plot.  These elemental dungeons are for high-level players, and feature a collection of bosses taken from later Final Fantasy games.  Final Fantasy II features an extra storyline known as the "Soul of Rebirth."  This mode is unlocked after completing the game and acts as an epilogue, featuring characters killed off in the main story.  Both games gain a Bestiary that tracks all the monsters the player has fought and their stats and weaknesses.Cheat: Do extra damage (FFII)To do extra damage, take any damage doing spell(such as Fire, Ice or Holy) Now go into a fight with only one monster and when your aiming your spell hit up to target every monster (even though there's just one) and attack. you do 1.5 more damage then if you attacked with it aimed only for the solo monster, because the way this damage is done is (Spell damage)x 1.5/ by the number of monstersCheat: Do extra damage (FFII)You still get the 1.5 boast to the spell, but it is divided by 1, thus not lowering its damage compared to if there were 2 monsters.Cheat: Do extra damage (FFII)Okay, once you get the toad spell to level 16, get on the snowship, then hold A and press the B button 22 times. The secret minigame will then pop up. Play the first one, but don't worry about winning. After you uncover all the toad squares, write the pattern down. Some look a lot alike, so be careful. After that, start a game and give up 31 times without playing. On the 32nd time, it will be the same exact pattern as the one you wrote down. You can now get the best sword and armor in the game.Cheat: New Game+Beat the game once and wait until it tells you to save after the credits.Cheat: New Game+Defeat the four fiends to unlock each new dungeon.  Each  features random maps, exclusive items, and bosses from other Final Fantasy Games.  I recommend beating all four fiends before venturing into the dungeons.Cheat: New Game+Beat Final Fantasy 1 and 2 once to unlock a sound test.Cheat: Final Fantasy 9 refrenceIn the Water shrine, go in it and find the area with all the dancers. Talk to alot of them and you should hear some say something about the Tatarus theater and the "I want to be your canary" play which is all Zidanes theater group in FF9!Cheat: Final Fantasy 9 refrenceIn Final Fantasy I when you visit Elfheim, press A on the left most tombstone behind the inn. It will say "Here lies Link." Link being the famous star of the Legend of Zelda series.Cheat: Final Fantasy 9 refrenceIn Final Fantasy II, directly South of Kashuan Keep is a forest, and within the forest is a small patch of grass. Walk over the grass to enter the hidden Chocobo's Forest, a large field of grass. If you find a Chocobo in it, you can ride it.Cheat: Final Fantasy 9 refrenceIn the whisperwind cove, on the floor where you must find a certain boy, there is one boy that says he wants a "Trance Kuja" doll.Cheat: FF1 Mini GameWhile on the ship, hold down A and keep tapping B. Soon, a sliding tile minigame will appear. The aim of the game is to put the numbered tiles in order from 1 to 15. If you do well, you gain items and money!Cheat: FF1 Mini GameSimply attack yourself one or two times, and your HP and/or stamina will be raised after almost every battle. Im REALLY early in the game and i already have over 1000 HP for each character, and it barely took me any time. As an added bonus, your weapon levels will also be raised.Cheat: FF1 Mini GameIn the jade passage in Final Fantasy II, there is a Magic seller behind the lowest level of the waterfall. Enter the waterfall by hugging the wall from the right of left, then when you stop, press the talk button.Cheat: FF1 Mini GameThis 2x2 piece of land is Northeast of the town of Pravoka. From Pravoka, head South to the mountains, then East until you see a dock, then from there, head North. The monsters you can find is a whole lot stronger then ordinary monsters around. Other then leveling up skills quickly, the equipments the monsters drop is the best you can get for quite a while; Winter Wolf drops the Ice Shield! Minotaur Zombie drops the Great Axe!Cheat: FF1 Mini GameIn Final Fantasy 2 go down from the first town to a peninsula and move around till a foe come out. There you fight very hard foes like Brains. You get major stat boosts if you survive. Great if you started a new file.Cheat: FF1 Mini GameAfter you've completed the main story, an additional option will appear at the Final Fantasy II main menu. Select Soul of Rebirth to begin a new journey...Cheat: FF1 Mini GameIn FF II there is a match-the-faces tile game that gives items and cash prizes.  When you are on the ice sled, hold A and keep pressing B to bring up the game.Cheat: FF1 Mini GameIn FF2, if you level up the Toad spell to lv16, the faces on the memory game change to toads.  Also, the prizes will change, yielding Genji equipment for many rankings, and a Masamune for a no-miss game.Cheat: This glitch will allow you to equip characters with normally-unusable weapons or armor and also generate and duplicate armor you already have (which can in turn be sold for endless amounts of Gil). To begin, enter the Configuration menu and change the cursor to Memory. From there, go to the Equip menu for a Warrior and select the slot you want to select equipment from. Next, place a unit next to the Warrior and select where the equipment will go to. Return to the Warrior's menu and the cursor should already be on the previously-selected slot. At this point, press L/R and X at the same time to switch to the recipient unit.Cheat: This can be done to give weapons to other characters that cannot wield these weapons, and the same for armor. More curiously, the glitch can be used to put weapons or armor in slots they are not meant to be in. This can either cause simple benefits (for example, equipping the Maximillian on the White Mage's head simply applies the boosts, though these boosts are much higher than normal for helms) or cause item transformations (such as making the Hammer turn into Knight's Armor).Cheat: Art Gallery allows you to view game art that you have unlocked.Bestiary give you information on monsters that you have defeated.Music Player allows you to play any BGM from the game.Time Chamber allows you to revisit floors of Labyrinth of Time that you have already beaten.Cheat: When you're on a boat, hold X and repeatedly tap Circle button (for the JP version, hold Circle and repeatedly tap X button). Then you should be able to play 15 Puzzle minigame.Cheat: Art Gallery allows you to view game art that you have unlocked.Bestiary give you information on monsters that you have defeated.Music Player allows you to play any BGM from the game.Soul of Rebirth adds additional gameplay.Cheat: When in the snow mobile, hold X and press O repeatedly (About 10 times) until a small card game appears where you match images. Match them quickly enough, with few errors, and you can win great prizes.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/11/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>6EWMtVWezSA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3422</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920240-final-fantasy-i-and-ii-dawn-of-souls</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/final-fantasy-i-ii-dawn-of-souls</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/final-fantasy-i-ii-dawn-of-souls/3030-17928/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1814642-box_ffdos.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/EMeijmv.jpg</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/44323-final-fantasy-i-ii-dawn-of-souls-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3422-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3422-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3422-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3422-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111199-final-fantasy-i-ii-dawn-of-souls-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111200-final-fantasy-i-ii-dawn-of-souls-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111201-final-fantasy-i-ii-dawn-of-souls-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111202-final-fantasy-i-ii-dawn-of-souls-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111203-final-fantasy-i-ii-dawn-of-souls-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111204-final-fantasy-i-ii-dawn-of-souls-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3422-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3422-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3422-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3422-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/j7vBbVg.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3422.png</clearlogo1>
</game>