<Game>
	<Name>Final Fantasy VI Advance (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This title are more than a simple port of the SNES classic  every aspect of the games has been reviewed and enhanced. Additionally, a host of brand-new elements has been seamlessly merged with the original game, providing unexpected surprises for longtime fans. With new dungeons, new job classes, and other exciting features, both old-school players and newcomers can enjoy this genre-defining FINAL FANTASY title in a portable format.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/930370.htmlCheat: Item DuplicationAt the end of the game, it is possible to duplication equipment en masse. Note that you must have this duplicated equipment on Terra. During the tiered, sequence battle at the end of the game, end each battle such that only Terra is alive. When the final battle starts, you'll find that there are two Terras in the fight. The equipment of this second Terra can be removed without affecting that of the first, although you must also unequip the first. (You only need to do the unequipping before the end: you can do this just before the battle's end if you know the final boss's HP and then estimate when he is near-dead and unequip then.)Cheat: Item DuplicationThis glitch can be used to reset a character's level in a given save file: however, note I say only "level". Only the character's level will reset, and all their other stats and anything about them - other than Level and EXP. - will be unaffected. This in turn makes it very possible to maximize a character's stats without intense optimization of Esper stat growth as you only need to continue leveling up. This is because leveling up is only based upon stat increments rather than pre-set statistics. Cheat: Item DuplicationTo begin this glitch, you must save and then quicksave your game. Return to the title screen and start a New Game and continue along it for a while. This length of time must be as long as it takes to recruit the character whose level you wish to reset on the originally-saved file, and you cannot save during this entire interval: thus, it is most practical to do this with early characters, such as Terra and Locke. Once the desired character joins the party, you now need to earn a Game Over. This will send you to the last time you saved (that is, the initial save), with the joined characters at the level they were at in the New Game file. However, only their level will be overwritten, making it possible to continue upgrading their level and further increasing their stats from the original stats pre-glitch.Cheat: Item DuplicationTo be able to use this glitch, Sabin must know the Blitz Mantra. You should have Sabin input the command sequence for Mantra and then, as soon as possible, have someone else Confuse him, preferably an ally for the sake of keeping the situation controlled. When Sabin does use his Blitz, it would, under most circumstances, be intended to heal the foe rather than the party because he is Confused; however, due to poor coding, it will actually deal damage to the foes: most importantly, if there is only one foe, for example, then 65,535 damage will be dealt (though it is shown as 9999). Otherwise, the damage calculation is as normal: Sabin's HP divided by the number of foes minus one, although the "one foe" instance causes a division by zero which forces maximum damage.Cheat: Item DuplicationThe famous glitch from the SNES version, revisited. This time, there's a new method to trigger it.Cheat: Item DuplicationStep 1: In battle, kill Cyan.Step 2: Revive Cyan.Step 3: Have Cyan use his Level 2 Bushido, "Sky," previously known as "Retort."Step 4: Cast "Imp" on Cyan.Step 5: Watch in awe as Cyan loses his mind and proceeds to attack continuously, uninterrupted, until every enemy is dead.Cheat: Item DuplicationThis glitch is the result of two smaller bugs involving "Imp" Status and being revived in combat; one that makes Cyan counter with physical attacks, rather than the "Sky" move, and another that makes Cyan counter any move performed by any character, not just a physical attack from the enemy to Cyan. As you can see, activating this glitch is done differently from the original SNES version of the game, but it results in the same thing: Cyan countering his own counterattack over and over again, until the battle is won.Cheat: Item DuplicationThis neat little trick from FF3US for the SNES still works, and with the addition of the new post-game hidden dungeon, it's even more useful!Cheat: Item DuplicationHave one of your teams in a multi-team dungeon move onto a Save Point. Next, switch over to one of your other teams. As long as you remain stationary with this second team, you can Save your game, or even better, use a Sleeping Bag or Tent for quick and easy healing!Cheat: Item DuplicationShould your party move out of place or if you want to save/use a tent again later on, simply switch back to the team on the save point, switch back to the party you wish to save with/heal, remain on one space, then do as you will.Cheat: Item DuplicationThis glitch will allow you to skip the obscenely-difficult battle against the Kaiser Dragon and in turn get the Diabolos Magicite it guards without battling. It would be prudent to save before this. You also should have the Sprint Shoes equipped and Auto-Dash in the Config menu on. First stand in front of the Kaiser Dragon. Then open the menu and quickly tap the D-Pad northward so as to attempt to get past him: if done correctly, you'll move into the Kaiser Dragon, and then can finish going through him to the Magicite.Cheat: Item DuplicationThis glitch also is abusable in a number of instances: this is merely the most functional of them. Note, however, that you must beat Kaiser to be able to reach the Soul Shrine or battle the Omega Weapon. You can use this glitch to go through walls and bypass tiles that trigger event battles to skip them.Cheat: Dragons DenDefeat the 8 Dragons in the World of Ruin. This dungeon is located at North-West of the world mapCheat: Dragons DenClear the Dragon's Den and beat the game. This secret dungeon is located on one of the small islands at North of Mobliz.Cheat: Dragons DenPerform the stated task in order to unlock a new option, which will then be available in the main menu, under "Extra".</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2007</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3465</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/930370-final-fantasy-vi-advance</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/final-fantasy-v-advance</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3465-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3465-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/78376-final-fantasy-v-advance-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3465-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3465-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3465-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3465-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3464-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3464-6.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3464-7.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3464-8.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263047-final-fantasy-v-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263048-final-fantasy-v-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-bartz.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3465-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3465-10.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3465-2.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3465-3.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3465-4.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3465-5.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3465-6.jpg</fanart7>
	<fanart8>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3465-7.jpg</fanart8>
	<fanart9>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3465-8.jpg</fanart9>
	<fanart10>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3465-9.jpg</fanart10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/1Q4WUj6.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3465.png</clearlogo1>
</game>