<Game>
	<Name>Final Fight One (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>A Port of the Super Nintendo version. With All three characters from the Original game: Cody, Guy and Mike Haggar. Besides having All three characters in the same game, what sets it apart from the SNES version, is the addition of the Industrial Area stage, and it's Boss fight with Rolento. Character art was also added into the game, which gave it a bigger story element, With profile shots of players and bosses talking to each other before a battle.This version also had link cable support, which gave you the option of 2 player co-operative play.Extras included, Color swapping, Extra lives, Stage select, rapid bunch and The Alpha versions of Guy and Cody as unlockable characters to play.FUN FACT:Damnd and Sodom Keep their names in this localization.Cheat: Unlock Alpha CodyTo play Cody with his alpha sprite, simply defeat 500 villains and he will become selectable.Cheat: Unlock Alpha CodyTo play as Guy with his alpha sprite, simply defeat 50 villains and Alpha Guy will become selectable.Cheat: Unlock Alpha CodyAs you progress through the game you will earn fighting points. These points go towards unlocking secrets in the game itself. If you want to unlock everything you will need 2000 points. Here is the order that the secrets are unlocked: Extra Lives: This allows you to have 9 lives. Stage Select: You can choose from level 1 to level 6. Color Change: Changes character color and unlocks [I]Alpha Guy[/I] and [I]Alpha Cody[/I]. Rapid Punch: Now you can simply hold the punch button and you will punch rapidly. Cheat: Gem/Points TrickTo get loads of gems, (and other items that gives you points only) just turn your back to the object that you are about to destroy, and quickly turn around and hit it. Take the first barrel on the second level for example. Walk forth to it, turn your back to it, quickly turn around and then hit it. This is an old trick that worked on the SNES version too. Points doesn't mean anything, but still, it's a trick.Cheat: Gem/Points TrickAs one may already know, with repeated pressing of the attack button, Guy or Cody hits with a few punches followed by a kick or uppercut to complete the combo and strike the enemy away. Most of the time, the enemy gets up and you have to wait for an open attack to repeat the process. Not anymore!!! I have found a way of killing an opponent with a chain unbreakable combo that takes all the energy from the enemy without retaliation.  Rapidly tap the attack button non-stop and as soon as the first 3 hits connect, quickly turn and face the other way so that the final uppercut or kick is performed in air, then turn back facing the opponent and repeat the process.  Since right after the opponent is hit, he/she takes time to recover and so by the time you turn round to punch again, there will just be enough time to carry on with the chain. This is best used for the boss. If done right, you can take out a Boss in under 20 seconds with no damage sustained to yourself.Cheat: Gem/Points Trick500 points- Start with nine lives. 800 points- Select any of six stages.  1300 points- Change the way that your character looks and unlock two extras. 2000 points- Aquire a rapid-punch move.Cheat: Gem/Points TrickIn the second ''subway'' level, if you jump on the first barrel and wait there for time to count down, you will be warped to the next section of the game</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Beat-Em-Up</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>8.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3425</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/471041-final-fight-one</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/final-fight-one/3030-29727/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3425-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3425-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3425-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3425-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3425-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3425-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/43718/1336015-finalfight_gba4.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/43718/1336014-finalfight_gba2.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/43718/1336012-final_fight_one_screenshot_001.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/43718/1336011-final_fight_one__2_.gif</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/43718/1336008-compare_gba.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/f/4/gfs_44164_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/p6Kt9ng.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3425.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Classic arcade action is unleased on the Game Boy Advance system in Final Fight One. There's trouble in Metro City. The members of the Mad Gear Gang have kidnapped the mayor's daughter Jessica and the clock is ticking. The mayor, an ex-street fighter himself, calls in the big guns to help, enlisting the iron fist team of Cody and Guy. Now, it's a race against time to scour the city, defeat an army of the Mad Gear Gang's minions, and rescue Jessica before it's too late!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab53f94e-c70c-42b8-b23f-a77d4fc3983a.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/39067d15-c9af-4fb6-ac4d-09e562ac947f.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/da935730-1281-40ea-aa9c-c918427f7f2a.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0f7b42e7-e938-4f87-95d8-6cdb84285377.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dc43fb68-b409-43a7-a73d-59d54251b0b8.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fb0d973e-25b7-487c-9f1b-f7f94434ab55.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a56d5e76-07b2-4032-b1a3-f26fd3d0e43a.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/040474f9-4a7d-477c-8e9a-c308a0048d34.jpg</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>