<Game>
	<Name>Final Fantasy Tactics Advance (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Story:A young boy named Marche (whose name is changeable at the start of the game) and his handicapped younger brother Doned move to a new town. When attending school he becomes friends with Ritz, a tomboy who dyes her hair pink, and Mewt, a boy who gets bullied a lot. Mewt buys a mysterious old book from a used bookstore and quickly takes it to Marche&#8217;s house. He has no idea that the book has magical powers and fulfills his wish that real life was more like video games (Final Fantasy in particular). After the day is over Marche goes to bed only to wake up in the magical world of Ivalice. He then sets off in search of his friends and to find a way home.Gameplay:The main hub world serves as the majority of time spend in Tactics Advance. In this world map you'll be able to accept missions, search for random treasure, and follow the story as you move on from different areas. Missions reward you with items, gil, and exp. You can take on missions in different pubs which range from regular, encounter, dispatch, and area. Regular missions are just normal battles in different areas, encounter missions are battles against a rival clan which can also be done on the map without going to the pub. Rival clans are presented by a character icon that can freely move about. They regularly peruse your icon in the map in order to engage in combat. Dispatch missions do not involve battle, the player must pick one member from their party and send them of for a certain amount of time. Area missions are mostly dispatch missions in which Marche's clan can liberate regions. The map opens up as you complete the main story, but it's mostly up to the player and how much time they invest in visiting every area on the map.Battle SystemTatics Advance uses turned based tactical battles that take place on a three dimensional isometric field. Game play mostly remains unchanged from the first Tactics except a few changes to jobs and other minor changes. The player has full control as to how they'll attack and defend their party members. The jobs system determines what kind of attacks they'll be able to do and how powerful the attack can be. The main way to play is to anticipate as to how your opponent will react. Don't go off and attack without a defensive stance, or else you'll lose more damage than usual.Different classes offer different ways to play. Having a mix of different classes is essential to winning. Use magic and physical attacks repeatedly during battles. Don't be to predictable or else you'll lose frequently. Use the grid to your advantage and place your party in smart areas that'll both protect them and get them close enough to do damage.The Law SystemThe biggest difference between Final Fantasy Tactics and Final Fantasy Tactics Advanced is the Law System. During combat, a judge will be present on the map. The Judge is neutral during battle and will only move out of possible harm and to retrieve fallen bodies during battle. Laws are set by judges, they're basically rules that accompany different battles. They change during each match and usually forbid the use of certain weapons, items, elemental spells, or status changes. If you break a law, you'll receive a yellow card as a warning and a red card as a final verdict. Once you get a red card, you'll be imprisoned for a certain amount of time but you can pay a bail fee to get your soldier out early. Judges can also be helpful as you gain Judge Points for using combos with allies or to summon a Totema. Judge Points are gained by killing an opponent. You can also nullify laws by using antilaw cards, This can only happen after Marche rescues Ezel Berbier. You can buy them from his shop. Antilaw cards range from White Law Card which impose new laws and Black Antilaw Cards which cancels out laws that are in effect.JagdsJagds are lawless areas that are encountered later on in the game. Judges aren't allowed to participate in battles, which means that there are no laws in each match. This also means that judges can't stop people from dying during combat. If you leave one of your party members KO'd after battle, they are permanently killed and will leave your party, Main party members like Montblanc can die in Jagds as well.Main CharactersThese are the important story characters:While Final Fantasy Tactics Advance does have a lot of main characters which are central to the plot in the beginning, a lot of the characters simply don't appear after the beginning until the very end of the game. It is also worth noting that Besides Marche and Montblanc, every other main character of the children is unplayable until the very end of the game and for most not until you actually beat the main story.Marche He is the hero of the story. You can actually change his name to whatever you want. He is a boy with a one track mind.MarcheDonedMarche&#8217;s younger brother. He is a sickly boy who is confined to a wheel chair but in the magical world of Ivalice he is completely healthy.DonedRitzA young girl who becomes Marche&#8217;s friend at school. She is headstrong, stubborn, and quite bossy but also loyal and protective of people being victimized. She is teased at school a lot because she dyes her hair pink because it's naturally white.RitzMewt A quiet boy who gets bullied a lot at school, him and his father have had a hard time getting over the death of his mother. Marche and Ritz come to his aid against bullies and become his friends. He is the one who finds the book that changes the world into Ivalice. He controls the world of Ivalice, it is his dream land. He is also a Prince in Ivalice.MewtMontblancA friendly moogle who helps Marche get his bearings in Ivalice. He is the leader of the Clan Marche joins.MontblancNonoNono is Montblanc's little brother. He runs a store out of an Airship. When his Airship is attacked you come to help him.NonoSharaA viera who is friends with Ritz. She has white hair and tries to make Ritz see that having white hair is a blessing.SharaEzel BerbierAn eccentric Nu Mou who finds ways around the Laws. He is the creator of Anti-Laws.Ezel BerbierBabus SwainIs an assistant of Prince Mewt. He only wants what's best for the prince.Babus SwainCidIs Mewt&#8217;s father. And in the magical land of Ivalice he is the Judge Master. He is also Prince Mewt&#8217;s protector.Judgemaster CidLlednar TwemIs the darker side of Mewt given an actual body. He takes over Cid&#8217;s position as Mewt's protector when Cid decides to leave the palace. He is seemingly invincible. His name is Mewt backward.Llednar TwemQueen RemediA reincarnation of Mewt&#8217;s dead mother.Queen RemediRacesThere are Five races that live in the world of Ivalice. And each race also has a special power called a Totema.HumansThey are the most plentiful of all the races. They are extremely versatile and very flexible when it comes to jobs. Their Totema is Mateus.Your typical human.MooglesThey are small, cute and friendly. This race also is quite intelligent and gifted. Their Totema is Framfrit.Cute little guys with funny Pom poms on there heads.Nu MouThey have very distinct canine features. The Nu Mou hold intelligence in high regard and thus really prefer to avoid physical confrontation. Their Totema is Ultima.Strange dog looking men with a Great affinity for magic.BangaaThey are a lizard like race that really enjoys physical combat. They hate to be called lizards. Their Totema is Adrammelech.Lizard men who live and love to fight.VieraThis is a race of swift female fighters, there are male Viera but they stay in Viera forest cities. They have rabbit like qualities. They tend to stay in their Woods but since they live a long time they do venture out in curiosity. Their Totema is Exodus.I thought Hugh Hefner owned the rights to the idea of Bunny women.Human ClassesSoldierSoldierA common fighting class.PaladinPaladinA holy knight who fights for the weak and helps team members.FighterFighterA stronger version of the Soldier that has more powerful attacks that sometimes inflict damage on the Fighter.ThiefThiefA nimble fingered pick pocket that specializes in stealing items from enemies.NinjaNinjaA very stealthy class that can wield two weapons.White MageWhite MageA healer type class.Black MageBlack MageA class that use black magic, which is elemental attacks.IllusionistIllusionistA magical class that has spells that hit all enemies.Blue MageBlue MageA class that learns monster skills by having them used on them.ArcherArcherA class that uses bows.HunterHunterA more skilled archer that can capture wild beasts.Moogle ClassesBlack MageBlack MageA class that uses Black magic.Time MageTime MageA magic user that is skilled in time manipulation.AnimistAnimistA friend of animals who calls them to help in battle.Mog KnightMog KnightA strong fighting class.GunnerGunnerA class that uses guns instead of bows.ThiefThiefA nimble fingered pick pocket.JugglerJugglerA class that like to throw items at the enemy to inflict status aliments along with damage.GadgeteerGadgeteerA class that depend on luck.Nu Mou ClassesWhite MageWhite MageA healer type class.Black MageBlack MageA class that uses Black magic.IllusionistIllusionistA magical class that has spells that hit all enemies.Time MageTime MageA magic user that is skilled in Time manipulation.AlchemistAlchemistThis class specializes in making items more effective.BeastmasterBeastmasterA class that can learn to control monsters.MorpherMorpherAre shape shifter who can take the form of monsters and use their abilities.SageSageA versatile class that can cast White and Black Magic.Bangaa ClassesWarriorWarriorIs a common fighting class for Bangaa.DragoonDragoonA spear fighting class.DefenderDefenderIs much like the Human Paladin class.GladiatorGladiatorAn upgraded version of the Warrior.White MonkWhite MonkA fighting class that can banish the Undead.BishopBishopThis is the only magic class available for the primarily physical attacking Bangaa.TemplarTemplarA class that is good at using Spears and knight swords.Viera ClassesWhite MageWhite MageA healer type class.FencerFencerA class that uses a light weight foil to attack.ElementalistElementalistThey harness the power of nature and use it to strike their enemies.Red MageRed MageA class that can use both White and Black Magic.SummonerSummonerThey have the power to summon spirits from long ago.ArcherArcherA class that uses bows.AssassinAssassinA class that teaches you deadly arts.SniperSniperThe best archer the world has ever seen.All the art work here does not belong to me it belongs to Creative Uncut. Here is a link to there wonderful art galleryhttp://www.creativeuncut.com/artffta.html</plot>
	<releasedate>8/9/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>_RI_mIFuSzc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2497</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/560436-final-fantasy-tactics-advance</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/final-fantasy-tactics-advance</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/final-fantasy-tactics-advance/3030-8721/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1814647-box_ffta.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/502Gm1m.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/25333-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59979-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-mine.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59980-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-great.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59981-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-look.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59982-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-just.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59983-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-not.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59984-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-deadly.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59985-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-status.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59986-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-abilities.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61558-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61559-final-fantasy-tactics-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2497-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2497-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/a8eNJwW.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2497.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>When Marche and his friends open an ancient magical tome, their small town is transformed into a fantasy-filled kingdom known as Ivalice. Now, Marche must take up the sword and master the arts of war if he has any hope of returning home. Guide Marche and his clan against countless foes in tactical combat and discover the wonders of Ivalice. How will you restore your town to normal...and do you even want to?</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>fL1Cjx7GbS8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4cc89503-533c-4e28-a1de-ba7581ad46d4.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cc116b59-0f60-4946-9160-6406fbfdc038.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3054015f-b32e-4394-a69e-980cadbe1db2.jpg</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Square Enix</Publisher>
</game>