<Game>
	<Name>Final Fire Pro Wrestling - Yume no Dantai Unei! (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Fire Pro Wrestling 2 is an Action game, developed and published by Spike,which was released in Japan in 2002.Cheat: All Wrestlers UnlockedAlright, just go into CAW.  Put this in as the name of the CAW: Nick Name: ALL Last Name (On the Left): WRESTLER First Name (On Right): CLEAR Exchange: Off Middle: Leave Blank Then, save the CAW.  After that, all wrestlers in the game should be unlocked.  After saving, you can then overwrite the CAW with another CAW if you wish and still have all the wrestlers unlocked.Cheat: All Wrestlers UnlockedTo unlock every wrestler in the Japanese version of Fire Pro 2, go to wrestler edit, and name entry, and put in the following information in katakana: NICKNAME: ki chi ji (small)yo u ji SHORT NAME: ka ra LONG NAME: a za bu ji (small)yu u ba n Hit start, and it will change the name of the wrestler and play a fanfare.  Make a new MoR game and save; voila, you have every hidden wrestler in the game.Cheat: Ironman Road - SpecialTo unlock the Special difficulty in Ironman Road, complete the Easy, Normal, and Hard difficulties in Ironman Road.Cheat: Ironman Road - SpecialIn manager of the ring mode pick WCW as your federation then sometime in your second year if your fed rank #1 you will unlock Rick Flair and he will be holding the Showman title.Cheat: Ironman Road - SpecialJust finish every step in training mode and you will unlock the trainerCheat: Ironman Road - SpecialTo unlock the following federations in MOR mode, you must place first at the end of the game.  Your federation's primary style at the end will decide which you unlock. Strong Style - New Japan Pro Wrestling Kings' Road - All Japan Pro Wrestling Stoic Style - Pride FC Showman Style - World Wrestling Entertainment Lucha Style - Triple A Hardcore Style - None Freestyle - None  Your federation's primary style can change if you use a different style often enough.Cheat: Ironman Road - SpecialTo unlock wrestlers for the US version, defeat them in their respective Ironman Road difficulties and complete the training mode to unlock the only non-Ironman Road wrestler.Cheat: Old Code MessageGo to the Edit Mode's Edit Wrestler Name Entry screen and enter the following: Nickname: ALL  Short Name: STYLE  Long Name: CLEAR  Exchange: OFF Middle: [] Then press start to go back to the Edit Wrestler screen and the name should now read: Noooo! It's Old CommandCheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn Manager of The Ring mode go to talent search and serch for Any for the style and for region pick AmericaCheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn manager of the ring mode, go to ''Talent Search''. Choose ''Strong'' for the fighting style and ''America'' for the region.Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyUnlock Dynamite Kid In manager of the ring mode, go to ''Talent Search''. Choose ''Showmen'' for the fighting style and ''Europe'' for the region.Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn manager of the ring mode, go to ''Talent Search''. Choose ''King Road'' for the fighting style and ''America'' for the region.Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn manager of the ring mode pick AJP as your federation then sometime in you third year you will unlock him. Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn Manager of The Ring mode go to talent search and then put in for style strong and for region pick America Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn Manager of The Ring mode go to talanet search mode then pick Lucha as the fighting style and pick Mexico for the region Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn manager of the ring mode, go to ''Talent Search''. Choose ''Strong'' for the fighting style and ''Japan'' for the region.Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn manager of the ring mode, go to ''Talent Search''. Choose ''Showmen'' for the fighting style and ''America'' for the region.Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn manager of the ring mode pick WCW as your federation then sometime in your second year if your fed is rank #1 you will unlock him.Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn manager of the ring mode, go to ''Talent Search''. Choose ''Stoic'' for the fighting style and ''Anywhere'' for the region.Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn manager of the ring mode, go to ''Talent Search''. Choose ''Stoic'' for the fighting style and ''Anywhere'' for the region.Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn manager of the ring mode, go to ''Talent Search''. Choose ''Strong'' for the fighting style and ''Europe'' for the region.Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn Manager of The Ring mode go to talanet search mode then pick Showman as the fighting style and pick America for the regionCheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn Manager of The Ring mode go to talanet search mode then pick Showman as the fighting style and pick Mexico for the regionCheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn manager of the ring mode, go to ''Talent Search''. Choose ''Lucha'' for the fighting style and ''Japan'' for the region.Cheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyPlay Manager Of The Ring for five years with Toryumon and if you are rank 1 overall sometime in your fifth year you will see a nurse screen and then when you look in your roster Ultimo Dragon will then be unlockCheat: Unlock D-Von and Bubba Ray DudleyIn Manager of The Ring mode go to talanet search and then pick Any as the fighting style and pick Europe for the region</plot>
	<releasedate>23/9/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Spike</Developer>
	<rating>7.6</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>14264</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/557186-fire-pro-wrestling-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/14264-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/1/3/16813_back.jpg</boxart2>
</game>