<Game>
	<Name>Fire Pro Wrestling A (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>In this second version of the Fire Pro series in the GBA over 200 wrestlers are available, with the usual CAW mode allowing to increase that number by 77. Along the Practice Dojo and the Exhibition match, the main mode is the Ironman road, where the initial roster of 10 wrestlers (11 once you finish training mode) is expanded as you beat your opponents one by one. Both Exhibition and Ironman Road feature match kinds such as Gruesome and Deathmatch (inside a electrified cage) with all assorted rule changes included. There's also the ability to play in a four-man Battle Royal.The CAW mode, one of the selling points of the original SNES titles, is as good as ever, allowing to create Wrestlers from scratch, personalizing them from how they look to how they fight, as well as trading them between federations.Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Note: Some knowledge of how to read Japanese is required to put this code in correctly.Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Go to Edit Mode, Edit Wrestler, and then Name Entry. Enter the followingCheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Nickname: (Katakana) Ha (dash located by Katakana N) Do Ko AShort Name: (Hiragana) WoLong Name: (Katakana) Ku Ri AExchange: ONMiddle: []Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)If entered correctly, a red star should appear under Tatsumi Fujinami along with everything that you unlock by completing the Hardcore style of Audience Mode unlocked. To save this so that it doesn't revert back to what it originaly was when you turn the game off, you start a new Audience Mode (any style) and save it. Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Note: Some knowledge of how to read Japanese is required to put this code in correctly.Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Go to Edit Mode, Edit Wrestler, and then Name Entry. Enter the followingCheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Nickname: (Katakana) Ru Cha (small Ya)Short Name: (Hiragana) WoLong Name: (Katakana) Ku Ri AExchange: ONMiddle: []Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)If entered correctly, a green star should appear under Tatsumi Fujinami along with everything that you unlock by completing the Lucha style of Audience Mode unlocked. To save this so that it doesn't revert back to what it originaly was when you turn the game off, you start a new Audience Mode (any style) and save it. Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Note: Some knowledge of how to read Japanese is required to put this code in correctly.Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Go to Edit Mode, Edit Wrestler, and then Name Entry. Enter the followingCheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Nickname: (Kanji)Select Kanji Select Hiragana OSelect character located in third row, fourth columnSelect Hiragana ToGo down 6 additional rows, select character in fourth columnShort Name: (Hiragana) WoLong Name: (Katakana) Ku Ri AExchange: ONMiddle: []Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)If entered correctly, a yellow star should appear under Tatsumi Fujinami along with everything that you unlock by completing the Royal Road style of Audience Mode unlocked. To save this so that it doesn't revert back to what it originaly was when you turn the game off, you start a new Audience Mode (any style) and save it. Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Note: Some knowledge of how to read Japanese is required to put this code in correctly.Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Go to Edit Mode, Edit Wrestler, and then Name Entry. Enter the followingCheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Nickname: (Katakana) Shi (small Yo) (dash located by Katakana N) Ma NShort Name: (Hiragana) WoLong Name: (Katakana) Ku Ri AExchange: ONMiddle: []Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)If entered correctly, a orange star should appear under Tatsumi Fujinami along with everything that you unlock by completing the Showman style of Audience Mode unlocked. To save this so that it doesn't revert back to what it originaly was when you turn the game off, you start a new Audience Mode (any style) and save it. Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Note: Some knowledge of how to read Japanese is required to put this code in correctly.Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Go to Edit Mode, Edit Wrestler, and then Name Entry. Enter the followingCheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Nickname: (Katakana) Su To I (Small Tsu) KuShort Name: (Hiragana) WoLong Name: (Katakana) Ku Ri AExchange: ONMiddle: []Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)If entered correctly, a white star should appear under Tatsumi Fujinami along with everything that you unlock by completing the Stoic style of Audience Mode unlocked. To save this so that it doesn't revert back to what it originaly was when you turn the game off, you start a new Audience Mode (any style) and save it. Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Note: Some knowledge of how to read Japanese is required to put this code in correctly.Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Go to Edit Mode, Edit Wrestler, and then Name Entry. Enter the followingCheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Nickname: (Katakana) Su To Ro N GuShort Name: (Hiragana) WoLong Name: (Katakana) Ku Ri AExchange: ONMiddle: []Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)If entered correctly, a dark blue star should appear under Tatsumi Fujinami along with everything that you unlock by completing the Strong style of Audience Mode unlocked. To save this so that it doesn't revert back to what it originaly was when you turn the game off, you start a new Audience Mode (any style) and save it. Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)In the Wrestler Edit menu choose to rename the default wrestler to the following:Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)(in hiragana) ZE N BU(in hiragana) WO(in katakana) KU RI ANote: Leave the bottom two options as they are (default)Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Press start to exit and you'll notice that the name changed to something entirely different. That means it worked.Cheat: Hardcore Style Audience Mode Completion (Japanese Version)Now to make this change permanent, go into Audience Mode and save.Cheat: Famous wrestlersGo to the Edit wrestler mode, and go to the Appearance setting. Move the cursor over to the Face section, then hold R and press right. The result is a wrestler with every face, many of them can't be found from the game otherwise (I've found the likes of Leatherface, The real Undertaker etc.)Cheat: Famous wrestlersGoto EDIT mode than NAME ENTRY and Enter this as follows Nick Name: ALL Last Name (On the Left): STYLE First Name (On Right): CLEAR Exchange: Off Middle: Leave Blank Now press start than hit B until you are out of the EDIT mode and on hte Main Menu. And here's how to store the code in hte system memory, cause by default it won't. Now go to Audience Mode than Start a new Game or Load a previous game. Now Press start than choose Save. Overwrite any data if your prompted. Now exit the mode. Now all the hiddens should be saved into the system memory.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/10/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>BAM! Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>3.1</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3430</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/471238-fire-pro-wrestling</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/fire-pro-wrestling-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fire-pro-wrestling-2/3030-7835/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3430-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3430-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178092-fire-pro-wrestling-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178093-fire-pro-wrestling-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-mode-selection.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178090-fire-pro-wrestling-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-caw-mode.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178091-fire-pro-wrestling-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-to-their.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178094-fire-pro-wrestling-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-exhibition.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178095-fire-pro-wrestling-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-cage.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178096-fire-pro-wrestling-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-preparing.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178097-fire-pro-wrestling-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-give-up.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178098-fire-pro-wrestling-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-rubbing-it.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178099-fire-pro-wrestling-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-gruesome.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Cac6sjq.png</banner1>
</game>