<Game>
	<Name>Fire Emblem - Rekka no Ken (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Marshall your forces and draw your steel--Fire Emblem has arrived.Fire Emblem combines strategy and role-playing in a story heavy on royal intrigue and backstabbing.As a military strategist, you must choose the best method of attack whether it is swooping from the sky with your Pegasus Knights or striking with a phalanx of armored juggernauts to crush the opposition.With dozens of soldiers, weapons, and magic spells at your service, Fire Emblem equips you with everything you need to dominate the battlefield.Cheat: View picture galleryGo to the sound test once you have unlocked it, then press R.  The screen for selecting songs will disappear.  Every time you press A, the picture will change-It should have all of the the still pictures of events that you have gotten, with several more in addition.  Press B or Start to exit.Cheat: Control Enemy UnitsPlace a Mine anywhere on the field. When an enemy unit walks onto it, while they are taking damage, reset your game. When you continue your game, it shows the enemy being damaged again, and then you can control your enemy units. Use this to make them discard all of their items, retreat, or attack units that you want to level up.  Note* Enemy units can only be controlled for one turn.Cheat: Control Enemy UnitsIf you wish to keep the effects of Nil's/Ninian's rings for more than one turn, have the affected character be rescued. This will allow you to keep the effect for another turn.Cheat: Control Enemy UnitsTo do this little nifty trick, first you must have an item such as a lockpick, or a healing item (Vulnerary or Elixer.) Okay, now the only thing you have to do is let an enemy thief steal your item, then just steal it back from him, and it will be completely usable at full. Cheat: Control Enemy UnitsExample: Lockpick 9/15 Usage, Enemy theif steals it, Your theif steals it back, it is now at full potential once again, and voilaCheat: Fire Emblem UnlockablesMany of these things can be unlocked by beating the game. Otherwise, it is as described.Cheat: Fire Emblem UnlockablesBeat the game once and in the Extra section,you will find Sound Test, Movie Gallery, and Tactician Rating.  You wont get all of the songs if you dont get 100% and play every side quest. Same thing for Movie Gallery, you must beat the all of the game once to see all the cutscenes. Tactician Rating rates you in four catergories on how well you did on the whole game.Cheat: Fire Emblem UnlockablesHector:Get an A support w/ either Florina, Farina, or Lyn before beating the game.Eliwood:Get an A support with either Ninian, Fiora, or Lyn before beating the game.Cheat: Fire Emblem UnlockablesUnlocking each gaiden stage, or side quest, must be done in the chapter of the same number (i.e. Lyn's chapter 7 gaiden must be unlocked by meeting the listed requirements in chapter 7). The only exception to this is Hector's gaiden 19xx, which has an additional requirement.Cheat: Sound Test: Random ModeIn the Sound Test, simply press select and you will go into Random Mode. By pressing left or right on the control-pad you can switch to a different song. Press either B or Select to return to the regular setting.Cheat: Different Game EndingsFire Emblem 7 actually has three different endings with changes in each. Here is how you obtain them:Cheat: Different Game EndingsEnding 1: The "default" ending. Complete one or fewer Kishuna chapters to obtain it.Ending 2: A hidden ending with minor changes to the final boss fight, such as a different death quote. Complete two Kishuna stages to obtain it.Ending 3: The hardest ending to recieve. It has major changes, including a different death quote from Nergal, new dialogue, and a new "Fin" picture at the end of the game with Nergal and his wife. Complete all three Kishuna chapters to obtain it.Cheat: Different Game Endings*Note: The "Kishuna" chapters are 19xx, 22x, and 32x.Cheat: Different Game EndingsSecret Shops are hidden on the maps and can only be found by a character with a Member's Card special item, which can be stolen from an enemy in chapter 19. These Secret Shops sell high-level weapons and even items to promote your characters. Chapter 19 - One is in the clearing between the two broken walls above the room with the two treasure chests in the upper left corner of the map, and the other is behind a wall in the lower-right corner. Chapter 21 - The empty room in the upper-left corner of the map. Chapter 23 - There are two versions of this map. If the boss is Linus, the shop will be on the right side of the map, on the island. Otherwise, it will be in the trees above the lone house slightly left of center. Chapter 29 - In the two-by-two square area left of the lone treasure chest at the bottom-left. You must use a warp staff to get there. Chapter 30 - In the very upper-right corner of the map, among the trees.Cheat: Different Game EndingsIn chapter 18x were there is a magic seal, have a thief steal it from the boss. The silver card will make the prices of items from shops cut in halve. NOTE: Make sure to steal the silver card before you break the magic barrier. You must be playing on Hard difficulty as well.Cheat: Different Game EndingsIn Hector's story, obtain Farina, Florina, and Fiora.  Then, use all of them on the field of battle.  Have two of them WAIT right next to an enemy (on your turn).  Use the third (most powerful out of those three is highly recommended) to attack that enemy.  In the battle sequence, you will see a really cool battle scene and you will do an automatic critical attack.  NOTE:  This will only work with these characters!</plot>
	<releasedate>3/11/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Fantasy</genre>
	<Developer>Intelligent Systems</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>n3OVfPf_1d4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3428</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/468480-fire-emblem</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/fire-emblem/3030-1520/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3428-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3428-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/12/120766/1879674-randomfewp.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/12/120766/1879671-feladies.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/7/9/gfs_44133_1_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/1/9/gfs_44133_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/0/9/gfs_44133_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/b/9/gfs_44133_1_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/6/9/gfs_44133_1_6.jpg</snapshot7>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3428-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3428-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3428-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3428-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3428-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3428-6.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3428-7.jpg</fanart7>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3428-g.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3428.png</clearlogo1>
</game>