<Game>
	<Name>Ford Racing 3 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ford Racing 3 is a racing game featuring a variety of Ford vehicles released between 1923 and 2004.GameplayThe beginning of a typical race, with successfully 'rev' boost.The sole focus of FR3 is on circuit racing, and unlocking the included vehicles and tracks; there is no plot or continuing campaign.The racing style in FR3 tends more towards arcade racing than simulation; drifting (in this case, effectively just skidding sideways) and collisions slow cars, drafting has no effect on speed and most tracks are unwinnable under constant maximum acceleration, but the game lacks even a cosmetic damage model or any car tuning or upgrades. Some race types also include a boost ability, and properly timing acceleration at the start of a race can provide an additional 'super start' boost. There is also no direct penalty for collisions or unsafe driving, and many obstacles on tracks have invisible walls that guide the player away from direct impacts. AI cars rubber-band towards the player on at least some levels of difficulty, mostly obviously when the player falls behind. The game includes two 'chase cam' views and a bumper cam, but no cockpit view, and does not permit the player to look around freely.As the player completes events and places highly, they are awarded points, which slowly upgrade their rank, in order: Rookie, Amateur, Semi Pro, Pro, Expert, Ford Legend. The game tracks several other statistics, including fastest lap for each vehicle class on each track, and longest jump, drift and wheel spin (the latter is measured in tenths of a second). These records are purely informational. The game displays the longest for each during individual races, but only saves the overall best.Racing EventsThe game includes eleven different races, most of which must be unlocked for free play by winning events involving them.Standard RaceTime AttackBoost: Standard Race with a maximum of two short-duration boosts per lapElimination: Beginning with six cars, the last two cars each lap are eliminated until only two remain, then the first across the line winsOvertake: The player must overtake a number of AI cars in convoys ahead in a time limit, with clean overtaking adding a time bonusDuel: The player races one car, then two, then three, each for one lap, with no pause between and increasing difficultyDrafting: The player must catch up to and follow AI cars driving in a convoy in a set time limitRacing Line: Boost with no limit on boosting but a requirement to drive closely to a suggested racing line to 'charge' boostsRelay: The player races one car at a time for three laps, drafting behind their next (temporarily AI-driven) car at the end of each lap to pass the 'baton'Driving Skills: The player must complete a single lap within a set time limit while driving cleanly between a minimum number of sets of cones on the track, with passes between cones adding to the time limitSeconds Out: The player must complete a single lap within a set time limit while driving over a minimum number of bonus pickups and avoiding negative pickupsAll race types are eventually available in free play, but are otherwise limited - Overtake, Duel, Drafting and Relay alter AI behaviour and so are never used in multi-race events, and Driving Skills and Seconds Out don't involve AI cars at all.Gameplay ModesQuick RaceThis starts a singleplayer Standard Race with no customisation, selecting randomly from the cars and tracks currently unlocked.Ford CompetitionFord Competition CupsA series of multi-race events, each unlocking further events, increasing in length and difficulty. Player and AI cars are awarded points for finishing position at the end of each race (10-6-4-2-1-0). The car with the most points at the end of the event wins; if the player places highly, they are awarded a Cup, and also unlock a bonus car for use in other modes. Collecting all Cups awards a Trophy.Competitions are unlocked from left to right, culminating in The GT WorldRace types are limited to Standard Races, Boost, Elimination and Racing Line, as all events have five AI cars; the majority of races are three laps (with exceptions - early races are limited to two laps, Oval races are 6 laps due to its short length, and the single Vintage event has single-lap races). Most events are themed by track or AI car selection; the player is free to choose any unlocked car from the relevant class, but cannot change it mid-event. The player can retire from an individual race at any time (scoring 0 points) or from an entire event (receiving no awards), or replay previously-completed events, but cannot replay or restart individual races within an event.CupDifficultyVehicle ClassEventsMovie Car ChasesEasyClassicMountain Drive - Race Lost Valley - Race Harbour Side - RaceOff Road RumblingsEasyOff RoadFishing Town (R) - Race Oil Refinery - Boost Voodoo Village - Race Logging Company - BoostA Classic CompetitionEasyClassicHarbour Side - Race City Highway - Elimination The Railroad - Race Logging Company (R) - BoostTruck TrialsEasyOff RoadColonial Grounds - Boost Fishing Town - Elimination White Sands - Race Logging Company - Racing LineSpecial Vehicles TeamMediumModernHarbour Side (R) - Elimination City Highway (R) - Boost The Railroad (R) - Racing Line Racetrack - Race Mountain Drive (R) - EliminationBattle of the CoupesMediumClassicRacetrack - Racing Line Summit Trails (R) - Race Harbour Side - Racing Line City Highway (R) - Race The Railroad - EliminationGlobal GearsMediumModernRacetrack - Boost Mountain Drive - Elimination Lost Valley - Boost Harbour Side (R) - Elimination City Highway - RaceFocus vs. GTMediumPerformanceThe Railroad (R) - Racing Line Summit Trails - Elimination Mountain Drive (R) - Racing Line Summit Trails (R) - Elimination Harbour Side (R) - RaceOriginal RacesHardVintageLost Valley (R) - Boost The Railroad (R) - Racing Line City Highway (R) - RaceAll races are one lap longDesign ConceptsHardPerformanceHarbour Side - Race City Highway - Racing Line The Railroad - Race Summit Trails (R) - Elimination Mountain Drive - Racing Line Racetrack - RaceRally vs. TrucksMediumOff RoadColonial Grounds (R) - Boost Oil Refinery (R) - Elimination Voodoo Village (R) - Boost Logging Company (R) - Racing Line White Sands (R) - RaceThe Stock Car CircuitHardPerformanceRacetrack - Race Oval - Race Racetrack - Race Oval - RaceSize MattersHardOff RoadColonial Grounds - Boost Fishing Town (R) - Racing Line Voodoo Village (R) - Elimination Oil Refinery - Race White Sands (R) - Elimination Logging Company - BoostThe GT WorldHardPerformanceSummit Trails - Race Mountain Drive - Race Lost Valley (R) - Race The Railroad - Race Summit Trails (R) - Race Harbour Side (R) - RaceAll AI cars are the Ford GT ConceptFord ChallengeChallenge TokensA series of pre-designed challenges, using a specific race type, car and event. Each can be played on three difficulties; winning on Easy rewards the vehicle used, winning on Medium awards the car paint options (if available) and winning on Hard awards the challenge's Token. Most challenges are locked at first, and unlocked as previous challenges are completed, with the player occasionally given an option on the order to unlock them. Collecting all four tokens for a particular group rewards the player with a Shield. Collecting all seven Shields awards a Trophy. If the player has collected both the Competition and Challenge Trophies, they are awarded the final Trophy (for 100% completion).Challenge ShieldsThunderbirds'55 ThunderbirdThe RailroadRacing Line'66 ThunderbirdLost Village - RTime Attack2002 Thunderbird ConvertibleLost VillageDrafting2003 Limited Edition ThunderbirdLost VillageStandard RaceMustangs'71 Mustang Mach IHarbour SideBoost'73 Mustang Mach ICity HighwayDuel1999 Mustang FR500City Highway - ROvertake2004 Mustang GT-R ConceptSummit TrailsDuelGenerations1931 Model A RoadsterMountain Drive - RBoost'49Harbour Side - RRelay'75 Torino SportThe RailroadTime Attack2005 Mustang GTLost Village - RSeconds OutConcepts1994 Powerstroke ConceptMountain DriveDuel2003 FR100 ConceptSummit TrailsDriving Skills1996 Indigo ConceptMountain Drive - RDrafting1992 Mustang Mach III ConceptSummit Trails - RRelayGT'66 Fairlane GTHarbour SideSeconds Out'73 XB Falcon GTThe Railroad - RRelay'68 Mustang GTSummit Trails - RDriving Skills'72 Ranchero GTCity HighwayOvertakeTrucks2002 Explorer Sport Trac XLTThe Fishing TownDuel2004 F-150 FX4Logging CompanyDrafting'48 F1White SandsRelay'56 F-100Colonial Grounds - REliminationSVT2000 Ford SVT Cobra RCity Highway - RTime Attack2002 SVT FocusSummit TrailsSeconds Out2002 SVT LightningMountain DriveDriving SkillsSVT Lightning ConceptThe RailroadOvertakeFord CollectionThis is the name for the freeplay mode. The player can choose between unlocked cars, race types and tracks and play them in singleplayer, but cannot unlock any further items in this mode.MultiplayerFR3 includes both split-screen, LAN and internet multiplayer options. Races can be played with any single vehicle class and track, from one to nine laps. Race types are limited to Standard Race, Boost, Elimination and Relay.Driver Details100% Completion TrophyThis is the location for records and statistics, as well as viewing collectibles - Ford Competition Cups, Ford Challenge Tokens and Shields, and Trophies.TracksFive track themes are provided, with two limited to Off Road vehicles. All tracks are circuits. Several provide 'shortcuts' of dubious use. Often, tracks within a theme take place on a single map, with barriers preventing access to the other tracks. WIth the exception of the Raceways theme, all tracks can be played in both forward and reverse directions.Pacific Drive (Off Road only)White Sands, Voodoo Village, Colonial GroundsArctic Breeze (Off Road only)Fishing TownFishing Town: A flat but winding track through a canyon, over and through rivers, and past a number of huts and wood buildingsLogging Company: An extremely uneven track through a forest, industrial buildings and past a harbourOil Refinery: A flat track through a refinery, constructed largely of straights and sharp cornersColonial RunHarbour SideHarbour Side: Rural streets through a seaside town of old mansions, past a lighthouse, completing the circuit via a highwayThe Railroad: Winding roads through farmland, even directly through a cornfield, occasionally alongside, over or under a railroad with moving train (the train itself is never an obstacle)Mountain Drive: Tree-lined country roads through a national park, along and over a lake and streamAsuka BattleSummit TrailsCity Highway: A night track largely on highways and interchanges, with skyscrapers occasionally visible in the distanceLost Village: A mix of paved and dirt roads, passing several Japanese sites including a large Buddha statue and construction areaSummit Trails: Fast roads up and down hills including a damaged snow shelter, highway cutting and a short dirt road portionRacewaysRacetrackOval: A short track with two parallel straights and titled corners, with high fences and grandstandsRacetrack: A sealed wide track featuring rumble strips, tire walls and sand traps, with several straights and tight bendsVehiclesModern carsThe game includes vehicles across Ford history, as far back as 1923 and up to its release. Cars have working suspension and brake lights, and partly-working headlights (a glare effect is shown, but nothing is lit), and most have visible interiors. Customisation is limited to paint, and only if the player has unlocked the paint option for each specific vehicle; some cars only have one design, and can't be repainted. Several cars have convertible models, with the roofs permanently lowered. The game does not include a cosmetic or functional damage model. Most cars have unique number plates.Vehicles are separated into various classes, and races can only include cars from a single class. Each vehicle is rated in four categories, with ratings from 1 to 8.VintageVintage car selection, showing the Model TOnly two Vintage vehicles are included, with a fifteen-year gap separating them from the next-oldest car. The single Competition event they are featured in is the shortest (totalling only three laps across its races), and they are used for a single Challenge event.YearModelSpeedHandlingAccel.WeightPlateColours1923Model T Sedan1412MOD-ELTBlack1931Model A Roadster1412 Silver, Tan, Maroon, BlueClassicYearModelSpeedHandlingAccel.WeightPlateColours1946Convertible453319 CONV45Black, Khaki, Red, Dark Green1949Ford Custom4533 Light Green, Blue, Red, Grey1949Coupe4533F 49Black1955Thunderbird523555 T BIRDBlue, Khaki, Dark Grey, Red1964Galaxie 5005235GAL AXIEBlue, White, Tan, Red1966Fairlane GT5335FAIRLANESilver, Black, Khaki, Blue1966Thunderbird5335T B1RD66White, Red, Blue, Yellow1968Mustang4445MUSCLEBlue, Tan, Light Blue, Cream1968Mustang GT544568 GTGreen1970Capri Mk I RS26005455RS26CAYellow, Green, Blue, Red1971Mustang Mach I5355A GENTRed1972Ranchero GT5336RANCHERORed/White, Yellow, Brown/Orange, White/Orange1973XB Falcon GT5345FALCON 73Green, Dark Blue, Yellow, Red1973Mustang Mach I5355S1XTYYellow1975Torino Sport5455351 V8RedModernYearModelSpeedHandlingAccel.WeightPlateColours1978Capri Mk III 3.055455C78APRIDark Blue/Red, Red/Red, Silver/Red, Red1994Powerstroke Concept5247 Yellow, Light Green, Teal, Red (note: DI TURBO DIESEL)1999Racing Puma4653PU99MABlue2000Ford SVT Cobra R5555COBRARed, Silver, Dark Grey, Blue2001Fortynine Concept5455(fortynine logo)Black, Maroon, Blue, Green2002Crown Victoria5535LX SPORTMaroon, Dark Blue, White, Black2002SVT Focus4653(focus logo)Blue, Black, Red, Silver2002SVT Lightning5337LIGHT 1Red, White, Blue, Dark Grey2002Thunderbird Convertible5554T BIRDWhite, Yellow, Light Blue, Black2003Falcon XR85554FALCON03Orange, Blue/Orange, Dark Blue, White/Orange2003Limited Edition Thunderbird5554LTD EDRed2004?SVT Lightning Concept5337LIGHTNINGBlue, Yellow, White, Beige2004Mondeo ST2205455ST22MNBlue, Dark Grey, Black, SilverPerformanceYearModelSpeedHandlingAccel.WeightPlateColours1971GT70 Concept6663GT70FDGrey1992Escort RS Cosworth6674ES92CRTDark Green, White, Blue, Black1992Mustang Mach III Concept6565MACH 3Green, Orange, Silver, Yellow1995GT90 Concept8384 Yellow, Black, White, Teal1996Indigo Concept7573 Red, Silver, Black, White1997Sierra RS5006685RS5TONWhite, Black, Silver, Red1999Mustang FR5007456(ford racing logo)Red, Black, White, Silver2001Focus FR2006754(ford racing logo)Orange/Yellow Flames, Yellow, Silver, Black/Purple Flames2002Taurus Stock Car8375 Various designs2003FR100 Concept6665FR100Grey2004Mustang GT-R Concept6665M GTR05Yellow2004?Ford GT Concept7673DETROITRed/White, Yellow/Black, Orange/Blue, White/Dark Blue2005Air Force Reserve Ford Focus6653 Air Force Reserve styling2005Mustang GT7565 Blue, White, Red, Dark GreyOff RoadYearModelSpeedHandlingAccel.WeightPlateColours1948F14226F1 1948Red, Black, Yellow, Dark Green1956F-100422646 F 100Orange, Teal, Blue, Brown1965F-1004326F 100Brown/White, Green/Cream, Red/White, Blue/Cream1973Escort RS20005445RS2KESBlue/Dark Blue, Red, White/Dark Blue, Teal1985RS2004663RS2TONWhite, Black, Orange, White/Dark Blue1998F-150 4X45336 Green, Grey, Brown, Dark Purple1999Focus Rally Car5554(ford racing logo)White/Blue, Blue/White2001EX Concept3542 White, Green, Grey, Blue2002Explorer Sport Trac XLT4445EXP 1Green, Dark Blue, Black, Beige2002Flareside F-350 XLT Sport4228F-350Khaki, Black, Purple, White2004F-150 FX45336F 150Yellow, Dark Grey, Black, Red </plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Destination Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>BiLLsbdwFRo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>25931</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929548-ford-racing-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/ford-racing-3_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ford-racing-3/3030-15536/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1801436-box_fordr3.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/354663-ford-racing-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/354664-ford-racing-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/354665-ford-racing-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-password-entry.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/354666-ford-racing-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-counting-down-to.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/354667-ford-racing-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-go.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742693-ford-racing-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-attempting-to-overtake.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742694-ford-racing-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-driving-through.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742695-ford-racing-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-taking-a-jump.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742696-ford-racing-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-overtake-into-first.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742697-ford-racing-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-won.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Experience the thrill of racing some of Ford's most prominent driving machines in the third edition of the Ford Racing series. From the ’55 Thunderbird, up to the latest concepts, Ford Racing 3 offers unparalleled access to the finest collection of automobiles in the world. Drive 20 Ford vehicles including the Fairlane GT, Focus Rally Car, Mustang FR500, RS200 and many more!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a511d978-8486-433b-96ed-e86882e49828.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/65db368b-9d5b-4aa5-8730-88d72fae4ff8.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Destination Software, Inc.</Publisher>
</game>