<Game>
	<Name>Freekstyle (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Picture flying through rugged terrain performing massive jumps at more than 70 mph, hitting a 40-foot jump at the ledge of a 200-foot cliff, and pulling off a backflip, a Tsunami, and a 360 all before you land. In Freekstyle, you can perform these tricks on nine different tracks. Choose from any of eight different riders with their own unique attitude and style, and then fly high in Circuit, Race, Freestyle, and Freeride game modes. If this sounds like your idea of a good time, then you're ready for the extreme lifestyle of motoX racing.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/917514.htmlCheat: CodesEnter the following at the code entry screen:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Destination Software</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>25932</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/917514-freekstyle</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/25932-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/5/6/gfs_52035_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/8/6/gfs_52035_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/3/6/gfs_52035_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/2/6/gfs_52035_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/4/6/gfs_52035_1_6.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Pir5Tkd.png</banner1>
	<Notes>You've been waiting for it and now it's here - FreekStyle - the ultmate go-for-broke freestyle motocross experience. EA SPORTS BIG brings you motoX like you've never seen it - pushing even the greatest riders to go full throttle while pulling the craziest tricks on awesome tracks. FreekStyle isn't just about being the fastest rider; it's about being absolutely fearless. Backflips, Tsunamis and Mulisha Airs - you can do it all against the world's craziest moto daredevils.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/756ac84e-6f54-40b8-ad10-1b8d59a94d7c.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/83327d1f-eb37-46ee-8f14-0eb1a3111b26.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Destination Software, Inc.</Publisher>
</game>