<Game>
	<Name>Gadget Racers (Europe) (En,Fr,De)</Name>
	<plot>Gear up and go! Grab your steering wheel and get ready for the race of your life! Equip your car with over 120 gadgets, including parts that help you soar above the competition or swim like a fish. Face challenging weather conditions, death-defying jumps, hairpin turns and more as you head for first place. Get ready to burn rubber with Gadget Racers!Cheat: Watch a demoEver wondered where the demo in this racing game went? Well here it is: When the game reaches the title screen and then it says ''Press start'', press B instead of start to see the demos, I think there are a total of 5 in all.Cheat: Honk Horn While DrivingWhile racing, press Up on the Control Pad to honk your vehicle's horn.Cheat: Honk Horn While Driving1st.You get the first medal by finishing all areas. 2nd.You get the second medal by collecting all body's. 3rd.You get the third medal by collecting all engines. 4th.You get the fourth and final medal by collecting all the parts.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/11/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Conspiracy Entertainment  Corp.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>19454</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/915173-gadget-racers</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/gadget-racers</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/gadget-racers/3030-15562/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/19454-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/9/7/14697_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61072-gadget-racers-game-boy-advance-screenshot-welcome-to-gadget.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61073-gadget-racers-game-boy-advance-screenshot-many-worlds-to-race.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61074-gadget-racers-game-boy-advance-screenshot-each-world-has-many.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61075-gadget-racers-game-boy-advance-screenshot-use-the-shops-in.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61076-gadget-racers-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-nice-top-of-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61077-gadget-racers-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-can-also-choose.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61078-gadget-racers-game-boy-advance-screenshot-there-are-many-kinds.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61079-gadget-racers-game-boy-advance-screenshot-some-tracks-allow.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/61080-gadget-racers-game-boy-advance-screenshot-tracks-come-in-many.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/644499-gadget-racers-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-track.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Sometime in the 1980s, the Japanese Choro-Q Racing toys made their way to U.S. shores. Renamed Penny Racers for the benefit of American sales, the wind-up cars were built to perform different tricks (wheelies and spins, mostly) when a penny was inserted into their chassis. The plastic racers are still very popular in Japan, inspiring a video game called CHORO-Q ADVANCE. The U.S. release of the game is called GADGET RACERS, and it's every bit as exciting as the toys that it's based on. Command any of 50 unique vehicles through 40 different courses of obstacles, tricks, and general mayhem. You can customize your racer to meet your specifications, using more than 130 different parts to soup things up upgrade your tires, brakes, steering, engines, and more. Adding to the excitement is the fact that you can get four players competing for glory via a link cable and for Game Boy Advance consoles. It's a mystery why the toys no longer roam the bedroom floors of American households, but maybe this awesome video game will create a resurgence.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/09be56a8-9986-41da-b73f-c9a7ae0f4e09.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f82040cc-7479-4831-a753-940f53984350.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Conspiracy Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>