<Game>
	<Name>Game Boy Wars Advance 1+2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>This Japanese-only game combines two games in one cartridge. The games included are Game Boy Wars Advance (known in the west as Advance Wars) and Game Boy Wars Advance 2 (known in the west as Advance Wars 2: Black Hole Rising.Cheat: If you would like to erase data, press L, Select, and right on the D-Pad immediately after turning the Gameboy Advance on. The delete data option will appear, and if you want to begin again, you can.Cheat: With this glitch you can edit Campaign and War Room maps. The changes are saved only in the in-game (during battle) save, not permanently in the cartridge. - Go to Field Training and play the Naval Forces mission. - Lose by letting Olaf destroy either your T-Copter or your Lander. - Go to the Design Maps, deploy an Orange Star unit and destroy it. - Your screen will be glitched now. You can go to a saved Campaign or War Room map and edit it. Don't forget to save the changed maps using the in-game save, not the Design Maps save. - To return to normal, just turn on/off the GBA.Cheat: To change certain icons in the main menu screen from their original color to a flashing gold, you must complete the condition listed next to them: Records: Complete all 20 war room maps, regardless of rank. Rank: Obtain the final rank, rank 1. Stats: Get both rank and records gold, and this'll turn gold too. Field Training: Get an A-Rank in all 14 training missions. Campaign: Complete the Advance Campaign, regardless of rank. War Room: Get an S-Rank in all 20 war room maps. Battle Maps: You have to unlock and buy every CO, and buy all the maps. Design Maps, Vs. Mode, and the Multiplayer menu cannot be turned gold. Note: The gold menus do nothing for you; they're just there for pride. Cheat: If you want to skip field training and get into the war campaign, map maker or etc., instead of winning every battle in field training, just go to the last one and beat it. It'll save time, and you can always go back to play it any time on the main menu.Cheat: To make the final mission a lot easier, allow Sturm to capture the Airport just north of the Orange Star base, and make sure you have Missiles in range of the Airport panel. Sturm will spend 22000 per turn building a Bomber that you can immediately destroy before use, making him much less of a threat.With Sturm wasting 22k per day making Bombers, his army is much weaker and easier to manage, no matter which allies you end up having in this battle.Cheat: Like in the first Advance Wars, you can erase your save data by holding L+Right+Select before turning the game on.Cheat: At the Design Maps/Map or CO screen, highlight Map and hold A + L + R. The screen will go blank, then the Nintendo map will appear.Cheat: To turn your menu icons from their regular colors into Sparkling Gold, do the tasks below for each icon. Cheat: To gain Neotanks , you have to capture a specific city in a specific map to get the lab map, and then beat a hidden mission. You have to do this in each country. Orange star  Flak Attack: City north of your HQ, within range of your units starting positions.  Secret Level: Test of Time  Blue Moon  Toy Box: South-Western most Neutral city, AKA: the one on the weird island.  Secret Level: Neotanks!?  Yellow Comet  Show Stopper: South-western most neutral city.  Secret Level: Sea of Hope  Green Earth  Sinking Feeling: Southernmost city on the western island  Secret Level: Danger X9 Cheat: To unlock the Gallery, beat the Campaign.  To unlock the all pictures, beat the Hard Campaign. The gallery is found in the Sound Room.Cheat: To unlock the soundtest, beat a normal campign with an any rank to purchase the soundtest. It costs 5000 points.Cheat: In campaign mode, if you are stuck on a level, just yield and the characters will give you hints on how to beat the level.Cheat: An easy way to get the Gold Multiplayer tab is start any map and then immediatley yield. Repeat this for all levels. With 3 &amp; 4 Player Maps, play as 2 or 3 people and yield for them all. It will count as a played and that much faster to get the Gold then playing them all.Cheat: Go to ''Design Mode'' and click on ''Map''. Then hold the L and R buttons while it's loading. Once you get there, you should see a map with three Japenese letters on it made out of mountains that spell out Nintendo.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/11/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/924948-game-boy-wars-advance-12</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/game-boy-wars-advance-12</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/game-boy-wars-advance-12/3030-45775/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82063/2613221-63904_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/0/4/63904_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/428783-game-boy-wars-advance-1-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/428784-game-boy-wars-advance-1-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-game.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82063/2613228-6905453046-gfs_5.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82063/2613227-2168729761-gfs_5.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82063/2613226-4069466422-gfs_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82063/2613225-8105855852-gfs_5.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82063/2613224-9882046056-gfs_5.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82063/2613223-6706416704-gfs_5.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/7/f/gfs_59847_2_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/a/f/gfs_59847_2_2.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>