<Game>
	<Name>Games Explosion! (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Games Explosion! is a compilation of 16 small games divided into 5 categories.1. Neon1. Neon Square - a Pong variant2. Sudoku - an adoption of the famous number puzzle3. Tic Tac Toe - an adoption of the classic pen and paper gameBoard1. Checkers - a variant of the classic board game4. Eliminate - a mastermind variantCyber1. Ice Jumper - isometric game where the player has to jump between platforms made of ice without falling off. The screen is constantly scrolling vertically 5. MC Rudolf - a simple platform game that scrolls vertically. The player has to jump between platforms to gain height6. Pizza Man - a Tapper variant where the player serves pizza to robots7. Warehouse Man - a sokoban variant featuring robotsZap1. Avoider - a Pang variant8. Music Pop - a music game where the player has to press the correct button when the notes reach an orange line9. Pipemaster - a Pipe Mania variant10. Space Shooter - a Space Invaders variantClub1. Blackjack - the classic card game11. Crazy Bowling - a simple bowling game that users different meters for aim, spin and power12. Darts - a simple dart game where a pointer is moving constantly and the player has to stop it at the right time</plot>
	<releasedate>20/8/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>1.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>24660</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/933932-games-explosion</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/games-explosion</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/24660-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/1/8/77718_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414964-games-explosion-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414967-games-explosion-game-boy-advance-screenshot-neon-square.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414965-games-explosion-game-boy-advance-screenshot-sudoku.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414966-games-explosion-game-boy-advance-screenshot-tic-tac-toe.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414968-games-explosion-game-boy-advance-screenshot-checkers.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414969-games-explosion-game-boy-advance-screenshot-eliminate.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414970-games-explosion-game-boy-advance-screenshot-ice-jumpers.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414971-games-explosion-game-boy-advance-screenshot-mc-rudolf.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414972-games-explosion-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pizza-man.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/414973-games-explosion-game-boy-advance-screenshot-warehouse-man.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>More games, more challenges, more fun for everyone with Games Explosion! Rack your brain, test your reflexes and jump into non-stop action with 16 entertaining games. Whether you're in the car, waiting for the bus or just taking a break, there's a game for everyone in the family.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e0b13285-d113-4100-a878-5e3abbdd501b.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/03258e85-7be8-4237-b5ec-0e78819f6de6.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>