<Game>
	<Name>Gekido Advance - Kintaro's Revenge (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>A year has passed since the epic battle that decided the fate of mankind and claimed the life of the beloved Angela. Dark omens once again tell of the return of an evil presence. Ushi is the last remaining master of the ancient art of Shin-Ken, and he calls upon Tetsuo, his disciple and adopted son, to investigate some strange happenings in a faraway farming village outside the city.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/552356.htmlCheat: Chapter Passwords (for Chapter 4 and 5)Chapter 4 with all Credits (8): SMART Chapter 5 with all Credits (9): YNUTSCheat: Chapter Passwords (for Chapter 4 and 5)Chapter One   - The Deathtoll Rises : Press Start Game d'oh! Chapter Two   - The Three Seals     : MIMMO Chapter Three - The Ancient Book    : HURRY Chapter Four  - Searching For Koji  : FLASH Chapter Five  - The Final Battle    : QUEENCheat: Chapter Passwords (for Chapter 4 and 5)These passwords work for the NA version of the game. Cheat: Chapter Passwords (for Chapter 4 and 5)This password is for the last levelCheat: Chapter Passwords (for Chapter 4 and 5)For unlimited energy you have to insert CRAZY in the password menu. You will get back to the title screen after that. Cheat: Chapter Passwords (for Chapter 4 and 5)Select Password from the title screen. When the password screen comes up, type in a code to either return to a stage or to generate an effect.  [Note: This code is for the U.S. version of the game and was found by another person. I take no credit for this, but it should be entered into Gamefaqs.]Cheat: Chapter Passwords (for Chapter 4 and 5)Enter the password screen and type in ''STARS''.  Tetsuo will now have Perma-speed</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Beat-Em-Up</genre>
	<Developer>Destination Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>taKr0iJpbSE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>19442</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/552356-gekido-advance-kintaros-revenge</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/gekido-advance-kintaros-revenge/3030-29649/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/221/1232327-gekido.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/5/1/5/16515_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/e/4/gfs_44795_2_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/3/4/gfs_44795_2_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/8/4/gfs_44795_2_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/9/4/gfs_44795_2_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/2/4/gfs_44795_2_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/17qRPYc.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>It's Time to Fight! A year has passed since the epic battle that decided the fate of mankind and claimed the life of the beloved Angela. Dark omens once again tell of the return of an evil presence. Ushi is the last remaining master of the ancient art of Shin-Ken, and he calls upon Tetsuo, his disciple and adopted son, to investigate some strange happenings in a faraway farming village outside the city.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/080534ee-e34b-4a84-a460-a7b7fd2f7f1d.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ca00e2b-5873-48ea-aa44-4ebad5f9149e.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/07ea308f-e5f2-490b-ad3b-3185d1074c78.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Zoo Digital Publishing</Publisher>
</game>