<Game>
	<Name>Golden Sun - The Lost Age (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>This traditional-style role-playing game continues the story of its predecessor,      Golden Sun, while expanding your abilities and allowing you to battle with up to eight players as you traverse seas, mountains, and skies in order to save the fantasy land of Weyard.Story The game picks up right after the events of the first Golden Sun. The Venus Lighthouse has just been lit and                Felix,               Jenna,              Sheba and Kraden set out to light the remaining Elemental Lighthouses, rendering the player's efforts in the first game to prevent exactly that from happening a gigantic waste of time. Their adventures take them across new lands where few have been before. On their journey they meet             Piers, a mysterious man from the equally mysterious Lemuria. They discover shocking truths about Weyard during their adventure. CombatFelix using the magical attack, Ragnarok! A classic turn-based combat system is used, but with some interesting quirks. At the beginning of every turn you choose the moves for all your characters and then the battle begins. Every character used in battle has magical abilities called Psynergy. HP and PP are the health and magic counters used. As your characters fight they level up and gain new Psynergy. As you progress through the game you acquire creatures called Djinn, which alter stats and can change the "class" of party members, and be used to cull powerful summons.  Characters  Felix     Felix is a Venus (earth) Adept was previously an enigmatic character thought to be an antagonist. Jenna is a Mars (fire) Adept who also made a brief appearance in the first game. Sheba, a Jupiter (wind) Adept, made a much smaller cameo in the first game but is a core character in this one, though despite the promise of a pivotal sub-plot (thought to have "fallen from the moon") little of her back-story is dealt with. Shortly into The Lost Age the party is joined by a Lemurian Mercury (water) adept Piers, who reveals the threat of Weyard's disintegration without alchemy. The former party (           Isaac,           Garet,          Ivan,         Mia) also join late in the game.  Like in the first game, two Mars Clan from Prox (    Agatio and    Karst) act as apparent antagonists, but after the party discovers Prox - on the edge of the disintegrating Weyard - their true mission to save their people is revealed.   Djinn   Djinn are the magical creatures that were unleashed on the world after Issac entered Sol Sanctum and removed the elemental stars. Each Djinn is aligned to an element, which in turn is aligned to a planet.  Some Djinn are only available by entering a code obtained by completing the original Golden Sun   New Djinn Venus (Earth)        The Venus lighthouse powers the Earth element, and each of the Djinn that use it. Echo Iron Steel Mud FlowerMeldPetraSaltGeodeMoldCrystal Djinn of Earth         Mars (Fire)         The Mars lighthouse powers the Fire element, and each of the Djinn that use it.      Cannon  Spark  Kindle  Char  Coal RefluxCoreTinderShineFuryFugueDjinn of Fire    Jupiter (Wind)         The Jupiter lighthouse powers the Wind element, and each of the Djinn that use it.      Breath  Blitz  Ether  Waft  Haze  Wheeze Aroma  Whorl  Gasp  Lull   GaleDjinn of Wind    Mercury (Water)         The Mercury Lighthouse powers the Water element, and each of the Djinn that use it.     FogSourSpringShadeChillSteam Rime Gel EddyBalmSerac Djinn of Water    Summons           Earth  Venus: one Venus Ramses: Two Venus  Cybele: Three Venus  Judgement: Four Venus    Fire  Mars: One Mars    Kirin: Two Mars    Tiamat: Three Mars    Meteor: Four Mars  Wind   Jupiter: One Jupiter    Atalanta: Two Jupiter    Procne: Three Jupiter    Thor: Four Jupiter   Water   Mercury: One Mercury    Nereid: Two Mercury    Neptune: Three Mercury     Boreas: Four Mercury Djinn  Multi Types Zagan : One Venus,One Mars     Megaera: One Mars, One Jupiter     Flora: One Venus, Two Jupiter    Moloch: Two Mercury, One Jupiter    Ulysses: Two Mercury, two Mars    Haures: Three Venus, Two Mars    Eclipse: Two Mercury, Three Jupiter    Coatlicue: Three Mercury, Three Jupiter    Daedalus: Three Venus, Four Mars    Azul: Three Venus, Four Mercury    Catastrophe: Three Mars, Five Jupiter    Charon: Eight Venus, Two Jupiter    Iris: Four Mercury, Eight MarsData Transfer     Golden Sun: The Lost Age allowed players to transfer their data from the        Golden Sun into The Lost Age by one of two possible methods.  The first was by the use of a GameBoy Advance Link cable between two Gameboy Advances as well both Golden Sun and Golden Sun: The Lost Age. The second was a password system which allowed the player to transfer data depending on their preference. There were three different types of passwords (Bronze, Silver &amp; Gold) which varied in length, and hence varied the amount of information sent across.   Password Types    BronzeCharacter levelsDjinn obtained Silver All Bronze dataCharacter stats  GoldAll Silver dataItems &amp; EquipmentCoins Data transfer was required for the player to obtain all the Djinn in The Lost Age and to access two hidden summons, Charon &amp; Iris.Cheat: Enter last town visitedWhen you load a saved game, hold the L+R+Start buttons while you load the game. If you entered the code correctly, you will be in the Sanctum of the last town you visited.Cheat: Enter last town visitedTo give alternate names to Jenna, Sheba, and Pierrs, press select 3 times while naming Felix.   If you are doing a non linked game, you may name Garet, Ivan, and Mia, too.  To do this press UP, DOWN, UP, DOWN, LEFT, RIGHT, LEFT, RIGHT, UP, RIGHT, DOWN, LEFT, UP, and SELECT.  You will hear a ''ting'' and will be able to name Garet, Ivan, and Mia.Cheat: Avoid water monsters and waste almost no PPOnly works after you get the flying wings and the hover jade. Go in the boat and instead of pressing b to fly, go into your psyenergy menu and select hover. The boat will rise and then fall but the bar will still be there and it won't go down (you won't lose PP). During that time the game will think you are flying, so no monsters will attack you and you will hear the flying noise and music (but you aren't flying). The glitch stays until you press B. In which the flying music will get louder and you will actually fly.Cheat: Avoid water monsters and waste almost no PPThe glitch at the Trial Road Dungeon makes copies of items in the artifact inventories of the shops.  From the time that Moapa opens the dungeon and until Felix beats Moapa every item that Felix and friends drop will be returned to Felix inventory when he leaves Trial Road.  Entering dropped items in the artifact inventory of the shops is already part of the game design.  Only the Laughing Fungus, Large Bread, Bone, Smoke Bombs, Sleep Bombs, Bramble Seeds, Oil Drops, Crystal Powder, and Weasel Claws will not be copied to the shop inventory.Cheat: Avoid water monsters and waste almost no PP When you enter trial road as soon as you control Felix drop an item you want to duplicate and then leave Trial Road.  Go to an item shop and buy the duplicates of the item you dropped.Cheat: Avoid water monsters and waste almost no PPThis can be used to duplicate Hyper Boots, the Swift Sword, Tear Stone, Lucky Medals, and Waters of Life.Cheat: Avoid water monsters and waste almost no PPIt is indeed possible to get to the land from the first Golden Sun! First, go to the small beach southwest of the village Loho. Get on your boat, and face in between the small beach, and the tiny piece of land below it. Hit the A button to get off your ship and you should end up on the other side of the mountains! All of the towns are gone, except for Vale, but you can't enter it. All of the caves are gone, so you can't explore the entire world. The only other visible places are Venus Lighthouse and Babi Lighthouse. You won't be able to reach either of them, though.Cheat: Listen to all Golden Sun musicGo into Battle Mode on the title screen (must be Golden Sun: The Lost Age), and walk over to the woman on the far left. Hold down the R button and talk to her. A whole list of music from Golden Sun 1 and 2 will come up, and you can listen to any you want by pressing A.Cheat: An extra way to get the Golden Sun: Book Two Theme in Battle.Put Felix, Isaac, and Jenna into the back row of the party. Now, when you enter Battle, you'll hear the Golden Sun: Book Two Theme.Cheat: An extra way to get the Golden Sun: Book Two Theme in Battle.When you get all of the Djinni from Golden Sun and Golden Sun 2. go to Contigo and use teleport in the circle in the middle of the town.  You will gain access to the dungeon only if you have all of the djinni.Cheat: An extra way to get the Golden Sun: Book Two Theme in Battle.After attaining a Clear Data file, select new game. After transfering, the game will ask if you want to play [Insert Mode Here]. Select No until it asks if you want to play on Easy Mode. Select Yes. Cheat: An extra way to get the Golden Sun: Book Two Theme in Battle.You need to have a ''Clear Data'' file and an empty file. Select ''New Game'' and after you transfer data or choose not to, then it will ask you if you want to play ''Easy Mode''. Select the ''No'' option and it will ask if you want to play ''Hard Mode''. Select ''Yes''. Hard Mode is like Regular mode except all enemies are a lot stronger.Cheat: An extra way to get the Golden Sun: Book Two Theme in Battle.For the original Golden Sun book one battle theme, simply have Isaac in your party without Felix and enter battle. For the Golden Sun book two theme, place felix in your party and enter battle. For ''Jenna's Theme'' (Song number 47 in battle arena's song request and played at the beginning of the game before Felix rejoins the party), have Jenna in your battle party, but exclude Isaac and Felix to the back row and enter battle. NOTE: All of the stated above themes can also work identically the same when used in battle arena in addition to battle in the game itself.</plot>
	<releasedate>14/4/2003</releasedate>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>nPzBeIATN74</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3771</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561356-golden-sun-the-lost-age</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/golden-sun-the-lost-age</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/golden-sun-the-lost-age/3030-4277/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82063/2621244-gslostage.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/WBNAHJA.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/mn7Wzye.jpg</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/44500-golden-sun-the-lost-age-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59987-golden-sun-the-lost-age-game-boy-advance-screenshot-no-i-m.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59988-golden-sun-the-lost-age-game-boy-advance-screenshot-nice-place.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59989-golden-sun-the-lost-age-game-boy-advance-screenshot-rock-climbing.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59990-golden-sun-the-lost-age-game-boy-advance-screenshot-too-cold.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59991-golden-sun-the-lost-age-game-boy-advance-screenshot-doom-dragon.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59992-golden-sun-the-lost-age-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-one.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59993-golden-sun-the-lost-age-game-boy-advance-screenshot-status.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/18559/620478-untitled5.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/18559/620477-untitled4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/18559/620475-untitled2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3771-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3771-10.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3771-2.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3771-3.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3771-4.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3771-5.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3771-6.jpg</fanart7>
	<fanart8>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3771-7.jpg</fanart8>
	<fanart9>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3771-8.jpg</fanart9>
	<fanart10>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3771-9.jpg</fanart10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WyxVYo3.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The story of Golden Sun: The Lost Age picks up right near the end of the first game. Golden Sun veterans will be surprised to learn that The Lost Age is played from the point of view of the party being chased as they try to light the remaining two lighthouses, which will unlock the power of alchemy for the world--or will it instead unlock the world's destruction?</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>rn34B4XhJ4I</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5cf0b655-a5f1-4863-9ddd-be3811f722c9.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1655e436-eec9-4e70-9f9d-6673a87c3e72.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b772b632-533c-424b-90ee-054abaae362b.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7f26bed4-2691-4ed6-8829-a5c18f97a5ea.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8afd920c-d65f-467d-b23c-75f3ee4914cb.png</clearlogo2>
	<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>