<Game>
	<Name>Golden Nugget Casino (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Experience the thrill of high stakes gambling in the Golden Nugget Casino with classic games like Blackjack, Craps and Roulette, plus Slots and Video Poker. When you're down on your luck, visit the ATM then hit the tables for more action.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/924101.htmlCheat: Start with 8 527 030$Type 1XCBv#dbbbxbM in Password on the main menu.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Card</genre>
	<Developer>Majesco Games</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>18437</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/924101-golden-nugget-casino</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/18437-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/4/2/62842_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/8/0/gfs_58013_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/5/0/gfs_58013_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/e/0/gfs_58013_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/f/0/gfs_58013_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/4/0/gfs_58013_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Experience the thrill of high stakes gambling in the Golden Nugget Casino with classic games like Blackjack, Craps and Roulette, plus Slots and Video Poker. When you’re down on your luck, visit the ATM then hit the tables for more action. With Golden Nugget Casino, you can be a high roller and leave your wallet at home. Master a variety of card and table games plus slots and video poker and pull the lever on slot machine games including Halloween Spooky and Wild West. Challenge yourself on Video Poker games like Deuces Wild, Joker’s Wild, Jacks or Better and Tens or Better. Get a loan from the cashier of up to $2,000 at a time, up to a maximum of $10,000. Password system allows you to enter a password and resume play with a previously saved bank account balance.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9bf6294-aa3a-45e1-b049-e70473ee19eb.jpg</boxart3>
	<Publisher>Majesco</Publisher>
</game>