<Game>
	<Name>Golden Sun (Spain)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Golden Sun LogoGolden Sun (also known as Ougon no Taiyou in Japan) is an RPG developed by Camelot and published by Nintendo for the Gameboy Advance. It was well received thanks to its interesting story, likable cast of characters, varied gameplay, and intriguing puzzles. The game takes place in a land called Weyard, where a group of people called adepts have the power to channel the elements of Earth (Venus ), Fire (Mars), Water (Mercury), and Wind (Jupiter). The game centers around two boys named Isaac and Garet who are attempting to stop two fire Adepts named Saturos and Menardi from lighting the four elemental lighthouses that will change Weyard forever. Along the way they meet a Jupiter Adept named Ivan, and a Mercury Adept named Mia.It was followed by a sequel, Golden Sun: The Lost Age on April 14, 2003, which picks up right where the original Golden Sun left off and let players carry over their character data and items via system link or a password. A third game in the series Golden Sun: Dark Down came out in 2010 for the Nintendo DS.Gameplay:Ragnarok - One of the game's many spellsOne of the most prominent features of the game is its nonstandard take on the RPG mechanic of magic, in this game called Psynergy, which can be used inside of battle to deal damage, buff allies, or inflict various statuses on enemies , but can also be used outside of battle to help solve the game's various puzzles by moving pillars, using gusts of wind to clear away leaves, or even freezing a puddle of water to create a temporary pillar.The game also featured a creature collection mechanic popular in video games at the time. Early on the Djinn, small magical creatures who are tied to the individual elements, are introduced. These Djinn could be obtained by encountering them in the wild, in towns, or in dungeons and more often than not required you to fight them in order to win them over. The Djinn system became the basis for the game's class mechanic as well and is one of the most deceptively deep systems in recent memory.Golden Sun featured an offline versus mode in which two Gameboy Advances were hooked up via link cable where players could use the parties from their own cartridges to battle each other. The game also included a battle arena where you could test your mettle against various enemies using the party you had faced in the main story mode.Story:A Boss BattleThe game starts out in a town called Vale 3 years before the actual adventure. The main characters Isaac and Garet are only kids at this time. A storm has erupted, and a boulder from Mt. Aleph is about to fall down and crush the town. Isaac's father and many other villagers go to stop the boulder. Isaac and Garret are sent to the plaza at the bottom of the village initially to meet up with Jenna, looking for help rescuing Felix, her trapped brother in the river. However, on returning with her, the boulder falls, crushing all the villagers that were trying to stop it, including Isaac's father and Jenna's family. Before Isaac and Garret can reach the Plaza, Saturos and Menardi find them and attack them. Isaac and Garret are left unconscious but are found by their family and taken to the plaza.CharactersThere are five party members you will meet on your journey. All of them can use any Djinni - although all five characters have a natural predisposition to one of the four psynergy types.IvanIsaac is the main character of Golden Sun, he uses a sword and attacks with Earth psynergy.Jenna is a temporary playable character in the earliest part of the game. She is friend to both Garret and Isaac and uses Fire psynergyGarret is Isaacs best friend and second party member recruited. They both come from the same town, Garret uses large swords and attacks with Fire psynergy.Ivan is the third party member recruited. He uses wind psynergy. He is the youngest of the group and carries a crescent staff.Mia is the fourth member that is recruited and the final permanent member of the party. She is a water adept who uses water psynergy. She joins the party in the town of ImilLocationsValeSol SanctumVaultLunpaBilibinImilMercury LighthouseBilibin BarricadeKolima VillageFuchin TempleXianAltin Village and MineLama TempleKalayKalay DocksAltimer CaveGandowan BridgeSuhullaVenus LighthouseLaLiveroBabi LighthouseDjinnDjinn are mysterious spirits that control the elements. When attached to a character, they enhance the stats and psynergy of the characters. They can eventually be used to summon powerful creatures who deal massive damage in battle, along with many other useful effects.The four types of Djinn are:Ivan with Jupiter DjinnEarth (Venus)Wind (Jupiter)Fire (Mars)Water (Mercury)Name of DjinnElementHPPPAtkDefAgiLuckEffect Upon Battle UseFlintEarth+8+4+3000"Strike a blow that can cleave stone."GraniteEarth+900+2+2+1"Create a mighty earthen barrier."QuartzEarth+10+300+30"Revive a downed ally."VineEarth+12+40+30+1"Tangle foes to drop Agility."SapEarth+100+300+1"Attack a foe and steal HP."GroundEarth+9+300+30"Use Gravity to hold a foe."BaneEarth+120+4000"Attack with nature's venom."ForgeMars+100+20+2+2"Boost party Attack with flame's fury."FeverMars+80+30+20"Wrap a foe in feverish delusion."CoronaMars+12+30+30+1"Boost party Defense with a heat aura."ScorchMars+80+3000"Stun a foe with a blast attack."EmberMars+9+40+2+20"Restore party PP with passion's flames."FlashMars+14+30+200"Block damage to party with a firewall."TorchMars+90+300+1"Penetrate defense with a melting blast."GustJupiter+90+20+20"Attack with mighty wind gusts."BreezeJupiter+12+50+20+1"Boost party Resistance."ZephyrJupiter+11+300+2+1"Boost party Agility with swift wind."SmogJupiter+90+3000"Veil a foe's vision in smoke."KiteJupiter+8+400+30"Attack twice next round."SquallJupiter+100+5000"Paralyze a foe with a storm."LuffJupiter+11+50+20+1"Seal a foe's Psynergy."FizzMercury+9+40+300"Restore HP with calming water."SleetMercury+120+300+1"Drench a foe to drop its Attack."MistMercury+110+4000"Lull a foe into deep sleep."SpritzMercury+8+400+30"Restore party HP with soothing mist."HailMercury+90+400+1"Freeze a foe to drop its Defense."TonicMercury+8+30+20+2"Heal all party ailments."DewMercury+13+400+40"Revive a downed ally."Name of SummonStandby Djinn Required (element)Picture of summonVenus1 Earth: Ramses2 Earth: Cybele3 Earth: Judgement4 Earth: Mars1 Mars: Kirin2 Mars: Tiamat3 Mars: Meteor4 Mars: Jupiter1 Jupiter: Atlanta2 Jupiter: Procne3 Jupiter: Thor4 Jupiter: Mercury1 Mercury: Nereid2 Mercury: Neptune3 Mercury: Boreas4 Mercury: Classes:Each character has multiple classes they can become based on the Djinn they have equipped. Each class has it's own skillset.Squire:Character: IsaacClassDjinn EquippedSquireKnight2 Fire: Gallant4 Fire: Lord6 Fire: Solider:Character: GaretClassDjinn EquippedGuardSoldier2 Fire: Warrior4 Fire: Champion6 Fire: Hero7 Fire: MagicianCharacter: IvanClassDjinn EquippedWind SeerMagician2 Wind: Mage4 Wind: Magister6 Wind: Swordsman 1Character: IsaacClassDjinn EquippedSwordsman1 Water: Defender2 Water: Cavalier4 Water: Guardian1 Earth: 6 Water: Protector2 Earth: 7 Water: Character: MiaClassDjinn EquippedCavalier6 Earth: Guardian1 Water: 7 Earth: Swordman 2Character: GaretClassDjinn EquippedSwordsman1 Water: Defender2 Water: Cavalier4 Water: Luminier1 Fire: 6 Water: Radiant2 Fire: 7 Water: PageCharacter: IsaacClassDjinn EquippedPage1 Wind: Illusionist2 Wind: Enchanter4 Wind: Conjurer1 Earth: 6 Wind: War Adept2 Earth: 7 Wind: ApprenticeCharacter: IvanClassDjinn EquippedEnchanter6 Fire: Conjurer1 Wind: 7 Fire: Character : GaretClassDjinn EquippedApprentice1 Wind: Illusionist2 Wind: Enchanter4 Wind: Conjurer1 Fire: 6 Wind: War Adept2 Fire: 7 Wind: MercenaryCharacter: IsaacClassDjinn EquippedBrute1 Fire: Ruffian2 Fire: Savage4 Fire: Barbarian5 Fire: Berserker1 Earth: 6 Fire: Chaos Lord2 Earth: 7 Fire: Character: GaretClassDjinn EquippedBrute1 Earth: Ruffian2 Earth: Savage4 Earth: Barbarian5 Earth: Berserker1 Fire: 6 Earth: Chaos Lord2 Fire: 7 Earth: Seer (Water)Character: IsaacClassDjinn EquippedShaman6 Water: Druid1 Earth: 7 Water: Character: MiaClassDjinn EquippedSeer1 Earth: Diviner2 Earth: Shaman4 Earth: Druid1 Water: 6 Earth: Oracle2 Water: 7 Earth: Seer (Wind)Character: IsaacClassDjinn EquippedShaman6 Wind: Druid1 Earth: 7 Wind: Character: IvanClassDjinn EquippedSeer1 Earth: Diviner2 Earth: Shaman4 Earth: Druid1 Wind: 6 Earth: Oracle2 Wind: 7 Earth: Monk (Water)Character: GaretClassDjinn EquippedAscetic6 Water: Water Monk1 Fire: 6 Water: Character: MiaClassDjinn EquippedPilgrim1 Fire: Wanderer2 Fire: Ascetic4 Fire: Water Monk1 Water: 6 Fire: Guru2 Water: 7 Fire: WiseCharacter: IvanClassDjinn EquippedHermit1 Water: Elder2 Water: Scholar4 Water: Savant5 Water: Sage6 Water: Wizard6 Water: Character: MiaClassDjinn EquippedHermit1 Wind: Elder2 Wind: Scholar4 Wind: Savant5 Wind: Sage1 Water: 6 Wind: Wizard2 Water: 6 Wind: Monk (Wind)Character: GaretClassDjinn EquippedAscetic6 Wind: Water Monk1 Fire: 7 Wind: Character: IvanClassDjinn EquippedPilgrim1 Fire: Wanderer2 Fire: Ascetic4 Fire: Water Monk1 Wind: 6 Fire: Guru1 Wind: 7 Fire: </plot>
	<releasedate>12/11/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>LR9EqKQb5-I</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3769</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/468548-golden-sun</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/golden-sun</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/golden-sun/3030-267/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/82063/2621230-goldensunbox.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nRJU3W6.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/N7PjO0P.png</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/44365-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24580-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-your-battle-actions.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24581-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot-your-djinn-management.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24582-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot-encounter.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24583-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot-welcome-to-the-village.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24584-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot-venus-djinn-in-action.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24585-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-your-psynergy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24586-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot-should-i-use-that-herb.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24587-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot-golden-sun-intro-screen.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24588-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot-stay-for-a-spell-the.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/386423-golden-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot-entering-the-temple.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3769-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3769-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3769-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3769-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3769-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3769-6.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3769-7.jpg</fanart7>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/zlOyO7Z.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3769.png</clearlogo1>
</game>