<Game>
	<Name>Gradius Galaxies (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The classic franchise Gradius comes to Game Boy&amp;reg; Advance! An evil force has taken over a distant star system and only you can stop them. Soar through a myriad of enemy attack units and blow them to bits using ultra powerful weapons including photon missiles and laser beams.Cheat: All WeaponsWhile in play, pause the game and enter the following code : Up, Up, Down, Down, L, R, L, R, B, ACheat: All WeaponsTo delete saved data, go to the options screen, select ''EXIT'', and then hold the L, R and B buttons, then press start.Cheat: All WeaponsPause the game and enter the following:Cheat: All WeaponsTo get one speed-up and full power-up of laser, options, and shield; pause and enter: Up, Up, Down, Down, L, R, L, R, B, A, Start This code works only once per game, including all continues. To momentarily get the power-ups listed above, and then self-destruct, pause and enter: Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Left, Right, B, A, Start This code may be used as often as you like.Cheat: Unlocking Challenge ATo unlock ''Challenge A'' just clear the game once. Then it can be selected from the main menu.Cheat: Unlocking Challenge ATo unlock Challenge B a harder version of Challenge A, you have to clear Challenge A.Cheat: Gradius one music from NES  Start a new mission on stage 1 of Gradius Galaxies. Somewhere in the stage, there are 2 strips of horizontal rocks (one longer than the other). Carefully travel through the small gap in between the 2 rocks and you'll get 5000 extra points. Complete the game as normal and when you return to stage 1 again on the next loop, the stage music will change to Gradius one from NES.</plot>
	<releasedate>7/11/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>Fk4UkX-bw78</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>9928</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/528151-gradius-galaxies</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/gradius-galaxies</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/gradius-galaxies/3030-2030/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2291745-box_gg.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/9928-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/130412-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116363-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116361-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-screenshot-option-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/116362-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-screenshot-selecting-the.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264852-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-screenshot-enemies-the-one.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264853-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-screenshot-getting-the-laser.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264854-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-screenshot-and-there-goes.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264855-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-boss.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264856-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-screenshot-not-many-enemies.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264857-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-screenshot-changing-craft.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264858-gradius-galaxies-game-boy-advance-screenshot-and-another-boss.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/0x3daZb.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The classic franchise Gradius comes to Game Boy® Advance! An evil force has taken over a distant star system and only you can stop them. Soar through a myriad of enemy attack units and blow them to bits using ultra powerful weapons including photon missiles and laser beams.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/99409a14-6300-4341-9f3d-8b5cb9673e55.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8737b5ca-d244-4dff-b212-08083cbb00ac.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2011e6a1-72e0-4098-84a3-e82a6e7231ce.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>