<Game>
	<Name>Grand Theft Auto Advance (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:GTA Advance is the first entry in the legendary sandbox series, Grand Theft Auto, specifically designed for a handheld system (unlike earlier Game Boy Color ports of Grant Theft Autos 1 and 2). Developed by an independant third-party developer, Digital Eclipse, it is also the first original game in the franchise's history not to be developed by Rockstar North. GTA Advance plays and looks similar to some of the earlier GTA games like GTA 2 with it's top-down perspective,but also includes the additional features such as vigilante and paramedic missions as well as rampages, stunts, and the hidden packages introduced in GTA III.The story of GTA Advance takes place a year before the events of GTA III (though no characters from 3 appear, nor are any of these characters referenced in it or fellow prequel Liberty City Stories), and features a small-time crook Mike who in his attempt to escape from the city along with his mentor and his friend, Vinnie gets caught in a pile of debt and trouble and decides to take revenge on the city. Due to various technical limitations of GBA, neither cutscenes nor voice acting is included in GTA Advance. It also features only a fixed soundtrack for a particular car.Cheat: Activate Cheat ModeEnter Cheat Mode (hold down A + B + Start) then do these cheats in game, without pausing.Cheat: Activate Cheat ModePreferably, you should have your fists equipped, so you don't accidentally blow yourself up or anything.Cheat: Activate Cheat ModeAt main menu press: Left, Right, Up, Down, L, R, Hold start and press A. This will unlock a option that displays all the levels Cheat: Cruise ControlWhile in a car, hold Up and release the gas. Your car will continue at the same speed you were at when beginning the sequence. Cheat: Get Police Bribes at HideoutComplete 12 Paramedic missions to never get tired when running.Cheat: Get Police Bribes at HideoutAs you collect the hidden packages, weapons will be delivered to your hideout.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/10/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Rockstar Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>M - Mature</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3784</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919434-grand-theft-auto</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/grand-theft-auto-advance</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/grand-theft-auto-advance/3030-3527/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3784-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3784-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/109007-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141389-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141390-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188808-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-have.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188809-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-vinnie.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188810-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-paramedic.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188811-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-first.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188814-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-busted.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/556909-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-wasted.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188815-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-my-first.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/610177-grand-theft-auto-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-dialogue.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8lFS1wG.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3784.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Grand Theft Auto Advance brings the thrills of the class GTA gaming series to your Game Boy Advance. In this all-new revenge-driven story, you're on the run from the cops after being framed for murder. You were set to do one last job for Vinnie, a local mob boss - until his car blew up, taking his life and all the cash he was paying you. You're the prime suspect and every cop in Liberty City is after you -- but you're not leaving until you can find out who set you up and shut them down.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/41d3fc32-c150-4455-ad9a-0d64288700a8.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a242a0a-fc57-438e-a03c-20aa407bd2d0.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Rockstar Games</Publisher>
</game>