<Game>
	<Name>Gremlins - Stripe vs Gizmo (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Gremlins: Stripe vs Gizmo is a 2D side-scrolling platformer based on the popular film series.  Christmas has come to Kingston Falls, and depending on which character is chosen, can either save or destroy the holiday.  Players can choose to play between Gizmo, the furry, friendly Mogwai, or Stripe, the mischievous,  and foul-tempered Gremlin.  Playing through five levels, Gizmo's intent is to save all of the Christmas presents and return them to their rightful children.  While doing this, Gizmo must also escape from the evil Gremlins that are trying to capture him and force him to eat after midnight - turning him into a Gremlin.  Gizmo uses his double-jump and flashlight to ward off attacks, or can roll into a ball and knock over enemies.Playing as Stripe, it is the player's goal to destroy as many presents as possible.  Players can capture Mogwais and turn them into Gremlins by hitting them with a cream pie.  Stripe can also attack by using his claws.Gremlins: Stripe Vs. Gizmo offers three distinct game modes: Adventure Mode, an "Against-the-Clock" Mode and a Multiplayer Mode (two players can compete in real time with link mode).Cheat: Gizmo Adventure PasswordsThe Bank GIZMO The Police Station BILLY The Cinema FUNNY THE FIRE HOUSE TORCH THE FINAL ENCOUTER GIFTS Cheat: Gizmo Adventure PasswordsThere is a password option on the main menuCheat: Gizmo Adventure PasswordsThere is a password option at the main menu:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>DreamCatcher Interactive Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11550</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/566364-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo/3030-4177/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11550-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11550-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276071-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276076-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276073-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo-game-boy-advance-screenshot-facing.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/276074-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo-game-boy-advance-screenshot-and-finishing.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/692500-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/692501-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo-game-boy-advance-screenshot-tutorial.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/692502-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo-game-boy-advance-screenshot-jumping.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/692503-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo-game-boy-advance-screenshot-climbing.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/692504-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo-game-boy-advance-screenshot-climbing.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/692505-gremlins-stripe-vs-gizmo-game-boy-advance-screenshot-little.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11550-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11550-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11550-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11550-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<Notes>In Gizmo's story, the cute Mogwai has to prevent Stripe from ruining Christmas for Kingston Falls by retrieving all the presents that Stripe has stolen. Gizmo uses a flashlight to kill gremlins after rolling into a ball and weakening the gremlins. He also must destroy any gremlins that get in his way. In Stripe's story, he comes up with a scheme to destroy his mortal enemy Gizmo and destroy mogwais.  If playing as Gizmo, all the enemies are generic gremlins. If playing as Stripe, the player will instead fight mogwais.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/38c3548d-d012-4a36-b65f-0777077b2d96.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>DreamCatcher Interactive</Publisher>
</game>