<Game>
	<Name>GT Advance - Championship Racing (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Install your car kits, head to the track, start your engines and get ready to challenge the most competitive racers on the circuit! Choose from over 45 authentic cars and race for championship gold on an amazing 32 different tracks. Upgrade your car's performance using 9 categories of upgradeable parts including the engine, suspension, aerodynamics and more.Cheat: Extra ModeHold the L and R buttons, then press Down/Right + B.Cheat: Extra ModeEnter the following codes at the startup screen (where it says Press Start): - To unlock the Indy Car Mode, Press and Hold L+R, then press Left on the D-   Pad, then press B. When you hear a sound press start and it will be unlocked. - To unlock the Go Kart Mode, Press and Hold L+R, then press Right on the   D-Pad, then press B. When you hear a sound press start and it will be   unlocked. - For all tuning parts, press and hold L+R then Down+Right (diagonal) then   press B. Cheat: Extra ModeEnter the following code at the Press Start screen....  Hold L + R and Press Up/Left + B  Then all of the cars should be unlockedCheat: Extra ModeOn the title screen (where it says ''Press Start'') Hold both L &amp; R shoulders, then hold diagonal Up,Right then press B. There should be a sound.  Now go to Quick race and all tracks should be available.Cheat: Extra ModeAt the main menu, press and hold L and R, then press Down, Right and B simutaneously. This will give you all car tune-ups in the game.Cheat: Extra ModeEnter the following code at the Press Start screen....  Hold L + R and Press Up + B  You should then see the creditsCheat: Level Passwords-At the password screen: Complete each of the races with a gold medalCheat: Level Passwords-At the password screen, enter the appropriate password (case-sensitive):Cheat: Access Extra 1 OptionTo gain access to the Extra 1 option on the main menu, you must first complete the Beginner's, Medium, and High Speed Classes in Championship mode. I'm not sure exactly what the requirements, cup-wise (gold, silver, bronze), are though; I had all Golds on all tracks when I opened up this options.Cheat: Access Extra 1 OptionTo gain access to the Extra 2 option on the main menu, you must complete all classes in Championship mode (Beginner's, Medium, High Speed, and Professional). You must have Gold Cups on all tracks to open up this option, too.Cheat: Access Extra 1 OptionComplete the following tracks with a gold medal to unlock these parts.Cheat: Access Extra 1 OptionComplete the final race in the professional class to unlock a seat which boosts all three stats.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/6/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>z8r_hHiouQ0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14838</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/471246-gt-advance-championship-racing</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/gt-advance-championship-racing</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/gt-advance-championship-racing/3030-14360/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/14838-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/14838-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/103566-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/113355-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/281961-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/113382-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/119280-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/245609-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/245763-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/245764-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/634159-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/634160-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/634161-gt-advance-championship-racing-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/14838.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Install your car kits, head to the track, start your engines and get ready to challenge the most competitive racers on the circuit! Choose from over 45 authentic cars and race for championship gold on an amazing 32 different tracks. Upgrade your car's performance using 9 categories of upgradeable parts including the engine, suspension, aerodynamics and more.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/03b2584c-bb55-46d6-9c1f-633158eda419.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9d0c5683-6bdf-439f-ad93-707e8ec9f32d.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>