<Game>
	<Name>Hamtaro - Rainbow Rescue (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:Hamtaro: Rainbow Rescue was released in Japan and Europe, but had its North American release cancelled with no reason given. The distribution of the game outside of Japan was convoluted, and copies of it in English are overall scarce.The game's core gameplay consists of navigating a fairly expansive world, whose hub is the hamsters' Clubhouse. Throughout these locations, the player is faced with several minigames, most of them with an unique mechanic, and winning a challenge nets the player collectible stickers, of which there are 451. The catch, however, is that each minigame can only be player by a specific character, which often have to be found in some part of the level by means of exploration and fulfilling tasks.The structure of the levels emphasizes the small size of the hamsters, with brooms and desks often being used as makeshift ladders, for examples. Enemies are portrayed as bigger animals, such as chicks and snakes. Objects such as rocks also present substantial obstacles for the hamsters to overcome. By combining forces, it is possible for them to get through such situations. It features a very substantial post-game segment, with an entire optional quest to be completed, and many stickers are impossible to get over the course of the main story. On top of that, painting features are available, and the stickers can be arranged at will on the many backgrounds that can be collected throughout the game.The playable Ham-Hams are Hamtaro, Bijou, Oxnard, Boss, Cappy, Maxwell, Pashmina, Penelope, Panda, Stan, Sandy, Howdy, and Dexter.Cheat: Get hidden Does She Know? coloringGet to the hamster that begins "Crazy Cap Catch" ham-game at Clover Elementary(as you enter,go one screen up,two screens right and one up to find that hamster).behind that hamster is a shogun wig,talk with it(you need to completely end the conversation)then immediately press  L,A,B,L,R.Cheat: Get hidden Does She Know? coloringGo to Rainbow Land,go up with the cloud,go a screen up using the stairs,go to the right/left screen and go up using those disks on the floor.talk with the green poster behind Bo(you need to completely end the conversation)then immediately press  L,A,L,B,A,B,R,R.Cheat: Get hidden Does She Know? coloringEnter Tip-Top Fair and go one screen left,there will be a big stage in that screen.in that stage there is a picture of Howdy and Dexter,talk to it(you need to completely end the conversation)then immediately press R,L,A,R,B.Cheat: Get hidden Does She Know? coloringGo to Hamstarr Manor. Behind Seed Pig-Out (the one with Mean Oxnard) there are three hamsters sitting behind a table. Talk to the middle hamster ONCE. Then, press the following buttons in order: B, L, A, B, A, R. You will receive the picture 'Too Much Good Stuff'.Cheat: Get hidden Does She Know? coloringStand in front of the blackboard in the Clubhouse and press the A button. After reading the message, press the L, R, A, B buttons in this order and you'll receive a secret coloring picture.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/5/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>LPRq9jjSFCc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>30558</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/582378-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/hamtaro-rainbow-rescue</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hamtaro-rainbow-rescue/3030-8512/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/30558-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/64084-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/64921-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178832-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178815-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178816-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-screenshot-sticker.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178818-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-screenshot-view-different.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178817-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-screenshot-playing.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178819-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-screenshot-bijou-was.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178820-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-screenshot-neat-greeting.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178822-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-screenshot-as-bijou.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178823-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-screenshot-seems-like.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178824-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue-game-boy-advance-screenshot-seems-the.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>One day while playing outside, Bijou witnesses a great rainbow. The rainbow disappears and Prince Bo falls to the ground. The Prince states that he can make rainbows by using his umbrella. He tries to prove it to disbelieving Stan and the rest of the Ham-Hams, but realizes too late that the colors on his umbrella are gone. And thus, Hamtaro and his Ham-Ham friends must set off on a journey in order to collect things that are the proper color for Prince Bo to use for his umbrella so he can create a rainbow to return home.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fd0c9906-19a0-406c-84fe-d9d5554a2232.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/80361eec-b814-47c1-9b7a-352a1524ffd4.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ca44cf9-66c1-4d6f-bd0b-11916ffa24ad.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a0ee54b9-8ed5-4e01-8cef-63002badf00e.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>