<Game>
	<Name>Harlem Globetrotters - World Tour (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Harlem Globetrotters: World Tour is a licensed basketball game featuring 2-on-2 matches. There are two main modes: Quick Match (only the fourth quarter of a game) and World Tour. The latter has the player go through a series of matches, beating the other teams to become world champion with gameplay similar to the NBA Jam games. Each character has a range of statistics such as speed, offense, defense and stamina. All the regular moves are present: player switches, a tip off, passing, 1-2 passing, shooting, targetting, steals and dunks with hoop hanging.While playing, a stamina bar is shown. A temporary boost can be activated, but the amount will slowly decrease during the match and eventually substitutions may be needed. Another feature is the special bar, fed by impressive dunks and passes. When maxed out, players are able to perform special dunks.Progressing through the World Tour unlocks new teams. The DS version adds multiplayer support for two players.Cheat: Level PasswordsIn order to unlock a certain number of teams, input the stated passwords in the Password option from the main menu.Cheat: Easily Winning MatchesIn order to easily win your matches, simply score more points than your opponent (even if it is just more 1 point than them), get the ball with one of your characters and move him to the lower left side of the field. Then, release the controls of the console and just let your character in there.While the time elapses, the opponent near you can't take the ball away, due to a glitch, and therefore you'll win the match.Cheat: Unlockable PlayersIn order to unlock new players, you have to score a total score of the stated points in your matches.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Destination Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>28156</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/933453-harlem-globetrotters-world-tour</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/harlem-globetrotters-world-tour</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/harlem-globetrotters-world-tour/3030-17238/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/561/220290-harlem_globetrotters_world_tour.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464320-harlem-globetrotters-world-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464321-harlem-globetrotters-world-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464322-harlem-globetrotters-world-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464323-harlem-globetrotters-world-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464324-harlem-globetrotters-world-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464325-harlem-globetrotters-world-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464326-harlem-globetrotters-world-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464327-harlem-globetrotters-world-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464328-harlem-globetrotters-world-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/1/2/gfs_76320_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>