<Game>
	<Name>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Da)</Name>
	<plot>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban is EA's game based on the third movie and book in the Harry Potter series. The big difference with the previous game in the series, Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, is that you take control of all three main characters at once. All characters have a speciality; Harry is the agile one, and he can do such things as climb on ropes and leap over  chasms the others can't. Ron can find secret passages the other characters cannot detect, and Hermione can squeeze through small opening in walls the other can't get through.You take classes in the game that are pretty much dungeons you must get through, and at the end you'll find a spellbook that'll give you a new spell, either an offensive one or a spell that'll get you  You now control all three characters through obstacles. While not taking classes, you can freely roam Hogwarts, which has been expanded upon since the last game. You can play minigames like flying a hippogriff, and you can interact with other pupils in the school for odd jobs. The broomstick that allowed you to fly around Hogwarts' grounds has been removed.You can also hook up an eye-toy  and play some mini-games, including one where you have to capture a snitch.Cheat: The 5 ChestsAfter unlocking the cards in the Folio Universitas, go to the Card Collecters Club room on the 5th floor of the castle. There are rewards in each chest.Cheat: Play Minigames at any TimeIn order to play the four minigames (Buckbeak's Hippogriff Glide, Riddikulus Boggart Challenge, Wizard Cracker Pop-It, and Tea Leaf Divination) at any time, you must first unlock the games in story mode. After you unlock them, you may play them at any time by choosing the Mini-Games option on the main menu and selecting the game you want.Cheat: Play Minigames at any TimeComplete your library of Wizard Cards to unlock the 5 secret chests on Floor #5.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/6/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>19864</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919439-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban/3030-3792/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/19864-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/19864-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92534-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92535-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92536-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92537-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92538-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92539-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92540-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92541-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92542-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92543-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/OMf9A1V.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>The Dementors are coming, and this time Harry needs his friends. From the opening scene on the Hogwarts Express to the climatic finale on the shore of the great lake at Hogwarts, Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban immerses you in the world of Harry Potter. As Harry, Ron, and Hermione, you'll face the dreaded Azkaban guards, fly the Hippogriff around towers, and explore Hogwarts with the Marauder's Map. Learn spells that allow you to freeze creatures, control dragons, and conjure a Patronus. New two-player mini-games include Flying Seahorse Fishing and Dueling Club mini-games.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9c5fa4d-8c4f-473e-93df-6d21ebc54bb3.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/55507a76-62b6-4995-8147-8430184e6655.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>EA Games</Publisher>
</game>