<Game>
	<Name>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Da)</Name>
	<plot>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire is EA's fourth entry into the Harry Potter game series based off the books and films. A big difference between the fourth game and the previous ones is the fact that Goblet of Fire is directly based on the movies. The previous games in the series were loosely based on the film, but they drew most of their influence from the books. The games also had a pretty kiddy art style, but in Goblet of Fire, the games strive to look almost exactly look like the film. The likeness of Daniel Radcliff, as well as his companions were recreated pretty accurately, as well as the other characters in the movie. Also, instead of free-roaming gameplay, where you can pretty much go around Hogwarts as you please, the game is now cut up into levels. This results in a loss of freedom, but much more cinematic events in each self-contained and scripted levels. Gameplay:You play as all three protagonists (Harry, Ronald and Hermione) in this game. Each level features puzzles that have to solved with spells, as well as enemies that have to be beaten using jinxes, which  The first challengeare offensive spells.Another gameplay mechanic added is the combining of spells to form new jinxes and stronger spells. Each level features collectibles, and you can receive medals ranging from bronze to silver, depending on how much Bertie Bot's every flavour beans you can collect. Inbetween these normal levels, Harry gets to take on the three challenges of the tournament his fourth year is pretty much about. These challenges vary a bit on the normal gameplay. For instance, the first challenge is an on-rails flying level where you have to navigate obstacles while avoiding the dragon. Another new feature is co-op, allowing you to complete the game with two other players[a multitap is required for three players]. Before each level select you are given the oppurtunity to customize your character this can help in more difficult levels near the end of the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/11/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>3 Sim</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22250</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/927367-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire/3030-18427/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22250-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/257321-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742480-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742481-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742482-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742483-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742484-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742485-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742486-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742487-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742474-harry-potter-and-the-goblet-of-fire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/RU4JLel.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Harry, Ron, and Hermione are back in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire--a game based on J.K. Rowling's fourth book. The game follows Harry, the wizard-in-training, as he confronts a fire-breathing dragon, rescues friends from the icy depths of the Black Lake, and navigates the twisting corridors of a maze. As Harry, Ron, or Hermione, you can cast a variety of spells in both single-player and cooperative modes.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c18e514e-d5a0-446f-8b2e-0b2c8d3d2e85.jpg</boxart2>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>