<Game>
	<Name>Harry Potter to Azkaban no Shuujin (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The Dementors are coming, and this time Harry needs his friends. From the opening scene on the Hogwarts Express to the climatic finale on the shore of the great lake at Hogwarts, Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban immerses you in the world of Harry Potter. As Harry, Ron, and Hermione, you'll face the dreaded Azkaban guards, fly the Hippogriff around towers, and explore Hogwarts with the Marauder's Map. Learn spells that allow you to freeze creatures, control dragons, and conjure a Patronus. New two-player minigames include Flying Seahorse Fishing and Dueling Club minigames.Cheat: The 5 ChestsAfter unlocking the cards in the Folio Universitas, go to the Card Collecters Club room on the 5th floor of the castle. There are rewards in each chest.Cheat: Play Minigames at any TimeIn order to play the four minigames (Buckbeak's Hippogriff Glide, Riddikulus Boggart Challenge, Wizard Cracker Pop-It, and Tea Leaf Divination) at any time, you must first unlock the games in story mode. After you unlock them, you may play them at any time by choosing the Mini-Games option on the main menu and selecting the game you want.Cheat: Play Minigames at any TimeComplete your library of Wizard Cards to unlock the 5 secret chests on Floor #5.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/5/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</genre>
	<Developer>Griptonite Games</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>19864</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919439-harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/19864-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/19864-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/6/d/gfs_41330_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/b/d/gfs_41330_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/f/5/gfs_27670_2_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/2/5/gfs_27670_2_2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/9/5/gfs_27670_2_3.jpg</snapshot5>
</game>