<Game>
	<Name>Harvest Moon - More Friends of Mineral Town (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Following in the footsteps of Harvest Moon: Friends of Mineral Town, on this occasion you play the part of a young girl striving for a new life in the country. To do so, you have to build and maintain a farm while making friends with the locals, keeping a track of your funds and taking a closer look at your love life ... there's some bachelors out there waiting.The main aim of the game is to maintain your farm. To do so, you must plant and take care of various kinds of crops, keep your own home in order and feed the livestock. You'll have the opportunity to both buy and sell goods, since without money the farm will soon fall under. Making friends and attending various events in the town will also help to gain your character some extra items, more business and perhaps that life partner who can help you out, in more ways then one.More Friends of Mineral Town also connects to Harvest Moon: Another Wonderful Life, providing extra content for both titles through the game link cable.Cheat: Obtain new seedsBy shipping 100 of the following crops, you can unlock new crops which will be sold at the Supermarket in the right season.Cheat: Obtain new seedsNOTE: You do not have to ship all 100 crops in one season, just as long as your Shippping List reaches 100 for the crop.Cheat: Bad EndingTo recieve a "bad ending" for the game, at the beginning of the game simply tell the Mayor that ou won't take care of the farm. He'll say something along the lines of "oh, that's too bad" and the credits will roll.Cheat: Bad EndingDuring the first week of Spring, if you go to the left channel on your TV, and keep pressing left until the Harvest Goddess shows up, she'll let you play a guessing minigame that gives you prizes for a good amount of answers in a row.  Good way to make money at the beginning of the game.Cheat: Bad EndingPS. Can be used during any Year, but has to be the first week of Spring.Cheat: Bad EndingBefriend Won by giving him gold ore every day until he lets you play his apple sorting game AND sell stuff to him. It shouldn\'t take more than a season or so.Play the apple sorting game and get a raffle ticket from him. Save and then try to get three numbers in a row. (1-2-3, etc.) He should give you the record titled "Love" as a prize. Now, sell it right back to him over the counter for up to 170,000 gold! You can do this repeatedly, for tons of cash early on in the game.Cheat: Bad EndingLet's say you messed up with your hoe, go get a fence log and deposit it on the messed up tile, then remove it. The tile should be back to normal. This also works with any objects you can deposit on the field (rocks, branches). Your character won't lose stamina/gain fatigue while doing this.Cheat: Bad EndingWhen its time for the horse race, save your game before you watch the race. Write down all the winners in order and turn off the game. When you turn it back on, bet all your money on the horse that won the race just after you saved it. The horse that won right after you saved should win again. Same with the other horses. This should help you get the jewel of truth which will save you a lot of time.</plot>
	<releasedate>26/7/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Natsume, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>kOhIMwZuzQc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3468</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919367-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town/3030-2067/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3468-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3468-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/155014-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/155013-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742504-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742505-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742506-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742507-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742508-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742509-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742500-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/742501-harvest-moon-more-friends-of-mineral-town-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/lMV7DNG.png</banner1>
	<banner2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3468-g2.png</banner2>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3468.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Live the simple life as a farmer in Harvest Moon: More Friends of Mineral Town. This game is similar to the original Harvest Moon: Friends of Mineral Town, but now you can play as a girl who has left the city to pursue a life on the farm. You'll take part in growing crops, managing livestock, finding a husband, and raising children.</Notes>
	<banner3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/baca31ef-b138-49e3-bcd5-9c1b65a4c5de.jpg</banner3>
	<banner4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/748c8550-2f0d-4a85-a199-c455f17958c7.png</banner4>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/52c31e7d-a4a4-4d0c-904d-1ff2f4dc56b7.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7abf7b68-f354-43f1-b5f0-168c850e3467.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/79f6855a-88e1-4827-a4ad-b095e9e89dac.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2e15c2c9-b27e-4adb-9988-59dfd96d4bcc.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Natsume</Publisher>
</game>