<Game>
	<Name>High Heat Major League Baseball 2002 (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>High Heat 2002 is the 3rd game in the "High Heat" series.  Gone from the previous two games is the Sammy Sosa title.  Like the previous games HH2002 is a total baseball simulator.  You can set back and just manage your team or you can get right on the field and play each game.  You can configure the game in many different formats.  You can:Lengthen or Shorten a seasonCreate new teamsRe-arrange the divisonsmove players from different teams before the game startsChange team settingsCreate custom made players...and generally do just about anything you wantFrom the swing of the bat to making blockbuster trades you have all the controls.Cheat: Unlocking PitchesMost of the time you can only choose from a ''fastball'' and a ''spliter''. Hold Left on the D-pad, then rotate the D-pad clockwise and press B to unlock more pitches. </plot>
	<releasedate>30/9/2001</releasedate>
	<Developer>3DO Company, The</Developer>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>28157</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/470807-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002/3030-5984/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/28157-1.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/272688-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/272689-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/272690-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/272691-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/272692-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/272693-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/272694-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/272695-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/272696-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/272697-high-heat-major-league-baseball-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>High Heat Major League Baseball was a series of baseball computer games, released on PlayStation, Xbox, PlayStation 2 and PC. There were six annual versions of the game released, started with High Heat Baseball 1999, and ending with High Heat Major League Baseball 2004.[1] The game, featuring the official licensed team and player names from all 30 MLB teams, was created by games company 3DO which subsequently filed for bankruptcy in 2003 soon after the release of the final version of the series, High Heat Major League Baseball 2004. In August 2003, Microsoft purchased the rights to the High Heat franchise from 3DO, however, Microsoft has yet to develop a new title in the series.[2] High Heat was traditionally known for possessing more simulation-style qualities than competitors World Series Baseball, All Star Baseball, or Triple Play Baseball, but frequently lagged behind in graphical quality. At the core of High Heat′s gameplay was its batter-pitcher interface, which was often hailed as the most realistic of its era.[3]</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a45aa1ac-f6c2-4727-8fef-4698ef8b2709.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/16d3ee6d-7956-4a52-aab2-80261bbbfdd2.png</clearlogo1>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Publisher>3DO</Publisher>
</game>