<Game>
	<Name>Hoshi no Kirby - Kagami no Daimeikyuu (Japan) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Once again, Kirby must save the kingdom from evil. But this time he'll need some backup. As Kirby, you can call up one of four alter egos for help during your quest. Each character features new copy abilities that range from arrow-shooting to melee moves. Practice your skills in new side games, such as Crackity Hack and Speed Eaters. In addition to new abilities and subgames, Kirby &amp; the Amazing Mirror also introduces new multiplayer modes.Cheat: UnlockablesBoss Rush Mode is on the menu Metaknight's Sword will appear in front of the Magic Mirror once you've unlocked it The Power Center door is in the main 'hub' of Rainbow Route (Area 1) in the top left corner and contains all of the Powers in the game The Sound Test/Kirby Colors can be accessed through the Treasure ListCheat: Super Smash Brothers ReferenceDuring the game, you will encounter Master Hand, who is the boss on Super Smash Brothers and one of the bosses on Super Smash Brothers Melee. After you kill him, he gives you Smash power, which gives you several abilities mixed up. However, these abilities are in the same control sequences and combinations as Kirby's controls for Super Smah Bros.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/10/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Flagship</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>2336</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919415-kirby-and-the-amazing-mirror</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2336-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2336-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/9/7/gfs_49351_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/4/7/gfs_49351_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/7/8/gfs_60176_1_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/0/a/gfs_49351_2_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/d/a/gfs_49351_2_2.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2336-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2336-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2336-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2336.png</clearlogo1>
</game>