<Game>
	<Name>Hot Wheels - Stunt Track Challenge (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>You are a contestant in a new game show in which players must complete dangerous stunts and win intense races. If you can beat your opponents and impress the audience, you'll advance into other episodes to win better cars. Choose from 30 authentic Hot Wheels cars in 24 stunt challenges, and race on 12 tracks set in such environments as Buccaneer Bay, Jurassic Jam, Zero Gravity Zone, Tiki Island, Spider Alley, and Lava Land. At the end of the season, the driver with the most courage and best stunt skills will cruise away in a gold-plated car as the Hot Wheels champion.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/920566.htmlCheat: Passwords for Champions League ModeEnter these at the password screen under options.Cheat: Passwords for Champions League ModeEnter these at the password screen under options.Cheat: Passwords for Champions League ModeEnter these at the password screen under options.Cheat: Unlock Champions League ModeFinish the whole Game Show Mode to unlock it.Cheat: Unlock Champions League ModeComplete these races in Game Show Mode to unlock these cars.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>THQ</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>25984</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920566-hot-wheels-stunt-track-challenge</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hot-wheels-stunt-track-challenge/3030-10923/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/25984-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/25984-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/2/d/gfs_59284_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/f/d/gfs_59284_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/4/d/gfs_59284_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/5/d/gfs_59284_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/e/d/gfs_59284_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Players are thrust into competition on a hot new extreme game show -- on which they must complete perilous stunts and win intense races. The goal is to beat opponents and impress the audience with fearless maneuvers, in order to advance into other episodes and win better cars. At the end of the season, the driver with the most courage and best stunt skills will cruise away in a gold-plated car as the Hot Wheels Champion. Players choose from 30 authentic Hot Wheels cars to compete in 24 stunt challenges on 12 different tracks set in environments such as Buccaneer Bay, Jurassic Jam, Zero Gravity Zone, Tiki Island, Spider Alley and Lava Land. Players can also customize their cars with unique colors, wheels and decals.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ba84abf1-a5f6-42b6-9fd4-ac091b47111b.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>