<Game>
	<Name>Hot Wheels - World Race (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Welcome to a world where life revolves around the Hot Wheels World Race circuit--a series of races involving treacherous jumps, challenging competition, and death-defying loops. This is the life you've chosen and you'll need a good team and a dependable Hot Wheels car to survive. When you're ready, you'll tear up the tracks, jump to extreme heights, and collect pickups to trigger shortcuts. Becoming champion of the Hot Wheels tracks won't be easy, but you can always practice with a friend in head-to-head races.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/914882.html</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>THQ</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>25995</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/914882-hot-wheels-world-race</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/25995-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/5/e/gfs_51924_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/8/e/gfs_51924_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/3/e/gfs_51924_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/2/e/gfs_51924_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/9/e/gfs_51924_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>In Hot Wheels Highway 35 World Race, racing is taken to a new level as players are thrust into the unique futuristic Hot Wheels fantasy world where life revolves around the most intense stunt racing ever imagined. Players race against the clock on extreme tracks featuring split/multi-level courses, obstacles and speeds unlike anything ever experienced before. Players will be able to pull-off wild gravity-defying stunts, speed through huge loops, drive up walls, find hidden shortcuts or simply just race opponents through volcanoes, ice, mountains and more. The game lets players choose from authentic Hot Wheels cars.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d54c1950-2655-4cc1-a095-561c20b7d82e.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9caab79f-c443-466e-bbfa-f6edb4a98acb.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>