<Game>
	<Name>Hudson Best Collection Vol. 6 - Bouken-jima Collection (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Hudson Best Collection Vol. 6: Bouken Jima Collection is a Miscellaneous game, developed and published by Hudson,which was released in Japan in 2006.Cheat: Near the end of the first level, before a sign that says ''G'' on it, jump up at the edge of the cliff that's after the platforms.  If you find an egg (that contains a bee), you know you've done it.  At any Game Over screen from now on, hold UP, A, and SELECT.  Then press START.  You should repappear in the start of the level you died at with some extra lives.  This game has a few versions and the code only works for some versions, oddly enough.Cheat: When you defeat the first boss, pause the game as the first boss leaves the screen. You'll be able to see the next boss.Cheat: Get to the Title screen. Press Down, Up, Left, Right, B, A, B, A. Cheat: Locate the fifth skull in the very first cave in the game.  Once you've pass it, jump around to find a new hidden room.  You'll find a bee.  At any Game Over screen from now on, hold LEFT.  Then press START.  You will continue regularly with all the items you had before.Cheat: When you're at the title screen, press the following buttons in this order:Right, Left, Right, Left, A, B, A, BYou will then be able to choose which Island you want to play on in this new ''World Select'' menu. Use A to confirm.Cheat: Choose the password option in the main menu and enter these codes. Higgins will start at his house with certain conditions. These conditions are: the number of hearts, which powers have been obtained, which dinosaurs have been freed, the current warp egg location, as well as which items he has in his inventory. For easier referencing, use the following list: (ex. Tools=3 means you have the first three tools on the list, Dino=0 means no dinosaurs have been saved, etc.)Cheat: SP.ITEM: Egg, Compass, HeartItem, Potion, HomeIcon, FairyTOOLS: Bone, Hammer, Torch, WaterGun, Snowboard, Spear, Umbrella, C.Hammer, Surfboard, Boomerang, Skateboard, TomahawksPOWER: P-power, J-power, D-powerDINO:Spade, Heart, Club, Diamond, Star</plot>
	<releasedate>19/1/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>Hudson</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/930308-hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bouken-jima</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bkenjima-collection</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bouken-jima-collectio/3030-44836/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/16/164924/2582381-6390278331-93030.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/8/7/6/71876_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179452-hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bokenjima-collection-game-boy.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179453-hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bokenjima-collection-game-boy.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179448-hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bokenjima-collection-game-boy.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179450-hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bokenjima-collection-game-boy.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179454-hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bokenjima-collection-game-boy.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179449-hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bokenjima-collection-game-boy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179455-hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bokenjima-collection-game-boy.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179451-hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bokenjima-collection-game-boy.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179456-hudson-best-collection-vol-6-bokenjima-collection-game-boy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/b/9/gfs_70727_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>