<Game>
	<Name>James Pond - Codename Robocod (USA) (En,Fr,Es,Pt)</Name>
	<plot>In his second adventure James Pond must retrieve the toys Dr Maybe has stolen. Pond has been armed with an Inspector Gadget-style stretch device, which he can use to view higher areas or claw onto ceilings so as to slide across them.The gameplay takes place across worlds themed around particular types of toys, such as sporting goods, candy and aircraft. The levels scroll sideways, although a small amount of vertical movement is included. On each level Pond must collect 2 penguins and reach the exit, although there are usually multiple exits and lots of secret areas to explore. After completing each pair of two worlds (each of which has three sub levels), a boss must be faced.http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/james-pond-2-codename-robocodCheat: Level PasswordsEnter the code's on the Password Screen, in Continue Game Option, on the Main Menu of the Game.Cheat: God modeAt the start go to the first building then stretch up to collect in this order:Cake, Hammer, Earth, Apple, Tap you are then invincible, the older among you like myself will remember this from the Amiga version. You may need to redo the task to get the invincibility before starting a new level or it may expire in the new level when sent back to the hub.Cheat: Power ComboCollect the following in order to refill your power batteries - Penguin, Oil Can, Wine Glass, Earth and Racket - spelling POWER.Cheat: Power ComboCollect the following items in order to gain an Unlimited Lives Combo - Lips, Ice Cream, Violin, Earth, Snowman - spelling LIVES.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Valcon Games</Developer>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>18438</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/544822-james-pond-codename-robocod</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/james-pond-2-codename-robocod</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/james-pond-2-codename-robocod/3030-397/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/93770/2364821-snes_superjamespond.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/145160-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464115-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464116-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464117-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464119-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464120-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464121-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464122-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464123-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464124-james-pond-2-codename-robocod-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Gp6FbNC.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/18438.png</clearlogo1>
</game>