<Game>
	<Name>Jazz Jackrabbit (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>A cross between Bugs Bunny and Han Solo, Jazz is up to his usual world saving tricks, although this time there's an even bigger incentive: money.In an original GBA exclusive title, Jazz must explore 24 levels for as much money as he possibly can. That money can then go towards new weapons with which to destroy the enemy, such as the usual assortment of blasters, rocket launchers and flamethrowers.Along with the single player adventure, multiplayer modes are also included for up to 4 people, with game modes ranging from the usual deathmatch style to capture the flag.Cheat: Bonus CreditsTo net yourself 500 credits, pause the game, and enter: Right, Left, Right, Left, L, R, Up, Up, R, R, L, L *Note: [I]This code only works once per game[/I]*Cheat: Bonus CreditsDuring the game, press START to pause the game and then enter the following codes:Cheat: Bonus CreditsAn even better credit code, this one nets you 5000 of them.  Like always, pause the game, and enter: Up, Right, Down, Left, L, L, Right, Left, R, R, L, L If you need more money than this, you can stack the other credit codes with this one as well. *Note: [I]Like the other credit codes, this can only be used once per game[/I].*Cheat: Bonus CreditsTo gain yourself an additional 1000 credits, pause the game, and enter: Up, Down, Up, Down, Left, Right, L, R, L, R, R, L Yes, this code does stack with the 500 bonus credit code, for a total of 1500 bonus credits. *Note: [I]This code can only be used once per game[/I]* </plot>
	<releasedate>19/11/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Jaleco Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>1.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>17490</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/562337-jazz-jackrabbit</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/jazz-jackrabbit_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/jazz-jackrabbit/3030-46792/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/17490-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/17490-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189688-jazz-jackrabbit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189689-jazz-jackrabbit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-there-are-four.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189690-jazz-jackrabbit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-starting-location.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189691-jazz-jackrabbit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-your-basic-weapon.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189692-jazz-jackrabbit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-enter-the-carrot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189693-jazz-jackrabbit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-will-need.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189694-jazz-jackrabbit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-medikits-will.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189695-jazz-jackrabbit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-first-boss.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189696-jazz-jackrabbit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-zoe-cottontail.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/189697-jazz-jackrabbit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-as-you-progress.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/FN8clZ4.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/17490.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Now our hero is jazzed up with trick new weapons and tactics, super-cool environments, and a slew of slimy opponents waiting to turn you into rabbit stew. Watch out for surprises as fantastic characters like Zoe Cottontail, Professor Lapin, Spaz and more, unite their powers to help Jazz kick some intergalactic butt.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f379422a-921c-431b-ae79-b27a9f772ae8.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dce2c4d2-04bb-4e05-8cdb-7fe2ac683bdc.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Jaleco</Publisher>
</game>