<Game>
	<Name>Jonny Moseley Mad Trix (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Jonny Moseley Mad Trix is a skiing game released for the Playstation 2 and Game Boy Advance. The game was developed by 3DO for the Playstation 2 and by GFX Construction for the Game Boy Advance. The game poses the question "What if it snowed in San Francisco?" and proceeds to show you just that. The player visits a variety of destinations across the globe and attempts to earn points to unlock new skiers, gear and levels.The game's namesake and cover athlete is a gold medal winning skier (1998 Winter Olympics), the former host of MTV's Real World/Road Rules Challenge, appeared on the cover Rolling Stone, and has even been featured on Saturday Night Live.Gameplay:The sole objective in Jonny Moseley Mad Trix is to earn a preset amount of points to earn either a bronze, silver or gold medal. As points are earned players are able to unlock additional equipment and new skiers. The best way to describe the gameplay is to think of it as a simplified version of the SSX series. The player controls their skier using the left analog stick (or D-pad on the Game Boy Advance version) and uses the rest of the controllers buttons to perform tricks. The game was generally very negatively received. Jonny Moseley Mad Trix has become a rather humorous point of ridicule for the video game community, becoming the butt of many jokes from Giant Bomb employees to X-play.LocationsCourses in this game cover real world locations, such as:AlaskaAntarcticaSan FranciscoLake TahoeRomeMachu PicchuLas VegasWashington D.CNepalMt. Kilimanjaro</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>3DO Company, The</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>26005</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/565739-jonny-moseley-mad-trix</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/jonny-moseley-mad-trix_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/jonny-moseley-mad-trix/3030-834/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/26005-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/170219-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/170220-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349280-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349281-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-screenshot-illegal.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349282-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-screenshot-medals.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349283-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-screenshot-character.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349284-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-screenshot-at-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349285-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-screenshot-bumpy-terrain.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349288-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-screenshot-leaping.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349289-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-screenshot-grinding.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349290-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-special.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/349291-jonny-moseley-mad-trix-game-boy-advance-screenshot-stage-select.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Jonny Moseley's bringin' new-school skills to the world's first trick-based skiing game! Rack up big points with tons of tricks including the Tai Pan, Illegal, and Moseley's signature move, the Dinner Roll. Get heli-dropped onto a mountain to huck yourself off every object that you can find. Take new school skiing to the max!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f53beb31-2da9-4276-b231-9e8a571b1631.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>3DO</Publisher>
</game>