<Game>
	<Name>Juka and the Monophonic Menace (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>A long time ago, the mysterious "Ancients" created machines across the land that were able to harness the power of sound.  The Ancients disappeared, leaving only their devices for future civilizations to discover.  Years later, the "Settlers" arrived and built their cities in the lands where the machinery was left, and all was prosperous.However, nothing remains perfect forever.  Powerful alchemists tried to harness the power of the Ancients' machines in their lust for power, and war broke out.  Those that tried to use the Ancients' machines, or The Dark Alchemists, as they became known, were killed or exiled, and peace eventually returned.  Rumour has it though, that the last of the Dark Alchemists, the Monophonic Menace, has returned to conquer the world.Juka and the Monophonic Menace is an action-adventure game.  The title character, Juka, is an alchemist who can collect ingredients from trees, water, bushes, and other places to mix and create potions.  Potions can be used as a form of defense against enemies, can alter the landscape, or even activate machines.  Juka also has a "Sound Staff", which can be used to absorb and fire back different types of sounds at certain enemies.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SouthPeak Interactive, LLC</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>14680</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/928484-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/juka-and-the-monophonic-menace</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/juka-and-the-monophonic-menace/3030-17024/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4647/1283854-jukau.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59571-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59572-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463344-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463345-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463346-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463347-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463348-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463349-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463350-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463351-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463352-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463353-juka-and-the-monophonic-menace-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/14680.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Taking place in the world of Obla, Juka and the Monophonic Menace follows the journey of young alchemist Juka as he sets out to save his village from the evil Monophonic Menace. Gamers will help guide Juka and his assistant Bufo through six different environments while searching for items, solving puzzles, and defeating the Monophonic Menace's minions. Juka can shimmy, swim, jump, and climb through the highly detailed environments. Plus, players can enhance and upgrade Juka's many abilities by completing quests and collecting the various items. Another feature of the game is the alchemy ability. By collecting the six different elemental ingredients, players can mix and create their own items and potions for use during the game. This is the only way to get many of the more powerful potions. Combat is also unique in JUKA. Instead of battling or using magic, players have to quickly match a series of patterns. The quicker and more accurately the patterns are matched, the more damage an enemy takes. Juka and the Monophonic Menace takes many concepts that RPG and action/adventure gamers have come to love and combines them with an innovative combat system and an unique storyline to create a game full of fun, challenge, and excitement.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0284ff64-2647-42c1-a2b5-3af6e4ee3d55.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7567a28e-ca1d-4cbe-a8ca-5d9592f778e6.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>SouthPeak Games</Publisher>
</game>