<Game>
	<Name>Kaze no Klonoa G2 - Dream Champ Tournament (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Floppy-eared hero Klonoa returns in another fast-paced, colorful side-scrolling adventure for the Game Boy Advance. In his latest challenge, Klonoa must race against time and other dream travelers in the Dream Champ Tournament to collect stars, sun and moon stones to become the ultimate Dream Champion. Combining platform, puzzle and adventure elements, Klonoa 2: Dream Champ Tournament is just the adventure fans of the series have been anticipating. Explore the intricate and puzzle-packed worlds where you&amp;#146;ll meet a wide variety of interesting creatures! Solve Fiendishly-Designed Puzzles &amp;#151; Use Boxes, Bomb Boxes, Switches, Pressure Switches, Goomis, Springs and Scales in your quest for glory. Hoverboard Races &amp;#151; Each world contains a fast-paced thrill ride of gem collecting fun! Master your Skills to Win &amp;#151; Klonoa must prove his skills against other dream travelers in the Dream Champ Tournament.Cheat: Unlock Dream GalleryThere is actually a purpose to collecting those Sun Fragments in each stage. If you get all of them in a world, an EX level is unlocked for you to play. In order to play the EX Stages, you must beat the game and have every Sun Fragment from every level of the game. Only then will you be able to play the EX stages.Cheat: Easier S-ranksAttaining the vaunted S-rank in each stage hinges on four requirements: acquiring all gems, taking no damage, using no retries, and collecting the sun fragment for each stage.  However, there's a trick to getting around one of these requirements.  If you're stumped or otherwise irreversibly stuck on any particular screen (i.e. a block is where it shouldn't be and can't be recovered) simply leave the screen and come back.  The enemies, blocks and monster pots will be reset to their original position, but it won't count as a retry when your final score is tallied!Cheat: Easier S-ranks(Note: there are a few rooms in the game where you can become physically stuck and unable to leave the room at all, however, these rooms are few and far between.)</plot>
	<releasedate>23/2/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Now Production</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ufmNfmFUvrc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2339</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/563078-klonoa-2-dream-champ-tournament</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2339-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2339-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/6/6/gfs_22529_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/b/6/gfs_22529_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/0/6/gfs_22529_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/1/6/gfs_22529_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/a/6/gfs_22529_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2339-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2339-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2339-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2339.png</clearlogo1>
</game>