<Game>
	<Name>Kessaku Sen! - Ganbare Goemon 1, 2 - Yuki Hime to Magginesu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>A port of the SNES adventure/platformers Legend of the Mystical Ninja and its sequel, Ganbare Goemon 2: Kiteretsu Shogun Magginesu for the GBA. In both games you play as the wily Goemon, a wacky adventurer from feudal japan, as he attempts to fight evil across the land.Both games are action platformers, with the unique addition of several mini-games and different gameplay sequences to mix things up a little. Goemon (and his pal Ebisumaru in the sequel) can use a wide variety of weapons and items, which can be collected in-game or bought at special stores.For the GBA version both games have been updated with a save-game feature, as well as with minor fixes and additions (such as the ability to switch characters on the fly). There's also a new playable character for the second game, new graphic effects and new mini-games which once unlocked can be played directly from the main menu.Cheat: In world 2, enter the town. Go all the way right and enter the house with the purple drapes. Buy the pass for 480 gold. Now leave the store and go right to where the guards are. With the pass they will let you go through. Go all the way up, then all the way left and smash the last barrel you see. It will open a hidden underground level which will lead you out of the town and will open up the hidden Forest level. Pass that stage and you'll reach the hidden Amusement Park stage. In that stage, you can play a bunch of minigames and see some cameos from other Konami games.Cheat: After finishing the game, load the save file, go back to the 2nd world and enter the hidden Amusement Park stage. Once in the stage, go one screen up and enter the castle in the center. Talk to the girl and then go out. You now have to get 4 demon heads to access the hidden Hell stage where Dracula (from Castlevania) is the boss. To get them, you have to play the hard versions of the Goemon Memory Game, Devil Bazooka, Floor Sweeper and XEXEX. After finishing a minigame, press Start to see the demon head you have received. It's extremely hard to achieve, but once you get 4 of them, go back to the castle and talk to the girl. She'll send you to the Hell level.Cheat: From the menu select "Continue" and then "From Logbook Entry" and enter this as your logbook to start on the last level with full health, a weapon at level three, all items, and all jutsus.  From here, simply keep heading up and left through the hallways until you get to a cell with a white wall.  Hit different parts of the wall until you hear a sound like you're making contact.  Keep hitting that spot and a door will open up.  Enter and you're on the last side-scrolling mission stocked to the gills.Cheat: From the menu select "Continue" and then "From Logbook Entry" and enter this as your logbook to start on the second to last level with full health, a weapon at level three, all items, and all jutsus. From here, keep heading up and go through the doors to the castle. You'll meet the king who will tell you to go find the secret passage.  Exit, go down one screen, go left until you see three statues.  Beat the middle one until it breaks.  Enter and you're on the second to last side-scrolling mission stocked to the gills.  (Because there's no 'heart' nor 'triangle' character on my keyboard, I've used  to mean 'heart' and  to mean 'triangle'.  Make the appropriate substitutions when entering the code.)</plot>
	<releasedate>21/4/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Konami Corporation</Developer>
	<rating>4.6</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/924761-kessakusen-ganbare-goemon-12</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/kessakusen-ganbare-goemon-12-yuki-hime-to-magginesu</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/265723-kessakusen-ganbare-goemon-1-2-yuki-hime-to-magginesu-game-boy-advance-front-cover.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/265724-kessakusen-ganbare-goemon-1-2-yuki-hime-to-magginesu-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465388-kessakusen-ganbare-goemon-1-2-yuki-hime-to-magginesu-game.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465392-kessakusen-ganbare-goemon-1-2-yuki-hime-to-magginesu-game.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465393-kessakusen-ganbare-goemon-1-2-yuki-hime-to-magginesu-game.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465394-kessakusen-ganbare-goemon-1-2-yuki-hime-to-magginesu-game.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/1/3/gfs_59432_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/c/3/gfs_59432_1_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/7/3/gfs_59432_1_3.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/6/3/gfs_59432_1_4.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/d/3/gfs_59432_1_5.jpg</snapshot9>
</game>