<Game>
	<Name>Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed Destiny (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Gundam Seed Destiny is an Action game, developed by Natsume and published by Bandai,which was released in Japan in 2004.Cheat: ItemsTo unlock Very Hard Mode, you must beat Hard mode with any MS. Then go buy Very Hard Mode at the shop for 1000 points.Cheat: Mini Game That Adds Extra Shop PtsAt the Ending Credits of Main Mode Mission (Any Level from Normal to Very Hard). press start then press A Button repeatedly till you see a number in the bottom right corner of the credits adding up. Every 100 button pushes gives you a added bonus to your shop points. My highest is 326 A Button Pushes. I got 600 points total. Whats yours?Cheat: Astray Red FrameIf you do not get beaten at all in the first 5 battles, Astray Red Frame will come out as an "emergency" gundam to fight you in the 6th battle.Cheat: Astray Red FrameOccasionally when you go into the shop, you'll find Cagalli in her blue 'formal' dress.Cheat: Astray Red FrameHowever, if you repeatedly enter and exit the store, the background will go purple and the shopkeeper will be Azrael. Instead of the usual items, he sells the unlockable mecha (Gold Frame Mina (Amatu), Astray, Freedom, Justice, Saviour, and the final boss, Legend, I think) for 10000 points apiece.Cheat: Astray Red FrameAlso note that the next time you enter the shop, the shopkeeper will be Lacus again, and she'll be wearing the pyjama top from Phase-Ten of SEED and looks rather out of it. (oh Kiiiiiiiira! You have some explanin' to do...) She'll nick off and change into one of her five outfits and the usual shop will be open for buisness again.Cheat: Astray Red FrameYou can repeat this as often as you like.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/11/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Fighting, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Natsume</Developer>
	<rating>7.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>7S-u9GJXpcs</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/924564-gundam-seed-destiny</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/3/8/7/63387_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/3/8/7/63387_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/d/2/gfs_58888_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/0/2/gfs_58888_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/b/2/gfs_58888_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/a/2/gfs_58888_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/1/2/gfs_58888_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
</game>