<Game>
	<Name>King of Fighters EX2, The - Howling Blood (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Overview: The King of Fighters EX2 is the second and final     KOF game for the Game Boy Advance. Aesthetic-wise, the game is based on    The King of Fighters 2000, with all of the backgrounds and music coming from that game. EX2 features 21 regular characters; this roster includes familiar KOF fighters,   KOF EX original Moe Habana, and three new characters. Reiji Oogami is a character who shares many similarities with  Chizuru Kagura, namely the ability to generate illusions to confuse the opponent, Jun Kagami is a very tall, strong woman that can smash her opponent off of the screen, and Miu Kurosaki is a schoolgirl who utilizes feathers and water manipulation.  Gameplay: As The King of Fighters is a four-button game, the controls easily carry over. In the default setting, B and A are the punch buttons, while L and R are the kick buttons. In addition to the regular four-button setup, there are also two easy-mode setups; one uses a combination of the face buttons and D-Pad for normal attacks, with L and R controlling other actions, while the other uses the two-button, pressure-based system from the Neo Geo Pocket Color KOF games.   All of KOF's basic gameplay mechanics return, including the four-jump system, rolling, and knockdown attacks. The Striker system from the NESTS-era games also returns, although it works a bit differently here: in EX2, the next available character becomes the Striker (this means that a Striker can't be summoned if the player is using his or her final character).  EX2 introduces Maximum Mode, which replaces the Counter and Armor modes from KOF 2000. Once a character receives the Master Orochi ranking (accomplished by beating Arcade mode with a certain score), he or she can activate Maximum Mode, which allows him or her unlimited Desperation Moves for a short period of time.Character RosterHeroes TeamKyo Kusanagi Moe Habana Reiji Oogami  Fatal Fury TeamTerry Bogard Andy Bogard Mai Shiranui  Ikari TeamLeona Heidern Ralf Jones Clark Steel  Korean TeamKim Kaphwan Choi Bounge Chang Koehan  Psycho Soldier TeamAthena Asamiya Sie Kensou Bao  Art of Fighting TeamRyo Sakazaki Yuri Sakazaki Takuma Sakazaki  Yagami TeamIori Yagami Jun Kagami Miu Kurosaki  Boss CharactersSinobu Amou Awakened Sinobu </plot>
	<releasedate>11/12/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>812tkTKxdAY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>11552</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/583198-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood/3030-19799/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11552-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11552-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141056-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141057-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141058-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141059-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141060-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141061-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141062-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141063-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141064-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/141065-the-king-of-fighters-ex2-howling-blood-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11552-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11552-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11552-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11552-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11552-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/wq46hfL.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/11552.png</clearlogo1>
</game>