<Game>
	<Name>Kirby - Nightmare in Dream Land (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:You are Kirby, your everyday inflatable pink blob, and you have to traverse across 2-D environments jumping over obstacles and defeating enemies. Using Kirby's unique sucking mechanic, you can suck up enemies and shoot them out in a star burst or swallow them and take over their power. These powers range greatly from giving Kirby a parasol for glide down with to having beams of plasma snaking around him.Gameplay:Kirby: Nightmare in Dream land plays like other games in the series. Kirby scrolls across the screen to point A to point B. In each lever there are hidden treasure chests and other secrets that unlock extra rooms in the hub worlds. The game has 7 worlds that all contain 6 rooms, a boss and other unlockable rooms including warps, rooms with power ups, small boss fights and sub-games.Sub-gamesThe sub-games, which are selectable in the main menu and in the hub world are simple games that can be played in multiplayer.Quick DrawA game where you press the A button at the perfect time to kill an enemy.Bomb Rally4 Kirbys hit a bomb back and forth at each other. If it's not hit at the right time, it explodes and the Kirby it was aimed at turns into a ball.Kirby's Air Grind4 Kirbys race Warp Stars on rails. Parts of the rails or rough and need to be slowed down over.Boss EnduranceIn this game, you fight all the bosses in the game (besides Nightmare) with only one life. Unlocked after game has been beaten.Extra ModeKirby must replay the entire game with half the health. Unlocked after 100% completion.Meta KnightmareThis mode stars Meta Knight, as he plays through the entire course of the game with 3 hits and no ability to save. Rather then the copy ability, Meta Knight can attack with a selection of swords attacks. Unlocked after the 100% completion, and after extra mode has been beaten.Abilities:BackdropBallBeamBurningCrashCutterHi-JumpFireFreezingHammerIceLaserLightMikeParasolSleepSparksSpikeStar RodStoneSwordThrowTornadoU.F.O.WheelCheat: Trick Mr. FrostyIn the first room of level 1-4, You can make Mr. Frosty appear before you enter the top part of the room by performing a small jump under the one-way tile (touches the tile).Cheat: Random AbilitiesWhen you suck up 2 or more enemies with abilities you can copy, the game randomly chooses one out of the 24 abilities in the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>2P2oxQDi6Ng</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2337</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561703-kirby-nightmare-in-dream-land</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kirby-nightmare-in-dream-land/3030-21775/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1865074-box_knidl.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/JbpE8Hh.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/8gWFbod.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/Hybi5bY.png</boxart4>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/210381-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/556803-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134186-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/434220-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134187-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134188-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134189-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-screenshot-still.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134190-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134191-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134192-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-screenshot-snorkel.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/134193-kirby-nightmare-in-dreamland-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2337-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2337-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2337-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/lmvy1JN.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2337.png</clearlogo1>
</game>