<Game>
	<Name>Klonoa Heroes - Densetsu no Star Medal (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Klonoa Heroes: Densetsu no Star Medal is a spin-off of the Klonoa franchise, released only in Japan on December 13, 2002. Klonoa Heroes was developed by Namco and published by Namco for the Game Boy Advance. Klonoa Heroes is a twist on the traditional Klonoa games, putting Klonoa in a more action role playing game along the lines of Legend of Zelda or Beyond Oasis. The game does have voice acting, as well. Kumiko Watanabe plays Klonoa, Takahiro Sakurai plays Guntz, Shouzou Iizuke plays Pango, and Yutaka Shimaka plays Garlen.Gameplay:Klonoa attacks an enemy in the first world.Klonoa Heroes' gameplay is very similar to the gameplay of The Legend of Zelda. Players can control one of three characters (Klonoa, Guntz, and Pango) in a top-down perspective, hitting enemies with various attacks (Klonoa with the Wind Ring seen in the platforming games, albeit with a few differences). Guntz uses a handgun, while Pango throws bombs. In addition, these characters can collect more weapons as the game progresses. Every enemy in the game is given a color (either blue or red), and the player must attack that enemy with the corresponding attack (as each weapon has a blue and red attack).Klonoa Heroes also has role playing aspects. Experience points are gathered by picking up Dream Shards after defeating enemies (failure to pick them up results in no experience). Enemies also drop coins, which can be spent on items and weapons. These items can be found in chests scattered throughout the levels, as well. Most items can be used to restore health, but there are various other uses (such as stat benefits). Leveling up also allows the player to distribute points in several different areas (traditional role playing game stats, such as attack, defense, and agility). These changes are not permanent, and can be changed at any time (when not in the middle of a level).WorldsBreezegaleJugkettle SeaThe Ruins of the MoonThe Sky TempleVolk CityThe Moon WorldLunar BaseDarkness of NahatombPlot:The game is set in an another world from the traditional Klonoa games. The game is centered around Klonoa and his goal of becoming a "true hero." The game begins with Klonoa in his hometown of Breezegale, walking around with his friend Chipple. They find a flower called the Hikari Sakura, which is said to be a rare flower that only appears during special times, and grants the person who plucks it good luck.After taking the Hikari Sakura, Popka (another friend of Klonoa) runs in to tell them that enemies have surrounded Breezegale. Klonoa goes to defeat them, and after doing so visits his friend Lolo. Lolo tells Klonoa of more enemies attacking from Bell Hill. Klonoa is surrounded at the top of Bell HIll by many small enemies, but is saved by a man named Guntz.The two continue their quest (and are eventually joined by Pango, who wants to heal his son Boris). In the end, it is revealed that a man named Garlen has joined forces with two other villains (Joka and Janga) and is behind all of the monsters in the game. The three protagonists manage to defeat them once and for all.Cheat: Music Player and Extra Visions4Cheat: Different Voices At Game StartPress L or R 3 times at the title screen (NOT the &amp;quot;Presented by Namco&amp;quot; screen). Then select any option from the main menu to hear either Pango's or Guntz's voice instead of Klonoa's.Cheat: Revival when KOedAfter you lose all HP but before you get returned to the map, there's a short amount of time in which you can use an item. This is especially useful with healing items, as they act like an Angelic Ring and revive you.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/12/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/562268-klonoa-heroes</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal/3030-1320/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/1614/820154-klonoa_heroes_gba_jp.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/80387-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/80388-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/304752-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/304753-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/304754-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/304755-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/304756-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/304757-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/304758-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/304759-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/304760-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/304761-klonoa-heroes-densetsu-no-star-medal-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b74883b2-af99-4b1e-9d0a-0d66712725de.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/699be040-51b7-487d-8e0f-55754a32e094.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5631b2d4-8efe-4f60-8bd0-1102168ee1b4.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>