<Game>
	<Name>Konami Arcade Game Collection (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Six Konami arcade classics arrive in Konami's Collectors Series: Arcade Advanced.For the first time in over ten years, play the original arcade version of the classic hit Frogger.Search the solar system, travel through time and space, and infiltrate enemy bases in Gyruss, Time Pilot, Rush 'n Attack, and Scramble.And test your martial arts skill in Yie Ar Kung Fu.With better graphics, levels, difficulty, and a multiplayer mode, Konami's compilation shows that its greatest games improve with age.Cheat: Konami Code Unlocks AddendumIn addition to the items listed in the code as written, the Konami code also unlocksCheat: Konami Code Unlocks AddendumTime Pilot - autofire, can fire constantly just by holding the shoot buttonCheat: Konami Code Unlocks AddendumYie Ar Kung Fu - Two extra fights at the end of the tournamentCheat: Konami Code Unlocks AddendumRush 'n' Attack - Two extra levels at the end of the gameCheat: Konami Code Unlocks AddendumGyruss - Extra lives, extra level at start, dual gun gotten from level at start remains with you throughout the gameCheat: Konami Code Unlocks AddendumType this code in individually in each game menu where you can choose the number of players: Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Left, Right, B, A You should hear a ring that means the code worked Frogger- Enhanced Graphics Time Pilot- Extra Level Kung Fu- Extra Characters in Vs. Mode Rush n' Attack- Extra Lives Gyruss- Enhanced Graphics Scramble- Enhanced Graphics Cheat: During Frogger's demo, when the frog gets to the last log, you can control him. You can move backward or in any direction once he gets to that last log.</plot>
	<releasedate>21/3/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>KCEA</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ULSnc-HqkTk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>23952</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/545599-konami-collectors-series-arcade-advanced</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/23952-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/1/5/9/16159_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/e/0/gfs_6974_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/3/0/gfs_6974_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/d/b/gfs_51083_1_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/0/b/gfs_51083_1_2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/b/b/gfs_51083_1_3.jpg</snapshot5>
</game>