<Game>
	<Name>Kunio Kun Nekketsu Collection 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Kunio-Kun Nekketsu Collection 2 is a Miscellaneous game, developed by Million and published by ATLUS,which was released in Japan in 2005.Cheat: Whenever you are in a screen with weapons and a wall, pick up the weapon, throw it into the wall so it bounces and lands on your feet, then pick up again and repeat the process until you maximize your points and easily win the championship.Cheat: When turning on the console, keep pressing Select. This resets an invisible time counter  to 0. Each time you press the A button, that counter goes up by 1, adding one minute of time for each half of the match (for example, press the A button 2 times to make each half of the match last 2 minutes instead of the usual 4).Cheat: The following passwords get you to a desired team in World Cup mode.Cheat: These passwords work for all teams, the only difference is the last two letters. So, use the letter combination from the key below, and insert it into the last two places of the password you want to use.Cheat: 00: USA01: Holland02: Japan03: France04: Cameroon05: Russia06: Mexico07: England08: Spain09: Brazil10: West Germany11: Argentina12: ItalyCheat: Play a "VS Match" and select the field you want to play the tournament on (Bumpy, Soil, Concrete, Sand, or Ice). At the end of the match, simply start playing "Tournament Mode", and the game will be set on the field you selected in "VS Mode".If you don't want to play the "VS Match" against someone, it's recommended to set the the timer to 1:00 minute (in codes section) and let the game play itself.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/10/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>Million</Developer>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/928692-kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection/3030-38425/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/14/149200/2216596-kunio_kun_nekketsu_collection___01.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/272220-kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection-2-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/649012-kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/649013-kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/649014-kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/649015-kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/649016-kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/649017-kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/649018-kunio-kun-nekketsu-collection-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/8/7/gfs_67933_1_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/5/7/gfs_67933_1_2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/e/7/gfs_67933_1_3.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>