<Game>
	<Name>LEGO Star Wars - The Video Game (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Lego Star Wars: The Video Game is a video game developed by Traveller's Tales and published by LucasArts. It covers the events of the first three Star Wars episodes (chronologically), and features characters modeled after the Lego Star Wars toy line. The game features no dialogue or voice acting of any kind, and as such, no explanation for the events of the game. Franchise familiarity is assumed in the player, and the game treats the source material in a largely satirical way.Gameplay:Mechanically, the game is an extremely simple hack and slash game presented in three dimensional levels, with light platforming elements. There are fifty-six playable characters in the game, (most of which are only playable in the Free Play mode), however they are all divided into four archetypes - Jedi, Blaster, Super Jump, Droid. Jedi characters can use the force to solve some simplistic puzzles and deflect enemy blaster fire; Blaster characters can shoot enemies with their blaster and possess a grappling hook; Super jump characters possess the ability to jump much higher than other characters, and droid characters do not get intentionally fired at by enemies, whilst possessing the ability to unlock certain doors.In game cutscenes add humor and life to ordinarily static Legos.As players progress through the " Story Mode", they recap the events of the New Star Wars Trilogy. This consists mainly of the Hack and Slash/Platforming gameplay, with occasional vehicular sections (for example, the large space battle featured in the opening to Episode III) breaking up the action. After a scenario has been completed, the player may enter this scenario in "free play" mode, which allows them to select any character for use in any stage of the game, including secret characters that have been unlocked. This allows various character special abilities to be used, opening the way to various secret areas not available in the story mode.As the game goes on, players accumulate "studs", the currency in the game. These may be traded in the "Diner" (hub world) of the game for bonus content, including playable characters. The entire game is playable Cooperatively, although there is no "head to head" mode.The Game-Boy advance version of the game resembles the console version, but with several differences:Portable Version.The number of playable characters is reduced to sixteen, studs are devalued, fewer levels, and a number of small gameplay tweaks. In addition, the cut-scenes are presented as still frames taken from the console versions cutscenes.The graphics of the Game-Boy Advance version of the game closely resemble the isometric graphics of Diablo.Critical ResponseThe game garnered scores in the mid-to-high 70% range, as collected by GameRankings and Metacritic. Reviewers praised the charming art style, diversity of characters and collection mechanics, however it also garnered some criticisms from the overly simplistic combat and short length of the game.Characters:If playing the PS2, Xbox, PC, or Gamecube version; these are all the characters in order of them being collected:Qui-Gon JinnObi-Wan KenobiTC-14Jar Jar BinksQueen AmidalaCaptain PanakaPadme (Battle)R2-D2Anakin Skywalker (Boy)Obi-Wan Kenobi (Jedi)R4-P17Anakin Skywalker (Padawan)PadmeC-3P0Mace WinduPadme (Clawed)YodaObi-Wan Kenobi (Episode III)Anakin Skywalker (Jedi)Chancellor PalpatineClone (Episode III)ChewbaccaWookieDarth VaderStormtrooperGonk DroidPK DroidBattle Droid (Security)Battle DroidBattle Droid (Commander)DroidekaRoyal GuardPadme (Casual)Darth MaulCloneGenosianBattle Droid (Geonosis)Super Battle DroidJango FettBoba FettLuminara UnduliKi-Adi MundiKit FistoShaak TiCount Dooku (Darth Tyranus)Grievous BodyguardGeneral GrievousClone Episode III (Sand)Clone Episode III (Pilot)Clone Episode III (Swamp)Clone Episode III (Walker)Mace Windu (Episode III)Disguised CloneDarth SideousRebel TrooperPrincess LeiaSoundLego Star Wars exclusively used music from the Prequel Trilogy of Star Wars.DevelopmentThe ship models used in the game were created out of virtual versions of single separately built Lego bricks. The developer Traveller&#8217;s Tales essentially turned Maya into an infinitely large Lego kit: &#8220;Slave-1, to build, is an afternoon. Building a new spaceship out of regular polygons would take a whole lot longer.&#8221; The cutscenes were originally animated in a Lego stop-motion style (similar to the internet videos of the same styling) with the characters being created as plastic mini figures within the game. This was eventually changed during development due to the restrictions created on the characters being represented in such a way.Cheat: Changing the color of lightsabre, force and gun shotsWhile in pause menu press each code for different color of lightsabre, force and gun shotsCheat: Changing the color of lightsabre, force and gun shotsEnter the following codes:Cheat: Unlock Characters to buy in FreeplayPlay throughout the game to unlock characters to buy in Freeplay mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/4/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Eidos, Inc., Giant Interactive Entertainment, Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>10rqUmkiav0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22262</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/924066-lego-star-wars-the-video-game</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/lego-star-wars-the-video-game_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/lego-star-wars-the-video-game/3030-251/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2284688-box_legosw.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/43277-lego-star-wars-the-video-game-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142688-lego-star-wars-the-video-game-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142689-lego-star-wars-the-video-game-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142690-lego-star-wars-the-video-game-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142691-lego-star-wars-the-video-game-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142692-lego-star-wars-the-video-game-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/142693-lego-star-wars-the-video-game-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7465/841294-lego_star_wars28.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8572/434429-lego_star_wars___the_video_game__usa__europe___en_fr_de_es_it_nl_da__14.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8572/434428-lego_star_wars___the_video_game__usa__europe___en_fr_de_es_it_nl_da__13.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8572/434427-lego_star_wars___the_video_game__usa__europe___en_fr_de_es_it_nl_da__10.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/22262.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Lego Star Wars blends Lego toys with the characters, stories, and vehicles from the prequel eras of the Star Wars universe. Now you can experience scenes from The Phantom Menace, Attack of the Clones, and Revenge of the Sith while controlling characters such as Obi-Wan Kenobi, Yoda, and Anakin Skywalker. Use the Jedi "force" to solve puzzles and manipulate environments. During your journey, you'll do everything from pod racing on Mos Espa to repelling the droid onslaught in the Genosian arena. Your friend can even join the action to help you at any time during your game.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>QwN2j_WJM-g</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9b91d070-646d-444b-b73d-5edb86b18151.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/609deb67-ff14-477d-b8b8-3cf4c93e3c5a.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Eidos Interactive</Publisher>
</game>