<Game>
	<Name>LEGO Star Wars II - The Original Trilogy (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Da)</Name>
	<plot>The game was released on September 12, 2006 in the United States and September 11, 2006 in Europe. The game was developed by Traveller&#180;s Tales for the PC, Xbox, Xbox 360, PS2, PSP, Game Boy Advance and Nintendo DS. It is based on the Star Wars toy line by the Lego Group and covers the events of the Original Star Wars Trilogy.The Nintendo DS version of the game was heavily criticized for its many bug and technical glitches, but featured a unique multiplayer mode that was not available on any other platform.This mode allowed players to play as a bounty hunter in one of 2 levels, the first level was deathmatch in Mos-Eisely, whilst the second was based off the popular game mode "Capture the Flag" and involved you rescuing a frozen Han Solo to gain points.Gameplay:A vast majority of the objects and settings are made out of the traditional Lego Bricks. One of the game&#8217;s unique features is its funny vision of the Star Wars franchise. All of the characters are silent protagonists; as the cut-scenes present no dialogue. Traveller&#8217;s Tales also included a new &#8220;Adaptive Difficulty&#8221; which shifts accordingly to the player&#8217;s skill, making the game a bit more difficult than previous versions. Also characters whose main weapon is a blaster received new moves; they can use melee attacks, automatically aim, dive and doge incoming enemy fire due to the decrease in Sith and Jedi characters. Players are also allowed to create their own custom characters. Creating custom characters was a new feature that was added by Traveller's Tales for this game. You can customize them to have a gun, a lightsaber...and if you choose a lightsaber...you can choose the colors red, green, blue, and purple.You also have to collect these things called gold bricks which you can obtain by buying them and getting them by completing special tasks. After you collect those gold bricks you can unlock the Infinite Stud Fountain When you get 66 of them you unlock the get 1,000,000 studs sub game.Characters (In Order of Obtained)LeiaRebel FriendC-3POR2-D2Ben KenobiLuke SkywalkerHan SoloChewbaccaLuke (Stormtrooper)Han (Stormtrooper)Leia (Hoth)Han (Hoth)Luke (Dagobah)YodaLuke (Bespin)Lando CalarisianLeia (Bespin)Leia (Boushh)Luke (Jedi)Han (Skiff)Leia (Slave)Lando (Palace Guard)Leia (Endor)Luke (Endor)Han (Endor)WicketDarth VaderUnlockable/Buyable CharactersRebel TrooperStormtrooperImperial Shuttle Pilot (Black)Tusken RaiderJawaGonk DroidSandtrooperGreedoImperial SpyBeach TrooperDeath Star TrooperTIE PilotImperial Officer (Gray)Grand Moff TarkinHan (Hood)Rebel Trooper (Hoth)SnowtrooperLuke (Hoth)LobotUgnaughtBespin GuardLeia (Prisoner)Gamorean GuardBib FortunaPalace GuardSkiff GuardBoba Fett4-LOMEwokImperial GuardThe EmperorAdmiral AckbarShipsX-WingY-WingMillenium FalconSnowspeederTIE FighterTIE InterceptorVader's TIE FighterTIE BomberImperial ShuttleSlave IIf playing the Playstation 2 version, then you can buy a brick that allows all of your favorite characters from the 1st Lego Star Wars game be playable in this. Those characters include: Jango Fett, Count Dooku, Darth Maul, Darth Sideous, Qui-Gon Jinn, Anakin from Episode II, Anakin from Episode III, a variety of Battle Droids, a Super Battle Droid, Kit Fisto, Shaak Ti just to name a few.Xbox 360 Game InstallationLego Star Wars II: The Original Trilogy requires 2.0GB of space to install on a Xbox 360 HDD.Cheat: Full Password ListEnter any of these at the counter of Mos Eisley Cantina under the '?' Codes optionCheat: Extras unlockablesIn the in-game store, there are some "extras" you can buy, which work as codes for the game. In order to unlock them, simply perform the stated operation.Cheat: Extras unlockablesIn order to unlock new characters in this game, which you can then use in the "Free Play" mode, you generally have to perform a certain task and then buy them from the store, for a certain number of studs.Below, you can read about what characters you can unlock and how to unlock them.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/9/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>LucasArts, TT Games Publishing Ltd</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>8wJebk0aYvc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>18916</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/932110-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy/3030-9631/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2284689-box_legosw2.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/69189-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/69190-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183908-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183909-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183910-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183911-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183912-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183913-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183914-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183915-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183917-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183918-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/HivRwxo.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/18916.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Lego Star Wars II: The Original Trilogy has you controlling LEGO versions of the original Star Wars heroes.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>8wJebk0aYvc</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ae35a701-7d7d-47a2-829f-454cabbd4878.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40b4d026-ada1-4a0c-83fe-9f6f6b3aae32.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>LucasArts</Publisher>
</game>