<Game>
	<Name>Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events (Europe) (Fr,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Based on the movie (and first three books of the series), Lemony Snicket's a Series of Unfortunate Events for Game Boy Advance puts players in the unfortunate shoes of the incredibly unlucky Baudelaire orphans: Violet, Klaus, and Sunny.Each orphan has an unusual talent that will let them progress through three chapters (each with over a dozen levels). Though the game looks like a traditional side-scroller, combat takes a backseat to clever puzzle-solving and adventure game elements. The three orphans must use their talents, along with items found in the world, and various interactions to escape each level and avoid the evil Count Olaf and his elaborate plans to inherit the children's fortune.Inventions also take a big role in this game, and players will have to assemble them from common household objects. For example, in one level, Violet will be hunting for ice cream scoopers, soup cans, and a crank to invent an "apple chucker" which can help defeat Count Olaf's friends.The game offers quite a bit of replayability, too, with quest points and exotic books earned for discovering all the game's quirky secrets.</plot>
	<releasedate>10/11/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Activision Publishing, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>26028</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920540-lemony-snickets-a-series-of-unfortunate-events</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/lemony-snickets-a-series-of-unfortunate-events_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/lemony-snickets-a-series-of-unfortunate-events/3030-3690/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1801450-box_lsasoue.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/55880-lemony-snicket-s-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/109010-lemony-snicket-s-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/145095-lemony-snicket-s-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/145096-lemony-snicket-s-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/145097-lemony-snicket-s-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/145098-lemony-snicket-s-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/145099-lemony-snicket-s-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/145100-lemony-snicket-s-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/145101-lemony-snicket-s-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4938/300322-7.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4938/300320-6.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4938/300317-5.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Lemony Snicket’s A Series of Unfortunate Events is based on the book series and DreamWorks Picture starring Jim Carrey, Jude Law and Meryl Streep. It is the only game that lets players experience first-hand the misadventures of the savvy and resilient Baudelaire orphans as they narrowly escape from the clutches of the villainous Count Olaf who is after their inheritance. In the game, players switch between the three orphans, mastering each one's skills to solve puzzles and collect various items to build ingenious inventions. Players make their way across 20 levels filled with puzzle-solving and platforming challenges. Each of the three kids has their own unique talents and skills. There's Violet, the oldest child and the inventor of the family. Then there's the middle child, Klaus, the bookworm. And lastly, there's baby Sunny, who has a penchant for mischief and four very sharp teeth.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/108b20b7-5f7e-4dfb-80d3-a278f1a3ee5d.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>