<Game>
	<Name>Lizzie McGuire - On the Go! (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Lizzie McGuire: On the Go! can be the centerpiece of any party.The game features the exciting multiplayer games such When Cheerleaders Attack! Gordo's Gunk, Dot's 'n Boxes, Box Bash, Memory, Droppers, and Hangman.Crazy party games--including Charades, MatchMaker, Fill-In's, and Operator--give you ideas to spruce up your own parties.Finally, to help plan for the next party, Lizzie McGuire lets players keep track of friends' contact information and important dates, plus horoscopes and biorhythms.Cheat: Cheat CodeChoose "PDA" from the main menu then select "Best Friends" and add the following name:Cheat: Mini-GamesGet to level 20 in the Attack Of The Cheerleaders to unlock two mini-games. For every five levels onward, you will unlock two more mini-games.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Disney Interactive</Developer>
	<VideoURL>1aqWKEeT2I4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>28169</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/918713-lizzie-mcguire-on-the-go</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/lizzie-mcguire-on-the-go/3030-39170/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/28169-1.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6087/2280398-gfs_52095_1_6.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6087/2280397-gfs_52095_1_5.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6087/2280396-20080723_105248_157.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6087/2280395-20080723_105239_330.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6087/2280394-20080723_105233_438.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/6087/2280393-1306.png</snapshot6>
	<Notes>Lizzie McGuire -- On the Go! is more than just a game! You can play the exciting arcade game "When Cheerleaders Attack!" and you and your friends can have fun with exciting games like, Gordo's Gunk, Dots 'n Boxes, Box Bash, Memory, Droppers and Hangman. You can also use Lizzie McGuire for the GBA as the centerpiece of any party! "Lizzie McGuire -- On the Go!" becomes the hit of the party as girls can use it to guide them through crazy party games like Charades, MatchMaker, Fill-In's (Mad-Libs anyone?) and Operator. Finally, to help plan for the next party, Lizzie McGuire for the GBA will let players keep track of friends' contact information, important dates, and of course, horoscopes and biorhythms! More than 20 games and activities to choose from in all!</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>1aqWKEeT2I4</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c04fb2b5-8ed6-4117-9fa6-6fb277110da4.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e6eecfd-7ab8-4834-8911-3149626bd166.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Disney Interactive Studios</Publisher>
</game>