<Game>
	<Name>Lord of the Rings, The - The Fellowship of the Ring (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Gameplay:The three playable characters in this game are: Frodo Baggins, Aragorn, and Gandalf the Grey. They each have their own weapons, items, and powers which change throughout the game. The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring plays like a hack and slash type game. The player runs through the levels killing any orcs stupid enough to get in your way, as well as several different bosses. The game's structure is very linear, allowing little deviation from the set path.The game received generally poor reviews, partially due to the fact that the game wasn't published with movie rights associated with the franchise's other releases: The Two Towers, The Return of the King, and The Third Age which many fans of the franchise had come to expect. This game did however follow the plot line of the book more closely than it's movie-based counterparts. The game does take the player through several familiar (untapped) book locations such as The Old Forest, the Barrow Downs, and Bree just to name a few. While playing through these locations the player is allowed to fight Old Man Willow as well as Barrow-wights and even meet with Tom Bombadil.This title refers to three different games: an Xbox version developed by WXP, a PC and PS2 version developed by Surreal, and a GBA version developed by Pocket Studio.Cheat: Dupe ItemsWhile trying to get across the bridge, put the item you want duped on the button the heavy object goes. Then save the game. Load it back up and take the item you dropped. There will be another one after you picked up the item you dropped! (This glitch will work with any item!)</plot>
	<releasedate>24/9/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Black Label Games</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11553</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/546323-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring__</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring/3030-4157/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11553-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/36295-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84301-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84302-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84303-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84304-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84305-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/632991-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/632992-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/632993-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/632994-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/632995-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-fellowship-of-the-ring-game-boy.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11553-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11553-2.jpg</fanart2>
</game>