<Game>
	<Name>Lord of the Rings, The - The Two Towers (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>GeneralThe Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers is the first adaptation of the movie trilogy published by Electronic Arts. This beat 'em up style game covers the events from the first two movies in the Lord of the Rings trilogy despite its' name. It boasts containing the original score from the movies as well as the actors doing the voice overs for their respective roles. The game was released on PlayStation 2, Xbox, Gamecube and Game Boy Advance. It became one of the best selling titles of 2002 and 2003, and went on to achieve Greatest Hits on PlayStation 2, Platinum Hits on Xbox, and Player's Choice on Gamecube. It is often considered one of the best movie-to-game adaptations.Game Boy AdvanceGandalf is in charge!This version of the game was met with less fanfare and as such received much less attention. In this version of the game the player may choose between playing as Aragorn, Gandalf, Frodo, Legolas, or Arwen. With these characters the player must follow along with the story and fight Saruman's hoards. Although it featured full motion video cut-scenes from the movie the actual game was far too simple to become a major seller.Plot:In this game the story is told through cut-scenes that play between missions. These cut-scenes, taken out of the movie, quickly sum up the events that take place between the various battle scenes in the movies and then seamlessly transitions into game play. The game does not follow Frodo and Sam 's separate journey but instead focuses on the rest of the fellowship. Each mission in the game helps move the story along.Mission 1: PrologueFight as Isildur in the Battle of the Last Alliance in Mordor.Mission 2: WeathertopThe Nazg&#251;l have come to take the ring from Frodo. Fight off the Nazg&#251;l with fire and protect Frodo.Mission 3: Gates Of MoriaThe path to Moria is too dangerous for the fellowship to travel. Clear the path to Moria so the fellowship may move safely. Defeat The Watcher.Mission 4: Balin's TombSurvive the onslaught of goblins and orcs. Kill the cave troll.Mission 5: Amon HenKill a certain amount of Uruk-Hai before they find Frodo. Kill their leader Lurtz.Mission 6: Fangorn ForestSearch for Merry and Pippin.Mission 7: Plains of RohanFight through town and save the villagers from the Uruk-Hai.Mission 8: The WestfoldHelp kill the Uruk-Hai and destroy the explosives.Mission 9: Gap of RohanKill the Warg soldiers to protect the citizens of Rohan. Kill the Warg captain.Mission 10: Helm's Deep 1: The Deeping WallDefend the wall by killing enemies and knocking down their ladders.Mission 11: Helm's Deep 2: Breached WallProtect the door to the Deep from Saruman's forces who are charging through the broken wall. Destroy the catapult.Mission 12: Helm's Deep 3: Hornburg CourtyardProtect the door to the Keep from the enemies who have broken through the barrier.Secret Mission: Tower of OrthancFight hordes of enemies in 20 circular rooms.Enemies:Axe-wielding OrcThere are three main types of enemies in The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers, each then have variations of their own.GoblinsThese are the easiest to kill.Normal Goblin - wields a short sword and are only dangerous in groups.Shielded Goblin - wields a club as well as a shield.Goblin Archer - wields a bow and shoots arrows tipped with fire.OrcsThese are harder to kill than Goblins as they are bigger and stronger.Axe-wielding Orc - wields two axes and spins to slash the player.Shielded Orc - wields a spear and a shield.Orc Archer - wields a bow as well as fire tipped arrows and arrows that explode on contact.Uruk-HaiThese are the hardest, but do not carry any shields.Normal Uruk-Hai - wields a very large sword.Soldier Uruk-Hai - wears a helmet and wields a large sword.Berserker - wields a very long sword and defends all basic and intermediate attacks.Exploding Uruk-Hai - carry explosives on their back and explode when they get close to their target or die.Uruk-Hai Archer - wields a bow and carry fire bombs that set the ground on fire.OtherCave Troll - very big, and very strong, carry a big spiked club.Oloh-Hai - easier trolls that also carry a pouch of logs to throw.Warg Riders - wield a bow but can also command their wargs to bite the player.Playable CharactersThere are three playable characters for most of the game, and one unlockable character at the end. Every character can perform both ranged and close combat.Aragorn - Aragorn wields a single long-sword and a bow. He is the most well-rounded and best at attacking at close range.Legolas - Legolas wields duel short-swords and a bow. He is the quickest character and excels at ranged attacks.Gimli - Gimli wields an axe and small throwing axes. He is the slowest, but most powerful character.Isildur (Unlocked) - Isildur wields a single long sword and bow and arrows. He is the same as Aragorn in all regards.Each playable character has their own unique moves, though execution of said moves is the same across all characters. Additional moves and upgrades can be bought as the player gains experience points, with the exception of Isildur who shares his move set with Aragorn. In fact, the only difference between Isildur and Aragorn is that Isildur has more health.ExperiencePerfect!Experience points are gained when a player kills an enemy. The more enemies that are killed consecutively or with combos the more experience points the player gains. Each attack is graded with a Fair, Good, Excellent or Perfect and the grade directly influences the amount of points received. After the player totals a certain number of experience points they gain a level and open up more moves and upgrades to purchase.UnlockablesBy beating certain missions or achieving certain levels with certain characters many extras are unlocked.Interview with Peter Jackson and Barrie OsborneInterview with Elijah WoodInterview with Ian McKellenMaking of "The Two Towers" video gameConcept ArtThe Fellowship of the Ring production photosFangorn Forest and Orthanc production photosRohan and Helm's Deep production photosInterview with John Rhys-DaviesInterview with Orlando BloomInterview with Viggo MortensenSecret Mission - AragornSecret Mission - LegolasSecret Mission - GimliSecret CharacterSecret Mission - Secret characterCheatsCheatsThe following Cheats are for the PS2 version of the game.Restore healthPause game play, then hold L1 L2 R1 R2 and press Triangle, Down, X, Up.Restore ammunitionPause game play, then hold L1 L2 R1 R2 and press X, Down, Triangle, Up.Add 1,000 experience pointsPause game play, then hold L1 L2 R1 R2 and press X, Down, Down, Down.Level 2 skillsPause game play, then hold L1 L2 R1 R2 and press Circle, Right, Circle, Right.Level 4 skillsPause game play, then hold L1 L2 R1 R2 and press Triangle, Up, Triangle, Up.Level 6 skillsPause game play, then hold L1 L2 R1 R2 and press Square, Left, Square, Left.Level 8 skillsPause game play, then hold L1 L2 R1 R2 and press X, X, Down, Down.Cheat: Easy Item ObtainmentThis trick can only be done once you've reached the Fangorn Troll boss fight. Fight the big troll and the little troll, using the health font in the upper right corner if you need to. Once you kill both trolls, they should drop items. Since this is a boss fight, the items tend to be of better quality &amp; more rare than usual. Collect the items, then save. Load up the save to fight the trolls again. Do this as many times as you want/need to get really good stuff. I myself, after many attempts, got the Glamdring "Unique" sword for Gandalf, as well as other good stuff for both Legolas and Aragorn. It's best to do this at a really high level, like 30+ to make the actual fight easier. Having Ent Water also helps. Make sure you are fully healed before saving. Cheat: Easy Item ObtainmentWhenever you find an item that gives negative melee armor (i.e. An item that has -1 melee armor), unequip all other items that add to your melee armor.  Now, with your armor class at 0, equip the item with -1 melee armor. This will cause your armor class to go negative, but instead of being -1, it results in a glitch, giving you over 65,000 armor class.Cheat: Copy ItemsIn multiplayer mode, player A gives item(s) to player B. then player A quits WITHOUT saving. When the screen says the GBA lost connection, player B saves the game and quits. Player A will still have the item and player B will have the copied item.Cheat: Copy ItemsWhile playing as Legolas, hold down the B button until your bow charges.  Then, while holding B, switch to overdraw and charge it by holding A.  After overdraw is charged, release the B button, and then release the A button.  You can now walk with a charged Overdraw.Cheat: Copy ItemsEnter a level with a forge, go to the forge and buy as many things as you can until you have below 30 gems. Exit the forge, then use all your SP and reenter the forge. Try to buy items and continue buying items until you hear a music sequence (it sounds like a &amp;quot;ringtone&amp;quot;).</plot>
	<releasedate>12/11/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11557</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561423-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-two-towers</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/lord-of-the-rings-the-two-towers-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-lord-of-the-rings-the-two-towers/3030-21334/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11557-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11557-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/125813-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers-dos-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76351-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/76352-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/22134-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/22135-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/22136-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/22137-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/22138-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/22139-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/22140-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/22141-j-r-r-tolkien-s-the-lord-of-the-rings-vol-ii-the-two-towers.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11557-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11557-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/o7jwOR7.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/11557.png</clearlogo1>
</game>