<Game>
	<Name>Lord of the Rings, The - The Return of the King (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King is the follow-up to The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers. The game is a brawler based on the movie of the same name, and it features ample footage of the movie trilogy. You can play as Aragorn, Legolas, Gimli, Frodo, Sam, Merry, Pippin, Gandalf and Faramir.Gameplay:The game features 13 levels following three story arcs. One story path will follow Gandalf the White, one will follow Aragorn's, Legolas' and Gimli's ventures, and the final path will follow Sam and Frodo, along with their guide, Smeagol. The game starts out with an introductory level from the second episode of the trilogy; the fight at Helms Deep. All story arcs will culminate in the same spot: the fight at the Black Gate and the level that takes place in Mount Doom.Combat is pretty simple. You have a weak attack and a powerful attack, a parry button that needs to be timed to block attacks, a button to kick enemies down, a move that will instantly kill downed enemies, and a ranged attack. Ranged attacks are tailored to specific characters, for instance, the Elf, Legolas has a very powerful bow, while Gimli has weaker throwing axes. If an enemy carries a shield, you must break it with a powerful attack or fully charged ranged attack. You can't move while parrying, although a quick sidestep move solves this problem.The game recreates scenes from the movie, but some fictional events are also turned into levels, for instance Gandalf's second level, which sees him going around Isengard slaughtering orcs.CoopTwo players can go through the entire game cooperatively, aside from the singleplayer's first level, the fight at Helm's Deep.The game's introductory level is the only one that can't be played through in coopThere used to be support for online coop, but the servers for this game were taken down in 2005 by EA, like many other games. However, with two controllers, coop on a single PS2 and TV is still possible. First the very first level in the game must be completed, then the entire rest of the game can be played with player 1 controlling whichever character is at the center of the story mode, and player 2 controlling a secondary character.Unlockables and ExtrasThere are some extras unlocked upon beating the game.Secret character: FaramirSecret character: PippinSecret character: MerryThe ability to replay any level with any character, except for the game's opening level, Helm's Deep, which can only be played through with Gandalf.Two bonus survival levels; Saruman's Palantir and Sauron's Palantir. In these levels, you are in a misty area, and you have to fight off 20 waves of enemies.Cheats, that can be activated in the pause menu during a mission.Interview with David Wenham, the actor for Faramir.Interview with Dominic Monaghan, Merry's actor.Interview with Billy Boyd, the actor who played Pippin.Interview with Andy Serkis, the actor who did the motion capture and voice for Gollum.Cheat: Duplicating Items in MultiplayerIf you are playing in multiplayer, there is a simple trick that you can use in order to give items away to other people without losing the item yourself. When you are in multiplayer, choose an item and give it to the other player. Then, quit the game without saving. Have the other person save and quit the game. When you reload, the game will not have recorded that you gave away the item so you will still have it. Since the other person saved, they will also have the item.Cheat: Duplicating Items in MultiplayerGo get a character that can equip a two-handed weapon, and a shield. Then, equip the sword and shield alternatly, and you will notice your damage on your stat screen going up. Carve armor runes to make your armor level rise too. This works with Eowyn, Gimli and Aragorn. The bug will reset once you leave an area. Cheat: Ancient ArtifactsTo unlock the ancient artifacts on your Game Boy Advance game, you must connect your Game Boy Advance Return of the King game to your GameCube Return of the King game. Ancient artifacts' names are in blue, but they are not unique items. Actually, they are fairly common once you unlock them, and some of the ancient artifacts have extremely good stats.Cheat: Ancient ArtifactsComplete the task below to unlock SmeagolCheat: Ancient ArtifactsYou can unlock Weathertop by collecting all of the artifacts. You can unlock Fanghorn by beating the game with all of the characters.Cheat: Ancient ArtifactsWhen you beat the game with any character, you unlock both of these bonus maps, which can be accessed on the main title screen.Cheat: Duplicating Items(NOTE: You'll need at least one blank save slot) To duplicate good items that you find in your quest, just: 1) Get to a level with any Forge or Shrine and a Ranger Hollow. 2) Have the item(s) in your inventory. 3) Save the game as normal, then save it to all the blank save slots you have. 4) Quit the game, start up one of the games in the save slots you just filled, and put the item(s) in the Ranger Hollow of the level. 5) Do this with all the save slots you filled. 6) Go back to your main save, and take all the items out of the Ranger Hollow, you know have duplicates of your item. 7) Repeat as wanted. Cheat: Duplicating ItemsMany people like myself don't have a Gamecube or GBA-GC Link so here's how to unlock Sam without one. First you may want to beat the game with Frodo to get all of the artifacts in his quest so then if you have all of the artifacts you can play at Weathertop with Sam. Then start a new game as Frodo. Make it through Shelob's tunnel and Shelob will ambush you making you have to use Sam. Save the game during the fight with Shelob then quit. Now you can hook up the Gameboy Advance link cable with Sam or play on bonus maps with Sam. This could also be used for training Sam against Shelob if your having trouble.Cheat: Duplicating ItemsThe the map should be 'Anduin River - Corsair Camp'. Talk to the old lady at the north of the map to do the Missing Brother Sidequest. After you return her brother, talk to her again, she'll drop a random item and you obtain 1 stat point as well. Proceed south from here, you'll meet the old lady again. Talk to her and defeat the Corsairs. After that, she'll open up her barn (or ranch), then talk to her and she'll drop another item. Save, quit, reload and repeat. (Note: If you didn't talk to the old lady after she opened the barn, when you reload, the game will know you've finished the missing brother sidequest, which means you can never get the 1stat point reward from her again.)</plot>
	<releasedate>6/11/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11559</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/914708-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king/3030-17686/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11559-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11559-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66325-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66326-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66327-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66328-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66329-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66330-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66331-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66332-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66333-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/66334-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-return-of-the-king-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11559-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11559-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/2Cj7ync.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/11559.png</clearlogo1>
</game>