<Game>
	<Name>Lufia - The Ruins of Lore (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Story:This game takes place 20 years after Lufia 2. The world is at peace and all seems perfect.But war is coming as a power hungry man allies himself with the .  As evil spreads and chaos reigns terror down on hapless villages a hero arises to fight back.Characters:EldinA young man whose father has disappeared. He qualifies as a monster hunter and leaves Parcelyte in search of adventure. His field ability is a sword, to chop through grass and bush.TormaEldin's best friend and fellow monster hunter, his field ability is a whip which can traverse gaps in the terrain.RamiEldin and Torma's friend from their hometown, she too is a monster hunter (qualified through dubious means) whose speciality is magic. Her field ability is that she can light fires, which is used to light candles, fuses, torches and the like.  Dekar  Dekar returns from Lufia 2, having not been involved in the fight against the Sinistrals. He has the same personality as in Lufia 2, being a womaniser whose strength is famed across the land. Throughout the game, however, he tries to become more responsible, as the older character in the story.   Cheat: Infinite NectarGo to the blacksmith in Gruberik. Make sure you have the ingredients for a Nectar (and found the alchemist). Make a Nectar. The blacksmith will make the item like normal, but you won't lose the ingredients! You can get infinite Nectars at no cost.Cheat: Infinite NectarSacrifice kills the enemy and the user. However, there is a glitch. If you use Sacrifice on yourself, you heal 999 HPCheat: Easy Gold in OrdensOnce you reach the town of Ordens go to the item shop and buy as many Blue Teas as possible for 100 gold each. Then you can sell them back for 150 gold each. You can make between 50 and 4450 gold each time. </plot>
	<releasedate>6/5/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>wdPfgEYTmfg</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>11196</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589582-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/lufia-the-ruins-of-lore</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/lufia-the-ruins-of-lore/3030-12264/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11196-3.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11196-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/185211-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264751-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264752-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-screenshot-story.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264753-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-screenshot-sunset.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264754-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-screenshot-zooming.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264755-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-characters.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264756-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264757-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-screenshot-story.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264758-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-screenshot-rand-is.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264759-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-characters.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/264760-lufia-the-ruins-of-lore-game-boy-advance-screenshot-gold-may.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/s3ZcfJb.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>This exciting new chapter in the Lufia saga follows the adventures of Eldin, Torma, and Rami, a group of friends and would-be hunters as they set out in search of treasure, only to discover that fate has much more in store for them! Will they be able to solve the mysteries of the ancient ruins and stop the power-hungry leader Ragule from resurrecting the ancient beast, or will Ragules ambitions be realized at the expense of mankind? Prepare for the Adventure of a Lifetime!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/714450e3-35c0-462f-afc3-ed32b22ad787.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ac2b6f31-c1e8-44d7-bdc4-78f0163b7745.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f9f9b255-6ff6-4b79-8112-cbe69905c5a1.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
</game>