<Game>
	<Name>Lunar Legend (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Based off the popular Sega CD and PSOne RPG title, Lunar Legend retells the story of Alex, the boy who aspires to be a Dragonmaster like his hero Dyne.  Grouped with all of his allies from the original game, Alex and friends embark on the traditional fantasy adventure quest to defeat Emperor Ghaleon from discovering and abusing the hidden power that Luna holds. This is a traditional turn-based combat RPG filled with magic spells, hidden weapons and quests to discover, and lots of humor in the overall story.Cheat: Equipment Duplication TrickTo duplicate equipment equip the item as you normally would.  Unequip it and save, when you load up your game you should have 2 of the original item.Cheat: Equipment Duplication TrickBefore you buy any cards from the card shop, save the game in slot 1. Then buy as many cards as you want. After you finish buying cards, save your game in slot 2, then load your game from slot 1. You will have the cards you bought, as well as the money you spent on them.Cheat: Equipment Duplication TrickAll you have to do is save your game and turn it off. When you turn it back on all your characters will be at full health and magic. You can do it as many times as you want.Cheat: Equipment Duplication TrickPetrify (using nash's stone skill or another skill) an enemy and then cast riot, it will do massive damage.Cheat: Equipment Duplication TrickBeat the Game Once to Unlock The Sound and Music Test in the Options Menu.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/12/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Ubi Soft Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>sJXRrK_OD9g</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3768</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/560993-lunar-legend</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/lunar-legend</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/lunar-legend/3030-5395/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2375804-box_lunarl.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3768-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/201394-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178692-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178694-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-options-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178693-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178695-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro-a-young-boy.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178696-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-we-see-alex-trying.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178697-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-good-one-nall.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178683-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-alex-s-friend-ramu.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178684-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-on-the-way-to-meet.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178685-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-gotta-love-free-items.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/178686-lunar-legend-game-boy-advance-screenshot-luna-singing.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/NVOqtcn.png</banner1>
	<Notes>You play Alex, a young boy who hopes to one day be a Dragonmaster like his dearly departed hero Dyne. One day, a wizard named Nash comes into town, and needs an escort to a nearby shrine in the woods. You, your childhood friend Luna, and your flying cat-like pet Nall accompany Nash to the shrine, and your adventure begins.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/79cf543e-360a-4732-b690-8303bf515d32.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4565946b-225c-45df-85cd-2ff747af2a60.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/60bd5f1a-0478-4735-9eaf-9617616a824b.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>