<Game>
	<Name>Madden NFL 2003 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>In the game you control the ball by players of your favorite team to win the match. Opposite players also has tactic commands of their coach to take the ball from you. The game for first time features on-line gaming capability and also adds new teams like Houston Texans, and new NFL division alignment.The game also has Create-a-Player option, where the players can determine in mini-games their physical conditions, for example, to be receivers or quarterbacks. Later you can include these players into teams. However, there is also availability to trade players instead of train them. Also the game has an option, which allows to play from playbook and then practice it. In XBox, Windows, PS2, PSX, GameCube versions the commentary is provided by Al Michaels. The game has rendered graphics with all animation based on it.The GBA version has graphics similar to Madden '94 for SNES and Genesis, but has multiplayer mode using GCN/GBA cable.The game is up to 4 players.Cheat: Sounds after a TouchdownAfter scoring a touchdown, press the A, B, R or L buttons to make various sounds. </plot>
	<releasedate>12/8/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>28175</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561310-madden-nfl-2003</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/madden-nfl-2003</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/madden-nfl-2003/3030-15987/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/28175-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/146081-madden-nfl-2003-gamecube-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/146082-madden-nfl-2003-gamecube-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/500252-madden-nfl-2003-windows-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/500254-madden-nfl-2003-windows-screenshot-credits.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/500255-madden-nfl-2003-windows-screenshot-bill-belichick-consults.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/500256-madden-nfl-2003-windows-screenshot-play-selection.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/500257-madden-nfl-2003-windows-screenshot-jeff-wilkins-is-set-for.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/500258-madden-nfl-2003-windows-screenshot-kurt-warner-s-stats-so.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/500259-madden-nfl-2003-windows-screenshot-marshall-faulk-celebrates.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/500260-madden-nfl-2003-windows-screenshot-deion-branch.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/500261-madden-nfl-2003-windows-screenshot-it-s-3rd-and-15-and-the.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/500262-madden-nfl-2003-windows-screenshot-grant-wistrom-suffers-a.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>In its 13th year, Madden NFL? Football is the undisputed leader in authentic NFL football simulation. Its combination of jaw-dropping graphics and animations, realistic player AI, in-depth play modes, and the most innovative features is beyond comparison. With a primary focus on in-game graphics and game play, this is the best looking, sounding and playing football game ever. This season Madden NFL Football continues to establish why it is the definitive interactive football experience. Madden NFL 2003 features online gaming capability for the first time and also includes the new Houston Texans and the new NFL divisional alignment.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3793748c-856f-48c2-b786-3cc8f74aa638.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/392a58eb-d50c-44ea-a2f2-5d5e90b45c4a.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>