<Game>
	<Name>Madden NFL 2002 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The undisputed leader in authentic NFL football simulation steps onto the turf for another gridiron conquest. Painstaking football realism comes alive in true-to-life graphics and time-tested gameplay. For the 12th year in a row and the second score on the PlayStation 2 computer entertainment system, Madden NFL Football brings the realism of the pro gridiron right to your fingertips. With all the teams, players, and features that you've come to know and love, Madden puts you right on the field with the big hitters!Play a full season with your favorite team and take them to the Super Bowl, or try the franchise mode and build a dynasty. You can even create teams and players so you can start from scratch! With all-new realistic player animations, Madden Cards, a training mode, and the Two-Minute Drill, Madden truly has it all!Cheat: Extra SoundsAfter scoring a touchdown, press either the A, B, R or L buttons to make sounds.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/11/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>28174</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/565736-madden-nfl-2002</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/madden-nfl-2002</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/madden-nfl-2002/3030-10845/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/28174-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/179824-madden-nfl-2002-gamecube-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/211121-madden-nfl-2002-gamecube-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/a/7/gfs_51534_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/7/7/gfs_51534_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/c/7/gfs_51534_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/d/7/gfs_51534_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/6/7/gfs_51534_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Everyone's favorite coach-turned commentator is back with another dose of hard-hitting pigskin. MADDEN NFL's signature style goes to the next level in this unbelievable game, delivering realistic football physics and photo-quality cutscenes. You'll have access to all of the real NFL teams and players all with accurate uniforms, abilities, and appearances. All of the standard modes of play are included, and there are a few new entries, such as Two-Minute Drill (earn points on offense by moving the ball quickly up the field) and Create-a-Team (build your franchise from the ground up including uniforms, helmets, and coaching philosophy). Coach's Corner will teach you about all the ins and outs of NFL Football, and all of the action is called by (you guessed it) John Madden, himself. All of the real playbooks and coaching strategies of the pro teams are at your fingertips, so you have no excuse for losing in this one, folks.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/297a5daf-473d-4dbd-9bb5-be855fd300a2.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a539b56d-66a9-4567-900c-7cc2b5e52e99.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>3</rating>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>