<Game>
	<Name>Madden NFL 2004 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Madden NFL 2004, featuring then-Atlanta Falcons quarterback Michael Vick on the cover, is the 14th installment of the Madden NFL Franchise. It was released on August 11, 2003.New features include a new owner mode that allows the player to control multiple financial facets of a franchise, such as vendor prices, advertising, stadium renovations and hiring and firing coaches. Other new features include a training camp to increase player stats in franchise mode, and offensive playmaker to let the player change the play on the fly using the right control stick.Michael Vick fell to the fabled "Madden Cover Curse" when he broke his right fibula in a preseason game against the Baltimore Ravens, just 5 days after the release of Madden NFL 2004. The curse continued to affect Vick when he was arrested for accusations of hosting and participating in dogfighting matches in 2007.Soundtrack:Adema - "Unstable"AFI - "The Leaving Song, Part II"Alien Ant Farm - "These Days"AM Radio - "Taken for a Ride"Avenged Sevenfold - "Chapter Four"blink-182 - "Action" (NOTE: The final version of the song is actually titled "Feeling This." " The song was also heavily edited for the game, taking out all of the sexual references.)Bone Crusher - "Never Scared (Madden Remix)"Bubba Sparxxx - "Back in the Mud"Gob - "Give Up the Grudge"Jet - "Are You Gonna Be My Girl?"Joe Budden - "Pump It Up"Killer Mike - "Akshon (Yeah!)"Killer Mike - "Akshon (Yeah!) (Madden Remix)"Nappy Roots - "Roun' the Globe"OutKast - "Church"Red Cafe - "May I (Madden Remix)"Serafin - "Day By Day"SOiL - "Pride"The Federation - "Mayhem (Madden Remix)"The Roots - "Rock You (Madden Remix)"Thrice - "All That's Left"Unloco - "Crashing"Yellowcard - "Way Away"Cheat: Easy sacks of the opposing quarterbackBy exploiting an easy to learn AI weakness, you can score a sack on nearly every play in Madden 2004.Cheat: Easy sacks of the opposing quarterbackWhen on defense, pick the Free Fire blitz from within the 4-3 package. Move your two interior lineman away from the ball one click each, move the lineback on the left down, and move the middle linebacker a little bit to the right and a little down. When the offense snaps the ball, the left tackle will go to block the linebacker on the left, the left guard will block the defensive end on the left, and the center will block the middle linebacker. This will give the interior lineman on the left side a huge hole and have a free path to the quarterback, which is a tactic that the offensive AI will hardly ever account for and can easily lead to several hundred sacks throughout the course of a season. Cheat: Easy sacks of the opposing quarterbackFor even better results, sub in one of the fastest players from your defensive backfield into the position of the lineman that will have a free path to the quarterback so that you can sack him that much faster.Cheat: Easy sacks of the opposing quarterbackThanks to being able to use any playbook in the game on offense as well as the ability to line up any player at any position, you can easily use this to your advantage and move the ball virtually at will.Cheat: Easy sacks of the opposing quarterbackRegardless of what team you're using, choose the Washington Redskins playbook and then put your best wide receiver at fifth on the wide receiver depth chart. When on offense, run the Slants play from the five wide receiver Shotgun formation. This will cause your best receiver to either be matched up against one of the worst defensive players from the other team or to be wide open outright on virtually every play. The defensive AI will never figure this out, and you can literally run this same play over and over again until you score whenever you have the ball. In the rare event that the defense drops back or adds extra defenders, simply Hot Route your best receiver and have him run a curl route; he'll always be wide open due to always being against one of the backups from the other team.Cheat: Easy sacks of the opposing quarterbackThis obviously works best with a team like the Vikings or Colts (who have Moss and Harrison on their teams, respectively), but the glitch is so cheap that you can use it with virtually any team in the NFL and have easy success.</plot>
	<releasedate>12/8/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.1</rating>
	<ESRB>RP - Rating Pending</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>28176</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589754-madden-nfl-2004</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/madden-nfl-2004</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/madden-nfl-2004/3030-11911/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/28176-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/24092-madden-nfl-2004-gamecube-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/24093-madden-nfl-2004-gamecube-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/799716-madden-nfl-2004-playstation-2-screenshot-the-game-s-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/799717-madden-nfl-2004-playstation-2-screenshot-the-game-s-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/799719-madden-nfl-2004-playstation-2-screenshot-the-madden-101-option.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/799720-madden-nfl-2004-playstation-2-screenshot-one-of-the-new-options.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/799721-madden-nfl-2004-playstation-2-screenshot-the-my-madden-option.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/799722-madden-nfl-2004-playstation-2-screenshot-the-game-features.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/799723-madden-nfl-2004-playstation-2-screenshot-this-screenshot-shows.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/799724-madden-nfl-2004-playstation-2-screenshot-the-player-can-create.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/799741-madden-nfl-2004-playstation-2-screenshot-the-playmaker-control.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/799786-madden-nfl-2004-playstation-2-screenshot-the-game-uses-it.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>The 2004 edition of Madden NFL Football includes several changes from the previous year. Madden 2004 on the Game Boy Advance features a complete list of NFL players and teams with statistics tracking. Multiple play modes include regular season, playoffs, and exhibition play. Create-a-player mode allows for the creation of a custom NFL player, which can be traded during a season. Newest addition to Madden NFL 2004 on the GBA is the option to connect to the Nintendo GameCube, which unlocks various game additions in the GameCube version of Madden 2004. Link play allows two players to go head-to-head.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dee6bd05-36b7-4681-b3da-75f3076b706c.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ece5af1c-91d1-4de8-9117-9c4adb694559.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>