<Game>
	<Name>Maniac Racers Advance (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Motocross Maniacs Advance is a Driving game, developed and published by Konami,which was released in 2002.</plot>
	<releasedate>21/3/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Motocross</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>5.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>14701</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/545598-motocross-maniacs-advance</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/14701-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/1/5/6/16156_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/9/a/gfs_44729_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/4/a/gfs_44729_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/f/a/gfs_44729_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/e/a/gfs_44729_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/5/a/gfs_44729_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/14701.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>If your fascination with motocross borders on unhealthy, you might just be a motocross maniac. Choose one of six racers each of which is graced with their own special abilities to take through the rigors of the competition. The tracks are packed with jumps, hills, and other stunt fodder, and there are four unique modes of play: Race, Time Attack, Action, and the infamous Link Battle. Link Battle supports up to four players (you provide the link cables and extra cartridges), challenging gamers to duke it out for bragging rights. Try to collect nitro power throughout the competition, boosting your bike to top speeds, planting bombs, and firing missiles all the while. Mixing top-notch racing with combative elements, the game is packed with hidden tracks and power-ups to keep the stakes high, and the graphics will make you forget you're playing on a handheld console. The long-running MOTOCROSS MANIACS series has had its share of great games, but this is the best of them.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d95c82ce-5d69-4592-907d-0d06998283f2.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7ef478b3-ed51-42a3-bf78-e6d318211644.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/adff2d41-f9ee-433d-b4f6-0cd5f6d3549d.png</clearlogo2>
</game>