<Game>
	<Name>Mario Kart - Super Circuit (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The title screen for the game.The sole title of the acclaimed kart racing series to show up on the Game Boy Advance, Mario Kart Super Circuit once again pits the Nintendo characters against one another in a frantic battle of item tossing and speed boosting to reach the finish first. This game is the third title in the Mario Kart series, preceded by Mario Kart 64 and followed by Mario Kart: Double Dash!! on the GameCube. This games features and combines the elements from the previous games in the series. The game was released on July 21 in Japan, August 27 in North America and September 14 in Europe. Super Circuit is also the first game in the series to be on a handheld.Gameplay:As with most racing games the goal is to finish first. All of the races within the game have eight characters to play with. In the game, the player can pick up items which are contained within item boxes. For the player these items are very useful however the AI-controlled players can also use the items against the player. Coins are dropped onto the course so that players can speed up to their top speed for the character. If a player has 0 coins and comes in contact with another racer they spin out of control.The game contains five different cups. Each cup has four different race courses. These cups are called Mushroom Cup, Flower Cup, Lightning Cup, Star Cup and Special Cup. If a player had collected 100 coins within a specific cup they could unlock the Extra Cup. This cup contained extra cups from Super Mario Kart, the first game in the series. With these courses added in, this game had contained the most courses within any other game in the series. If a gold trophy was collected with a Cup the title screen would change to a sunset. If there are three star ratings on all the cups for each engine class, the title screen would change to night and be accompanied with a new tune.RacersLightweightToadPrincess PeachYoshiMiddleweightMarioLuigiHeavyweightDonkey KongWarioBowserGame Modes:This game has four different game modes. All of these modes were accessed by a single player expect for the battle mode. In battle mode four players could participate using a "Game Boy Advance Link" cable with the cartridge. But all players that would be using the single cartridge mode would only be limited to selecting from four courses from Super Mario Kart and can only use Yoshi and different colors of him.Grand PrixIn the Grand Prix mode, a single player or two players would race against the AI. The player chooses a Cup and the fours courses to play within the Cup. The player earns points by finishing in the first four positions of the race. If the player finishes in fifth or lower then the player must restart the race. The player can restart the race up to three times before they are unable to restart the race again. If two players are playing the game moves onto the next race if one player finishes in the first four places. At the end of the Grand Prix, the player with the most points will win.Time TrialPlayers can race to get the best times on each course without any obstacles After achieving a best time they can save ghost data onto the trial course. Players are given three mushrooms each to use during the time trial.Quick RunThis mode is a one player mode unique to this game. Players can race on any the tracks within the game without any restrictions or regulations. Players can alter the number of laps, appearance of coins and item boxes by pressing select before accessing the mode.VS ModeUp to four players can race against each other without any AI controlled opponents on any course.Battle ModeUp to four players are given three balloons and must use items against other opponents to take them out. Once all three balloons are lost, the player loses. If there are more than two players, the player is turned into a bomb. Bombs can run into other opponents for damage, and once exploded, they are respawned on the course and can charge at other players until a winner is decided.RankingDepending on the players performance in the Grand Prix they will achieve a rank. This can include "Triple Star" being the highest rank to "E" the, lowest rank.TracksMushroom CupFlower CupLightning CupStar CupSpecial CupPeach CircuitMario CircuitLuigi CircuitSnow LandLakeside ParkShy Guy BeachBoo LakeSky GardenRibbon RoadBroken PierRiverside ParkCheese LandCheep-Cheep IslandYoshi DesertBowser Castle4Bowser Castle1Bowser Castle2Sunset WildsBowser Castle3Rainbow RoadCheat: Extra Speed Boost!When you have a Mushroom Turbo boost Power up and you are about to go on a Spring Ramp, Use you're Turbo Boost power up, If you use it JUST BEFORE you go on the ramp/spring You can go much further and faster.  This works on just about every course with a spring/boost on it, but I don't think it is very effective on massive red and yellow ramps...Cheat: Extra Speed Boost!Once you have an Item and it is scrolling to decide which one you get press ''L'' a few times and the scrolling will stop so you get the Item twice as fast!Cheat: Extra Speed Boost!On the Player Select screen, press L to make the rotating image of the character you put the cursor on shoot a green shell straight ahead. You can also press R to make that character jump. Do this as many times as you please, it's just a little trick to try if you want.Cheat: Extra Speed Boost!As in Mario Kart 64, you are able to power slide in this game as well! To perform a power slide, press and hold R to hop while holding Left or Right. When you land, you'll slide in the direction you were holding. After about 2 seconds, let go of the R button and stop sliding. When you drive straight, you'll be given a boost, which is the result of a power slide. It may take a little bit of practice to pull it off, but it helps when trying to get around hairpin turns, or if you want to cut a couple seconds off your time when racing in Time Trial mode.Cheat: Extra Speed Boost!When you run straight into a Banana or another hazard, you'll notice your kart goes off balance before spinning out totally. To get back on balance before spinning out, release the acceleration and press the brakes (you must do this before you actually spin out, or else it'll be worthless). If you did it correctly, you'll see a music note appear above your character's head, showing you pulled it off successfully.Cheat: Extra Speed Boost!If you fall off the track or get stuck underwater for more than a couple moments, Lakitu comes to pull you out and place you on the track again. When he picks you up, wait until just before you touch the track again, then press the acceleration and you'll get a turbo boost if you timed it correctly. Cheat: Extra Speed Boost!To get a turbo boost to give you a head start in the race, do not press/hold the acceleration button before the race. Wait until just before the final light appears, then hold down the accelerator If you time it correctly, you'll be shot ahead, giving you a quick start!</plot>
	<releasedate>27/8/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>awF8rvh6bXc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>8704</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/371318-mario-kart-super-circuit</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mario-kart-super-circuit</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mario-kart-super-circuit/3030-16769/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8704-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/8704-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/6dgdJ0d.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/rPHSbHF.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/mKaRZPy.png</boxart4>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/71492-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84323-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/556693-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-japanese.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84324-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84325-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-character.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84329-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-waiting.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84326-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-driving.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84327-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-grab-a.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84328-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-final.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/257045-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-cup-selection.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/257046-mario-kart-super-circuit-game-boy-advance-screenshot-collect.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8704-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8704-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8704-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8704-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8704-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/x7mu01H.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/8704.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Whoever hands out driver's licenses in the Mushroom Kingdom is about to be in some serious trouble. Classic Mario Kart action is back once again, this time in a colorful, lightning-fast game that you can take anywhere. Mario, Luigi, Peach, Toad, Wario, Yoshi, and Bowser are all tearing up the track, tossing Koopa Shells and laying banana peels along the way. Mario Kart: Super Circuit puts your driving skills to the test on 40 tracks, each littered with wild weapons and obstacles. Four players can compete in Mario Kart: Super Circuit using only one Game Pak. If each player has a copy of the game, bonus features and new modes of play become available.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>YQBQRcC20ks</VideoURL1>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4503d0f6-3dad-4dfd-8ab5-54be64130f4d.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/576da839-91ba-455b-b23a-5f641cc8d775.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>