<Game>
	<Name>Mario Golf - Advance Tour (Spain)</Name>
	<plot>Similarly to Mario Golf for Game Boy Color, Mario Golf: Advance Tour allows players to create two of their own custom characters and experience golf by progressing through an RPG-like story.  The ultimate goal of the story is to make your player climb through the ranks of the various clubs, ultimately reaching the goal of the elite Mushroom Kingdom golfers, such as Princess Peach, Donkey Kong, and of course, Mario.It's possible to earn experience for either character either by playing through rounds of golf, or by successfully completing various types of mini-games and contests that help you hone your putting, swing, and other golf skills.  Distributing experience is more difficult now, as you now have to make sure that both characters are sufficiently levelled up so that you can succeed in doubles matches as well as your solo play.Advance Tour also links up to Mario Golf: Toadstool Tour for the Nintendo GameCube.  By doing this, you can earn even more experience points by transferring your characters over and playing the various modes in Toadstool Tour.  Of course, it's also possible to link up to another copy of Advance Tour for GBA multiplayer too.Cheat: 1-Ups by connecting with Mario Golf: Toadstool TourTo unlock these 1-Ups complete the necessary Side Game on Mario Golf: Toadstool Tour and connect Mario Golf: Advance Tour to transfer the data.Cheat: 1-Ups by connecting with Mario Golf: Toadstool TourTo unlock Mario, Peach, Yoshi, and Donkey Kong's Star Characters in Quick Game mode, you must beat them in a Character Match.Cheat: 1-Ups by connecting with Mario Golf: Toadstool TourTo get these characters in Mario Golf: Advance Tour you have to link up with Mario Golf: Toadstool Tour.Cheat: Change Memorial Room look and obtain the rarest drink.To change the statues in the Marion Club Memorial Room, you must first beat all the memorial scores of each Club (including Mushroom) in Singles and Doubles. When this happens, enter the room. Toad will enter after you and say it's gift for your high scores. Choose "Yes" when he asks you if you like it and he will give you the super-rare Hyper Drink, which increases the drinker's drive distance by 5 yards! The golf club statues will also be changed to Mario character statues.Cheat: Change Memorial Room look and obtain the rarest drink.NOTE: You MUST beat the Memorial scores through Story Mode.Cheat: Change Memorial Room look and obtain the rarest drink.Win the Links Tourney, then go to your Partner's  room. Face the lamp and press A, your Partner will ask you to change his/her name if you wish.</plot>
	<releasedate>21/6/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>VWm-23CY9_o</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>7514</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589376-mario-golf-advance-tour</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mario-golf-advance-tour</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mario-golf-advance-tour/3030-20058/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/7514-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/7514-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/122619-mario-golf-advance-tour-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/363372-mario-golf-advance-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/363373-mario-golf-advance-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/363375-mario-golf-advance-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot-glossary.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/363378-mario-golf-advance-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot-selecting.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/363379-mario-golf-advance-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot-selecting.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/363374-mario-golf-advance-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot-getting.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/363376-mario-golf-advance-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot-it-s-a.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/363377-mario-golf-advance-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot-peach.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/363380-mario-golf-advance-tour-game-boy-advance-screenshot-trying.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7697/399038-mariogolf_8.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/7514-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/7514-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/5kq7lrP.png</banner1>
</game>