<Game>
	<Name>Mary-Kate and Ashley - Girls Night Out (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Do you have good rhythm? Mary-Kate and Ashley have organized a girls night out filled with hip fashion and some hip-hop dance moves. First, you've got to have the right look to get into the club: select from the twins' wardrobe of clothes, shoes, and accessories. Then it's time to dance the night away. Like other popular music games, Girls Night Out will challenge you to repeat a series of key-press patterns to the game's music. Dance well and you'll unlock new dance moves, new songs, and even clothes. You can also rock the house by playing DJ for the club. The game lets you create and save your own music mixes from techno, house, and disco clips.</plot>
	<releasedate>14/3/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>28177</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/567517-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out/3030-6207/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/28177-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/122389-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741440-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741442-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741443-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741444-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741445-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741446-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741447-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741448-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741449-mary-kate-and-ashley-girls-night-out-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>These twins went from cute little toddlers on television to international fashion examples in a matter of just a few years, and they're ready to celebrate their success with a night on the town. Join the duo for an evening of clubbing and high style, dancing to the beats of techno, house, and disco music for the duration of the handheld gaming adventure. Just how does one go about dancing on a Game Boy Advance? Well, your fingers will represent your feet, as you try to master the correct combination of buttons and direction pad taps which isn't exactly as easy as it seems. Of course, you're nothing without the right clothes; choose your own shoes, shirts, pants, hairstyles, and accessories in this all-inclusive experience. One of your primary objectives will be to unlock all of the game's secret steps, songs, and clothes and that will take a combination of smarts and reflexes.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/75882e1d-51e2-43dc-92fc-9a55c4bc5972.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>