<Game>
	<Name>Mawaru - Made in Wario (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>After accidentally discovering spin technology, Wario reassembles the developers at WarioWare, Inc. to make a new set of wild minigames. WarioWare: Twisted! maintains the fast-paced style of gameplay from the original WarioWare and introduces a new gyro sensor that lets you control the gameplay by rotating the Game Boy Advance SP left and right. The new controls play into more than 200 minigames. Play through them all to unlock souvenirs, such as bonus games, figurines, and instruments.Cheat: Extra Unlockable ItemOnce you complete Warioman you will unlock the Minigame Towers.  I dont know if there is a boss tower. Cheat: Extra Unlockable ItemUpon completing the game to a certain extent, you can unlock in-game items via "Gatcha Koron".Cheat: Extra Unlockable ItemThese unlockable stages will replace the ? marks on the Story menu.Cheat: Change words on title screenWhen you are on the title screen if tilt left and right fast enough then the wording will change and it will say something different.Cheat: Change words on title screenOn the title screen, if you wait long enough, little Wario noses will scuttle onto the screen. Rotating the GBA makes them scurry off the screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>23/5/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>6xWFF3sMJPo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4137</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/922156-warioware-twisted</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/4137-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4137-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/c/d/gfs_57532_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/1/d/gfs_57532_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/a/d/gfs_57532_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/b/d/gfs_57532_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/0/d/gfs_57532_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/4137-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/4137-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/4137.png</clearlogo1>
</game>