<Game>
	<Name>Mazes of Fate (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>The ancient gods have passed judgment, and as a result all of mankind has been sentenced to be replaced with a new, less sinful race. The only chance for redemption lies withing a magical item that will allow mankind to atone for its sins. But the item in question has been stolen by the enemies of humanity, and the verdict of the gods will soon come to pass.Mazes of Fate is a fantasy medieval first person "dungeon-crawler" RPG in which you create a character based on gender, class and attributes (or take your pick from one of the three pre-made characters) and set out in a quest to save the human race from oblivion. The game alternates between world and town map sequences in which you control your party from an overhead perspective and visit shops and get quests from NPCs and the many dungeons that compose the bulk of the game itself. While dungeon crawling the game switches to a first-person perspective from which you control your party as it fights all the monsters that cross your path and loot the treasures uncovered. Combat is real-time although the game pauses while you navigate action menus.Features loads of items, weapons and quests, as well as tons of monsters and up to 5 recruit-able party members.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/12/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Graffiti Entertainment, LLC</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>M53Q0gfvTiA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14686</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/937231-mazes-of-fate</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mazes-of-fate</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mazes-of-fate/3030-5162/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/14686-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/266268-mazes-of-fate-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose-your-language.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/266269-mazes-of-fate-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/266270-mazes-of-fate-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-what-class.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/266271-mazes-of-fate-game-boy-advance-screenshot-surprise-surprise.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/266272-mazes-of-fate-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-rats-a-the-weakest.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/266273-mazes-of-fate-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-move-around.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/266274-mazes-of-fate-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-get-set-up-early.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/266275-mazes-of-fate-game-boy-advance-screenshot-these-enemies-appear.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/266276-mazes-of-fate-game-boy-advance-screenshot-check-the-corpses.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/266277-mazes-of-fate-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-equipment-screen.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Mazes of Fate is set in a dark fantasy world that is facing divine punishment. The ancient gods, disgusted by humanity’s pride, intend to wipe mankind out and replace it with a new, more submissive race of goatmen. One party of adventurers is left to make the ultimate choice. Should they fight back against overwhelming odds, or sentence humanity to a fate that may be worse than death? While playing Mazes of Fate, you will explore dungeons, solve intricate puzzles, and go on multiple quests with a party of up to three adventurers. You can select your protagonist from one of three premade characters, or create your own, then seek out and recruit six unlockable allies for your crew. The adventurers can be customized as you see fit, using nineteen skills, forty magical spells from three different schools of magic, and more than three hundred items and equipment to find and use. Mazes of Fate spans the length and breadth of a huge, dynamic world, with more than a hundred characters you can interact with, an hour of original music featuring thirty-five different themes, and twenty-five hours of gameplay.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/85a9e473-1c01-49ea-8040-a43e28ce203d.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a45ec125-1416-46d0-a36a-46f93fe236c9.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Graffiti Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>