<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man Battle Network 2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Mega Man Battle Network 2 is the second game in the Battle Network series, and continues the story of Lan Hikari and his virtual friend, MegaMan.EXE, three months after the previous game. The first screens show that Earth is peaceful after Lan and friends defeated the evil organization WWW in the first game. That peace is soon shattered as numerous crimes take place as a result of a mysterious organization known only as "Gospel".You control both Lan and Megaman throughout the game-Lan in the real world, and Megaman in the virtual universe. As you progress in the game, more areas of both world are opened up for you to explore at your will. At the end of most areas you face a tough Gospel-hired boss in the virtual world, who usually is causing trouble in the real world as well. After each climactic battle you gain new powers, and unlock new areas to visit.The game was released in 2001 in Japan, 2002 in the US, and 2002 in Europe. It is followed by Megaman Battle Network 3 : Blue and Megaman Battle Network 3: White.SystemThis game plays extremely similarly to the first Mega Man Battle Network; battles take place on a 3x6 grid, with MegaMan.EXE using the card-like BattleChips to d efeat his opponent(s). Therefore, this section will exclusively cover changes made by MMBN2.Removed FeaturesThe 3X3 battle area as well as CustomGuage (located at top)The Armor system is removed in favor of Style Change.Style ChangePerhaps the biggest new addition, the Style Change allows MegaMan to gain extra abilities based on his fighting style. There are five different styles: GutsStyle which focuses on boosting the MegaBuster's power, ShieldStyle which focuses on defense, TeamStyle which focuses on using NaviChips, CustomStyle focuses on gaining more chips to use, and the unlockable HubStyle, which features the best features of all of the other Styles...at the cost of 50% Max HP. When a Style is obtained (after a certain amount of Battles), a random element is also assigned, changing MegaMan's charged MegaBuster weapon and making him weak to the appropriate element.BattlefieldThe Battlefield now features different types of panels, such as Grass Panels which double the damage dealt from Fire attacks and Magnet Panels that attract the player towards them.MegaBusterMegman Fighting in Heatguts styleThis game no longer requires a PowerUp placed in the "Charge" category to use the ChargeShot.Custom ScreenSome BattleChips can now have a wildcard "*" chip code; these chips can be used with chips of any other code. The Chip Add feature is changed; now the player must choose chips to discard in order to add extra BattleChip slots until the end of the battle. The maximum amount of chips to choose from is reduced to 10. "Regular chip" allows you to have a single chip automatically appear during your first turn. Finally, the player is now given an option to retreat by pressing the L Button and confirming; if the retreat fails, MegaMan must go a turn without BattleChips ("Escape" chips are still included, however).FolderOnly 5 of the same chip can be used in a single folder, as opposed to 10 in the first game. There are now multiple folders, making it more convinent to carry folders with different strategies.Other FeaturesOther features include the adding of a "Subchip" folder, which allows MegaMan to use certain chips outside of battle. These chips can heal MegaMan or open locked items. The Internet is greatly improved in this game, as it is split up into distinctive sections and is overall less confusing than in the first game. MegaMan can now also visit markets on the net to buy things as well as BBS boards for different things ranging from sidequests to intel for the whereabouts of certain Navis and objects. Net Squares are also present, some acting as marketplaces, with some having other functions and there are 1 per area of the internet.Other miscellaneous smaller changes are made, such as the Chip Trader automatically saving the game and enemies being much faster.ChipsCannonHiCannonM-CannonShotGunV-GunCrossGunSpreaderBubblerBub-VBubCrossBubSprdHeatShotHeat-VHeatCrosHeatSprdMiniBombLilBombCrosBombBigBombTreeBom1TreeBom2TreeBom3SwordWideSwrdLongSwrdFireSwrdAquaSwrdElecSwrdFireBldeAquaBldeElecBldeStepSwordKunai1Kunai2Kunai3CustSwrdMuramasaVarSwrdSlasherShockwavSonicwavDynawavQuake1Quake2Quake3GutPunchColdPnchDashAtkWreckerCannBallDoubNdlTripNdlQuadNdlTridentRatton1Ratton2Ratton3FireRatTornadoTwisterBlowerBurnerZapRing1ZapRing2ZapRing3Satelit1Satelit2Satelit3Spice1Spice2Spice3MagBomb1MagBomb2MagBomb3Yo-Yo1Yo-Yo2Yo-Yo3CrsShld1CrsShld2CrsShld3HammerZeusHamrLanceBrnzFistSilvFistGoldFistPoisMaskPoisFaceWhirlplBlckholeMeteor9Meteor12Meteor15Meteor18TimeBom1TimeBom2TimeBom3LilCloudMedCloudBigCloudMineFrntSnsrDblSnsrRemobit1Remobit2Remobit3AquaBallElecBallHeatBallGeyserLavaDragGodStoneOldWoodGuardPanlOut1PanlOut3LineOutCatcherMindbndrRecov10Recov30Recov50Recov80Recov120Recov150Recov200Recov300PanlGrabAreaGrabGrabRvngGeddon1Geddon2Geddon3EscapeAirShoesRepairCandle1Candle2Candle3RockCubePrismGuardianWindFanAnubisSloGaugeFstGaugeFullCustInvis1Invis2Invis3DropdownPopUpStoneBodShadow1Shadow2Shadow3UnderShtBarrierBublWrapLeafShldAquaAuraFireAuraWoodAuraElecAuraLifeAura1LifeAura2LifeAura3MagLineLavaLineIceLineGrassLineLavaStageIceStageGrassStageHolyPanlJealousyAntiFireAntiElecAntiWatrAntiDmgAntiSwordAntiNaviAntiRecvAtk 10Atk 20Atk 30Fire 40Aqua 40Wood 40Elec 40Navi 20Navi 40RollRollV2RollV3GutsManGutsManV2GutsManV3ProtoManProtoManV2ProtoManV3AirManAirManV2AirManV3QuickManQuickManV2QuickManV3CutmanCutmanV2CutmanV3ShadowManShadowManV2ShadowManV3KnightManKnightManV2KnightManV3MagnetManMagnetManV2MagnetManV3FreezeManFreezeManV2FreezeManV3HeatManHeatManV2HeatManV3ToadManToadManV2ToadManV3ThunderManThunManV2ThunManV3SnakeManSnakeManV2SnakeManV3GateManGateManV2GateManV3PharohManPharoManV2PharoManV3NapalmManNapalmManV2NapalmManV3PlanetManPlanetManV2PlanetManV3BassBassV2BassV3Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.When fighting Thunderman, when one of the clouds is about to move on a pannel near you (when it's about half way on), move onto the same pannel. The game recognizes it as hit, but you don't take damage. If done right, you should have the Invis chip effect for about 1/4 of normal time. This is a useful trick for S ranking him.Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.Requirements:2 GBA/SP2 MMBN2 game paks.Link cableCheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.This glitch allows you to duplicate your lost chipdata in a netbattle against your oppenant, do not worry about it damaging your gamesave, I have done this hundreds of times and my gamesave has not suffered.Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.You and your friend (or just you on your own, still possible to do) must go into network and compete in a real netbattle against eachother, and one must win without flaw, when the battle is over, as soon as the chip datas name is shown, the LOSER must reset his game. (A+B+Start+Select), as a result, where the winners data is saved and the losers is not, the losers chip data is not lost and the winners is still saved resulting in a duplication of the chip.Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.WARNING: If the winner resets, instead of duplication you will simply DESTROY the chip, because the loser still loses and the winner doesn't save the fact it was won.Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.What are the benefits to this? Well in short, imagine how easy it'll be to duplicate and share your secret chips, Bass V3s, Lifeaur3s and other rare only get one of me chip data. You can even duplicate the final chip data, Sanctuary. Of course the better the busting level, the better the chip you'll duplicate.Cheat: Invis effect in Thunderman battle.Put a ZeusHammer into your folder. Go into battle and take damage on purpose till you have 200HP or less. Then kill the virus or escape. Now, find a Mole2 Virus in WWW Area 3. (This can be done with Mole1, too, but it's harder.) Attack the virus till it has 200HP or less. Then use your ZeusHammer. The Mole2 is deleted and you take 200 damage. Your HP is reduced to zero but you still win the battle. Now you can walk around the net with zero HP. Note: Have a healing subchip or you'll get deleted when next battle starts.Cheat: 5 StarsYou can get up to 5 stars, which will help allow you to unlock Hard Mode.Cheat: 5 StarsAfter you beat Gospel, secret Navis are fightable to you, if you meet the requirements.Cheat: Gamecube LogoAt the end of ShadowMan's level (the Mother Computer), on the right there is the Gamecube Logo.Cheat: Unlock HubstyleTo unlock this special style, you must defeat all V3 navis (excluding Bass) with an S-rank. Then, the next time a style change occurs, you will get Hubstyle.Hubstyle is a unique style that is non-elemental, and combines the benefits of every other style in the game. It will halve your max HP though.This style will only show up once per game, so if you skip or erase it, it will be gone for good.To confirm this unlockable, talk to the girl in ACDC Town behind the trees near the park. She will tell you which V3 navis you have defeated with an S-rank, and say that she sees all the available "ghosts" if you have defeated them all.</plot>
	<releasedate>15/6/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>oGzwNcvDYeU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6926</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561218-mega-man-battle-network-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mega-man-battle-network-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-man-battle-network-2/3030-5113/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6926-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6926-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/67754-mega-man-battle-network-2-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59994-mega-man-battle-network-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-i-always.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59995-mega-man-battle-network-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-bet.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59996-mega-man-battle-network-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-quiet.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59997-mega-man-battle-network-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-fighting.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59998-mega-man-battle-network-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-more.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/59999-mega-man-battle-network-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-let-s.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60000-mega-man-battle-network-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-quite.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60001-mega-man-battle-network-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-cut-enemy.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7539/495056-mega_man_battle_network_2___gba_62.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7539/495054-mega_man_battle_network_2___gba_61.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/OIEt2ae.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/6926.png</clearlogo1>
</game>