<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man Battle Network 4 - Red Sun (USA)</Name>
	<plot>It's been rather quiet after Lan and Mega Man defeated the WWW in Mega Man Battle Network 3.  Little do they know that they're about to embark on yet another adventure.  An asteroid has been spotted in outer space which is heading towards Earth, and scientists are planning to destroy it with a giant laser.  In addition to this, a mysterious Navi called ShadeMan is terrorizing the Internet, sucking the life out of other Navis, much like a vampire.  Can Lan and Mega Man stop this new threat?Mega Man Battle Network 4 is an RPG-like game, and a continuation of the Battle Network series.  You play as two characters - a young boy, Lan, in the real world, and a Net Navi called Mega Man on the Internet.  Lan can talk to people and interact with the real world, however, when he 'jacks in' to the Internet, Mega Man takes over.  In addition to interacting with Navis on the net, Mega Man also encounters random viruses and battles them in a mix of turn-based and real-time battle.A new feature of Battle Network 4 is the "Soul Unison" feature - as players progress through the game, they can defeat certain Navis and earn the ability to merge with them to become more powerful.  The catch with this is that the Soul Unison only lasts for three turns, and that a particular Battle Chip is required to perform it.The Soul Unisons that you acquire through the game are specific to each version - to get them all, you must link up with a copy of Mega Man Battle Network 4: Blue Moon.  You can also trade different Battle Chips (some are exclusive to particular versions) and Net Battle with a friend.Cheat: Code to get in to Park AreaOnce you beat the normal Navi decode this AJEKDUR2437561 and put it into  the Staff Code window.Cheat: Code to get in to Park AreaAfter you get the chip NeoVari N from Undernet5, you can push the A button for a slash that does 240 DMG. But, if you put in certain combonations while you hold the A button down, you can increase the range of the sword.Cheat: Code to get in to Park AreaOnce you get the VarSword chip you can use &amp;quot;secret swords attacks&amp;quot; in every battle you want . When you are in a battle select the VarSword chip , press and hold A and enter this codes quick.Cheat: NumberMan Trader CodesWhen Higsby gets the NumberMan Trader, enter these codes to get the items.Cheat: Avoid Random Battles (JP Version Only)To avoid random battles, save your game about every 20 steps. This will reset the game's random seed, which also resets when your next random encounter will be. Now you can go through the entire 'Net without running into a single fight, or resetting your system because you got into a fight!Cheat: First (or All) Seven Save IconsThe Save Icons are as follows:Cheat: First (or All) Seven Save IconsTo obtain the rare giga-level battle chips, you will have to complete some of the game's most arduous tasks. It is expected that you have an almost full-library and high stats before attempting to obtain most of these.Cheat: Easily defeat Dark users in MultiplayerIn multiplayer, Dark users are very tough because they become the Darksoul when you reduce them to 0 hp. However, if you use a chip or PA that freezes time and deals many hits, you can kill them without allowing them to become the Darksoul. A great example is the Pile Driver PA. Hope this helps you take out those cheap Darkies!Cheat: Easily defeat Dark users in MultiplayerTo get past the gate in Ura Internet area 5, you need all 150 regular chips. Once you get past it, you can fight the secret boss, Forte, and get his chip, Forte.Cheat: Easily defeat Dark users in MultiplayerAfter completing the Black Earth dungeon, exit (plug out) and re-enter. You can now encounter Forte SP in Black Earth area 2, and obtain Black Barrier from him.Cheat: Easily defeat Dark users in MultiplayerOne more thing to add: To fight Duo SP, you need to have all the 7 symbols 1 for Duo 1 for Soul Complete 1 for Standard library complete 1 for Mega Library Complete 1 for Giga Library Complete 1 for P.A. Complete 1 for Forte SP Go back to where Duo was and fight him there! Cheat: Easily defeat Dark users in MultiplayerThere is a large hole surrounded by purple slime on a platform in Ura Internet area 6. In order to approach it, you need the chips ''Bug Charge'', ''Muramasa Blade'', ''Black Wing'', ''Element Dark'' and ''Poison Anubis''. Once you get close enough, it will suck you down to the secret dungeon, Black Earth.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/6/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>tqoPCZCXWR4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6934</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/918999-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6934-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6934-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176492-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176493-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176494-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176495-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176496-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176497-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176498-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176499-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176500-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176501-mega-man-battle-network-4-red-sun-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/bX5ssPx.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/6934.png</clearlogo1>
</game>