<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man Battle Network 4 - Blue Moon (USA)</Name>
	<plot>It's been rather quiet after Lan and Mega Man defeated the WWW in Mega Man Battle Network 3.  Little do they know that they're about to embark on yet another adventure.  An asteroid has been spotted in outer space which is heading towards Earth, and scientists are planning to destroy it with a giant laser.  In addition to this, a mysterious Navi called ShadeMan is terrorizing the Internet, sucking the life out of other Navis, much like a vampire.  Can Lan and Mega Man stop this new threat?Mega Man Battle Network 4 is an RPG-like game, and a continuation of the Battle Network series.  You play as two characters - a young boy, Lan, in the real world, and a Net Navi called Mega Man on the Internet.  Lan can talk to people and interact with the real world, however, when he 'jacks in' to the Internet, Mega Man takes over.  In addition to interacting with Navis on the net, Mega Man also encounters random viruses and battles them in a mix of turn-based and real-time battle.A new feature of Battle Network 4 is the "Soul Unison" feature - as players progress through the game, they can defeat certain Navis and earn the ability to merge with them to become more powerful.  The catch with this is that the Soul Unison only lasts for three turns, and that a particular Battle Chip is required to perform it.The Soul Unisons that you acquire through the game are specific to each version - to get them all, you must link up with a copy of Mega Man Battle Network 4: Red Sun.  You can also trade different Battle Chips (some are exclusive to particular versions) and Net Battle with a friend.Cheat: NeoVariableSword codes1.Select a NeoVariableSword in the custom menu2.Press "OK"3.Hold "A" when that chip appears and quickly input one of the codes below:Cheat: NeoVariableSword codesOnce you get the VarSword chip you can use "secret swords attacks" in every battle you want . When you are in a battle select the VarSword chip , press and hold A and enter this codes quick.Cheat: NumberMan Trader CodesWhen Higsby gets the Numberman Trader machine in the shop, enter number codes to get various items.Cheat: Avoid Random Battles (JP Version Only)To avoid random battles, save your game about every 20 steps. This will reset the game's random seed, which also resets when your next random encounter will be. Now you can go through the entire 'Net without running into a single fight, or resetting your system because you got into a fight!Cheat: Avoid Random Battles (JP Version Only)You need the Blue Moon version for this. If you play the Woodman story on a DS, you will encounter this glitch. When you jack-in to the Park Area and Woodman attacks you, go into a random battle. Run away or delete the viruses. The screen will turn white and freeze. The only way to stop this glitch is to play the Woodman story on a Gameboy Advance SP or on a regular Gameboy Advance. Cheat: Extra ModesThe save icons are as follows:Cheat: Extra ModesTo obtain the rare giga-level battle chips, you will have to complete some of the game's most arduous tasks. It is expected that you have an almost full-library and high stats before attempting to obtain most of these.Cheat: Secret BossTo get past the gate in Ura Internet area 5, you need all 150 regular chips. Once you get past it, you can fight the secret boss, Forte, and get his chip, Forte Another.Cheat: Secret BossAfter defeating Forte in Ura Internet 5, Forte SP can be randomly encountered in Black Earth 2. He can drop Delta Ray Edge in Blue Moon, and Black Barrier in Red Sun.Cheat: Secret BossOne more thing to add: To fight Duo SP, you need to have all the 7 symbols 1 for Duo 1 for Soul Complete 1 for Standard library complete 1 for Mega Library Complete 1 for Giga Library Complete 1 for P.A. Complete 1 for Forte SP Go back to where Duo was and fight him there!Cheat: Secret BossThere is a large hole surrounded by purple slime on a platform in Ura Internet area 6. In order to approach it, you need the chips ''Bug Curse'', ''Muramasa Blade'', ''Black Wing'', ''Element Dark'' and ''Poison Anubis''. Once you get close enough, it will suck you down to the secret dungeon, Black Earth.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/6/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>oB8Kwpk9qbM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6929</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919000-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6929-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6929-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/460513-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/460514-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741476-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741479-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741480-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741481-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741482-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741483-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741484-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741485-mega-man-battle-network-4-blue-moon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/UNCwNep.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/6929.png</clearlogo1>
</game>