<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man Battle Network 6 - Cybeast Falzar (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Lan and his family have moved house to Cyber City, which is famous for its new technology.  Lan and Mega Man quickly make new friends, and find out about the legend of the Cybeasts, two ancient creatures with such power that they eventually destroyed each other.  However, a shady organization is intent on reviving and controlling the Cybeasts for their own nefarious needs, and Mega Man gets caught in the middle!  While they capture the wolf-like Gregar, Mega Man captures the phoenix-like Falzar.  By harnessing this new power, Lan and Mega Man must save the internet once again!Mega Man Battle Network 6 is an RPG-like game in which you navigate through both the real world, and the cyberworld of the internet.  As Lan, you move through the real world, interacting with people and finding places to 'jack-in' to the cyberworld for Mega Man to take control.  As Mega Man, you can fight viruses in a hybrid of turn-based and real-time battle: you select which battle chips you need to use each turn, and then use them while actively dodging enemy fire.New to Battle Network 6 is the "Cross Change" system.  After beating certain enemy Navis, Mega Man can copy their strengths (as well as their weaknesses!) and use them to his advantage, similar to the original Mega Man games.  For example, you could take on the aqua power of Aqua Man, or the cutting power of Tomahawk Man.At a certain point in the game, Mega Man also gains control of the powerful Cybeast, Falzar.  Using this power, Mega Man can transform into a phoenix-like Navi, boosting his attack power for three turns, and enhance the power of certain battle chips.  If players continue to push Mega Man, he will enter the "Beast Over" state, with even more power, but at the loss of control and a severely weakened Mega Man.  It's also possible to combine the Cross Change with Falzar, creating even more powerful attacks.This game also links up to Mega Man Battle Network 6: Cybeast Gregar.  Players can trade battle chips that are specific to each version, or net battle against each other.Cheat: Compress Navi Customizer ProgramsTo compress program pieces in the navi customizer, open up the navi customizer screen, and highlight the piece you wish to shrink.  Hold Right on the D-pad and press the corresponding set of buttons to shrink the piece.  To decompress the piece, repeat the process.Cheat: Lottery Chip Machine CodesOnce you are able to enter the chip shop in Central Town, go inside to find a green machine on the right-hand side.  Upon pressing A in front of the machine, you will be able to enter a series of numbers to receive bonus items.Cheat: Giga ChipsThe list of Giga chips are below:Cheat: Giga ChipsIn each of the Net areas (excluding the ACDC and Green Areas), there is a Net Cafe where you can buy coffee for 10z a cup. Each time you buy a cup, they will give you a small piece of information. After you buy enough coffee, the owners will recognize you as a regular customer and give you an item.Cheat: Giga ChipsThere are secret bosses in the game that require having a certain amount of chips or having a certain Title Screen Icon.Cheat: Giga ChipsCheat: Giga ChipsUpon completing the tasks listed below, various icons showing your accomplishments will be displayed at the top of the title screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/6/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>1Y7dfQYxxDw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6932</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929992-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6932-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6932-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176311-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176312-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176313-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176314-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176315-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176316-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176317-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176318-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176319-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/176320-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/m1C3Khr.png</banner1>
	<Notes>In Mega Man Battle Network 6, Lan's father has received a job transfer and the family moves to Cyber City, a town known for conducting various technological experiments. Lan will meet new people and build new friendships in the real world while Mega Man befriends helpful Navis and encounters dangerous new enemies on the virtual plane. Together they will face threats far more powerful and perilous than they ever have before.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2c11d8c5-f6a0-416d-ba8f-8194d5e00fa2.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5e27b761-2708-40ce-94eb-019086b5ad7d.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/13070bd7-8eb5-44fe-8b50-990781a149d0.png</clearlogo1>
	<rating>4.5</rating>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>