<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man Battle Network 3 - White (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>LAN, the young hero, is invited to attend a local net-battle tournament with his Personal Electronic Trained character, Mega Man. However, during the tournament, Mega Man and LAN discover a plot by an evil corporation, who hope to once again take over the network.Using an RPG style, you must guide Mega Man through various levels defeating enemies along the way and collecting the various chips to upgrade Mega Man's weapons and other items.Exclusive to this, the White Version, are specialy developed chips (Giga Class chips) that only the White Version of Mega Man can use. You can also trade various chips between players using either Blue or White versions of BN3. Other differences include exclusive enemy bosses in areas and a unique battle style for each games version that Mega Man can use.Cheat: Secret Boss NavisAfter beating LifeVirus, you can fight four secret Navis if you meet the requirements.Cheat: Entering Deeper Parts of the InternetAs you make your way through the many areas of the Internet, you'll notice that there are gates in the way of links to following areas. Those gates have question marks on them, and you must fulfill a certain requirement within that area of the Internet, then go to the gate in order to open it and proceed to the next Internet area. Here's a quick list of requirements to get into the later areas: Area 11: You cannot escape any battles in Area 10. Area 12: Busting Level after every battle must be above 3 in Area 11. Area 13: You cannot escape any battles in Area 10. Area 14: You must win at least 10 chips in battle from enemies in Area 13. Area 15: You must stay out of battles as much as you can in Area 14 (less than 7, I believe). Area 16: Busting Level after every battle must be above 4 in Area 15.Cheat: Entering Deeper Parts of the InternetCollect 174 chips, all except Dream Aura chip (No.127). Go to the deepest Internet Area (Internet Area 16, in the area where you can get Paradin Sword). Walk around that area until you find him. He can appear everywhere in that area. If you can beat him, he should give you the Dream Aura chip. Please remember, Forte CAN'T give his chip to you.Cheat: Entering Deeper Parts of the InternetIn the School's computer network, there are several doors you'll come to that require you to input a 2-digit passcode. Here's a list of the codes for each door (for the ones marked as random, you're given hints if the number is higher or lower each time you guess wrong): Door 1: 09 Door 2: 30 Door 3: Randomly generated Door 4: Randomly generated Door 5: 15 Door 6: Randomly generated Door 7: Randomly generated (Requires Teacher's Passcode to access)</plot>
	<releasedate>24/6/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>LcKqSVv1UoE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6928</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/457634-mega-man-battle-network</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-man-battle-network/3030-8238/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6928-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6928-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/56783-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/445134-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/495491-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/495489-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/495490-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/495492-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/495493-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/495494-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/495500-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/495495-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/495496-mega-man-battle-network-3-white-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/BDwpRz5.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/6928.png</clearlogo1>
</game>