<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man Battle Network 5 - Team Proto Man (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Lan and Mega Man return in the fifth entry to the Battle Network series of games.  In this sequel, a mysterious group is distributing Dark Navi chips in the hope of corrupting Navis worldwide.  Lan and his friends must storm the Dark Chip Factory and put a stop to this problem before it becomes any worse.The game uses an RPG style over-world in which Lan and Mega Man navigate and interact.  In the real world, you control Lan, and can interact with objects and talk to people.  When you need to enter cyberspace, you 'jack-in', and take control of Mega Man.  Mega Man must also battle viruses in addition to navigating through the internet.  This is done with a combination of action and turn-based battle, where you select powerful chips to give you an edge each turn, then use the chips and dodge shots in realtime.The game also features Liberation Missions, which are a more traditional turn-based style of play.  In this mode, you must 'liberate' dark tiles on your way to confront the boss.  Liberation Missions play somewhat like a complicated game of chess, with the player actually fighting the battles between the pieces.Unique to this version of the game is the ability to play as Protoman partway through the story. The game can also link up to Mega Man Battle Network 5: Team Colonel to trade and complete your battle chip collection - certain chips are only available in one version of the game.Cheat: GyromanInput this code as soon as you use the Gyroman Chip. Hold the buttons down. Cheat: GyromanAs soon as you use the Larkman chip press this sequence, it will make a beep if entered correctly.Cheat: GyromanTo enter these codes, have the desired Navi Customizer Program highlighted in the Navi Customizer screen. Hold the Right (-&amp;gt;) button on the D-Pad, then enter the 10 button code (Composed of different combinations of the buttons A, B, L and R) for that NCP to compress it.&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;Once compressed, the Navi Customizer Program's size will be reduced by one block, or square. Only non-textured programs can be compressed (AutoRun cannot be compressed either), and inputting the code again will decompress it.Cheat: GyromanIf you hold down 'A' and put in a button sequence fast, you will get a wider range for NeoVarSwrd.Cheat: GyromanGo to the numberman machine in Higsby's shop when it is placed there and enter the passwords to get your prize.Cheat: GyromanWhen you use the Shademan SP/DS chip, as soon as you see Shademan come up, immediately press the following codes for an extra effect to his attack.Cheat: GyromanTo use these, you must hold down the 'A' button and quickly put in the sequence. These only work with VarSwrd.Cheat: GyromanTo use this, you must hold the A button while using Z-Saber, and input the following code on the third slash. You must be holding A while it is slashing, and the code must be inputted on the third slash.Cheat: Use Medis Liberation Ability at No CostThis glitch works in the Japanese version of the game only; it was removed in the European and American versions.Cheat: Use Medis Liberation Ability at No CostFirst, get into a Liberation Mission and walk Medi up to a panel and select the TwinLiberate ability. Two panels (the one Medi is at and the one at the other end of the row) will be outlined in green. However, select 'No' when Medi asks you to use TwinLiberate.Cheat: Use Medis Liberation Ability at No CostSwitch to another Navi (don't do anything else before this!) and take him to the second panel that was outlined in green (not the one Medi was at) and press 'A' on the panel. See how the command changed from 'Liberate' to 'TwinLiberate', and how that panel and one Medi is at are now outlined in green? Select 'TwinLiberate' and if you win, it will function exactly like Medi's ability - without the Order Point cost.Cheat: Liberation Mission PrizesAfter every Liberation Mission you get a prize depending on how many phases it took for you to complete the mission.Cheat: Liberation Mission PrizesThis doesn't include Zenny prizes.Cheat: Liberation Mission PrizesThere are secret bosses in the game that require completing all Liberation Missions (including Nebula Area Liberation Missions).Cheat: Boktai 2 Crossover Battle ModeWith attaching the Wireless Adapter before the Title Screen appears. Under Continue you will get Crossover Battle Mode.Cheat: Boktai 2 Crossover Battle ModeWith this mode you can face Shademan and link up Wirelessly to Boktai 2 to see who the fastest is to beat Shademan using the EXE 5 and Boktai 2 System.Cheat: Boktai 2 Crossover Battle ModeRequires Two Wireless Adapters.Cheat: Boktai 2 Crossover Battle ModeAfter winning the End Area 5 Liberation Mission, there will be a gold Mr. Prog there who will recreate the battle. Talk to him and start the battle. Send a Navi to liberate the first item square and you should obtain 1800 Zennys. Next, retreat. You will leave the battle, however you will keep the 1800 Zennys. Repeat as many times as you want for more Zennys.</plot>
	<releasedate>21/6/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Co., Ltd., Capcom Entertainment, Inc., CE Europe Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>qqMUmwy2LrA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6931</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/924452-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6931-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6931-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/56791-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183021-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183022-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183023-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183024-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183025-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183026-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183027-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183028-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183029-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/183030-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-protoman-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/RtTP96b.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/6931.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Team Protoman is the first edition of Mega Man Battle Network 5. In the game, you can join forces with characters from previous installments of the Mega Man Battle series, and you can play in a new fighting mode. Team up with other cyberheroes in an effort to stop an evil organization from taking control of the global Internet.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>KUJPZa7_4LA&amp;list=PLEC_af5wK6YPWAAqXy5g3X07krzmF0u9b</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/871bb8c2-d16f-4feb-8d8b-10457d11c9bb.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fcb26373-965b-483d-b3a4-32b067ff8330.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/fbedefbc-6a74-4e2c-845e-fff34c70258c.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2094f529-5c34-4741-b8a6-c5d5fd3dedd3.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d241f937-546c-446d-b402-dc52c898ec23.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>