<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man Battle Network 5 - Team Colonel (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Lan and Mega Man return in the fifth entry to the Battle Network series of games.  In this sequel, a mysterious group is distributing Dark Navi chips in the hope of corrupting Navis worldwide.  Lan and his friends must storm the Dark Chip Factory and put a stop to this problem before it becomes any worse.The game uses an RPG style over-world in which Lan and Mega Man navigate and interact.  In the real world, you control Lan, and can interact with objects and talk to people.  When you need to enter cyberspace, you 'jack-in', and take control of Mega Man.  Mega Man must also battle viruses in addition to navigating through the internet.  This is done with a combination of action and turn-based battle, where you select powerful chips to give you an edge each turn, then use the chips and dodge shots in realtime.The game also features Liberation Missions, which are a more traditional turn-based style of play.  In this mode, you must 'liberate' dark tiles on your way to confront the boss.  Liberation Missions play somewhat like a complicated game of chess, with the player actually fighting the battles between the pieces.Unique to this version of the game is the ability to play as Colonel partway through the story. The game can also link up to Mega Man Battle Network 5: Team Protoman to trade and complete your battle chip collection - certain chips are only available in one version of the game.Cheat: Chip Attack BonusesAfter you activate the chip, push the combinations to activate their other abilities.Cheat: Chip Attack BonusesEntering a button command will an enhancement to certain chips when used.Cheat: Chip Attack BonusesTo enter these codes, have the desired Navi Customizer Program highlighted in the Navi Customizer screen. Hold the Right (-&amp;gt;) button on the D-Pad, then enter the 10 button code (Composed of different combinations of the buttons A, B, L and R) for that NCP to compress it.Once compressed, the Navi Customizer Program's size will be reduced by one block, or square. Only non-textured programs can be compressed (AutoRun cannot be compressed either), and inputting the code again will decompress it.Cheat: Chip Attack BonusesIf you hold down 'A' and put in a button sequence fast, you will get a wider range for NeoVarSwrd.Cheat: Chip Attack BonusesGo to the numberman machine in Higsby's shop when it is placed there and enter the passwords to get your prize.Cheat: Chip Attack BonusesTo use these, you must hold down the 'A' button and quickly put in the sequence. These only work with VarSwrd.Cheat: Giga ChipsThese are the giga chips and how to get them:Cheat: Giga ChipsSave Icons that go on top of the Title Screen for what you have accomplished in your saved game. Cheat: Giga ChipsThere are secret bosses in the game that require completing all Liberation Missions (including Nebula Area Liberation Missions).Cheat: Easy ZennyA easy way to make Zenny is during or after Cosmoman's liberation mission. Get NumberMan to search the 3 item panels straight ahead of the start point. You should get 1800 Zenny. Retreat and restart the mission. The item panels will be back, along with the 1800 Zenny. Repeat until you have all the zenny you need.</plot>
	<releasedate>21/6/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>APPW04UuDFk</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6930</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/924453-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6930-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6930-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/293276-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/293277-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741489-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741490-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741491-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741492-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741493-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741494-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741495-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741496-mega-man-battle-network-5-team-colonel-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/FAJhnGd.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/6930.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Team Colonel is the second edition of Mega Man Battle Network 5. In the game, you can join forces with characters from previous installments of the Mega Man Battle series, and you can play in a new fighting mode. Team up with other cyberheroes in an effort to stop an evil organization from taking control of the global Internet.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/60cd5369-be3c-4d3a-b4a0-db063a5932d6.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6a11e597-e673-4474-8c7b-c5d35a2812f3.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0b391dbe-80f3-41ff-84f0-9aa39aa35924.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>