<Game>
	<Name>Mega Man Battle Network 3 - Blue (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>IntroductionMegaman Battle Network 3 was released as two versions, Blue and White. Both versions has the same story, but minor differences in boss fights and battlechips. They were released in 2002 in Japan and the US in 2003, the Mega Man franchises 15th birthday. The game follows Lan Hikari and his NetNavi MegaMan. The terrorist organization WWW, defeated in the first game, has returned and are collecting "TetraCodes", four pieces of data hidden in various areas of cyberspace. Lan and Megaman travel to new areas to stop WWW. The gameplay is virtually identical to the previous two installments. The only differences are the inclusion of more "styles", forms that add different powers, elemental and non-elemental, to MegaMan. MegaMan Battle Network 3 was the first Battle Network game to feature two different versions.Story:Lord Wily has reformed the terrorist organization WWW, and now seeks to release Alpha, an bugged prototype for the current Internet. To do so, Wily needs the four TetraCodes, pieces of data that unlock the firewalls that surround Alpha.Lan Hikari and his NetNavi, Megaman, attempt to protect the TetraCodes from Dr. Wily, but fail to do so. Wily, with the help of Bass, releases Alpha, which consumes Wily and Bass, proceeding to infect the entire Internet with his bugs.Megaman battles Alpha, and is able to defeat him. As Alpha begins to delete, the network around him begins to crash. Megaman is unable to escape, and is destroyed. Lan's father manages to recover Megaman during a salvage operation of the affected network location, and is able to revive him.SystemThe gameplay in Battle Network 3 is similar to that of its predecessors, taking the basic design of Mega Man Battle Network and applying the gameplay improvements from Mega Man Battle Network 2.Removed FeaturesThe PowerUp system is gone, replaced with the Navi Customizer. In addition, apart from a few BattleChips (which are mainstays in the Battle Network franchise), the chip selection is mostly new; this philosophy of changing up the chip list instead of building on it would continue throughout the franchise.Navi CustomizerThis game's major contribution to the Battle Network franchise, the Navi Customizer allows players to augment MegaMan's powers by arranging Tetris-esqe puzzle pieces (referred to as "programs") onto a grid. However, if the player breaks certain programming rules, MegaMan will behave irregularly during battle.Style ChangeThis game introduces three more Styles: BugStyle, which afflicts MegaMan with random glitches (both positive and negative), and the version-exclusive Ground and Shadow Styles (the former focuses on changing Battlefield conditions, while the latter focuses on evasion). HubStyle is removed in this game. Leveling up each style yields Navi Customizer programs, allowing the player to mix and match MegaMan's abilities (within certain restrictions).FolderThis game establishes new chip classifications: Standard Chips (which you can now only have 3 duplicates of), MegaChips (stronger chips and most NaviChips; no duplicates allowed and only 5 per folder), and GigaChips (the strongest NaviChips and the 5 version-exclusive chips; only 1 per folder).CounteringThis game introduces the concept of "countering," or deleting an enemy right before they attack. Countering in this game yields "BugFrags" which are used in the Virus Breeder (see below) and at a special, end-game Chip Trader. This is the only game where the MegaBuster can be used to Counter.Other FeaturesBattle Network 3 features the Virus Breeder, where viruses (that must be found first somewhere in the net) are kept and can be fed using bugFrag. When a virus is found and put in the breeder, a chip for that virus is obtained. Feeding each virus BugFrag levels up their chip accordingly. After a family of a certain type of virus has been fed to the max, they will release information to the player as to where their King can be found.White vs. BlueThere are several differences between the White version and the Blue version. Since the Blue version is a special edition version (the western White is simply Rockman.EXE 3 in Japan, while western Blue is Rockman.EXE 3 Black) it features more content and is arguably the better game.White Version-Ground Style-MistMan as a boss-GigaChips NaviCycle, Balance, Bass, Serenade, Alpha Arm SigmaBlue Version-Shadow Style-BowlMan as a boss-Punk as a boss-GigaChips FolderBack, Dark Aura, Bass Plus, Delta Ray, Alpha Arm OmegaMain CharactersCharacterPictureChat Box PortraitIn Game SpriteLan HikariMayl SakuraiDex OyamaYai AyanokojiBosses:Boss NamePictureChip PortraitBattlefield SpriteAlphaBass.EXEBeastMan.EXEBowlMan.EXEBubbleMan.EXEN/ADarkman.EXEDesertMan.EXEDrillMan.EXEFlameMan.EXEFlashMan.EXEGutsMan.EXEJapanMan.EXEMetalMan.EXEMistMan.EXEAlpha: Final Boss of the game7 StarsThe following stars appear on the game's title screen once they are unlocked.StarHow to UnlockYellow Star (1st Star)Defeat the Original AlphaGreen Star (2nd Star)Defeat Bass GS in Secret Area 3Light Blue Star (3rd Star)Beat all of Serenade's Time Trials in Secret Areas 1, 2, and 3Blue Star (4th Star)Complete Standard Chip Library (200 Chips)Purple Star (5th Star)Complete Mega Chip Library (85 Chips)Red Star (6th Star)Defeat all 15 Omega NavisOrange Star (7th Star)Complete Program Advance Library (32 Combos)List of ChipsRegular chipsCannonHiCannonM-CannonAirshot1Airshot2Airshot3LavaCan1LavaCan2LavaCan3VolcanoeShotGunV-GunSideGunSpreaderBubblerBub-VBublSideHeatShotHeat-VHeatSideMiniBombSnglBombDublBombTrplBombCannBallIceBallLavaBallBlkBomb1BlkBomb2BlkBomb3SwordWideSwrdLongSwrdFireSwrdAquaSwrdElecSwrdBambSwrdCustSwrdVarSwrdAirSwrdStepSwrdStepCrosSlasherShockWaveSonicWavDynaWaveBigWaveGutPunchGutStrgtGutImpctDashAtkBurnerCondorBurningZapring1Zapring2Zapring3IceWave1IceWave2IceWave3Yo-Yo1Yo-Yo2Yo-Yo3AirStrm1AirStrm2AirStrm3Arrow1Arrow2Arrow3Ratton1Ratton2Ratton3FireRatnWaveRedWaveMudWaveTornadoSpice1Spice2Spice3Shake1Shake2Shake3NoBeam1NoBeam2NoBeam3HammerGeyserRope1Rope2Rope3Boomer1Boomer2Boomer3PoisMaskPoisFaceRockArm1RockArm2RockArm3CrsShld1CrsShld2CrsShld3Magnum1Magnum2Magnum3Plasma1Plasma2Plasma3RndmMetrHoleMetrShotMetrNeedler1Needler2Needler3Totem1Totem2Totem3Sensor1Sensor2Sensor3MetaGel1MetaGel2MetaGel3PawnKnightRookTeam1Team2TimeBombMineLanceSnakeGuardPanlOut1PanlOut3PanlGrabAreaGrabGrabBackGrabRvngRockCubePrismWindFanFanfareDiscordTimpaniRecov10Recov30Recov50Recov80Recov120Recov150Recov200Recov300RepairSloGaugeFstGaugePanicGeddon1Geddon2Geddon3CopyDmgInvisShadowMole1Mole2Mole3AirShoesBarrierBarr100Barr200AuraNrthWindMettaurBunnySpikeySwordyJellyMushyMomograKillrEyeScuttlstHoleHolyPanlLavaStgeIceStageGrassStgSandStgeMetlStgeSnctuaryAntiDamgAntiSwrdAntiNaviAntiRecvAtk 10Fire 30Aqua 30Elec 30Wood 30Navi 20MegaChipsMuramasaHeroSwrdZeusHamrStandOutSalamndrWatrLineFountainLigtningBoltGaiaSwrdGaiaBladMeteorsGuardianAnubisGodstoneOldWoodJealousyPoltrgstLifAuraFullCustAtk 30Navi 40RollRollV2RollV3GutsManGutsManV2GutsManV3GutsManV4ProtoManProtoMnV2ProtoMnV3ProtoMnV4FlashManFlashMnV2FlashMnV3FlashMnV4BeastManBeastMnV2BeastMnV3BeastMnV4BubbleManBubblMnV2BubblMnV3BubblMnV4DesrtManDesrtMnV2DesrtMnV3DesrtMnV4PlantManPlantMnV2PlantMnV3PlantMnV4FlameManFlamManV2FlamManV3FlamManV4DrillManDrillMnV2DrillMnV3DrillMnV4MetalManMetalMnV2MetalMnV3MetalMnV4KingManKingManV2KingManV3KingManV4MistManMistManV2MistManV3MistManV4BowlManBowlManV2BowlManV3BowlManV4DarkManDarkManV2DarkManV3DarkManV4JapanMan(YamatoMan)JapanMnV2JapanMnV3JapanMnV4Punk (JAPAN ONLY)GigaChipsFoldrBak (Blue Exclusive) / NavRcycl (White Exclusive)Bass+ (Blue Exclusive) / Bass (White Exclusive)DarkAura (Blue Exclusive) / Serenade (White Exclusive)DeltaRay (Blue Exclusive) / Balance (White Exclusive)AlphArm&#937; (Blue Exclusive) / AlphArm&#931; (White Exclusive)GutsManV5ProtoMnV5FlashMnV5BeastMnV5BubblMnV5DesrtMnV5PlantMnV5FlamManV5DrillMnV5MetalMnV5KingManV5MistManV5BowlManV5DarkManV5JapanMnV5BassGS (Capcom Promotional Event Exclusive)Program AdvancesZeta-Cannon1 (Z-Canon1)Zeta-Cannon2 (Z-Canon2)Zeta-Cannon3 (Z-Canon3)Zeta-Guts Punch (Z-Punch)Zeta-Guts Straight (Z-Strght)Zeta-Guts Impact (Z-Impact)Zeta-Variable Sword (Z-Varibl)Zeta-Yo-Yo1 (Z-Yoyo1)Zeta-Yo-Yo2 (Z-Yoyo2)Zeta-Yo-Yo3 (Z-Yoyo3)Zeta-Step Sword (Z-Step1)Zeta-Step Cross (Z-Step2)Bubble Spread (BubSprd)Heat Spread (HeatSprd)Hyper Burst (H-Burst)Life Sword (LifeSwrd)Elemental Sword (ElemSwrd)Evil Cut (EvilCut)Hyper Ratton (HyperRat)Giga TimeBomb (TimeBom+)Raining Gel (GelRain)Endless Curse (EverCrse)Mother Quake (MomQuake)Poison Pharaoh (PoisPhar)Body Guard (BodyGrd)500 Barrier (500Barr)Big Heart (BigHeart)Guts Shoot (GtsShoot)Deux Hero (DeuxHero)Double Hero (2xHero)Grand Prix (PrixPowr)Master Style (MstrStyl)Cheat: Secret Boss NavisAfter beating LifeVirus, you can fight four secret Navis if you meet the requirements.Cheat: Entering Deeper Parts of the InternetAs you make your way through the many areas of the Internet, you'll notice that there are gates in the way of links to following areas. Those gates have question marks on them, and you must fulfill a certain requirement within that area of the Internet, then go to the gate in order to open it and proceed to the next Internet area. Here's a quick list of requirements to get into the later areas: Area 11: You cannot escape any battles in Area 10. Area 12: Busting Level after every battle must be above 3 in Area 11. Area 13: You cannot escape any battles in Area 10. Area 14: You must win at least 10 chips in battle from enemies in Area 13. Area 15: You must stay out of battles as much as you can in Area 14 (less than 7, I believe). Area 16: Busting Level after every battle must be above 4 in Area 15.Cheat: Entering Deeper Parts of the InternetCollect 174 chips, all except Dream Aura chip (No.127). Go to the deepest Internet Area (Internet Area 16, in the area where you can get Paradin Sword). Walk around that area until you find him. He can appear everywhere in that area. If you can beat him, he should give you the Dream Aura chip. Please remember, Forte CAN'T give his chip to you.Cheat: Entering Deeper Parts of the InternetIn the School's computer network, there are several doors you'll come to that require you to input a 2-digit passcode. Here's a list of the codes for each door (for the ones marked as random, you're given hints if the number is higher or lower each time you guess wrong): Door 1: 09 Door 2: 30 Door 3: Randomly generated Door 4: Randomly generated Door 5: 15 Door 6: Randomly generated Door 7: Randomly generated (Requires Teacher's Passcode to access)</plot>
	<releasedate>24/6/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>LcKqSVv1UoE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6927</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/457634-mega-man-battle-network</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mega-man-battle-network-3-blue-version</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-man-battle-network-3/3030-13189/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6927-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6927-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/23252-mega-man-battle-network-3-blue-version-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60002-mega-man-battle-network-3-blue-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60003-mega-man-battle-network-3-blue-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60004-mega-man-battle-network-3-blue-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60005-mega-man-battle-network-3-blue-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60006-mega-man-battle-network-3-blue-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60007-mega-man-battle-network-3-blue-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60008-mega-man-battle-network-3-blue-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/60009-mega-man-battle-network-3-blue-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/17953/783100-normal_serenade.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7784/569136-megamanbn3whitegba_003_large.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/lp8MGkE.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/6927.png</clearlogo1>
</game>