<Game>
	<Name>Metal Slug Advance (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Metal Slug Advance plays almost identical to every entry in the Metal Slug series. It's a side-scrolling, arcade style 2D action game with a heavy emphasis on non-stop action. Players quite literally run through levels, shooting everything in sight. Power-ups can be attained usually through rescuing captive soldiers or killing some enemies. Players have the choice to play as either Walter Ryan or Tyra Elson, a blue-haired male and female redhead respectively, and the story involves a Peregrine training camp on an island that is invaded by General Morden. Walter and Tyra are new recruits, thrust into an actual mission.Gameplay:The protagonist, either Walter or Tyra, has a pistol with infinite ammo as a default weapon. There are various weapon pickups to be found such as Rocket Launchers, Heavy Machine Guns, Shotguns, and a few other surprises. Grenades can also be thrown. There is also some vehicle gameplay to be had as characters step into various Metal Slugs, The Slug Gunner and The Slug Flyer.The two new systems introduced in Metal Slug Advance are the life system, which is simply a health bar that replaces the lives from the previous game, and the e-card system, which provides bonuses if the player finds special cards scattered throughout the stages. Weapons:Enemy ChaserDrop ShotFlame ShotSuper GrenadeHeavy Machine GunIron LizardLaserRocket LauncherShotgunCheat: Bypass Airplane LevelAfter you jump into your plane slug in Mission 5 and go onto the next screen, quickly press up until you're on top of the screen, press left and hold it. Now the enemy planes won't show up on screen and if you hold your position long enough, you will finish the level without encountering any enemies.Cheat: Complete a missionIn a mission, rescue every prisoner and collect every available item (the X-Ray scan card is useful for this) to get a golden "COMPLETE" sign over a mission on the map screen.Cheat: Complete a missionIn mission 5, find and kill Allen. (He has a large machine gun, throws grenades and will slash you with a knife if you get close and is different to any normal enemy) When you do kill him, he will drop a card. Collect it, then complete the level without dieing to keep the Allen Jr card.Cheat: Complete a missionWhen you are fighting a boss, you must destroy it very quickly to get its card (A message will appear on screen informing you that you have the card) To defeat the bosses quickly you must have lots of grenades and a special weapon (like the flame shot for the fourth boss) or use the Metal Slug if you can get it (Second, third and final boss)Cheat: Complete a missionCollect all 99 cards in the game to get the final 100th "All cards" card.Cheat: Complete a missionYou need the "paper thin" card. Turn it on, then complete any mission. With paper thin turned on you will die with just one hit. The easiest way to get the decoration card is to complete mission 2, mainly because there is a Metal Slug at the near start of the level which is shielded, so if you can manage to get through the level with the Metal Slug it shouldn't be as difficult to get the card.Cheat: Complete a missionYou just have to clear the mission, you can die as many times as it takes.Cheat: Complete a missionIn Mission 5, find and collect the dungeon card. Then complete mission 5 and go to the mission select screen and to the top left there is an extra mission called dungeon.Cheat: Parachute route in mission 5In mission 5, jump into the plane slug. Now as soon as you start the level proper, press L to crash the slug. You will eject and go onto a different route where you parachute down into the enemy docks.</plot>
	<releasedate>30/11/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SNK Corporation</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ZVxr47jkufM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>11164</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/582683-metal-slug-advance</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/metal-slug-advance</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/metal-slug-advance/3030-8583/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11164-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11164-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/45807-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107982-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107973-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-any.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107974-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choosing-a.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107975-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-disembarking.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107976-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-is-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107977-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-mission-map.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107978-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-what-an-immense.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107979-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-vertical.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107980-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-3-missile-aerial.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107991-metal-slug-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-tyra-was-damaged.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11164-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/JHbPfbV.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/11164.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Now you can have all the 2D arcade action of Metal Slug in the palm of your hand, because Metal Slug Advance has arrived on the Game Boy Advance. Through five action-packed missions, you must move out on foot or in slug vehicles across rugged terrain and underwater bases. Your objective is to rescue hostages by destroying enemies and solving strategic puzzles. Completing your missions becomes easier when you collect more than 100 types of E-cards, which enhance your character's abilities.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cde6e0e9-e38d-48e6-a194-3a1ac29d305f.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/278f6e77-1dbd-4b10-9caa-d08be55d83d2.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5211fca7-d0dc-4c53-9dda-f2fd7a5309f6.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/83c4fe37-2773-495f-bb70-aa58839e3fae.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e9a2f52c-25b4-4184-8ef0-0e3785d4d1ce.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1e321e52-e365-4472-9bf2-be0a484526ae.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0290ce21-3ce9-403f-bd59-eac42087abf1.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>SNK Playmore</Publisher>
</game>