<Game>
	<Name>Midnight Club - Street Racing (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:From publisher Rockstar Games and developer Angel Studios, Midnight Club: Street Racing was released on the Playstation 2 on October 25, 2000 to coincide with the launch of the Playstation 2.  The game is of the racing genre, and has the player compete in illegal street races to progress through the career mode.  The career mode takes you through both New York and London and are open for exploration right at the start. Both cities are large and full of cars driving the city streets, police cars patrolling, and pedestrians strolling the sidewalks.  There are approximately 42 vehicles to choose from in Midnight Club: Street Racing all of which are based on real life car models, but aren't officially licensed. The game has you free-roaming through city streets, looking for other racers (visible on your mini-map) to find and compete against in numerous races.  When you have found another racer, you can activate a race against that driver and his gang with the reward being that driver's vehicle being added to your collection. The career mode is also filled with countless secrets that can be found throughout each city and add to the overall short length of career mode. The game modes consist of checkpoint races, a joyride mode, and capture the flag, as well as featuring multiplayer for up to two players. Plot:A mysterious group of urban street racers known as the Midnight Club race for pride, power, and glory in sleekly customized, enhanced sports cars. As a regular New Your City cab driver, the player learns about this secret club and decides to join.The player begins with a relatively unmodified and slow vehicle. Through a series of races, each with different goals, they defeat other racers and win faster and more expensive vehicles. The goal is to defeat the world champion, who is revealed to be a young Japanese woman named Anika whose father manufactures concept cars in Japan. Being the only person to beat her in a race, the player is the only one who sees her identity and become the World Champion of the Midnight Club, along with winning her concept car. Anika returns to Japan afterwards.    </plot>
	<releasedate>8/11/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Destination Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>19451</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/539989-midnight-club-street-racing</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/midnight-club-street-racing</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/midnight-club-street-racing/3030-10124/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2428404-box_mcsr.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/16074-midnight-club-street-racing-playstation-2-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/16075-midnight-club-street-racing-playstation-2-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/a/2/gfs_51054_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/7/2/gfs_51054_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/c/2/gfs_51054_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/d/2/gfs_51054_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/6/2/gfs_51054_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/fPlje90.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Midnight Club brings the action of high speed driving and adventure to the Game Boy Advance. The concept behind this game derives from the illegal races of real-world Midnight Clubs. The core gameplay consists of races of high-speed maneuvering through completely open city streets. Live life in the insane lane, escape the law and accumulate an arsenal of vehicles.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2ff0b285-8e97-49b9-b75c-7b442ba2386e.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bda15c1d-5946-42dd-917c-c642c80c5852.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>DSI Games</Publisher>
</game>