<Game>
	<Name>Miteluode - Lingdian Renwu (China)</Name>
	<plot>Space Pirates attack a Galactic Federation-owned space research vessel and seize samples of Metroid creatures. Dangerous floating organisms, Metroids can latch on to any organism and drain its life energy to kill it. The Space Pirates plan to replicate Metroids by exposing them to beta rays and then using them as biological weapons to destroy all living beings that oppose them. While searching for the stolen Metroids, the Galactic Federation locates the Space Pirates' base of operations on the planet Zebes. The Federation assaults the planet, but the Pirates resist, forcing the Federation to retreat. As a last resort, the Federation decides to send a lone bounty hunter to penetrate the Pirates' base and destroy Mother Brain, the mechanical life-form that controls the Space Pirates' fortress and its defenses. Considered the greatest of all bounty hunters, Samus Aran is chosen for the mission. Samus lands on the surface of Zebes and explores the planet, traveling through the planet's caverns. She eventually comes across Kraid, an ally of the Space Pirates, and Ridley, the Space Pirates' commander, and defeats them both. Along the way, Samus finds and destroys Mother Brain. However, while Samus leaves the planet in her gunship, it is attacked by Space Pirates, causing it to crash back on to Zebes, near the Space Pirate Mothership. Exploring the Mothership, Samus eventually reaches the Ridley Robot, a mechanized form of Ridley. After defeating it, Samus escapes the planet using one of the Space Pirate's shuttles, while the Mothership self-destructs.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/2/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3745</thegamesdb_id>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3745-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3745-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3745-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3745-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3745-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3745-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/3745-5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3745-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3745-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3745-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3745-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3745-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3745-6.jpg</fanart6>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3745-g.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3745.png</clearlogo1>
</game>