<Game>
	<Name>MLB SlugFest 20-04 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>The second title in Midway's baseball series, SlugFest 20-04 continues to pour on the rough-housing gameplay, bizarre codes, and humorous commentary.  In addition to the new Home Run Derby mode and Create-A-Team options, the game features the ability of pitchers to catch "On Fire" and impossible Special Pitches that zigzag, arc, and whizz by in ways that would leave any batter humiliated.  New secret teams have been added to the previous bunch, including aliens, minotaurs, and Sub-Zero of Mortal Kombat fame.  The customizable Instant Replay is another nice touch, allowing you to relive the awkward moments once you pause the game.  And, of course, Tim Kitzrow and Jim Shorts return to the commentators' booth, making their signature random comments and incessant arguments.Cheat: Cheat CodesThis code are to be entered at the matchup screen. In the codes listed below, the first number refers to how many times to hit the B button, the second number refers to the A button and the third is for the R button. Finally, push the indicated direction to lock in the code. If done correctly, a message will appear.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/3/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Midway Home Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22243</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589425-mlb-slugfest-20-04</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mlb-slugfest-20-04</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mlb-slugfest-20-04/3030-6304/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22243-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/160231-mlb-slugfest-20-04-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/160232-mlb-slugfest-20-04-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/160233-mlb-slugfest-20-04-game-boy-advance-screenshot-team-selection.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741508-mlb-slugfest-20-04-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-field.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741515-mlb-slugfest-20-04-game-boy-advance-screenshot-next-game.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741516-mlb-slugfest-20-04-game-boy-advance-screenshot-here-comes.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741517-mlb-slugfest-20-04-game-boy-advance-screenshot-here-comes.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741518-mlb-slugfest-20-04-game-boy-advance-screenshot-hit-the-ball.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741519-mlb-slugfest-20-04-game-boy-advance-screenshot-running-for.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/741509-mlb-slugfest-20-04-game-boy-advance-screenshot-good-hit.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>MLB SlugFest 20-04 is the first and only aggressive-style baseball videogame franchise, delivering a proprietary blend of hardcore, lightning-fast, adrenaline-style gameplay combined with key baseball features that will please even the most diehard sports fan. Game features include adrenaline-style gameplay, revolutionary, fast-action batter/pitcher interface, strategic contact, and intuitive, fast-action, adrenaline-style controls.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ff3ea606-3e33-4a05-8a3d-6413af7ba798.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/71fc073a-b19f-4929-8621-70b7def8faee.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Midway</Publisher>
</game>