<Game>
	<Name>Mobile Suit Gundam Seed - Battle Assault (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Mobile Suit Gundam Seed: Battle Assault pits eight (plus four unlockable) Alliance and ZAFT pilots against each other in armored combat in the Bloody Valentine War. Each Gundam's attacks are split between physical close range attacks and long range beam/gun attacks. Gundams can boost to quickly move on the ground or change directions in mid-air, as well as enter Berserk mode that trades reduced armor for increased attack power as well as unlocking their Ultimate Attack. Before the game starts the player can reduce their boosting ability to increase their Gundam's armor or HP.Game modes include a simple story mode, training, time attack, survival, free battle, and 2-player versus.Cheat: Alternate color for the Mobile Suits (2P color)To use this Code for any specific Mobile Suit, you must have cleared the Story Mode using that Mobile Suit. (ie. to use the alternate color for the Strike Gundam, you must have completed its story in any difficulty.) At the Mobile Suit Selection screen for any Mode, highlight the Mobile Suit and press and hold Select, then press A to select it. Then, do the rest of the set up. Once you enter the battle, your Mobile Suit should have the alternate color.Cheat: Misc. PasswordsEnter the following at the password screen:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Bandai America, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>BUhhUrlf-VE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>26048</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920412-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault/3030-31311/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/26048-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/6/3/59663_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/192097-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465724-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465725-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465726-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465727-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465728-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465729-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465730-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465731-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465732-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465733-mobile-suit-gundam-seed-battle-assault-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/meNGJDG.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Gundam Seed: Battle Assault, a great new action game, is the first Gundam game to become available on the Game Boy Advance. Gundam Seed is the next big thing to hit the world of Gundam. Based on the anime aired in Japan in 2003 and in the US on Cartoon Network TV in 2004, the game features 12 playable mobile suits from the show. Also included are seven gameplay modes including a two-player VS mode that allows gamers to link up to four Game Boy Advance systems using a Game Boy Advance Game Link Cable (sold separately) for head to head action. To make the game accessible to wide audience, the game includes a difficulty level for all players: choose automatic or manual mode, and then adjust armor, HP and energy gauges to maximize the challenge.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b01d45f-b765-4419-90e8-5e3d540cca81.jpg</boxart3>
	<Publisher>Bandai</Publisher>
</game>