<Game>
	<Name>Monopoly (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>This time, a Monopoly game on your computer, as good as it knows to be in your reality. Every move of yours can be in 3D animation, or off if you don't want to see animations. There can be up to 6 players at once, and it can be played over the Internet. Music is in midi format, and the sound quality is at the wav format. Roll, spin, and don't miss to give us a grin.http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy/monopoly</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/1991</releasedate>
	<genre>Board Game</genre>
	<Developer>Parker Bros</Developer>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>2909</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/926475-monopoly</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2909-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/3/2/65732_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/1/f/gfs_62867_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/c/f/gfs_62867_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/7/f/gfs_62867_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/6/f/gfs_62867_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/d/f/gfs_62867_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2909-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/dzGGPAa.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2909.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Being a real-estate magnate used to be hard work. Thanks to technology, the computer does all the hard stuff, like rolling dice, for you. Freed of the anxiety of arguing over leaners, you have plenty of time to strategize your next financial move. Up to four players, or you and three computer opponents, take turns around the board. A player wins when the others go belly up. You can also play a quick game mode or a time limit game. In any of the game modes, you can institute your own house rules. Some of those could include awarding a person for landing on free parking, dealing out some properties at random to begin the game, or changing the number of properties you have to own in a group before you can build houses. The easy-to-use interface makes it easy to manage your finances. When you have multiple players, the games can take a long time to finish, but that's the nature of Monopoly.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/571f1c47-5767-498f-9d11-532088ed90e6.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/30b243c3-8f1a-46a0-af70-55a630b11a66.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Destination Software Inc</Publisher>
</game>