<Game>
	<Name>Monster Truck Madness (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>  Monster Truck Madness (abbreviated as MTM or MTM1) is a PC racing game that includes a roster nothing but Monster Trucks. The game was developer by Terminal Reality and published by Microsoft in 1996. The game had four single player modes and was possible to play against another human player over DirectPlay. Throughout the game, race commentary is provided by "Army" Armstrong, giving one liners every time the player does something interesting or different than was intended.  The game was ported to the Game Boy Advance and even had a version on the Nintendo 64.Game Modes Players can race on several different tracks in the following game modes: Drag, Circuit, Rally, and Tournament.Available TrucksBearfoot Bigfoot Boogey Van Carolina Crusher Grave Digger Monster Patrol Overkill Power Wheels Bigfoot Rampage Samson Snake Bite Wildfoot   Drags B.C. Place Indiana State Fairgrounds RCA Dome Tacoma Dome Trans World Dome Circuits Crazy Eight Canyon Adventure Mud Pies Round and Round Winding Way Rallies ArizonaHighlands RallyYucatan Adventure  Community  Nearly all of the MTM communities are now inactive. However, the game enjoyed significant popularity among casual gamers in the late 90s, and its success was largely carried through into the 2000's. The game's popularity reached its peak during 1999; in this year, 776 custom tracks were submitted to the unofficial fan site MTM2.com, compared to 456 tracks in 1998 and 464 tracks in 2000. Popular activities within MTM communities include the making of custom tracks and trucks and the organization and running of MTM Racing tournaments.Cheat: Best truckThis vehicle looks more like a chicken than a truck and all four of the stats are full, so this could be VERY useful! But you need to beat ALL, and I mean ALL of the records on the 30 tracks So if you want it ASAP, you need to beat the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/8/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>19452</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561848-monster-truck-madness</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/monster-truck-madness-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/monster-truck-madness/3030-7017/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/19452-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/69669-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/55354-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465224-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465225-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-screenshot-name-entry.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465226-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465227-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-screenshot-start.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465228-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-screenshot-having-difficulties.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465229-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-screenshot-lifted-off.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465230-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-screenshot-picked-up.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465231-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-game.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465232-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-coloured.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465233-monster-truck-madness-game-boy-advance-screenshot-result-screen.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>One of the best selling auto-racing games on the PC comes to Game Boy Advance with a variety of vehicles and tracks for the some stompin' good fun on the go. Get behind the steering wheel of the world's most powerful vehicles as they crush, splatter, jump, and roll their way to victory.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/417f4013-1483-44cb-9259-f7ffb031663e.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>