<Game>
	<Name>Monster Rancher Advance (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Monster Rancher Advance is a monster raising sim that allows players to raise and customize 440 monster types. These monsters can then be tested in in-game tournaments, or battled against other players in 2P mode with the GBA link cable. Monsters are created in the game's shrine through the entry of letters, numbers and punctuation symbols. Players begin with the ability to enter up to 4 characters to make monsters, and can unlock the ability to use up to 8 characters through gaining higher trainer ranks. Different words or combinations of characters can not only make different types of monsters, but each monster can have varying attributes and characteristics, making each one unique.Players then train the monsters by choosing  which foods to feed, which drills to do to raise attributes, what training to send them to for new attacks, and what items to give them. The game starts with a modest amount of money with which food and items can be purchased, more money is earned in tournaments. Gameplay revolves around planning training sessions, adding new attacks and juggling a bank account, along with attempting to win tournaments. As monsters age, they can be added to a coaching staff to help raise new monsters to better attributes, or they can be combined with other monsters to make stronger babies. Monsters do not die in this game, however, they do face an enforced retirement age.There is a fairly straightforward storyline, where some characters from older Monster Rancher games visit, and new characters are introduced. The gameplay itself, like most other Monster Rancher games, is open-ended and has unlimited replay value.The 2 Player mode, involving a link cable and two copies of the game, allows players to test the monsters they have raised against other players. The 2P mode also allows players to trade items and cash with one another, to wager items or cash on tournaments, and trade raised monsters into each others' games.Cheat: Golden MonstersSeveral Golden monsters can be unlocked.  Their stats are average, but they look cool.Cheat: Golden MonstersAll passwords are CaSe SeNsItIvE.Cheat: Golden MonstersDuring a game, enter the Shrine, and enter any of the following names to inlock the corresponding monster.  Passwords are case sensitive.Cheat: Golden MonstersWhen making a monster at the shrine for the first time, use the tablet and type in:'Hobo' Cheat: Golden Monstersit's case sensitive so do it like that, anyway, you'll get a knight, it's a green color and it's no. 326 and it's name is Lezaal no idea about anything else but that it's restricted.Cheat: Special MonstersThere are some monsters that are classified as ''Special'' and they have stats that dwarf the normal monsters, some of the ''Special'' monsters can be obtained by entering these words. *Note these are case sensitive* Pabs Luminous Paladin - (durahan) Ninja LIKETEA - (naga) Santa - (momo) Cabbit  - (psiroller)  KEEPSLY -(zuum) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; There are many more, try and find them on your own! </plot>
	<releasedate>29/11/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Tecmo, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>21701</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/516681-monster-rancher-advance</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/monster-rancher-advance</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/monster-rancher-advance/3030-4700/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/21701-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/29701-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161043-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161045-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-at-the.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161046-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-register.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161047-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-is.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161048-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-meet-aroma.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161061-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-is.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161049-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-decide.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161050-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-is.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161052-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161053-monster-rancher-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-using.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8ASdPGS.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Monster Rancher Advance is a Strategy Role-Playing game, developed and published by Tecmo, which was released in 2001.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/645ba763-7c35-40d7-877a-ed37c1aad77e.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Tecmo</Publisher>
</game>