<Game>
	<Name>Mortal Kombat - Tournament Edition (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>This semi-sequel to Mortal Kombat: Deadly Alliance brings together a handful of the previous characters with a host of new and well-known faces making their debut on the GBA, including Bo Rai Cho, Johnny Cage, Raiden, Sareena, Nitara, Cyrax, Mavado, Reptile, Hsu Hao and Drahmin.Game modes include a collection of new multiplayer modes, such as the Race to Raiden, where two players compete against a set of characters, and the first to reach and defeat Raiden wins. Up to 4 players can compete in Tournament mode to see who is the best fighter. Plus there's plenty of single player modes including Survival, while you can link Tournament Edition with Deadly Alliance to play some of the multiplayer modes.Cheat: Different Color WeaponsEnter this at the screen where they show you who your opponent is. Hold both buttons until the round begins. These can also be done in between rounds.Cheat: Different Colored Reflection of WeaponDo the Colored weapons code except RED and when on a stage where the floor is reflective (for example, Swamp arena), do the weapon fatality for that character and the weapon will be seen as red but the reflection on the floor will be the color that was inputted with the colored weapon code.</plot>
	<releasedate>25/8/2003</releasedate>
	<Developer>Midway</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>M - Mature</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22266</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/914923-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mortal-kombat-tournament-edition</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mortal-kombat-tournament-edition/3030-16172/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22266-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159410-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/159411-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/170272-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/162764-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/162765-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/162766-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/162767-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/162768-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/162769-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/163421-mortal-kombat-tournament-edition-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/q8JwfHF.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The deadly alliance between Shang Tsung and Quan Chi remains intact. In Mortal Kombat: Tournament Edition, however, a new set of warriors seeks revenge against these evil warlords. See who proves victorious as you fight your way through both tournament and tag-team action on your Game Boy Advance. In addition to more fighters, this installment in the Mortal Kombat series provides multiplayer support for up to four players (via Game Boy Advance link cable), a variety of gameplay modes, and new battlegrounds.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7d02b3b8-e30e-457d-b9b4-cc90f2275236.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d03614d3-67f1-42ee-82f0-2413614ad434.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eefee903-61b0-4880-8cac-5a08d36319e7.png</clearlogo1>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	<Publisher>Midway</Publisher>
</game>