<Game>
	<Name>Mother 1+2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Mother 1+2 cartridgeMother 1+2 is a compilation cartridge released for the Game Boy Advance only in Japan on June 20, 2003. The compilation was published by Nintendo and developed by HAL Laboratory and Ape. The game is a port of Mother (also  known as EarthBound Zero) and Mother 2 (released as EarthBound in North America). The original announcement commercial for Mother 1+2 also announced that Mother 3 was going to be released.When it was originally released in 2003, the game was packaged with a limited edition Mr. Saturn cell phone strap for those who had pre-ordered the game. The cell phone strap became very popular, however, and was sold on Amazon's Japanese website for a short time. The cell phone straps are now relatively rare, especially in North America.Although there was never an official English release of the game, well-known EarthBound fan-site Starmen.net is currently in the process of translating the game. After finishing the Mother 3 translation, Tomato (who also works as a professional translator in anime and video games, working on such things as One Piece, various mobile games, and even Kingdom Hearts II) expressed interest in doing a Mother 1+2 translation. The project is currently being worked on by the same primary team that did the Mother 3 translation (Tomato and Jeffman).Mother 1+2 is in the process of being translated into English.There were many changes made to Mother, that are found in EarthBound Zero (the translated version; but not the original Mother). These changes include adding a running button, several changes to enemies due to Nintendo of America's strict standards, and various programming changes. Originally, these changes were thought to have been made in a fan translation, but when they were kept in Mother 1+2, it was proven that they were official changes.Mother 1+2 was well-received by Japanese critics, receiving a 35/40 score from Famitsu. In addition, in a 2005 issue, Nintendo Power listed Mother 1+2 as one of their most wanted import games. Mother 1+2 sold approximately 280,000 copies in Japan.Gameplay:The first and second Mother games are very similar in terms of gameplay features. There are several differences between the two, however. The first Mother had completely random battle encounters, while EarthBound (Mother 2) has the enemies visible onscreen. Being a traditional role-playing series, there are many of the regular actions, such as a physical hit, using an item, guarding, running away, and--for some characters--PSI attacks (basically the equivalent of magic attacks).Battles in both games look something like this.In overworld (out of battle) gameplay, players can communicate with several non-playable characters. There are shops, inns, and hospitals. Shops are to purchase items, weapons, clothing, and sometimes special "characters" to help you in battle (such as a teddy bear). Inns are where players can completely heal their party for a price. Hospitals are where fainted characters can be revived, and certain status effects can be removed.Plot:The plot of Mother and Mother 2 is completely unrelated, but shares certain details such as general setting, some character similarities, enemies, and the same final boss. Mother follows Ninten, Ana, and Loid on their quest to defeat an alien menace known as Giegue. The prologue text of the game introduces George and Maria, a couple who were kidnapped and sent to Giegue's homeworld. Maria ended up getting an emotional connection to Giegue, while George stole the secrets of PSI from the aliens, and managed to escape back to Earth. Ninten, Ana, and Loid manage to defeat Giegue with the Eight Melodies, a song taught to the group by Maria that she used to sing to Giegue.Ness is the main character of EarthBound.EarthBound (Mother 2) followed Ness, Paula, Jeff, and Poo, the four chosen ones. Ness is visited by a creature from the future named Buzz Buzz, who tells Ness that he and three other kids must defeat Giygas (an older version of Giegue). Ness's neighbor, Pokey, also plays a pivotal role in the plot of EarthBound. He becomes Giygas's servant, and serves as Ness's nemesis for the larger part of the game. In the final battle against Giygas, the group manages to defeat Giygas with Paula (and many of those met along the journey) praying for the group to be able to defeat Giygas.Cheat: Note: This only works in the Super Famicom version of Earthbound(Mother 2).In Mother 2, you could use the Exit Mouse in the Cave of the Past, which was never intended obviously, since the feature is missing in Earthbound.Cheat: You can use the Rock Candy in battles an unlimited amount of times to increase your stats. You have to have it in one of the two very bottom spaces of one of your characters' inventories, and you have to use it with any condiment (preferably something like Sugar Packets or Jars of Delisauce, because they will increase one of your stats by 2 instead of one). This will allow you to get greater boosts in stats when you level up.Cheat: Outside of the hotel room in Twoson, there will be a man sitting at a table. Constantly speak to him (his response will change each time) until he decides to hand you $50 so you can leave him alone. It takes about 20 sessions of talking for him to fork it over, but it's well worth it, plus it'll make up for the night you spent at the hotel.Cheat: If you go into a room with a large amount or any amount of enemies in it, you can exit the room and re-enter it and the amount of enemies changes sometimes even taking them all out of that room. This can eliminate time consuming fights.Cheat: By opening the Menu often out in the field, you will encounter enemies much less often. This is a bug in the game that was removed in future releases such as Mother 1+2.Cheat: The doctor charges you half your money currently on you.  Just deposit all your money to make him charge you very little to none.Cheat: After getting Loid in your party, return to the Sweet's Factory where you got your first bottle rocket. Now the trash can disperses infinite bottle rockets.Cheat: While in Magiciant in the northern area you can find a red weed sitting in the middle of a bunch of green weeds. "Check" the red weed and you will recieve the Red Weed. Now bring the Red Weed to the Fountaain in the North West of Magiciant and "Use" the Red Weed. The Red Weed will change into a Magic Herb.Cheat: Do this as many times as you like to recieve unlimited Magic Herbs.</plot>
	<releasedate>19/6/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>19044</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/914618-mother-12</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mother-12</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mother-12/3030-3775/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/19044-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/19044-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/352058-mother-1-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/352059-mother-1-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose-your-game.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/352060-mother-1-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen-for-mother.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/352061-mother-1-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-opening-story-for-mother.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/352062-mother-1-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-starting-location-for.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/352063-mother-1-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen-for-mother.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/352064-mother-1-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-opening-story-for-mother.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7395/1213915-trippy.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7395/1202994-666.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7395/1202993-stopping.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/lftqu32.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Mother tells the story of Ninten, a 12-year-old boy who journeys around the world using his psychic powers to collect eight melodies in order to save the planet from an evil race of mind-controlling aliens. Mother 2 tells the story of Ness, a young boy who journeys around the world also using psychic powers to collect eight melodies in order to save the future from an alien of pure evil, intending to sentence all of reality to the horror of eternal darkness.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>1</nPlayers>
	<VideoURL1>https://www.youtube.com/watch?time_continue=31&amp;v=KN9wBCKAO20</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c01009f-eca1-4eae-9234-7c6d07826465.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/669e0481-a4da-42fe-9fb6-78b2e94a7827.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>