<Game>
	<Name>Mr. Driller A - Fushigi na Pacteria (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Mr. Driller Ace (also known as Mr. Driller A) featured link cable connectivity features with Mr. Driller: Drill Land for the Gamecube. However, both games were only released in Japan.Cheat: Driller Grand Prix UnlockablesTest your skills even further in the Grand Prix's more challenging courses. Just come in first overall in the course to unlock the next! Go for gold.Cheat: Driller Grand Prix UnlockablesOnce you reach the depths of the Amazon, 1500 M. deep, you not only watch the ending of the Mission Driller story, but an even more difficult challenge awaits. Arrive at the South Pole and see if you can reach the bottom, 2000 M. away! If you do, you get Usagi, the black rabbit, who is often seen with dark Hori Atoru. This little rabbit can climb up two blocks run and dig incredibly fast, and digs in a range of three blocks wide, all without wasting too much air! Usagi can be used in the Mission Driller and Grand Prix modes.Cheat: Driller Grand Prix UnlockablesAs you play through the Wonderful Pacteria mode, you will arrive at many different ruins with more challenging distances to travel, all to solve the mysteries of the Pacteria. If you complete the Valkyrie Ruins for the first time, you watch the end of the story. When you begin again, you have a new Pacteria to take care of, and the new Pacteria Ruins will be available to play through. The other areas will also be reopened for good, so you can drill through the easier ones for Pacteria items. But the Pacteria shrine is the toughest area to drill in, but the most rare Pacteria items are found here, so drill carefully...</plot>
	<releasedate>23/8/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561125-mr-driller-ace</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mr-driller-ace-fushigi-na-pacteria</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mr-driller-a/3030-25434/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/7439/900785-561125_19553_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/4/0/1/17401_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/768250-mr-driller-ace-fushigi-na-pacteria-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/768249-mr-driller-ace-fushigi-na-pacteria-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/768251-mr-driller-ace-fushigi-na-pacteria-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/768252-mr-driller-ace-fushigi-na-pacteria-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/768253-mr-driller-ace-fushigi-na-pacteria-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/768257-mr-driller-ace-fushigi-na-pacteria-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/768255-mr-driller-ace-fushigi-na-pacteria-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/768256-mr-driller-ace-fushigi-na-pacteria-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/4/1/gfs_19553_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/9/1/gfs_19553_1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/01eaa8ec-4622-4de1-b045-1ff3dc210306.png</boxart3>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Namco</Publisher>
</game>