<Game>
	<Name>Muppet Pinball Mayhem (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Muppet Pinball Mayhem is a pinball game based on the ever-popular Muppet characters. This game features recognizable music and sound effects from the Muppet Show, along with backgrounds based on Muppet characters.There are three tables, one for Kermit, one for Miss Piggie, and one for Gonzo. There is also a secret hidden table for an undisclosed character. The hidden table is unlocked in "Adventure Mode", where you must get a high score and hit a specific target to progress from one table to the next.Each table has a variety of scoring opportunities, including ramps, spinners, and various table games. 4 players can compete in a competion mode, where each player takes a turn trying to get the high score.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/5/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>NewKidCo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>26054</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/565541-muppet-pinball-mayhem</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/muppet-pinball-mayhem</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/muppet-pinball-mayhem/3030-4195/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5768/745483-muppet.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/23099-muppet-pinball-mayhem-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/23100-muppet-pinball-mayhem-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179265-muppet-pinball-mayhem-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179266-muppet-pinball-mayhem-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179267-muppet-pinball-mayhem-game-boy-advance-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179268-muppet-pinball-mayhem-game-boy-advance-screenshot-adventure.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179264-muppet-pinball-mayhem-game-boy-advance-screenshot-competition.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179262-muppet-pinball-mayhem-game-boy-advance-screenshot-starting.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/179263-muppet-pinball-mayhem-game-boy-advance-screenshot-here-s-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/5768/745487-gonzo.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/9/6/gfs_49650_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/4/6/gfs_49650_1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Everyone's favorite puppets are the stars of this blistering, addicting pinball extravaganza. Jim Henson's beloved creations grace every nook and cranny of this deliriously exciting handheld game, which was created specifically to commemorate the 25th Anniversary of THE MUPPETS. Play as Kermit, Miss Piggy, Animal, or a handful of other franchise characters each of which will give the table slightly different physics. There are four tables for you to master, which makes for an extremely high replay value. There are also more adjustable settings than you can shake a stick at, meaning the game grows to match your skill level, as you become a more advanced player. In the unlikely event that you should conquer all four levels, try your hand at any of the 20 mini-games that are included to round out the package. Fabulous graphics and classic MUPPET humor are ever present in MUPPET PINBALL MAYHEM for the Game Boy Advance.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bb8bdd4a-95f3-4372-a66e-4ff8e5173680.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3bfd4087-3ba2-493b-b5fe-b7956007849d.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>NewKidCo</Publisher>
</game>