<Game>
	<Name>Namco Museum - 50th Anniversary (USA)</Name>
	<plot>IT'S PARTY TIME! Namco celebrates 50 years of bringing you the greatest games on the planet with the ultimate portable collection of all-star arcade classics. Namco Museum 50th Anniversary features five of the most treasured games in arcade history. Put the arcade experience in the palm of your hand and this time... leave your quarters at home.Cheat: This glitch will make all enemies dissapear in the current level, but the level will not end. This let's you to get as many points as you want from eating all the dirt!1) Get the game down to two Pookas. If you only leave one, it will escape thus ending the round.2) This works best in horizontal tunnels under the rocks.3) Get a Pooka to follow you, inflate as necessary to delay him a little.4) Right when you are next to the rock, inflate the Pooka once to just delay him. When he moves at your character again, move under the rock.5) Quickly turn around and start pumping the Pooka up. Using the delay of the rock dropping, you should be able to cause the Pooka to burst at the same time the rock drops on him.6) If you are successful, then the other Pooka will disappear and you can amuse yourself digging out tunnels all day long in the dirt. NOTE: To return the game back to normal, drop another rock and you will go into the next round.Cheat: On most revisions of Galaga, there's a trick that stops enemies from firing at your ship.  In Stage 1, kill all aliens except the two bees in the bottom-left corner.  Allow the bees to dive down and shoot at you, while dodging their shots.  After around 15 minutes or so, the bees will continue to drop down, but they won't fire.  Let them drop down another 5 or 6 times, then kill them.  After all this, enemies will not shoot at you for the rest of the game.Cheat: Wait until one of the top ships(the green ones that take two shots to kill) comes down and fires off a tractor beam(the beam that can capture your ship).  Let it capture your ship.  Now, wait until it swoops down again with your ship behind it.  Simply kill the head ship(the green one), and it will lose your ship.  Your ship will then lock on to the side of your current ship, giving you two ships to play with at the same time!  Now, be careful.  Not only will both ships be firing at you after your ship gets captured, but if you accidently shoot your captured ship, you'll destroy it.  Also note, this will cost you one life, but will definately make the Challenging Stages, and perhaps the game itself, a little easier to play.Cheat: Note:  This works in all non-bootleg/hack versions of [I]Galaga[/I], as well as most of the sequels and Arranged Mode in [I]Namco Classic Collection Vol. 1[/I].</plot>
	<releasedate>27/8/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Hometek Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11189</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/927820-namco-museum-50th-anniversary</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/namco-museum-50th-anniversary_</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11189-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/9/6/67696_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188816-namco-museum-50th-anniversary-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188817-namco-museum-50th-anniversary-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188818-namco-museum-50th-anniversary-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188819-namco-museum-50th-anniversary-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188820-namco-museum-50th-anniversary-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/0/a/gfs_66779_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/d/a/gfs_66779_1_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/6/a/gfs_66779_1_3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/7/a/gfs_66779_1_4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/c/a/gfs_66779_1_5.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/11189.png</clearlogo1>
</game>