<Game>
	<Name>Namco Museum (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Ms. Pac-ManMs. Pac-man plays like it's predecessor Pac-man with a few changes such as the orange ghost being named "Sue" instead of "Clyde". The game offers four different mazes each represented by a different color. The goal of the game is to control Ms. Pac-man through each level collecting dots while trying to avoid ghosts. If you eat one of the levels Power-Pellets you become temporally invincible and able to eat one of the ghosts sending the enemy back to the starting area. Once all the dots are consumed you go on to the next level in which the game gets faster and harder to avoid the ghosts.Dig DugDig dug is an arcade style game where you play as the hero "Dig Dug" later named "Taizo Hori" where the goal is to dig your way through each level earning points while avoiding or fighting monsters by inflating them with your weapon.Pole PositionPole Position is a racing game that was released in 1982. The object of the game was to get a fast enough time in the time trial so that you could compete in F1 against other AI racers at the Fuji Racetrack.GalagaGalaga is a space shooter where you can control a ship fighting off hordes of alien ships. Your ship is at the bottom of the screen and can only move left and right, while the aliens are at the top who fly down towards you in formations firing projectiles. The object of the game is to kill each ship and progress to the next stage.Critical ReceptionGame Informer gave the review scores of 7 and 8 (out of ten). Andy McNamara, who gave the higher score did not give a reason for his score or much of a description of game other than, "...go buy your Game Boy Advance a copy so you can play Galaga and Ms. Pac-Man on the go like the rest of us...".Matt wrote, "...sounds great on paper, until you begin to realize that three of these five 'classics' haven't aged well at all. Dig-Dug is still good for a few laughs, but I got tired of burrowing around... Pole Position, ...just flat-out sucks... When you look at games like Castlevania, Tony Hawk 2, and Dodge Ball Advance, it's hard to want to go back to the 'good old days'."Cheat: Make the Galagas stop firing.Just like in the arcade version of Galaga, you can make the enemies stop firing missiles.  In round 1, kill everything but the two left flies on the bottom row.  Let them fly around for about 15-20 minutes, until they stop firing their missiles.  Kill them, and for the rest of the game, none of the enemies will shoot at you.Cheat: This glitch will make all enemies dissapear in the current level, but the level will not end. This let's you to get as many points as you want from eating all the dirt!1) Get the game down to two Pookas. If you only leave one, it will escape thus ending the round.2) This works best in horizontal tunnels under the rocks.3) Get a Pooka to follow you, inflate as necessary to delay him a little.4) Right when you are next to the rock, inflate the Pooka once to just delay him. When he moves at your character again, move under the rock.5) Quickly turn around and start pumping the Pooka up. Using the delay of the rock dropping, you should be able to cause the Pooka to burst at the same time the rock drops on him.6) If you are successful, then the other Pooka will disappear and you can amuse yourself digging out tunnels all day long in the dirt. NOTE: To return the game back to normal, drop another rock and you will go into the next round.Cheat: On most revisions of Galaga, there's a trick that stops enemies from firing at your ship.  In Stage 1, kill all aliens except the two bees in the bottom-left corner.  Allow the bees to dive down and shoot at you, while dodging their shots.  After around 15 minutes or so, the bees will continue to drop down, but they won't fire.  Let them drop down another 5 or 6 times, then kill them.  After all this, enemies will not shoot at you for the rest of the game.Cheat: Wait until one of the top ships(the green ones that take two shots to kill) comes down and fires off a tractor beam(the beam that can capture your ship).  Let it capture your ship.  Now, wait until it swoops down again with your ship behind it.  Simply kill the head ship(the green one), and it will lose your ship.  Your ship will then lock on to the side of your current ship, giving you two ships to play with at the same time!  Now, be careful.  Not only will both ships be firing at you after your ship gets captured, but if you accidently shoot your captured ship, you'll destroy it.  Also note, this will cost you one life, but will definately make the Challenging Stages, and perhaps the game itself, a little easier to play.Cheat: Note:  This works in all non-bootleg/hack versions of [I]Galaga[/I], as well as most of the sequels and Arranged Mode in [I]Namco Classic Collection Vol. 1[/I].</plot>
	<releasedate>11/6/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Hometek Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>LYZV_Q_q8IM</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>11186</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/516671-namco-museum</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/namco-museum_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/namco-museum/3030-32352/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2469700-box_nmgba.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/14258-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/213025-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/305723-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/305724-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose-one-of-the.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/305725-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-screenshot-ms-pac-man-gameplay.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/305726-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-screenshot-ms-pac-man-gameplay.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/305727-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pole-position-gameplay.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/305728-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-screenshot-change-some-of-the.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/305729-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-screenshot-dig-dug-title-screen.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/305730-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-screenshot-dig-dug-gameplay.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/305731-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-screenshot-galaga-gameplay.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/305732-namco-museum-game-boy-advance-screenshot-galaxian-title-screen.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/emSLNkh.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/11186.png</clearlogo1>
</game>