<Game>
	<Name>Naruto - Ninja Council (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Naruto: Ninja Council is another game that was taken from a famous Japanese anime series and is also the first installment of the Ninja Council series. It's a side scrolling, action oriented game with two modes to choose - Story mode and Free mode - and two playable characters. The story of Ninja Council starts from the survival exam and ends with Orochimarus attack at the Hidden Konoha Village. Apart from that there are no actual events between that - that take place on the anime although there are fights with certain characters that do like the fight with Haku and Orochimaru.The characters that are available are Naruto and Sasuke. When you start a new game at the beginning of each stage Kakashi sensei appears to give you hints about the controls and other useful staff like a boss weak point or attack patterns. There are also hidden characters you can find who can restore your health when you run out of life. Stages have a time limit of 5 minutes to complete. At the end of each stage there is a boss fight and the timer resets at 5 minutes in which you have to win the battle in order to advance the game and be able to save your progress.The two available characters - Naruto and Sasuke - can both use the same combo hits and weapons that can be picked up in each stage like shuriken and kunai. Every second stage the player will also find scrolls that contain elemental power ups like the Lightning Style Scroll that can be used either for attacking opponents or for progressing in the game. Apart from that each one has a set of three unique special attacks that can be used but only if you have sufficient amount of chakra.Cheat: Secret JutsusOn the Leaf Village Arena level, 1st Area (first level where you get the wind scroll) near the end of the level, you will fight a jounin-level enemy (big green ninja) and to the right of the platform he is standing on, there is a small crawl-way. Inside of the room, there is a large invisible scroll. When you acquire it, that character will permanatly learn level 4 Jutsus (if you save your game.) Naruto Red - Uses Kyuubi to heal himself. Yellow - Uses Kyuubi to heal himself, then deals damage to all enemies on screen. Sasuke Red - Preforms an upward kick-aerial combo. Yellow - More powerful version of the red combo. Kakashi Red - Preforms Chidori, hits all enemies on screen. Yellow - More powerful version of red jutsu.Cheat: Secret JutsusUse Naruto's Naruto Rendan (3rd special) in the red part (causing him to fail) against Kiba. Naruto will fart and cause Kiba to be paralyzed then Naruto will finish it up with Naruto Rendan.Cheat: Secret JutsusCertain bosses are dealt extra damage when certain Jutsus are used on them. Using Naruto's Harem no Jutsu on Ebisu will cause Ebisu to have a bloody nose and die instantly. Using Kakashi's Dog Summoning no Jutsu on Zabuza will make all the dogs latch on to Zabuza, and Kakashi will preform Chidori on him, just like in the anime and manga. Using Naruto's Harem no Jutsu on the 3th Hokage at the end of the final level will make give him a bloody nose also.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/3/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Tomy</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>6iwcpl2-faE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>29210</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/583525-naruto-ninja-council</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/naruto-ninja-council</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/naruto-ninja-council/3030-12313/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/29210-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/3/6/3/44363_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/29210-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/29210-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253452-naruto-ninja-council-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253428-naruto-ninja-council-game-boy-advance-screenshot-game-modes.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253455-naruto-ninja-council-game-boy-advance-screenshot-uzumaki-naruto.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253445-naruto-ninja-council-game-boy-advance-screenshot-sasuke-uchiha.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253433-naruto-ninja-council-game-boy-advance-screenshot-kakashi-sensei.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253460-naruto-ninja-council-game-boy-advance-screenshot-also-if-you.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253459-naruto-ninja-council-game-boy-advance-screenshot-naruto-fighting.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253435-naruto-ninja-council-game-boy-advance-screenshot-konohamaru.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/caYXR7p.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Action game, based on the Shonen Jump manga. Slip into the role of series hero Uzumaki Naruto and make your way through side-scrolling levels with the help of Sasuke and Kakashi.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>cN5yTLSEo-Y</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a754e9f4-46de-4434-9fac-621bf3402491.jpg</boxart3>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f939fa5c-9760-4948-b128-86ba6041d275.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/22069331-4d58-4585-a2e8-7040d8cf11f6.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>D3 Publisher</Publisher>
</game>