<Game>
	<Name>Naruto - Ninja Council 2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This is the second Naruto title for the Ninja Council series and follows the adventures of Naruto, Sasuke and Sakura as they try to pass the Chunin Exam in a total of seven stages.Unlike the first title you can now control three characters by changing them anytime you want inside the game. Each one has unique sequences of punches and kicks and can use 3 special techniques with varying results from one character to another. The shuriken, kunai and fuma from the first game are still here although this time one hit is enough to dispatch an enemy. Along the stages you can also find summoning scrolls and use them in fights to call Kakashi, Choji and others to attack the enemies. Another addition to the gameplay is the Teleport move which as the name implies allows you to teleport near or behind an enemy to attack him or simply dodge his attacks. At parts of each stage you may be given certain objectives such as to defeat all the enemies or finish the stage within a time limit and parameters like the use of only one character. At the end of each stage you get a grade depending on how many enemies you killed, how fast you finished the stage, how many characters you are left and how many leaves you have collected. At the end of the game these grades will be accumulated to decide your final rank.The game also features two additional modes  the Co-op Mode and the Vs. Mode but you need the link cable for that.Cheat: Play Gambunta vs Shukaku mini gameWhen you are in the level where you are looking for  Gaara, get Sakura and Sasuke killed. Then contiue as normal with Naruto. When you beat Gaara in his sand shell you will play the mini game.</plot>
	<releasedate>10/10/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>D3Publisher of America, Inc., Tomy</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>_gmmR_rd9N0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>14937</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920937-naruto-ninja-council-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/naruto-ninja-council-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/naruto-ninja-council-2/3030-6939/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/14937-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/1/7/60917_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/14937-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/14937-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/261713-naruto-ninja-council-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro-gaara.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/261714-naruto-ninja-council-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro-naruto.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/261715-naruto-ninja-council-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/261716-naruto-ninja-council-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-dialogue.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/261717-naruto-ninja-council-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-controls.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/261718-naruto-ninja-council-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-sasuke.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/261719-naruto-ninja-council-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-sasuke.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/261720-naruto-ninja-council-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-your-stats.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/HRkuILz.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/14937.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Action game, based on the Shonen Jump manga. This sequel to the very first Naruto game on the GBA (the second game was a much different simulation/adventure) has three-times the amount of stages and characters twice the size. The action is streamlined and more dynamic. Players can transform into Naruto, Sasuke and Sakura and use their abilities to defeat the scrolling stages. The game also utilizes the link cable for a two-player co-op mode and for a four-player battle mode.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c19ff37d-3a82-4897-839b-a13d308d091d.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cdc4b43a-83b5-4564-9dbe-868e11888bf0.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/578506f8-0e00-4aa7-8dc7-a6c9208a8ca9.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a7a90ec3-7e84-4d84-9b95-2ec60d965d4d.jpg</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>D3 Publisher</Publisher>
</game>