<Game>
	<Name>Need for Speed - Porsche Unleashed (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Need for Speed is back with more! Drive over 80 different Porsches, from the first 356 Ferdinand to the 2000 911 Turbo over multiple tracks. Some tracks have alternate paths. Others are rally tracks where you go from one end of the track to the other instead of doing circuit racing. Two completely different single-player modes available. First, there's factory driver, which have you join Porsche as a test driver. As you complete different challenges, which can vary from doing specific manoeuvres in pre-alloted time to racing fellow drivers, you will make your way up to Ace Test Driver. Second, there's Evolution, which is the "career mode", you start with enough money to buy one 356, and start racing. As you win races, time will pass, new cars will become available, or you can peruse the used car market. Buy/repair/sell cars, win races, buy enhancement parts for your car, and make your way to the end of the modern era...You can also play online via EARacing.com, where you can pick customized cars in your Evolution stable or choose stock cars and race up to 7 other cars simultaneously. The graphics have been enhanced and the physics model changed to reflect a true 4-point system, and you can feel the difference between the different vehicles.Cheat: Infinite Speed/AccelerationI have tested this glitch with all cars, and it only works with the Moby Dick car. Select manual transmission. Once in a race, simply leave it in first gear and hold the A button, you will continue accelerating at a constant rate. The fastest I've gotten the car up to with this glitch is 618 km/h. It also works in reverse.</plot>
	<releasedate>15/3/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Simulation</genre>
	<Developer>Destination Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22346</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/577495-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed/3030-8831/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1793305-box_nfspu.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/257479-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-playstation-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/257480-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-playstation-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/194577-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-playstation-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/194578-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-playstation-screenshot-main.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/194579-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-playstation-screenshot-car.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/278225-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-playstation-screenshot-view.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/278223-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-playstation-screenshot-two.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/278222-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-playstation-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/278224-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-playstation-screenshot-racing.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12976-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-windows-screenshot-intro-screen.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12977-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-windows-screenshot-tinker.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12978-need-for-speed-porsche-unleashed-windows-screenshot-your-mission.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Unleash the power of Porsche! Push yourself to the limit and break the will of your opponents, as you climb into the driver's seat of Destination Software's Need For Speed Porsche Unleashed racing game for your Nintendo Game Boy Advance system, sub-licensed from series originator Electronic Arts. Need for Speed Porsche Unleashed features circuit track racing, streetcar excitement, open road thrills, crashes, traffic, and more. Feel the surge of adrenaline as your own driving savvy and years of Porsche excellence come together at your fingertips for a thrilling ride at breakneck speed. Features 25 different models of Porsche cars, link cable support for four players (multiple cartridge), and cartridge save ability with four slots.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/194b8420-c590-4316-be85-a7241b66f7b5.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3dd3e1bc-eaab-4b5d-bf70-bf83253cb905.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Destination Software</Publisher>
</game>