<Game>
	<Name>Need for Speed - Underground 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,It)</Name>
	<plot>Electronic Arts brings back the import-tuning illegal street racing culture back into it's Need For Speed series with Underground 2. Like the original Underground, the sequel focuses more on the underground street racing rather than the series' traditional circuit racing. The biggest addition to Underground 2 is the ability to freely roam around in the game's open-world city. Also, there are newer racing modes like Street X and URL and a much deeper and greater customization option than the original. Underground 2 includes the voice acting talent of various celebrity models like Brooke Burke and Kelly Brook. Official SoundtrackArtists A-Z Capone- I Need Speed Chingy- I Do Christopher Lawrence- Rush Hour Cirrus- Back On a Mission Felix Da Housecat- Rocket Ride Fluke- Switch/Twitch Helmet- Crashing Foreign Cars Killradio - Scavenger   Killing Joke - The Death &amp; Resurrection Show  Ministry  - No W  Mudvayne  - Determined   Paul Van Dyk - Nothing But You (Cirrus Remix)  Queens of the Stone Age- In My Head   Rise Against - Give it All   Septembre  - I am Weightless  Skindred  - Nobody  Sly Boogy  - That&#8217;z My Name  Sin - Hard EBM   Snapcase  - Skeptic  Snoop Dogg feat. the Doors - Riders On The Storm (Fredwreck Remix)  Sonic Animation- E-Ville  Spiderbait - Black Betty   Terror Squad - Lean Back   The Bronx - Notice of Eviction   Unwritten Law - The Celebration Song  Xzibit -LAX CarsAcura RSXAudi A3Audi TTCadillac EscaladeFord FocusFord MustangHummer H2Hyundai TiburonMazda RX7Lexus IS300Lincoln NavigatorMazda RX8Mazda MX5 / MiataMitsubishi EclipseNissan 240SXNIssan SentraNissan Skyline GTR Pontiac GTOToyota CelicaToyota CorollaToyota SupraVauxhall CorsaVolksagen GolfMistubishi Lancer Evo VIIIMitsubishi 3000GTNissan 350ZPeugeot 206Subaru Impreza WRX STiAmerican and Canadian versions of the game do not have the Vauxhall Corsa. They have a different car, which is the Honda Civic.Reception:The game sold 9 million copies and was a best-seller on each of the consoles. Reviews for the game were positive but there was several things that were criticized. Among those were having to drive for to long to get to races, bad voiceacting and strong product placement for companies with no connection to auto racing for example Cingular, which was integrated into the game's messaging system. Another thing that was criticized was the GameCube versions framerate issues and inferior graphics.Cheat: Custom Nissan 350ZComplete the game and you will unlock a Nissan 350Z with a Carbon Fiber Hood and a NFSU2 Vinyl. NOTE: You cannot change the visual appearance of the car.Cheat: Custom Nissan 350ZComplete 'Go Underground' mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>15/11/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>b9imG8XeE_0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22328</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920468-need-for-speed-underground-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/need-for-speed-underground-2_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/need-for-speed-underground-2/3030-9651/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22328-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/263609-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/296446-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/170772-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/170773-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/170774-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-earn.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740870-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-underground.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740871-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740872-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-event.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740873-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-on.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740874-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-driving.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740875-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-taking.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740876-need-for-speed-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-crossing.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Vq4QNkG.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/22328.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Need for Speed Underground 2 will challenge gamers to immerse themselves in the tuner culture, exploring an expansive, free-roaming city divided into five distinct neighborhoods. Gamers will encounter rival racers who will initiate events, tip players off to the hottest racing spots, and show them where to buy the most sought-after licensed aftermarket upgrades. The game will feature new game modes, deep new performance customization and tuning, and more than 30 licensed cars. The game also delivers twice the visual customization upgrades as the original game, providing a staggering 70 billion possible car combinations for total automotive self-expression.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ddfb6169-dbe9-48f5-a2d8-ca5b602d2192.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0d5b9eab-3e75-492f-b9bc-1fdf91d667df.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>