<Game>
	<Name>Need for Speed - Underground (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,It)</Name>
	<plot>PremiseThe developers changed from giving players exotic cars like in previous NFS games to more mod-firendly cars perhaps trying to capitalize on the phenomenon of illegal street racing arguably brought to mainstream view by the movie "The Fast and The Furious." It has robust car customizing tools which let the player edit the look and performance of the car to their liking. To keep with the theme, all the racing in the game takes place at night time.Plot:Starting off as a rookie, the player is thrust into the illegal street racing scene. The player must win an Abilitease race, before being promptly woken up by Samantha--the player's lady friend--for daydreaming. Now the player is given the chance to buy their vehicle from an extremely limited selection of cars, including Hondas, Nissans and Fords. As days--and races--pass, the player becomes acquainted with fellow racers who soon become enemies. Over time races become longer, more complex, and, ultimately, far more difficult. The player, wanting to have a shot at the top dog, agrees to race Samantha. This is without her consent, however, leaving her angry and distressed; they race, resulting in a defeated Samantha seeing her car towed away while the Player celebrates. After all 120 races are complete the player must win one more race, head to head against the ultimate street racer. While there is no real ending per se, the player is greeted with his name at the top of all the racing rankings.Gameplay:Need for Speed: Underground does away with the previous realistic track driving model in favor of a more arcade style racing model. While drifting is not a main gameplay mechanic, it is certainly encouraged. The exception being the Drift Events (See Below). There are a number of different races the player may participate in: Drag Races, Knockout Races, Drift Events, Sprint Races, Time Challenges &amp; Circuit Races.Drag RacesThese are purely straight line races, normally over about a mile and a half. The focus is purely on timing your shifts perfectly. Instead of controlling the car directly, the car moves left to right in a slot car like fashion.Knockout RacesThis type of race usually involves four competitors going around a regular circuit. The person in last place when crossing the start/finish line is eliminated from the race. This process is repeated until there is only one competitor remaining. One criticism against this mode is that it does not give any of the competitor's times; it only says "Eliminated."Drift EventsWhile not a race, it involves you drifting around corners, stacking up a multiplier while aiming not to hit any barrier surrounding the track. While the player is against AI, there is no one else on the track, you only see your opponents score on the HUD during the race.Sprint RacesVery similiar to a Circuit Race [See Below] the player will race against anything from 2 - 4 opponents. The catch is that the start point is completely seperate from the finish line, resulting in no laps being performed and at no point does the player see the same scenery twice.Time ChallengesOnly in Underground Mode, the player races against the clock in order to get Custom Parts from PJ; an illustious engineer who is a friend of Samantha's.Circuit RacesThe main race in the game, racing anything from 2 - 5 opponents, and anywhere from 2 - 7 laps. This classic game mode is in no way altered to create a uniqe spin on the genre, it takes it straight from the book. This means that there are split roads, there are numerous shortcuts to perform on any given circuit, aswell as numerous hazards.Featured CarsThe following is a list of cars featured in the game:2003 Volkswagen Golf GTI 2.02000 Honda Civic Si Coupe2003 Peugeot 206 GTi/S161999 Mazda Miata MX51999 Dodge Neon 2-Door1999 Mitsubishi Eclipse GSX2002 Toyota Celica GT-S2003 Mitsubishi Lancer ES2003 Ford Focus ZX32003 Subaru Impreza 2.5 RS2003 Hyundai Tiburon GT V62004 Nissan Sentra SE-R Spec V1992 Nissan 240SX SE1998 Toyota Supra2003 Acura RSX Type-S2000 Acura Integra Type-R2003 Honda S20002003 Nissan 350Z1999 Nissan Skyline R34 GTR1995 Mazda RX-7Soundtrack:Overseer - DoomsdayThe Crystal Method - Born Too SlowRancid - Out of ControlRob Zombie - Two-Lane BlacktopBT - KimosabeStatic-X - The OnlyElement Eighty - Broken PromisesAsian Dub Foundation - Fortress EuropeHotwire - InvisibleStory of the Year - And the Hero Will DrownAndy Hunter - The Wonders of YouJunkie XL - Action RadiusFuel - QuarterJerk - Sucked InFluke - SnapshotLostprophets - To Hell We RideOverseer - SupermovesFC Kahuna - GlitterballBlindside - SwallowLil Jon &amp; the Eastside Boyz - Get LowMystikal - Smashing the Gas (Get Faster)Dilated Peoples - Who's WhoNate Dogg - Keep It ComingX-ecutioners - Body RockPetey Pablo - Need For SpeedT.I. - 24's</plot>
	<releasedate>22/12/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>2.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>wsYuHpuC-bA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22329</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/914764-need-for-speed-underground</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/need-for-speed-underground</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/need-for-speed-underground/3030-12254/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22329-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/28862-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/28863-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67546-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67547-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67548-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-screenshot-this-is-my-ride.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67549-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-screenshot-select-a-race.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67550-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-screenshot-line-up.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67551-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-screenshot-the-abandoned.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67552-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-screenshot-check-out-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67553-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-screenshot-off-roadin.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67554-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-screenshot-race-results.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/67555-need-for-speed-underground-gamecube-screenshot-racing-through.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ocpQiwE.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/22329.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Electronic Arts' Need For Speed series takes a note from the Fast and Furious handbook with its latest release entitled Need For Speed: Underground. Purchase, race, and customize 20 different licensed cars from major manufacturers such as Honda, Mitsubishi, Toyota, Volkswagen, Nissan, and more. Race other customized cars through a detailed nighttime cityscape, dodging city traffic and navigating shortcuts all the while. Customize vehicle performance as well as your car's physical appearance, changing rims, stickers, paintjob, spoilers and more. Multiple racing modes range from drift competitions, street racing, and drag racing. Experience high-speed racing and vehicle customization with Need For Speed: Underground for the Game Boy Advance.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e71506ff-a29f-435e-9add-e7d1dbc2cc0c.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5cd5a232-4310-4af5-b045-d3590fc4a831.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Electronic Arts</Publisher>
</game>