<Game>
	<Name>NFL Blitz 20-02 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>NFL Blitz 2002 is extreme-style football the way it was meant to be played. Lightning fast gameplay and action play selection screens make for non-stop action. Over-the-top animations mean you'll see bigger hits and wilder plays then you have ever dreamed of. Real teams, real players, real attitude!Cheat: CodesEnter the following codes at the Vs. screen (first number changed with L, second with B, third with A):</plot>
	<releasedate>7/2/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Midway Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22336</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/536920-nfl-blitz-20-02</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/nfl-blitz-20-02</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nfl-blitz-20-02/3030-9044/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22336-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/241101-nfl-blitz-20-02-gamecube-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/16176-nfl-blitz-20-02-playstation-2-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/8/7/gfs_44622_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/5/7/gfs_44622_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/e/7/gfs_44622_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/f/7/gfs_44622_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<Notes>NFL Blitz 20-02 is a game based on the American Football sport. As the whole series, it takes away most rules and tactics (leaving 36 offensive and 18 defensive plays) while focusing on an action oriented approach. Because of the limited control scheme of the system, the options on the field are less in comparison to the main console version: besides the usual movement, passing and player moving commands, the player also may tackle, leap or activate a turbo boost. The playing perspective is an angled pseudo-3D view with the goals at the top/low side of the screen. Both in the exhibition and season mode (17 weeks), the game offers the choice between 32 teams with different statistics regarding passing, defensive and line. The mini games, which can be also selected from the main menu, are basically practice modes for field goal and goal-line situations as well as a NFL trivia quiz.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7caa647-5ae2-4dd0-924e-c152cefdd406.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/75ad7afe-7a82-4dc9-9cd1-dcd93c30969d.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Midway</Publisher>
</game>