<Game>
	<Name>NHL 2002 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>NHL 2002 is the only entry in Electronic Arts' hockey series to be released on the Game Boy Advance. With the console versions having migrated to 3D graphics years earlier, the handheld game retains a 2D top-down view very similar to the earliest titles in the series on the Genesis and SNES.Besides a standard mode for exhibition games, the game has a practice mode where the number of players on the field can be freely chosen. Season mode is unusual in that, unlike in other games, the player doesn't select a team to lead through a season. Instead, the game includes the full game schedule of the 2001-2002 NHL season, and any team in any scheduled game can be played. If no games of interest are scheduled on a given day, it can be skipped and the results simulated. The season mode also includes the ability to trade players, sign free agents and even to create players.The game also includes a multi player mode over the link cable, with up to four players able to join for cooperative or competitive play.Cheat: Zamboni on start-upHold L+R while turning on the game. Instead of a puck a zamboni will drive by.Cheat: Extra teams and Create-a-player pointsWhen you turn on the game, wait for the press start screen to fully load. Then, hold select, alternate pressing L and R while the Select button is still being held. When the main menu eventually appears, you should hear "It's in the game." This gives you two extra teams in the play now mode, and 1000 points to use in the create a player mode! </plot>
	<releasedate>6/3/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Electronic Arts, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>2.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22334</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/557703-nhl-2002</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/nhl-2002_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/nhl-2002/3030-18520/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22334-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/19620-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/376475-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot-game-intro-featuring.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/376476-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/376477-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-main-menu-where-you.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/376478-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose-your-teams-and.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/376479-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot-time-to-drop-the-puck.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/376480-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-boston-forward-gets.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/376481-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot-great-scoring-chance.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/376482-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot-get-to-rough-and-the.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/376483-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot-two-minutes-in-the-sin.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/376484-nhl-2002-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-hawks-and-bruins.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>In NHL 2002, Electronic Arts has included several game modes including Practice, Exhibition and a Full Season. You can even pull off one-timers and blocked shots in a head to head match, with up to four players. Multiplayer action requires GBAs and Game Paks for every player and enough GBA Game Link cables to connect all systems. NHL 2002 allows anyone to play like a pro make the first hockey game on the Game Boy Advance enjoyable.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eda39376-1e79-4600-a923-b63b3d9e37e0.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5fe561ae-5a21-44cb-994c-cf260cd250c3.png</clearlogo1>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ceb7668b-cddd-46cf-a349-046d974915ae.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>EA Sports</Publisher>
</game>