<Game>
	<Name>Open Season (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Sv,No,Da,Fi)</Name>
	<plot>Open Season for GBA is based on the movie and it is a completely different game experience than the console version. The story in the game follows the movie pretty well and it is well presented through in-game and comic dialog style cinematics. It's about a Grizzly bear named Boog who is very happy with his domesticated home. But one day he gets in trouble with his new friend Elliot and the town's authority decides to put them back in the woods where they belong. Unfortunately, for them, the hunting season has just begun and Boog has no idea how to survive outside of his garage home with his beloved caretaker, Beth. The game begins just before Boog and Elliot are dropped in the woods. You control Boog and he has many cool moves. He can jump, roll, grab and throw forest animals as well as roar. The goal of the game is to protect the forest animals from the hunters. The forest is full of hunters and boss hunters in each animal territory. It is your job to clean up the forest so play it wild and rally an army of forest critters in a hilarious quest to scare off the hunters!Cheat: Extra lives and skip levelsAt any time during the game, press start to pause and then hold down the L button.  The words "Cheat Mode" will appear on the screen.  Continue to hold L down and enter any of these passwords for the desired affect.  Note that you can only use three cheat codes per save file and that you must be on a level in order to skip it.  The words "Cheat Mode" flash green if entered correctly.Cheat: Change Boog into a Polar BearAt any time in a level, bring up the pause screen and hold down L. While holding L press Down, Up, Down, B, A. When you resume the game, Boog will now be snow-white giving the appearence of a Polar Bear.</plot>
	<releasedate>19/9/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ubisoft, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<VideoURL>QUxx9w3Mp7o</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>28186</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/932556-open-season</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/open-season_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/open-season/3030-14642/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/28186-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/87985-open-season-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/228304-open-season-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/228309-open-season-game-boy-advance-screenshot-to-go-ahead-boog-must.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/228308-open-season-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intermission-shaw.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740880-open-season-game-boy-advance-screenshot-avoid-the-blue-creature.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740884-open-season-game-boy-advance-screenshot-rolling-along.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740885-open-season-game-boy-advance-screenshot-help-the-deer.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740886-open-season-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-a-supermarket.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740887-open-season-game-boy-advance-screenshot-get-some-bubble-gum.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740888-open-season-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-ve-been-hit.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740889-open-season-game-boy-advance-screenshot-it-s-hunting-season.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Open Season is a riotous romp in the great outdoors, where the rowdy brood of forest animals turns the tables on a bunch of unsuspecting hunters. When a domesticated grizzly named Boog gets lured into leaving the creature comforts of home by a fast-talking mule deer named Elliot, he finds himself lost in the woods just three days before hunting season. Forced to "rough it" in the great outdoors, Boog goes native, rallying all the forest animals to take back their home and send the hunters packing. The Open Season video game allows players to relive the movie experience by playing as Boog and Elliot. Throw skunk bombs, hurl rabbits, use acorn-firing squirrels and pull outrageous woodland pranks to scare the pants off the hunters in this action-adventure romp through the forest.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67d725d8-8800-4a85-a2d4-6ef22848a9a0.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c642057c-3013-4e07-91c6-fa35958856f9.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>