<Game>
	<Name>Pac-Man World (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Pac-Man World is a 3D platform game for the PlayStation and Game Boy Advance. This game celebrates the 20th anniversary of Pac-Man. The game was also planned for PC, Nintendo 64, and Sega Dreamcast, but was canceled.Story:All of the Pac people going over to celebrate Pac-Man's 20th birthday. As they were going to the party, all of them were kidnapped by ghosts. When Pac-Man comes home, he finds his house completely ruined, with all the party decorations and cake destroyed. Pac-Man discovered that Toc-Man was behind the attack and now Pac-Man must attempt to rescue all his friends.Gameplay:As with other games in the franchise, Pac-Man eats pallets - including power pellets, which allow him to consume ghosts. There are also numerous other enemies besides ghosts. Besides being able to eat ghosts, he can also use a ground pound attack, a spin dash to get through areas quickly, as well as being able to throw his pellets at non-ghost enemies. Players also have a life bar which them to take four hits before dying. There are 6 worlds to explore with 23 levels to beat in order to help Pac-Man save his friends.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco</Developer>
	<rating>10.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>AU1ZL2fkgD4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5488</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/922251-pac-man-world</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pac-man-world/3030-64/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/5488-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/5488-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/16/160705/2265913-pmwscreen3.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/16/160705/2265912-pmwscreen2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/16/160705/2265911-pmwscreen1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/9/0/gfs_60739_1_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/4/0/gfs_60739_1_2.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/f/0/gfs_60739_1_3.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/e/0/gfs_60739_1_4.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/5/0/gfs_60739_1_5.jpg</snapshot8>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/5488.png</clearlogo1>
</game>