<Game>
	<Name>Pac-Man Collection (Japan) (En)</Name>
	<plot>Four classic Pac-Man games are included in this collection from Namco:1. Pac-Man: The original arcade classic, complete and un-cut. 2. Pac-Mania: A conversion of the 1987 update to Pac-Man, which takes the elements of the original arcade game and puts it into an isometric view, as well as adding the ability to jump.3. Pac-Man Arrangement: Never re-produced outside of the arcade, Arrangement again uses the elements of the original Pac-Man and adds a fifth ghost, who can change shape and size when combined with the other 4 ghosts, and make life harder for Pac-Man. New power-ups are also included, like the ability to dash quickly around the screen, warp points to get from one place to the other and new ways of catching ghosts.Pac-Attack: Like Tetris before it, you must fit falling blocks together to complete a line to clear the screen. In this case, the falling tiles also have ghosts in them, and once the Pac-Man tile appears (a tile with the Pac-Man symbol), Pac-Man will eat all of the ghosts that are in his path until he gets to a dead end.Cheat:  Pac-Attack AppendixFirst enter the Pac-Attack game. Then highlight the Puzzle mode option and immediately press Right and A. In this slightly changed version, Pac-Man appears less times and none of the clusters will be random.Cheat: Level PasswordsPlease enter the following at the password screen:Cheat: Level PasswordsIn Pac-Attack, type in the password ''FFF'' and you will be treated to the screen which you normally have to beat all 100 levels to see.Cheat: This password will allow you to use a music test and some other options in the game.</plot>
	<releasedate>11/7/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Limited</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22268</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/516683-pac-man-collection</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/pac-man-collection</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pac-man-collection/3030-38989/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2421681-box_pmc.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/14087-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/213021-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84447-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84448-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84449-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-screenshot-original-pac.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84450-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-pause-menu.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84451-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu-for.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84452-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pac-tris.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84454-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pac-mania-title.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84456-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-screenshot-3d-pac-man.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84457-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pac-man-arrangement.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/84458-pac-man-collection-game-boy-advance-screenshot-one-dot-to-go.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ayc8JTd.jpg</banner1>
</game>