<Game>
	<Name>Pinobee - Wings of Adventure (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Grandpa Bee has kidnapped before finishing you, Pinobee - a robotic bee made to defend the world. The player must go through 9 worlds in order to find and rescue your creator. There are multiple storylines with multiple endings. Pinobee can take out most enemies by jumping on top of then, but the most important means of attack is a dash, which can be executed in any direction (also diagonal). The amount of consecutive dashes can be upgraded when meeting a certain character. Pinobee collects flower and question mark bubbles provide power-ups, enhancing the dashes, providing temporary shields or other bonuses. Players can use the Game Link to collect and trade items with friends for power-ups.Cheat: Secret Transformation When you get all 16 regular items from one category, the King and Queen items will be avaliable. Normal items will be in the time capsules on the map. After you collect these two items and you will be transformed into Super Pinobee.</plot>
	<releasedate>31/5/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Activision Publishing, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>2.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3530</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/445178-pinobee-wings-of-adventure</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/pinobee-wings-of-adventure</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pinobee-wings-of-adventure/3030-6584/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3530-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3530-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/303279-pinobee-wings-of-adventure-game-boy-advance-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/303280-pinobee-wings-of-adventure-game-boy-advance-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/303281-pinobee-wings-of-adventure-game-boy-advance-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/303282-pinobee-wings-of-adventure-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/303283-pinobee-wings-of-adventure-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/303284-pinobee-wings-of-adventure-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pinobee.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/303285-pinobee-wings-of-adventure-game-boy-advance-screenshot-his.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/303286-pinobee-wings-of-adventure-game-boy-advance-screenshot-power.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/303287-pinobee-wings-of-adventure-game-boy-advance-screenshot-moving.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/303288-pinobee-wings-of-adventure-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-secret.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/6e4XQw1.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Pinobee: Wings of Adventure takes full advantage of Game Boy Advance's 32-bit color graphics. From Pinobee's fluid animation to the detailed environments he explores, it's obvious that a lot of spit and polish has been applied to this Pak. Pinobee screenshots may lead you to believe that this is a standard action platform game, but that is far from an accurate description. Pinobee can walk along the ground or shimmy up walls, but his main means of locomotion is dashing through the air. As he makes it deeper in his quest, Pinobee gains the ability to dash farther and farther through the air. Soon enough, he's spending more time hovering and dashing through the sky than on the ground. This unique play control system gives Pinobee a fresh feel.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/376c837c-b5d5-4ac4-8682-8930df730d91.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9678b144-4a8f-4128-98a9-65b86ecc6a8c.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6c997a76-f89f-4d37-b47f-5e3911e49a49.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Hudson Soft</Publisher>
</game>