<Game>
	<Name>Pirates of the Caribbean - Dead Man's Chest (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Three VersionsThere are technically three types of the game Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest. Each one is different is the way they are played and the presentation.PSP The psp version of Pirates is a 3D hack'n'slash game. You run around and defeat the enemies before they defeat you. You have essentially two different attacks, which, when used in a specific order, will defeat different enemies. You can also use alternative weapons, which include bottles and throwing knives, which immediately One-Hit-KO's the enemy.GBAThe GBA version of Pirates is an open-ended 2D platformer ARPG. While following the events of the movie Jack will sail around the islands of the Caribbean. Each island has a store and several 2D levels filled with enemies to pass through. By learning rumors Jack can find treasures in these levels. Some treasures level up Jack or the Black Pearl's stats, while others are needed to convince new shipmates to join Jack's crew.Jack always has his cutlass with him in fights, and he can learn a small number of combos over the course of the game. On the open sea the Black Pearl can get into ship-to-ship fights with other pirates or the royal navy. In ship fights both ships try to maneuver into position to fire their cannons, but the crew will need time to reload after each salvo. Both Jack and the Black Pearl can use limited ammunition weapons, like throwing knives and burning oil for Jack, or ballast and chained shots for the Pearl.After a sea battle opponent is sufficiently weakened it can either be boarded, switching to a side scrolling level where Jack loots its holds while fighting the crew, or just destroyed outright. The Pearl can be upgraded with new guns, masts, and hulls found on boats, or purchased in stores.Cheat: Cheat ModePause game play, then press Select to display the "Enter Cheat Code" prompt. Then enter one of the following codes to activate the corrosponding function.</plot>
	<releasedate>27/6/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Buena Vista Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>qoXfxm1W4LU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22269</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/932136-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-mans-chest</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-mans-chest</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-mans-chest/3030-4400/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22269-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/106894-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/144654-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172203-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172204-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172205-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172206-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172207-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172208-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172209-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172210-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172211-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/172212-pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Based on the follow-up to the blockbuster original movie, Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest follows the movie's unlikely heroes as they explore and brawl across land and sea on a memorable quest in search of the legendary Dead Man's Chest. The games not only features thrilling moments from the movie, but also expands the fantasy of the franchise by offering exciting new adventures and locations inspired by the rich "Pirates of the Caribbean" universe. The Game Boy Advance version of Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest lets players take the helm of the Black Pearl as Captain Jack Sparrow in three-dimensional seafaring action to battle other ships or sail to 15 islands. The game includes 50 side-scrolling adventure maps.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a9e5304a-a90a-435c-8ac7-cbdd9eb10954.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b846527b-98d3-4ee8-af61-f0b75324ed04.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Buena Vista Games</Publisher>
</game>