<Game>
	<Name>Planet of the Apes (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>Based on the series of 1960's movies that starred legendary actors such as Charlton Heston and Roddy McDowell, the player takes control of a deep space astronaut by the name of Ulysses who crash lands on Earth after 200 years in space and awakens to discover that apes have become the dominant species and has nearly wiped out the human race.  Joining with a group of survivors, the player must make their way to the heart of the Ape Empire and stop General Ursus, who is planning a final attack on mankind.The gameplay is a side-scrolling action game, similar to Prince of Persia, having the player avoid various traps and pitfalls by jumping and climbing.  They must also avoid various enemies including armed apes that will try to stop the player at all costs, but the player has weapons of there own.  The player will start out with a knife and eventually will upgrade to a pistol and a shotgun.There are 13 levels in all, with the story being told through still picture cut scenes that are modeled after the films.  There is also a password feature for players to pick up and play at their leisure.Cheat: Cheat MenuAt the title screen, press B, A, Left, Down, Up, Right. Start the game to access a cheat menu containing a level select and toggles for infinite health and all weapons.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ubi Soft Entertainment Ltd.</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>26114</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/565782-planet-of-the-apes</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/planet-of-the-apes_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/planet-of-the-apes/3030-29549/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/26114-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463742-planet-of-the-apes-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463743-planet-of-the-apes-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463744-planet-of-the-apes-game-boy-advance-screenshot-start-of-a.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463745-planet-of-the-apes-game-boy-advance-screenshot-taking-on-a.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/0/a/gfs_5889_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/d/a/gfs_5889_1_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/6/a/gfs_5889_1_3.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/7/a/gfs_5889_1_4.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/c/a/gfs_5889_1_5.jpg</snapshot9>
	<Notes>Fight for humanity as Ulysses, a deep-space astronaut shipwrecked on Earth nearly 2000 years into the future. To his horror, a deadly breed of intelligent apes has evolved from mankind and now dominate the Earth. Hunted to near-extinction, the rag-tag human survivors huddle in fear of the Ape Empire. Against impossible odds, Ulysses must infiltrate the simian society and halt the genocidal plan of Ape General Ursus.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eb4da8dd-4617-4b01-9a32-a6833b1fd3f0.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d5f8c07d-4a57-4fcd-b436-70b823ae87e2.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>