<Game>
	<Name>Pocket Monsters - Ruby (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pok&amp;eacute;mon Ruby.This entry in the Pok&amp;eacute;mon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pok&amp;eacute;mon, and addictive RPG gameplay.One of the biggest additions to Pok&amp;eacute;mon Ruby is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively.You can also showcase your Pok&amp;eacute;mon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pok&amp;eacute;mon contests.With new Pok&amp;eacute;mon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pok&amp;eacute;mon Sapphire takes the Pok&amp;eacute;mon experience to the next level.Cheat: Berry Masters Wife PasswordsTell the Berry Master's Wife certain phrases to receive the following berries. You can only tell her one of these each day.Cheat: Berry Masters Wife PasswordsGet at least 5 badges. Go to the Petalburg Pokemon Center. Talk to the guy at the PC. When he asks you your profile, tell him MYSTERY EVENT IS EXCITING. You will be able to scan E-Reader cards with this.Cheat: Capture Trainer PokemonFor this glitch to work, you need to have not caught the Latios (Sapphire) or Latias (Ruby) roaming in Hoenn. (Note that this glitch means that, on this file, you cannot capture that Pokemon without trading.) Enter a trainer battle of some sort; this Trainer must have the Pokemon you wish to catch, exactly as that Pokemon is. You can, for example, enter Battle Tower battles to obtain a quick Level 100 Pokemon. (Note that non-Battle Tower Pokemon may turn into Bad Eggs!) Lose to the trainer and then proceed to beat Latios or Latias without having any battles - wild or Trainer - in-between. You MUST make the Latios or Latias faint in that one encounter, without catching them or them escaping. Repels are useful to circumvent wild battles, and Mean Look and Shadow Tag to prevent Latios/Latias from leaving.Cheat: Capture Trainer PokemonAfter beating Latios/Latias, Pokemon #2-#6 of the previous Trainer's party will be used right after that, as if the Latios/Latias were their first Pokemon. These Pokemon will fight, however, as wild, roaming Pokemon do and thus are capable of escaping like Latios/Latias are. Still, you are nonetheless able to capture them as your own. The battle ends with the first Pokemon you catch, so if you want to catch a different Pokemon in the opponent's party, you'll have to defeat the others until you reach it; this can make for some easy EXP. as well.Cheat: DiplomasYou can get five different kinds of Trainer Cards; Green, Copper, Silver, Bronze and Gold. You start off with the green card. And when you beat the Elite Four you get the Bronze card. beating 50 trainers in a row in battle tower will get you another upgrade. When you beat all of the contests you will receive another upgrade. And then catching all 200 Pokemon will give you another one. It doesn't matter what order you do those tasks in, but you can't complete the dex untill you have beaten the E4. It goes Green to bronze to copper to Sliver to gold.Cheat: DiplomasFind Blue, Green, Red, and Yellow Shards. These may be found near Mossdeep, under the water. Go to the Hunter's House. Trade him Blue Shards for Water Stones, Green Shards for Leaf Stones, Red Shards for Fire Stones, and Yellow Shards for Thunder Stones.Cheat: DiplomasGo to Slateport City. Talk to the Chairman in the Pok&amp;#233;mon Fan Club. If your lead Pok&amp;#233;mon has maximum coolness, he will give you a Red Scarf. If your lead Pok&amp;#233;mon has maximum beauty, he will give you a Blue Scarf. If your lead Pok&amp;#233;mon has maximum cuteness, he will give you a Pink Scarf. If your lead Pok&amp;#233;mon has maximum smartness, he will give you a Green Scarf. If your lead Pok&amp;#233;mon has maximum toughness, he will give you a Yellow Scarf.Cheat: DiplomasWin at least 50 battles in a row in the Battle Tower. You will receive the Silver Trophy. Win at least 100 battles in a row in the Battle Tower. You will receive the Gold Trophy. Get 5 pictures painted in the Lilycove Art Museum. You will receive the Glass Sculpture.Cheat: Shiny PokemonEvery time you encounter a pokemon you have a 1/8192 chance of the pokemon being a different color, this is called a shiny pokemonCheat: Avoid wild Pokemon!Now, you can use CUT to hack away grass that wild Pokemon live in. You can save money not buying repels and can travel without being interrupted by wild PokemonCheat: Avoid wild Pokemon!If you go to the department store in Lilycove City, and go to the counter where you can buy poke balls, you can get 1 free premier ball for every 10 poke balls you buy (they have to be poke balls, not great balls or ultra balls). Premier Balls are just like poke balls but are all white with red rims.Cheat: Avoid wild Pokemon!If you deposit a pokemon in a box and then pull it out, it is completely healed. This is useful for places like the Day-Care center that do not have a heal station. There are a few other places in which there are PC's but no heal station.Cheat: Avoid wild Pokemon!You can get Corsola without fishing. In order to get Corsola you need a Bellosom( Evolve Gloom with sun stone ) and you need to go to Pacifidlog Town and talk to the lady in one of the houses and she will trade you a Corsola for a Bellosom. Cheat: Avoid wild Pokemon!It's really simple. All you have to do is to bring a Pokemon that knows Sweet Scent and use it over and over again. You can attract as much Pokemon as you want without wasting steps.Cheat: Avoid wild Pokemon!when you put a pokemon in a day care center, each step you take equals one exp. point. if you want to level up a pokemon faster while it is in the center, you must first obtain the acro bike from rydel. then fly over to lavaridge town and bike all the way right until you reach the desert. bike over to the mudslide and face it. now here is the tricky part, find a way to hold down the UP button on your gameboy. leave it on overnight, and your set. this may not work as well for people without an sp.Cheat: Avoid wild Pokemon!If you have the Acro Bike equipped, get on it while you're in the Safari zone. If you hop up and down in one spot of grass, you can run into Pokemon without using up steps.</plot>
	<releasedate>19/3/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Game Freak</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>p-q10A-F1s4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2363</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/471243-pokemon-ruby-version</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2363-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2363-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/3/3/gfs_27078_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/e/3/gfs_27078_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/2/a/gfs_68769_1_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/a/e/gfs_27078_2_1.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/7/e/gfs_27078_2_2.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2363-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2363-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2363-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2363-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2363-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/2363-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2363.png</clearlogo1>
</game>