<Game>
	<Name>Pocket Monsters - LeafGreen (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Pok&#233;mon Leaf Green adds more content and features to one of the first Pok&#233;mon games ever released. In this version of the classic role-playing game, you can collect all of the monsters from different Pok&#233;mon installments, including Ruby, Sapphire, and Colosseum. The game comes with a wireless adapter, which lets you connect with your friends' Game Boy Advances to chat, trade Pok&#233;mon, and participate in battles. Other new features include a tutorial mode, a recap system, minigames, and more.Cheat: Saving Time in the Safari ZoneWhen you are in the Safari Zone, it counts the number of steps you take to determine the amount of time you have left. Well, if you want to catch a rare Pok&amp;eacute;mon, but don't want to run out of time, enter the grass, then lightly tap the directional pad. You will change the way you are facing, but it will not count as a step. You can have near-infinite time in the Safari Zone doing this. It is helpful when some Pok&amp;eacute;mon, such as Chansey, appear in only one section of the Zone.Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!In FireRed, and LeafGreen you can get the 3 dogs depending on your starter pokemon. Here are the steps:1: Beat the Elite Four2: Randomly in the wild, you can get 1 of the 3 dogs by your starter pokemon.Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!You have to have gone to the second island. Your pokemon have to trust you enough and you have to have the one of three starters.(only the one you started with can learn these moves. (Frenzy Plant, Hydro Cannon and Blaast Burn)Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!There are places in the game where important people/Pokemon have stood at one point. If you use the Itemfinder on the EXACT spot where they were, a special item will be found which is usually very rare. You cannot find these items any other way.Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!For each 25 times you enter the Hall of Fame, she'll add a new doll to the collection in her house on Four Island. She'll stop after adding a total of eight dolls.Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!When you first visit Three Island, you'll come across a miner looking for gold in one of the caves. If you return to him after beating the Elite Four, he'll hand over a Nugget, an item that can be sold at high prices.Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!When you first visit Two Island, the local Pokemart will be severely limited in the items for sale. As you complete various tasks, more items will become available.Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!Go to 'Island 4' and go to the bragget house where he asks you what you want to Brag about.Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!By completing certain tasks, it is possible to upgrade your trainer card a total of four times, from the intital blue to green, bronze, silver, and gold.  The upgrades can be obtained in any order, and each one adds a star to your trainer card and upgrades the color.Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!At the beginning of LeafGreen/FireRed, you can only trade between the two respective versions. However, if you complete a certain task in the game, you can trade to Pokemon Colosseum on the Gamecube, and Pokemon Ruby/Sapphire, the two other Pokemon games on the GBA.Cheat: Get the chance to get the 3 dogs!When you have access to Two Island, save the Game Corner owner's daughter, then deliver the package. The grateful owner will open some mini-games that you and your friends can play.Cheat: Shiny PokemonEvery time you encounter a pokemon you have a 1/8192 chance of the pokemon being a different color, this is called a shiny pokemonCheat: Determining Pokemons feelings towards you.When you use an item on one of your Pokemon outside of a battle, such as a Potion, the Pokemon will either move closer or away from you in the short intermission sequence. How far the Pokemon moves depends on how much it likes you. If it does not move at all, it feels neutral.Cheat: Determining Pokemons feelings towards you.You don't need to find one pokemon of each gender in order to breed them.  You simply have to put your pokemon of choice and a ditto into the daycare center.  After a short while, the old man will tell you that they found an egg, and when it hatches, it will be whichever pokemon you matched up with DittoCheat: Determining Pokemons feelings towards you.On Island 5, there is an area to the northeast called Gorgeous Resort. There are 2 wealthy trainers you can face. They are named Lady Jacki and Lady Gillian. Lady Jacki gives you $10000 if you beat her($20000 with Amulet Coin) and Lady Gillian gives you $9800($19600 with Amulet Coin). The pokemon they use also carry expensive items. Jacki's 2 pokemon carry Stardust, Gillian's 2 Mareep have Stardust, and Gillian's Flaafy has a Nugget. Just use Thief or Covet to obtain these items.Cheat: Determining Pokemons feelings towards you.In the Gamecorner in Celadon City, go talk to the man at the far right Slots. He will give you 20 free coins. Talk to the man on the slots beside him. He will give you 20 free coins, also. Go to the left side of the Gamecorner. Talk to the guy that looks like a fisherman, and he will give you 10 free coins.Cheat: Determining Pokemons feelings towards you.Apparently, the folks in the Game Corner don't hold on to their coins very well!By using the Itemfinder or looking by yourself, you'll find that many spots in the Game Corner have some number of coins lying on them. If you find them all, you'll find 200+ coins!</plot>
	<releasedate>7/9/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Game Freak</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>8.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>vM1FKnIgwas</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2314</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/918916-pokemon-leafgreen-version</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2314-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2314-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/c/c/gfs_54947_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/9/5/gfs_87748_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/5/9/gfs_53827_2_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/8/9/gfs_53827_2_2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/3/9/gfs_53827_2_3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2314-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2314-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2314-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2314-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/2314-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2314.png</clearlogo1>
</game>