<Game>
	<Name>Pokemon - FireRed Version (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Pok?mon FireRed takes the player into the world of Kanto on a mission to catch all of the 350 pok?mon for Pok?mon researcher Prof. Oak. Pok?mon are animal-looking creatures that pretty much form this and all the other games in the Pok?mon Universe. Your challenge is to capture them all using pok?balls and your own set of these strange creatures, as well as training them for the ultimate battle, the Elite Four!It is a remake of the original and offers the same diversity of gameplay as the original. However, this game's got everything you might miss in the classic game: updated art, splendid graphics, new pok?mon and perhaps the most interesting: the wireless adapter. This makes you able of wirelessly trading with your friends within a limited radius. In addition to all of this, FireRed lets you explore a new set of islands outside of Kanto, the Sevii Islands! Enter the union room, make the team of your dreams or explore the world of Kanto in this epic gameplay experience from the Universe of Pok?mon. Gotta catch 'em all!http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/pokmon-fireredCheat: DiplomaTo get the diploma, catch all 386 pokemon (i.e. fill the national dex).Cheat: DiplomaOnce you have beaten the Elite 4 and have more then 60 pokemon in the pokedex, go to Pallet Town and see the Professor. He gives you and Gary the National Dex, which allows you to view the entries of all 386 pokemon.Cheat: DiplomaThere are places in the game where important people/Pokemon have stood at one point. If you use the Itemfinder on the EXACT spot where they were, a special item will be found which is usually very rare. You cannot find these items any other way.Cheat: DiplomaGo to any Poke Mart and click on the clipboard near the shopkeeper. The clipboard is a questionaire. Type in the 4 words "Link Together With All" and the shopkeeper should notice and gives you access to the Mystery Gift system. Save the game and restart. At the Front Menu, there should be a new option called "Mystery Gift" With Mystery Gift, you can unlock many things.Cheat: DiplomaGo to Island Four and go to the lowest house and talk to the man inside and do the following things:Cheat: DiplomaBy completing certain tasks, it is possible to upgrade your trainer card a total of four times, from the intital blue to green, bronze, silver, and gold.  The upgrades can be obtained in any order, and each one adds a star to your trainer card and upgrades the color.Cheat: Shiny pokemonevery time you encounter a pokemon you have a 1/8192 chance of the pokemon being a different color, this is called a shiny pokemonCheat: Determining Pokemons feelings towards you.When you use an item on one of your Pokemon outside of a battle, such as a Potion, the Pokemon will either move closer or away from you in the short intermission sequence. How far the Pokemon moves depends on how much it likes you. If it does not move at all, it feels neutral.Cheat: Determining Pokemons feelings towards you.Enter the Saffron City Gym, and step onto the warp panel. Now, go:North, South, South, North, South, North, North, South, South, North, North, North, South, South. You will now be in Sabrina's room, without having to fight any battles.Cheat: Determining Pokemons feelings towards you.This only works on grass. Once you obtained CUT, you can cut the grass so you won't find any Pokemon.Cheat: Determining Pokemons feelings towards you.In the safari zone , stand in any grassy area.  Instead of moving left and right, just tap left or tap right so that your character turns but you dont move.  By doing this, you'll still run into random encounters but your time in the safari zone will not decrease.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>g4G2hRpVw8A</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3490</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/918915-pokemon-firered-version</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/pokmon-firered-version</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/ci6lvcT.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/KxcSobE.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/5Vfp4vT.png</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/166593-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267490-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267491-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-another.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267492-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267493-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-game.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267494-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-familiar.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/356903-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-john-dosen.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267495-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-your.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267496-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-front.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267497-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-prof.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/267498-pokemon-firered-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-one-of.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3490-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3490-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3490-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3490-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/jrm8sa3.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3490.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Pokemon FireRed and LeafGreen take place mostly in the fictional region of Kanto. This is one distinct region of many in the Pokemon world, which includes varied geographical habitats for the Pokemon species, human-populated towns and cities, and routes between locations. Some areas are only accessible once the player acquires a special item or one of the player's Pokemon learns a special ability. Near the end of the plot, the protagonist is able to venture to the Sevii Islands, a new area not available in the original Red or Blue games. It consists of an archipelago of seven islands that contain Pokemon normally exclusive to the Johto region.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>g4G2hRpVw8A</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/df92c9fc-87fa-42d6-8750-f3ec35273f6a.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6cb6058b-0215-47cf-9691-af3e78ce23a6.jpg</boxart4>
	<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d8fbe59a-03cd-4aa7-a437-e70e869468fc.jpg</boxart5>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bd025dd1-d161-40f1-a0c0-b60f3cc3f2b8.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e7b1531f-2c1d-46f5-b269-5f8e9eea6c4d.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9e6152b6-d5c4-4820-899a-35b30d2e1d48.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a1de569e-a92b-4ca4-9c0a-b967ab53c588.png</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>