<Game>
	<Name>Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Red Rescue Team (USA) (Demo) (Kiosk)</Name>
	<plot>For the first time ever, the player is a Pok&#233;mon, speaking and interacting with other characters in a world populated only by Pok&#233;mon! Features a deep, involving and dramatic story brings the player into a world of Pok&#233;mon not seen or experienced before. Strategic battles enhance the adventure. Randomly generated dungeons make every mission unique. One day the player awakens to find that he or she has been turned into a Pok&#233;mon. The land is being ravaged by natural disasters so the player decides to form a rescue team with a partner Pok&#233;mon. The player can interact with many different Pok&#233;mon on various missions while trying to uncover their true purpose and destiny. An engrossing story of adventure, redemption and, most of all, friendship.Cheat: Unlock Special MissionsInput these codes in at the Wonder Mail screen.  It will unlock special missions for good prizes.Cheat: Unlock Special MissionsNOTE: "..." is one character. Also, the parts in the brackets ([,]) are the yellow parts of the code. Cheat: Ability to Evolve your PokemonTo gain the ability to evolve your pokemon you must beat Rayquazza. After you have beaten Rayquazza and the credits have rolled, you will gain access to Luminous Cave which is found at Whiscash Pond just north of the Pokemon Square. There will be a commotion in Pokemon Square prompting you to go there and learn about evolution. Then the next time you try to leave and go on any mission, your partner will stop you and tell you how to change leaders and travel using just one pokemon. Enter Luminous Cave with just the pokemon that you wish to evolve. The pokemon that you are evolving must meet the required level for evolution and in some cases might need an item such as a moon stone or sun stone. A link cable can also be used. To check if your pokemon is capable of evolution, check it's summary page and under evolution it will be Possible, Not Now, or No More.Cheat: Ability to Evolve your PokemonAll of this can only be locked AFTER you beat the game. This are the dungeons where you'll recruit a lot of legendary Pokemon.Cheat: Ability to Evolve your PokemonRescue Mission Ranks also go up as you go up in Rescue Team Ranks</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>3_7j-C_cUFo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2372</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929408-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/pokmon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pokemon-mystery-dungeon-bluered-rescue-team/3030-13974/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/4UX62tl.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/iLe22aM.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/9I7a7cO.png</boxart3>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/135098-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/190179-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/190180-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/190176-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/190169-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/190170-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/190171-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/190172-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/190173-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/190174-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/190175-pokemon-mystery-dungeon-red-rescue-team-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2372-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/mu2R60f.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2372.png</clearlogo1>
</game>