<Game>
	<Name>Pokemon Pinball - Ruby & Sapphire (Japan) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>The pocket monsters are back on the pinball table, this time with the latest batch of creatures from the Ruby &amp; Sapphire series on GBA joining the already established cast of characters.Your job is to not only use the Poke-ball as a pinball and rack up the biggest score on the table, but to also capture the Pokemon through a selection of mini-games and challenges during the usual pinball game. Simply hit the required areas of the board with the ball and you'll capture the monster available. There's 200 to find in total.Two different boards are on offer, each based on the two versions of Pokemon for GBA (i.e. Ruby and Sapphire). Each board represents a new challenge as well as which Pokemon you can catch during play.Although there is no 2 player battle mode of sorts, you can trade Pokemon and high scores using the link cable.http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/pokmon-pinball-ruby-sapphireCheat: Erase saved data in Pokedex + High ScoresOn the Pokedex OR High Score screen, hold ''L'' on the control pad, and tap the ''L'' and ''R'' shoulder buttons AT THE SAME TIME - you will receive a prompt confirming whether or not you want to erase your saved data.Cheat: Unlimited points and ball upgradesWhen you have 3 Chinchous going in a clockwise circle, shoot the ball up at them. If you did it right, you should go past the Chinchous. If this doesn't work, try again until you get it abouve the Chinchous. When it falls down again, it should hit a Chinchou and fly up again. It should repeat this until you tilt the machine to make the ball get out of this endless loop.Cheat: Jirachi AppearanceDo travel mode 6 times to go to the Ruins area where you can catch Beldum, Rejirock, Rejice and Rejisteel.Cheat: Jirachi AppearanceDo the following codes to go to the corresponding bonus stages.Cheat: Easily catch a pokemon -- sapphire field onlyIn catch em mode, when the ball saver is lit (it always is for the first half of catch em mode), drop the ball. This will cause the pokemon to get hit twice (it goes down, hits it, then bounces off the bumper and hits it again). This only works AFTER you hit the chinchou\shroomish bumpers three times, and only in the sapphire field.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Pinball</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>tWf6YZMVTj8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3533</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/914978-pokemon-pinball-ruby-and-sapphire</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/pokmon-pinball-ruby-sapphire</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/pokemon-pinball-ruby-sapphire/3030-8812/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3533-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3533-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/56897-pokemon-pinball-ruby-sapphire-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128844-pokemon-pinball-ruby-sapphire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463746-pokemon-pinball-ruby-sapphire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128845-pokemon-pinball-ruby-sapphire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/128846-pokemon-pinball-ruby-sapphire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463747-pokemon-pinball-ruby-sapphire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463748-pokemon-pinball-ruby-sapphire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463749-pokemon-pinball-ruby-sapphire-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/608/409891-pokemon_pinball_rs_us_23.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/608/409890-pokemon_pinball_rs_us_22.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/608/409889-pokemon_pinball_rs_us_21.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/tMsxOmH.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3533.png</clearlogo1>
</game>