<Game>
	<Name>Polarium Advance (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Polarium Advance is basically the same as Polarium for the Nintendo DS, but a couple of new blocks have been added.This is a puzzle game in which the player must create horizontal lines of all the same color (either black or white). To change the color (or "polarity") of a block, you must select the blocks in one line. In most puzzles, you can use the border to lengthen the line. The new blocks in the Advance version are: Hurdle Tiles, which you cannot pass, Multi-Tiles, which count as black or white, and Solid Tiles, which will not turn but are removed so that the tiles above them fall down. There are 365 puzzles in this mode (Daily Polarium) ranging from very easy to quite challenging.The Time Attack Mode requires you to solve either ten easy puzzles or five hard puzzles within the time given. Leaving a block of the wrong color in a line results in a 30 seconds penalty. It is possible to create your own puzzles and share them with friends. Puzzles created in the Nintendo DS version of the game are compatible with the GBA version.Cheat: 3 Special PuzzlesYou need to complete Daily Polarium for at least two "full" months (i.e. your first month would not count unless you start on the first day of any month). You will unlock either a tile or cursor set on the first day of the following month, depends on the month (see below). The last set will be unlocked when you finish a year in Daily Polarium.Cheat: 3 Special PuzzlesNote that you don't need to complete the secondary objectives (e.g. start and end on specific point etc) to unlock these. Once unlocked, these can be chosen in the option menu.Cheat: 3 Special PuzzlesThese sets can be chosen in teh options menu, once unlocked.Cheat: 3 Special PuzzlesOnce unlocked, this mode is accessible from the Time Attack menu.Cheat: 3 Special PuzzlesInsert your copy of Polarium Advance into the DS GBA Slot when playing Actionloop (Puzzloop) and you will unlock an extra Tile set on Polarium Advance.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3491</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929333-polarium-advance</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/polarium-advance</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/polarium-advance/3030-15464/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/625697-929333_69019_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3491-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/64947-polarium-advance-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/166518-polarium-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/166519-polarium-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740910-polarium-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-basic-rules.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740911-polarium-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-turn-the-tiles.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740912-polarium-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-making-a-path.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740913-polarium-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-clear.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740914-polarium-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-solving-another.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740915-polarium-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-tiles-on.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740916-polarium-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-using-the-border.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8273/625704-1149470583_00.png</snapshot10>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3491-g.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>A GBA version of Nintendo's simple, stylish puzzle game (originally designed for the Nintendo DS.) Make your line through the game board, flipping black and white tiles to change and match their color.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/325e58f7-71ed-4ed8-91dd-37126774029a.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/074203f4-2066-4521-8ff6-9f16168fa6f7.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f6baca14-8d8d-42ae-a76e-9c63ba2991f2.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>