<Game>
	<Name>Pro Beach Soccer (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt)</Name>
	<plot>With flashy moves, laser shows, and DJs, Ultimate Beach Soccer is not your ordinary soccer game. This new sport features aerial passes, special moves, combos, ball-juggling, and flashy goals and saves. These moves are not all for show; use them to dominate your opponents in quick matches, long-term competitions, and custom tournaments. Ultimate Beach Soccer takes you around the globe to locations including Rio, France, Japan, and Venice Beach, California. Each stadium features cheerleaders, commentators, and pitch-side shows with DJs.</plot>
	<releasedate>3/11/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports, Miscellaneous, Arcade</genre>
	<Developer>Magic Pockets</Developer>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>26122</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/578718-ultimate-beach-soccer</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ultimate-beach-soccer/3030-10790/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/26122-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275033-71.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275032-69.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275031-65.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275030-61.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275029-59.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275028-57.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275027-55.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275026-53.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275025-51.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275024-49.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Ultimate Beach Soccer is the first game based on the Summer variation of football, played by five players aside on a sandy surface. The game includes 32 national teams (some with their real stars) plus 6 all star teams to be unlocked in 3 game modes (Exhibition, Pro Beach Soccer Tour and Tournament) played in Bangkok, Rio de Janeiro, Marseille or Venice Beach. Gameplay is classic arcade, with one button to pass, another to juggle the ball and another to shoot. One of the key aspects is the "State of Grace"; by making fancy moves (such as overhead kicks, heel passes or heading the ball back and forth) and scoring goals, a power bar starts filling, and when it's full, all team attributes are maxed up and the players are given the ability to quickly run with the ball.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1bdd5a45-3c43-44d9-b87d-36bbb0df5582.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33d75ae8-7ab0-4145-ae69-74e2664c3bf4.png</clearlogo1>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
</game>