<Game>
	<Name>Puyo Pop (Europe) (En,Ja)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Puyo Pop ("Minna de Puyo Puyo" in Japan) was the first game in the Puyo Puyo series to be released after Compile's closure. Sega, who had previously distributed the arcade versions of each Puyo Puyo game, now had exclusive ownership of the franchise and its Madou Monogatari characters; using their Sonic Team banner, they developed this game.The game's mechanics strongly resemble those of Puyo Puyo 2, with Hard Puyo and Point Puyo from the same game coming into play at times. The single-player mode, however, is all new: Carbuncle has run off, and Arle gives chase while simultaneously collecting several runes. Each stage consists of a different ruleset and a handful of opponents that are faced sequentially. After clearing the game once, the player begins a sidequest; upon completion, the player unlocks an extra stage that features every opponent in the game.This game is the last to focus exclusively on the Madou Monogatari cast, as Sega's next Puyo Puyo game ( Puyo Pop Fever) features an almost entirely new set of characters.Stages:Hamaji Forest: Skeleton T, Incubus, SeririGold Town: Kikimora, Suketoudara, Harpy, Minotauros, NohohoGachinko Dungeon: Kikimora, Zoh Daimaoh, Harpy, Rulue, Draco CentaurosMagical Tower: Kikimora, Incubus, Suketoudara, Schezo Wegey, WitchDark Prince Castle: Lagnus the Brave, Zoh Daimaoh, Minotauros, Skeleton T, Schezo Wegey, Rulue, Dark PrinceCheat: Sound TestTo access a hidden sound test in the Options menu, defeat Kaakun twice in Trial Labyrinth to receive CARD 18. Select 18 in Gallery mode in the Options menu, and you'll be presented with the Sonic Team artwork for the 5 Puyo.  Every time you press 'A', you will be greeted with another sound effect, including the 'gloop' sound of puyo and ojyama being dropped, which is curiously absent from the game itself.Cheat: Sound TestSigns let you gain access to new areas. The WELCOME SIGN lets you into Hajimari Forest; you start with it. The MERCHANT SIGN lets you into Goldtown; win from Seriri in Hajimari Forest. The WARRIOR SIGN lets you into Gachinko Dungeon; win from Nohoho in Goldtown The CONJURER SIGN lets you into Magical Tower; win from Draco Centaur in Gachinko Dungeon. The MONARCH SIGN  lets you into G. Dark Prince Castle; win from Witch in Magical Tower. The last sign is the hardest to get. Defeat Satan-sama twice to get the DUBIOUS BOOK. Defeat Witch in magical Tower with the BOOK to get FLAME EXPANDER. Defeat Draco Centaur in Gachinko Dungeon with FLAME to get NOHOHO RUCKSACK. Defeat Nohoho in Goldtown with the RUCKSACK and get SCALE PENDANT. Defeat Seriri in Hajimari Forest with the PENDANT and she'll give you the GODDESS SIGN, which lets you into Trial Labyrinth, the 6th and final area.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>THQ</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>8.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3539</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/551521-puyo-pop</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/puyo-pop_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/puyo-pop/3030-40279/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3539-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3539-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/690502-puyo-pop-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/690503-puyo-pop-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-mode.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/690504-puyo-pop-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-course.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/690505-puyo-pop-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-story.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/690506-puyo-pop-game-boy-advance-screenshot-here-comes-the-pieces.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/690507-puyo-pop-game-boy-advance-screenshot-placing-the-pieces.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/690508-puyo-pop-game-boy-advance-screenshot-your-opponent-has-placed.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/690509-puyo-pop-game-boy-advance-screenshot-your-winning-at-the-moment.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/690510-puyo-pop-game-boy-advance-screenshot-both-screens-filling.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/690511-puyo-pop-game-boy-advance-screenshot-he-won.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/GgBUNY4.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3539.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Help Arle and Carbuncle make their way home! Take on all of the wacky characters you meet in challenging games of Puyo Pop so you can make your way through the land and back to safety. It's a mad scramble to erase Puyo, create chain combos, and fill up your opponent's playfield in this fast-paced puzzle game.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3c028a48-55b0-4aae-959a-313d5b34e0c1.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e17782c6-b454-49b5-9ddf-b35f965b656d.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bc9b15a5-0c20-4b29-9745-39a293b10452.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>