<Game>
	<Name>Puyo Pop Fever (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The title screen of the GameCube version.Puyo Pop Fever (known as Puyo Puyo Fever and Puyo Puyo 5) is a game in the popular    Puyo Puyo franchise. The game was released on PlayStation 2, Dreamcast, Nintendo GameCube, Xbox, Mac OS, Game Boy Advance, PC, PlayStation Portable, Nintendo DS, and arcade. The game was published by    Sega,    Atlus,    THQ,    Namco, and    Ignition Entertainment and developed by    Sonic Team. Puyo Pop Fever was originally released in North America on July 20, 2004.The game began as a project to merely keep the franchise alive, but Sonic Team began to implement entirely new features, characters, and gameplay aspects. The creators of the Puyo Puyo franchise,    Compile, had recently gone bankrupt before the release of Sonic Team's first Puyo Puyo game,    Puyo Pop on the Game Boy Advance. Despite their bankruptcy, all of the original characters of the franchise returned.Gameplay:Puyos must be aligned four-in-a-row of a single color.Puyo Pop Fever stars     Amitie, who is attending a school of magic. She is learning how to use Puyos to cast spells. Puyos are jelly-like creatures of several different colors. Puyos fall in a game field (similar to game fields in other puzzle games, like    Tetris or    Dr. Mario), where they must be aligned depending on color. Four Puyos of the same color in a row will cause those four to "pop." Then a "spell" is cast onto the other player's field, causing grey Puyos (or "garbage" Puyos) to fall.Puyo Pop Fever adds a Fever Mode (as the gameplay detailed above is identical to that of Puyo Pop). There is a bar in the middle of the screen that must be filled up to trigger Fever Mode. In Fever Mode, there are several pre-arranged puzzles in which the player must send in one chain of Puyos to erase (or pop) all of the Puyos on the screen. This continues until the time runs out.Puyo Pop Fever also has a multiplayer component, for which it was most praised. This mode is similar to the single player, except there are two players. The multiplayer mode was especially praised for the Nintendo DS version, which supported two to eight players at a time (previous games only allowed two to four players).Plot:Puyo Pop Fever puts players into the role of Amitie, a girl who is attending a magic school. Her teacher, Ms. Accord, has lost a magic wand. Amitie decides to try and find it for her, as she offered a reward. Amitie then travels through the world, meeting many of the characters from the Puyo Puyo world. Her rival is Raffine in the hard mode version of the story.Characters: Arle Nadja Onion Pixy Oshare Bones Hohow Bird Amitie Dongurigaeru Ralfine Rider Popoi Frankensteins Tarutaru Prince of Ocean Klug Accord Yu CarbuncleCheat: Get character select in Endless Puyo PopPick Endless Puyo Pop in the main menu, then move the cursor to the mode you want to play. Press UP, DOWN, SELECT, A. You will hear a sound and the character select menu will pop up.Cheat: Get character select in Endless Puyo PopBy default, you will be using the plain old drop set (like Arle's). To use the character's own drop set, hold select as you confirm your choice.Cheat: Get character select in Endless Puyo PopAt  the "Gallery", highlight "View Cut scenes"Cheat: Extra CharactersThese must be completed on Normal difficulty or higher.</plot>
	<releasedate>24/7/2004</releasedate>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>4.6</rating>
	<ESRB>RP - Rating Pending</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>11597</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/921227-puyo-pop-fever</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/puyo-pop-fever</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/puyo-pop-fever/3030-7226/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/11597-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/11597-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/162560-puyo-pop-fever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/162561-puyo-pop-fever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740936-puyo-pop-fever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-a-course.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740937-puyo-pop-fever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-meeting-your-teacher.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740938-puyo-pop-fever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-ready.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740939-puyo-pop-fever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-here-comes-the.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740940-puyo-pop-fever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-placing-a-large.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740941-puyo-pop-fever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-big-blue-one-next.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/740942-puyo-pop-fever-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-won.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/15744/491377-puyoscreen.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11597-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/11597-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vpoFqMT.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/11597.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Puyo Pop Fever is the fifth installment in the popular Puyo Puyo puzzle game series. The basic game mechanics are mainly similar to those of Puyo Puyo: the player has a 6x12 board, and must decide where to place incoming groups of variously-colored blobs, or puyo. After placing each set of puyo, any groups of four or more of the same colored adjacent puyo will pop. Any above will fall down and can form more groups for a chain reaction. Each time groups of puyo pop, the player will score points and, more importantly, send trash (aka garbage and nuisance) to their opponent. These trash puyo are colorless and will only pop when puyo next to them do so, rather than in groups as normal. When a player's board fills up, either if they cannot make groups or if they are sent a large amount of trash (usually the latter), they lose and the other player will win.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/94627bab-f307-4671-9db4-e429c19398cd.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6a10461d-6449-4722-bf1b-d3d7c477c02a.png</clearlogo2>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>