<Game>
	<Name>Rayman 3 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl,Sv,No,Da,Fi) (Beta)</Name>
	<plot>Summary:Rayman fights against both the hoodlums and the pirates. But are they working together?The plot of the handheld adaptation loosely follows what occurs in the console versions of Rayman 3. However in this version it appears that Captain Razorbeard and the pirates attempt to harness the power of the black lums to conquer Rayman's world. Much of the music, level scenery and enemies present suggests that this may have originally been conceived as an adaptation of Rayman 2 The Great Escape. Gameplay flows similarly to the original Rayman on 32-bit platforms but features powers and moves from Rayman 2 and Rayman 3. However none of the power suits from the console version of Rayman 3 appear in this game. Instead they would appear in a later handheld adapation called Rayman - Hoodlum's Revenge.Releases:Game Boy AdvanceThe base version of the handheld edition Rayman 3. The game features multiplayer for up to four players using either Single or Multi Cartridge connectivity. The game can also be connected to the Nintendo Gamecube version for additional challenge levels.N GageGameloft, Ubisoft's mobile games division, ported Rayman 3 to Nokia's N-Gage soon after the Game Boy Advance release. The N-Gage version is exactly the same has the Game Boy Advance version, however it lacks the Mode 7-based 3D levels and (unsurprisingly) features no GameCube connectivity. However, the N-Gage release featured online and local multiplayer by either Bluetooth or now defunct N-Gage arena. The N-Gage release of Rayman 3 was well received by critics and is one of the highest rated N-Gage games ever to be released.Cheat: Bonus levelsLink the Game Boy Advance to the Gamecube version of Rayman 3: Hoodlum Havoc to unlock ten bonus levels after collecting over 100 Orbs. Cheat: Bonus levelsDoing the Ly bonus stages in the 2nd and 4th world will earn you extra multiplayer games.</plot>
	<releasedate>4/3/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ubi Soft Entertainment Software</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>ln_JMmOaD2Y</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5490</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/563594-rayman-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/rayman-3</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/rayman-3/3030-26350/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/5490-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/5490-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/23158-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104414-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104400-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-if-you-go-to-play-the.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104401-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-menu-screen-is-very.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104405-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-here-you-can-select-the.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104402-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-grab-in-the-plants-to.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104409-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-rayman-s-current-situation.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104403-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-to-talk-with-murfy-find.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104404-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-guy-is-very-hunger.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104406-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-observing-the-danger.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/104407-rayman-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-don-t-lose-your-precious.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/5490-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/5490-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/EgMS4zd.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Rayman 3 (Game Boy Advance) is a portable version of the console game of the same name which was released for the Game Boy Advance in 2003. It is the first handheld Rayman game to feature multiplayer modes which made use of the Game Boy Advance/GameCube link cable, to link to the GameCube version. It is a 2D side-scrolling game with elements from Rayman, Rayman 2, and Rayman 3, though it is mostly centered around the story of Rayman 2. It is thought that it was originally developed as a Game Boy Advance version of Rayman 2, and that its Rayman 3 elements were added late in its development so that it could be marketed as a Game Boy Advance version of Rayman 3.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>ln_JMmOaD2Y</VideoURL1>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aaed99bf-b842-444c-a60a-309ce1f62866.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a56dd586-d618-4863-bb57-cb13e38d4122.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>