<Game>
	<Name>Reign of Fire (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Based on the movie, Reign of Fire lets you play as either a human or a dragon in an epic battle. As a human, you'll take the role of a resistance fighter who's trying to defend the last remaining humans from attack. You must make your way to the site of the sole male dragon using a variety of well-equipped vehicles and high-tech weaponry. As a dragon, you'll take the role of an infant, led by instinct to attack foes, and you'll attempt to eradicate the human race. With your natural fire-breathing and flying abilities, you can destroy everything on the ground or in the skies.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/561534.htmlCheat: Unlock All LevelsPlease enter the following as a password:Cheat: 7th dragon missionBeat the 6th dragon mission and when the credits are done select ''try again'' from the menu that appears.  The 7th mission should be the same area as the human 10th mission and you start were Ashley would be, and you have no objectives and the compass points to a spot of little importance. There's also no pickups or enemies in this ''mission''.  (Note: I think this was going to be a mission, but it wasn't completed. I think that the objective might have been to bring the eggs to Ashley.)</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous</genre>
	<Developer>Bam Entertainment</Developer>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3585</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561534-reign-of-fire</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3585-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3585-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/d/4/gfs_52558_1_2.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/6/4/gfs_52558_1_3.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/7/4/gfs_52558_1_4.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/c/4/gfs_52558_1_5.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/1/4/gfs_52558_1_6.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3585-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3585-g.jpg</banner1>
</game>