<Game>
	<Name>Road Trip - Shifting Gears (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Similar to Gadget Racers, your goal is to complete multiple challenges to open to tracks and challenges in order to win the game.Finish in the top 3 in each challenge and win money to upgrade your car.  There are over 100 upgrades available such as new engines, tires, steering wheels, shifters... even new car bodies and paint.The game consists of 150 challenges on 60 different tracks.  These come in the form of standard racing, drag racing, stopping on time within an area, jumping onto "bullseyes", running circles around a cone, and more.  You'll never be bored from doing the same thing on the same track.Enjoy tracks that are paved, sand, and snow.  Also, enjoy racing in the rain where traction is poor.  With the right upgrades to your car, you can handle these dangers.  Without them, you may not finish in the top 3.In order to progress in the challenges, you need to finish in the top 3 in each race.  If you finish first, you not only get more money, but you also get a prize.  Prizes are free parts for your car.  This can save you money and can allow you to get certain upgrades more quickly as not all upgrades are available from the start.Besides the normal challenges, there are also sprint races and battle races to choose from.  Play all these races in single player, or linked with up to 3 other players.  Or, connect to the GameCube with Road Trip: Arcade to unlock more content.The game tracks all your parts that you have acquired, completed races, race results, and more.Cheat: Unlock Dragon PartsComplete the Angel Cup. From the main title screen, go to Options then Change Name. Enter ''DRAGON'' as your name to unlock the Dragon parts. You'll get a screen telling you they are unlocked. You can change your name back anytime after that.Cheat: Super Race CupsTo unlock the Super Race Modes, Complete each race type once, including GP Mode, doing Bronze Silver and Gold cups. After this, you will see the credits. When you resume playing, the Super Bronze, Super Silver and Super Gold Cup races for each race type will be unlocked.</plot>
	<releasedate>6/4/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing</genre>
	<Developer>Conspiracy Entertainment  Corp.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>19454</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/915135-road-trip-shifting-gears</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/road-trip-shifting-gears</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/road-trip-shifting-gears/3030-11709/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/19454-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68291-road-trip-shifting-gears-game-boy-advance-screenshot-your-trip.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68292-road-trip-shifting-gears-game-boy-advance-screenshot-make-your.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68293-road-trip-shifting-gears-game-boy-advance-screenshot-customize.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68294-road-trip-shifting-gears-game-boy-advance-screenshot-buy-different.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68295-road-trip-shifting-gears-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pick-what.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68296-road-trip-shifting-gears-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pick-a.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68297-road-trip-shifting-gears-game-boy-advance-screenshot-one-of.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68298-road-trip-shifting-gears-game-boy-advance-screenshot-another.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68299-road-trip-shifting-gears-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-this.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/68300-road-trip-shifting-gears-game-boy-advance-screenshot-completing.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Game Boy Advance multiplayer racing adventure game, released in Japan as Choro Q Advance 2. Road Trip: Shifting Gears continues the Takara-developed racing series on the GBA, and has the ability to link to Road Trip: Arcade Edition on the GameCube for unlockable extras. Players have full control over car customization, down to the most minute detail with a body paint shop, more than 100 different parts, and numerous fantasy attachments. Players compete in 150 racing events, minigames, in more than 64 courses. The game supports link cable connectivity for up to four players.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e32ff7ac-f044-48d5-9c05-6df794ccd7e5.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82c68f20-55cf-44d5-96e5-d9cba2930cf7.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5f7ef09e-8e89-440b-9d19-465d9ac94074.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2d5ac996-2a6b-4a4e-85fc-c6b12d5083b3.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/98b8d654-90f2-4b35-923a-1627560b1cbe.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/80417ce2-7132-4e30-8486-2e69fb5dad2a.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7eb807df-3e0c-49e8-8aed-810f061af736.jpg</snapshot13>
	<Publisher>Conspiracy Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>