<Game>
	<Name>Robopon 2 - Ring Version (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Having earned the title "Legend 1," in the original game, Cody sets off to a new land and a new tournament. However, things take a turn for the worse when a violent storm strands him on an island far from home. He discovers that the nearby lands are being terrorized by the evil Maskman. In order to set things right, Cody must gather his strongest Robopon and embark on an adventure that will take him 20 years into the past!http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/582397.htmlCheat: Unlimited mushroomsWhen you find a mushroom pick it up and leave the room. When out of the room send the mushroom to the wharehouse. Walk back into the room and a new mushroom should be there; pick it up and repeat as desired.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus Co.</Developer>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3589</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/582397-robopon-2-ring-version</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3589-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3589-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/b/b/gfs_46608_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/6/b/gfs_46608_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/d/b/gfs_46608_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/c/b/gfs_46608_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/7/b/gfs_46608_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/WzsMCWP.png</banner1>
	<Notes>After becoming the Legend 1 of Porombo Island in the original game, Cody sets off to a new land, and a new tournament. Things take a turn for the worse when a violent storm destroys Cody's boat, and sends him adrift at sea. He awakens inside a shack in the land of Majiko but all is not well. He discovers that the nearby lands are being terrorized by the Maskman and his cronies. In order to put things right, Cody must travel back 20 years into the past and back again.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/550868e7-457a-4186-a216-fa49d712f657.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/81aa85e6-1a2e-475a-8aac-79a7ca3c2e96.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9a23d6c9-2263-49bb-93f4-acc3d9613196.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
</game>