<Game>
	<Name>Robot Wars - Advanced Destruction (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Robot Wars is a game based on a BBC television series where you control robots and engage them in combat with other ones in the four modes of the game. In the Quickstart mode the CPU allows you to quickly step into battle by randomly selecting two robots from the ones available for a versus fight. The Robot Workshop is where you can create and save up to four unique robot models and have them compete in any mode you choose.From the Games mode you can select one of the following three: Championship, Vengeance Battle and Robot Mayhem.1. Championship is the place where youll play against other robots to unlock more models.In Vengeance Battle you can choose your robot along with the opponents one and also the arena that you want to play to.Robot Mayhem gives you no time restrictions and one round where you must destroy as many enemy robots as possible.Theres also a Multiplayer mode where up to four players can compete via the link cable.Cheat: Misc. PasswordsWhen naming a robot, enter the following as names:</plot>
	<releasedate>30/10/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>BBC Multimedia</Developer>
	<rating>1.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3303</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/562023-robot-wars-advanced-destruction</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/robot-wars-advanced-destruction</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/robot-wars-advanced-destruction/3030-19360/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3303-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3303-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/265892-robot-wars-advanced-destruction-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/265893-robot-wars-advanced-destruction-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/265894-robot-wars-advanced-destruction-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/265895-robot-wars-advanced-destruction-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/265896-robot-wars-advanced-destruction-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/265897-robot-wars-advanced-destruction-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/265898-robot-wars-advanced-destruction-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/265899-robot-wars-advanced-destruction-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/265900-robot-wars-advanced-destruction-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/265901-robot-wars-advanced-destruction-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/Kkwz0Ih.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>In just over 4 years the Robot Wars TV series has grown from cult status to become a massive worldwide phenomenon, with the BBC show now attracting a weekly audience of around four million viewers. Taking its cue from the latest series, this GBA Robot Wars game cranks up the action with new events, new robots, new arenas and a wide range of new game features. The game brings together all the elements of the TV show - players can design and build their own robots, drawing upon a database of body parts, armour, engines, wheels and weapons. Once complete, battle can commence! The game also features a quick start `pick up and play' function, so gamers can select from a range of pre-built robots, and get straight to the realistic 3D action.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4ce25b0b-3762-4daa-94dc-485cf7b72883.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a7d7de42-f4dd-407d-ab55-95c3c630dee4.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>BBC Multimedia</Publisher>
</game>