<Game>
	<Name>Rockman EXE 6 - Dennoujuu Falzar (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>In Mega Man Battle Network 6, Lan's father has received a job transfer and the family moves to Cyber City, a town known for conducting various technological experiments. Lan will meet new people and build new friendships in the real world while Mega Man befriends helpful Navis and encounters dangerous new enemies on the virtual plane. Together they will face threats far more powerful and perilous than they ever have before.Cheat: Compress Navi Customizer ProgramsTo compress program pieces in the navi customizer, open up the navi customizer screen, and highlight the piece you wish to shrink.  Hold Right on the D-pad and press the corresponding set of buttons to shrink the piece.  To decompress the piece, repeat the process.Cheat: Lottery Chip Machine CodesOnce you are able to enter the chip shop in Central Town, go inside to find a green machine on the right-hand side.  Upon pressing A in front of the machine, you will be able to enter a series of numbers to receive bonus items.Cheat: Giga ChipsThe list of Giga chips are below:Cheat: Giga ChipsIn each of the Net areas (excluding the ACDC and Green Areas), there is a Net Cafe where you can buy coffee for 10z a cup. Each time you buy a cup, they will give you a small piece of information. After you buy enough coffee, the owners will recognize you as a regular customer and give you an item.Cheat: Giga ChipsThere are secret bosses in the game that require having a certain amount of chips or having a certain Title Screen Icon.Cheat: Giga ChipsCheat: Giga ChipsUpon completing the tasks listed below, various icons showing your accomplishments will be displayed at the top of the title screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/6/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom</Developer>
	<rating>8.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>1Y7dfQYxxDw</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>6932</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929992-mega-man-battle-network-6-cybeast-falzar</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/6932-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/6932-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/c/8/gfs_70194_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/0/0/gfs_73922_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/d/0/gfs_73922_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/6/0/gfs_73922_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/7/0/gfs_73922_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/6932-g.jpg</banner1>
</game>