<Game>
	<Name>Sega Smash Pack (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Three classic Sega Genesis titles on your Game Boy Advance. Ecco the Dolphin, Sonic Spinball, and Golden Axe. Three of Sega's best sellers. In Ecco you play a dolphin in an extensive underwater action adventure. It is up to you to learn why your friends are gone and the world needs to be saved.Sonic the hedgehog is now a pinball game. Filled with classic Sonic action as well. Defeat the evil Dr. Robotnik.Golden Axe is the ultimate side scrolling hack and slash that started it all. Multiplayer action with your Game Link cable. Three Great Sega Games!Cheat: Begin the game and move Ecco left and right.  Press Start to pause the game while Ecco is turning.  You have to pause it when Ecco is directly facing you.  When you do that, press Right, B, C, B, C, Down, C, Up.  If you did it right, a cheat menu that has options such as stage select, message test, sound test, and more, will appear.Cheat: Enter the code SHARKFIN for infinite air and sonar.Cheat: Input a valid password, then press Start, and wait for the screen that shows the name of the level you're currently in with your password.  Next, hold A and Start.  Keep hold of A and Start until Ecco appears on the screen.  Now press Start to unpause and you will be invincible.Cheat: AJPPOWAX is the password for this levelCheat: When you are in the "password entry" screen, you can enter these "please" codes to reach the corresponding levels. Cheat: The Last Fight: KNLMLMLCCheat: The Undercaves: UYNAINCC The Undercaves 2: DQDIACCI The Vents: FKWLACCACheat: The Lagoon: NDRBRIKR Ridge Water: HYAUGFLV Open Ocean: FNCQWBMTCheat: The Ice Zone: DWFFZBMV Hard Water Zone: QGDJRQLA Cold Water Zone: MCLFRQLWCheat: The Island Zone: UWXIOQLK Deep Water Zone: EILQOQLC The Marble Sea: XAKUQQLSCheat: The Library: FDGXQQLC Deep City: ZUVPQQLU City of Forever: AABBRQLUCheat: Jurassic Beach: PLABUNLT Pteranodon Pond: FQREUNLI Origin Beach: QXKIUNLXCheat: Trilobite Circle: OBEMUNLX Dark Water: JNXPUNLA Deep Water 2: WSGAKNLCCheat: City of Forever 2: ZBPIGPLD The Tube: KUVEKMLK The Machine: SDDBKMLGCheat: NVNAINCRCheat: By entering an even combination of A's and N's in different sequences for your password, you can gain access to a variety of levels within the game. Here's a list of password combinations and the levels they take you to:Cheat: AANNNNAA: Deep CityNNNAANAA: The Marble SeaAAAANNNN: Origin BeachNNNNAAAA: Island ZoneNNNAAAAN: UndercavesAAAAAAAA: UndercavesNNNNNNNN: Welcome to The MachineAAANNNNA: Welcome to The MachineANANAANN: The VentsAANNAANN: The VentsNNAANNAA: Dark WaterNANANNAA: Dark WaterANNANNAA: Dark WaterANANANAN: Hard WaterNANANANA: Hard WaterAANNANAN: Hard WaterNNAANANA: Hard WaterCheat: All other combinations will not work, and will transport Ecco back to the starting screen of the game.Cheat: Cheat: Cheat: Cheat: Cheat: Cheat: Start arcade mode. When you get to the character select screen, hold down+left and hit A+C+Start. Nothing really confirms the code except until you get game over. If you input it correctly, the next time you get Game Over, it should say you have 9 credits instead of 3.Cheat: At the options menu, enter the opposite of the level select code: C, Up, B, Up, A, Up, C, B, Down, C, A, Down, B, A, Down. Complete the code correctly and the credits will start immedeately.Cheat: First, Access the Options from the title screen. On the Options Menu, take controller one and press these buttons in this order: A, DOWN, B, DOWN, C, DOWN, A, B, UP, A, C, UP, B, C, UP. If you did it correctly, you will hear a special sound. Go back to the title screen and hold button A and press START for Level 2, B and press START for Level 3, and C and press START to begin on level 4.Cheat: In Level three, The Machine, there is a moving platform where you start which takes you to either side of the area. If you stand on the platform and press up or down, the platform will stop, allowing you to get a good look around or plan your jump carefully.</plot>
	<releasedate>24/9/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA Corporation, THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<rating>3.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>rxTv8-LXYz4</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22297</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/551519-sega-smash-pack</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/sega-smash-pack-</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sega-smash-pack/3030-3340/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4647/836007-551519_44784_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/4568-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/58932-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12007-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12008-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-screenshot-altered-beast-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12010-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-screenshot-altered-beast.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12011-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-screenshot-altered-beast-2-players.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12012-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-screenshot-columns-title-screen.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12013-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-screenshot-columns-diagonal.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12014-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-screenshot-columns-vertical.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12015-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-screenshot-golden-axe-title-screen.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12016-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-screenshot-golden-axe-charge.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/12018-sega-pc-smash-pack-windows-screenshot-golden-axe-thieves.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/0ZMbjVL.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The Smash Pack was originally released on Dreamcast as part of Sega's final system bundle before Dreamcast made its ride off into the sunset. Of course, as we all know, classic games never die and that's exactly what the smash pack featured. Because of that Sega and THQ announced that the Smash Pack would be making its way to Game Boy Advance. While the GBA version doesn't feature the exact same titles it does showcase Sonic Spinball (one of the lesser known titles), Ecco the Dolphin and Golden Axe. All three titles were classics on Sega Genesis in the early 90's/late 80's.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8f10a9d4-f1ae-42ba-b58b-8c1048ae33f2.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/92beeba7-ab53-46e0-86ea-95bf285c063e.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>