<Game>
	<Name>Sega Arcade Gallery (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>4 classic Sega arcade titles return on one GBA cartridge:Outrun has you racing to the finish line, with multiple paths to race through, different conditions, plus plenty of traffic to dodge past. You can also choose from a range of background musical tracks with the radio.Space Harrier has you flying and blasting your way through level after level of aliens, dodging incoming fire and other obstacles in your way.Super Hang On, the second racer in the compilation, is a motoGP style racer where turbo boosts come into play. Beat the clock and the opposing racers while keeping yoru bike on the track to avoid falling off.Finally, there's the flight sim action title, After Burner, which has you flying over land and sea, dogfighting with enemy craft.Cheat: Infinite time for Outrun &amp;amp; Super Hang-On / Infinite continues in Afterburner &amp;amp; Space HarrierAt the Main Menu select any of the four games. At the Title Screen for any of the four games, press &amp; hold L-Trigger + R-Trigger + select &amp; then press up on the d-pad while still holding the other buttons. The options bar at the top of the screen will change to say "Show Credits". Select the Show Credits option &amp; when the credits begin you will see a series of sets of letters in bubbles appear &amp; then fade. When the first set materializes enter left, right, left, right on the d-pad before the letters fade(at each of the first three set of letters the buttons must be pressed before the bubbles fade). At the second set of letters enter up, down on the d-pad. At the thirds set of letters press A Button. If the code is entered correctly, you will here a woman's voice say "Congratulations." Effects for each of the games will now be enabled until you enter the code again(you will hear a man's voice say "Be careful!" if entered correctly to disable the codes), or turn the power off. So you can exit a game to the main menu to play another game without having to re-enter the code.Cheat: On the following stages, input these codes for the following effects.Cheat: Right before the road forks, press and hold Start. When you choose one of the roads and the other one disappears from view, a secret credit message will come up on the screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>19/5/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc., THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22247</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589357-sega-arcade-gallery</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/sega-arcade-gallery</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sega-arcade-gallery/3030-4335/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/4647/834413-589357_47210_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/26660-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/26661-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263747-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose-your.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263748-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263749-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose-which.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263750-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-screenshot-afterburner.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263751-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-screenshot-afterburner.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263752-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-screenshot-afterburner.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263753-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-screenshot-afterburner.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263754-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-screenshot-afterburner.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263755-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-screenshot-afterburner.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263756-sega-arcade-gallery-game-boy-advance-screenshot-outrun-choose.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/aShftzI.png</banner1>
	<Notes>THQ and Sega are teaming up to bring you four of the most popular classic arcade games ever created. Combining speed, action, and hi-flying adventure, Sega Arcade Gallery brings After Burner, OutRun, Super Hang On, and Space Harrier together for ultimate arcade fun on the Game Boy Advance!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9bf6836c-c668-46b9-92a3-da6a887d2d44.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7cd300d1-d4ff-4192-a77f-c039aeb9626b.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>