<Game>
	<Name>Shaman King - Master of Spirits (Europe) (En,Fr,De)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Master of Spirits is low on story, only focusing on character interaction using certain scenes from the show. It is however, a Metroidvania style adventure game where the player can collect different spirits, of which five can be equipped to gain different abilities and benefits. Some spirits can be combined for more powerful abilities.Gameplay:Spirits01. Amidamaru - Powerful slash move02. Mosuke - Increase attack power by 3 levels 03. Tokageroh - Push wooden boxes04. Corey - Freeze the enemy with a punch05. Eliza - Avoid the effects of Poison06. Silver Shield - Increase defence power 2 levels07. Silver Tail - Increase movement speed 2 levels08. Silver Wing - Increase furyoku recovery speed 2 levels.09. Silver Horn - Increase attack power 2 levels10. Silver Rod - Increase max health 2 levels11. Mic - Sprint faster and leap further.12. Lee Pai-Long - Use a fast special move travel under low places.13. Bason - Rapid attack move14. Grand Tao Dragon - Warp to the next zone if you've passed it15. Chloe - Attach to a hook16. Michael - An angel attack on the enemy17. Kanta - An attack with a shower of white paint18. Gussy Kenji - A short-range rapid punch19. Tamegoroh - Recover health slowly while still20. Shikigami - A projectile that uses up leaves21. Frankensteiny - Increase movement speed 1 level22. Ponchi - Block forwards23. Konchi &#8211; A projectile arrow24. Chimi-Moryo - Projectile that slows down enemies (uses up pebbles)25. Shaolin - A shockwave attack26. Black Raven - Increase furyoku recovery speed 3 levels27. Tao the Great - full screen massive damage attack28. Ian - Increase attack power 1 level29. Nizba - Increase defense power 1 level30. Dreisa - Increase max health 1 level31. Yopia - Increase furyoku recovery speed 1 level32. Badbh - Thaw out33. Vodianoi - Reduces water resistance34. Deht the Viking - Stop slipping on icy surfaces35. Gororo - More powerful version of Nipopo Punch 36. Zenki - Block attacks from the front37. Kohki - Block attacks from behind38. Golem &#8211; A powerful beam projectile39. Orona - Stop an enemy's movement40. Pascal Avaf - Pause in mid-air41. Yamagami - 4 balls of fire spin around the player42. Gundari - Occasionally stops effect of enemy attack43. Raphael - Lengthen the time footholds take to fall44. Gabriel - Make light in the darkness45. Uriel - Reduce damage done when falling in a pit46. Metatoron - Reduce damage from needle piles47. Sariel - Reduce damage from fire48. Remiel - Reduce damage from electricity49. Mash - Decides if an enemy is guilty or innocent50. Blaumro - Reduce the enemy's health with a whip51. Footballer - A body slam to damage the enemy52. Shion-Shion - An attack with disc attached to a chain53. Blocks - Produce blocks which can step onto54. Jen - Defeat 50 enemies to make a wish come true55. Ashcroft - Attack by throwing spears56. Jack - Attack with throwing knives57. Chuck - Attack with a ring laser58. Carlos &amp; Joao &#8211; Attack with an exploding cactus59. Antonio - Sets a small doll on the rampage (Uses up dolls)60. Jose - Sets a small doll on the rampage (Uses up dolls)61. Pancho - Sets a small doll on the rampage (Uses up dolls)62. Zapata - Sets a small doll on the rampage (Uses up dolls)63. Miguel - Sets a small doll on the rampage (Uses up dolls)64. Magnescope - Look around65. Mama - Turn into a small sheep and move at high speed66. Cifer - Stop the enemy moving with a hammer attack67. Spirit of Fire - Recover health each time you kill an enemy68. Matamune - Full screen sword attack that does massive damageSpirit Combos1. Revival (Ian, Nizba, Dreisa, Yophia)When you die 4 spirits take you to the world-map and recover all your health instead of giving you a game-over screen. This is a good way to avoid losing life as long as you have it as one of your 4 sets.2. Totem Attack (Silver Shield, Silver Tail, Silver Wing, Silver Horn, Silver Rod)This is a powerful beam attack that shows the player with large shoulder cannon.3. Grand Halo Blade (Amidamaru, Mosuke)It is much like regular Halo Bump attack however, done 4 consecutive times.4. Cavalry Charge (Bason, Black Raven)The player with rush forward as long as the attack button is pressed, attacking rapidly.5. Grande Phantasma (Antonio, Jose, Pancho, Zapata, Miguel)A skeleton hand holding a big knife comes from the opposite side of the player and attack full screen, this is the most powerful move in the game.6. Ray of Light (Michael and any 4 of these 6 spirits : Gabriel, Raphael, Uriel, Sariel, Remiel, Metatoron)This is a full screen attack where angles appear and fly all over the screen attacking everything they touch.7. Jaguar Man (Mic and Pascal Avaf)You can only activate it while jumping, when you do, the player wears a jaguar suit and will slowly fall down and you can move the player left or right until he touches the ground.</plot>
	<releasedate>9/11/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.2</rating>
	<VideoURL>CnXABVueR4s</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3680</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919443-shaman-king-master-of-spirits</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/shaman-king-master-of-spirits</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shaman-king-master-of-spirits/3030-19486/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2209417-box_skmos.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3680-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59668-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/250320-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/250321-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/250322-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/250323-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/250324-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/250325-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/250326-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/250327-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/250328-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/250329-shaman-king-master-of-spirits-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/x6DBSyY.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3680.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In this game you play Yoh Asakura from the Shaman King japanese Manga and TV Anime series. Much like the anime and manga it is based on, is centered on Yoh Asakura and his battles to become Shaman King. The story within the game plays like a "Sidestory", referring to elements within the story of both the manga and anime while not conforming to any particular continuity. In it, Yoh's goal is to stop the Guardian of Demons from being resurrected by a gang of rogue shaman.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/062c96b2-51dd-4840-b732-60f832e07422.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/34eb585c-9596-470c-ae3f-929556e8f16d.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/08cc7bff-f37e-45d6-a762-ea9c51089c43.png</clearlogo2>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>