<Game>
	<Name>Shining Soul (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>IntroductionShining Soul makes the player take the role of a warrior torn between two directly opposing groups: The Dark Dragons and the Shining Fleet. The game lets the wizard choose to pertain to one of four classes: fighter, wizard, archer, or dragonute. The game allows high customization of the character, including weapons, clothing, color schemes, armor etc. The game allows link up play with up to four players, to fight in cooperative combat. The gameplay presents itself as a typical hack-n-slash RPG, with the opbective of collecting gold, clothes, weapons etc. as well as constant hunting for experience points to level up.  The game has a sequel called, simply   Shining Soul II, in which the core gameplay remains practically the same but many extra features ($ new classes, collectible cards, arena, side quests etc.) are added. Classes &amp; skillsKnight: Sword - sword power up, charge attack Axe - axe power up,  charge attack Spear - spear power up,  charge attack Def build-up - improves defenseEfficacy - increases recovery power of itemsMentalpower - raises immunity against attacksCold res - improves defense against coldLightning res - improves defense against thunder   Wizard:  Blaze - spell that casts balls of fireFreeze - spell that casts balls of iceSpark - spell that casts thunderboltsHellblast - spell that casts tornadoInferno - spell that reduces area to ashesRes - improves resistance against magicHeal - spell that recovers HPSlow - Spell that slows down enemies     Archer:Bow - bow power up, charge attackSpear - spear power up, charge attackLeap - raises weapons' throwing rangeCritical - increases chance of critical hitHealing - HO recovers graduallyAnti-flying - more damage to flying enemiesFire res - improves defense against flameCold res -  imporoves defense against coldDragonute:Axe - axe power up, charge attackFlail - flail power up, charge attackBrak armor - lowers enemies' defenseEmit - counterattacks with brathDef build-up - improves defenseUndead - more damage to undead enemiesFire res - improves defense against flameLightning res - improves defense against thunder  Stages &amp; bossesArea 1Name: Beast Mountain Number of levels: 3Boss: Beast King Titan fighter.Area 2Name: Labyrinth Death Shadow Nuumber of levels: 7Boss: Titan Fighter - a mighty war machine that shoots energy beams out of his eye-like sockets. After the armor is destroyed you fight the ball-formed core that uses rolling attacks.      BulzamArea 3Name: Equal DungeonNumber of levels: 10Boss: Bulzam - the first dragon general. Teleports himself around the room and shoots multiple fireballs.      Michaela.Area 4Name: Forest of Another WorldNumber of levels: 10Boss: Michaela - the second dragon general. Uses her own replicas to attack the hero with ice missiles.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/9/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus U.S.A., Inc., SEGA of America, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3683</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/537260-shining-soul</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/shining-soul</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shining-soul/3030-16201/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2525264-box_ssoul.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3683-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/26705-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63764-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-screenshot-it-has-begun.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63766-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select-from-four-characters.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63767-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-screenshot-introduction.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63768-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-introduction-continues.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63769-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-screenshot-moving-around-the.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63770-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-screenshot-battling-some-enemies.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63771-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-screenshot-these-doors-take-you.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63772-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-screenshot-open-chests-to-see.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63774-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-screenshot-when-you-level-up.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/63775-shining-soul-game-boy-advance-screenshot-here-is-your-status.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3683-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/9qJNVzx.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3683.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Enter a world of magic and mystery, where your closest allies may sometimes turn out to be your worst enemies. Shining Soul puts you in the middle of a desperate struggle between the Dark Dragon and a group of warriors known as the Shining Fleet. In the final stage of the war, you can play one of four character classes: fighter, wizard, archer, or dragonute. Customize your character's color schemes, weapons, and armor, and then explore the world of Shining Soul either alone or with three of your friends.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c0f20727-0faf-4a01-a4ac-f8425ef7d410.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d97794a-726a-4c66-ab83-aacbb90aa321.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/059bafe2-8f63-41f3-a87e-a2d055698635.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8bafc0c0-000a-4f6e-ae5f-41ac297d9f9d.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e5e3b052-9248-44a3-9682-47acb3e2c87c.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>