<Game>
	<Name>Shin Megami Tensei (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Story:From the Mega CD introPlayers take the role of a nameless high-school student who attempts to defend Tokyo from an invasion of demons that threaten to turn the city into the next battlefield for the endless struggle between the forces of Law and Chaos. There are a variety of demons based on several religious mythologies, and each family has its own racial alignment. Players will develop a Lawful, Chaotic or Neutral alignment over the course of the story, depending on the actions they take and the demons they befriend or fight. Different alignments will result in entirely different endings for the game, all of them equally valid - although the sequel assumes the player completed the Neutral ending.The story begins, after a strange dream sequence, with the discovery of a computer program e-mailed to the protagonist by a mysterious ally, allowing him to communicate with demons and summon ones allied with him via his hand-held computer, or COMP. Shortly afterward, missing persons are reported, fellow students go missing, and the protagonist is attacked by the demons which he so conveniently now has the capability of conversing with and summoning. Attempting to unravel the reasons behind all of this (and save Tokyo) is what makes up a majority of the story.Gameplay:The game's first-person dungeon crawling.Movement is split into two areas. When outdoors, the game presents an overhead view of a map of the local area, and the player can move the icon representing the protagonist around the streets and into buildings. Random encounters with demons begin to hinder your movement here after an early plot point. W hen indoors, all movement takes place in a first-person view remeniscent of old PC RPGs like Eye of the Beholder.Encounters with demons begin with an opportunity to attempt to talk before fighting. Depending on what the player says, the demons may decide to fight, run away, offer a bribe, or join the player's party and become an ally. What demons players battle and ally with will partially influence their alignment, which will affect how other demons react to them in the future. Demons whose alignment oppose the player will never join their party. Alignment can also affect what items can be equipped and what bosses are fought.A pixie appears!Once combat is initiated, you select actions for each of your party members to take. Turns occur simultaneously for both sides, with each combatant taking their action in the order of initiative as determined by their speed and other similar factors. The protagonist cannot use any spells, but most of the other characters and demons have some form of magic at their disposal. Killing a demon nets you some experience and money, and each time you gain enough experience to increase your level, you can select a character stat to increase. Although spells are specific to each character, all other statistics are determined by you during the dream sequence, which means you can decide whether your team consists of glass cannon wizards or melee bruisers as you like. Players should take note, however, that this is an Atlus RPG and hence isn't very forgiving.There are also some stores in the city where you can purchase weapons, armor, or usable items as needed. A bit into the game, you can purchase some additional items with more useful traits, although they are very expensive.Demon CompendiumDemons are ordered from highest level to lowest. Races are organized by affinity (Light-Neutral-Dark) and alignment (Law-Neutral-Chaos). Demons marked with (MCD) only appear in the Mega CD version of the game.Deity (L-L)82 Vishnu72 Indra70 Brahma(n) (MCD)64 Fudo Myo-o60 Baal (MCD)58 Odin51 Arahabaki42 Freyr (MCD)40 LokiMegami (L-L)64 Lakshmi50 Kikuri-Hime46 Urd (MCD)39 Sarasvati34 Verdandi (MCD)28 Kushinada-Hime22 Skuld (MCD)16 Ame no UzumeSeraph (L-L)96 Gabriel91 Raphael83 UrielDivine (L-L)67 Cherub61 Throne52 Dominion46 Virtue40 Power34 Archangel14 AngelAvian (L-L)72 Garuda65 Yatagarasu57 Phoenix52 Toufei (MCD)47 Jatayu36 Feng HuangHoly (L-L)41 Xuanwu38 Qilin31 Pabilsag22 Bai Ze17 UnicornAvatar (L-N)62 Barong55 Chimera54 Sphinx (MCD)52 Narasimha50 Pegasus (MCD)46 Bastet (MCD)42 NandiElement (L-N)40 Salamander30 Undine25 Sylph20 Gnome17 Flaemis14 Aquans11 Aeros8 ErthysOmega (L-C)88 Shiva80 Mahakala73 Wu Kong67 Indrajit60 Yama53 Ravana47 AgniKishin (L-C)75 Bishamonten68 Nio65 Take-Mikazuchi63 Kagutsuchi59 Jikokuten57 Koumokuten55 Zouchouten46 Nagasunehiko43 Take-Minakata38 Oumononushi31 Kotoshironushi23 HitokotonushiDragon (L-C)74 Ananta70 Tiamat (MCD)67 Maya62 Baek Yong56 Vritra49 Ganga44 CoatlicueYoma (N-L)63 Hanuman60 Ganesha58 Efreet (MCD)55 Kinnara52 Tengu50 Choronzon43 Ongkot41 Loa37 Watcher34 Isora21 Apsaras15 KinnariFlight (N-L)46 Siren34 Badb Catha18 Kokakuchou7 HarpyJirae (N-L)50 Atlas47 Giant43 Sarutahiko35 Kwancha26 Dwarf19 Buccaboo16 Tsuchigumo12 Fachen6 Kobold4 Knocker2 BrownieMessian (N-L)53 Scanner37 Magus22 Temple Knight18 AdeptFairy (N-N)64 Oberon61 Senko59 Cu Chulainn57 Dullahan (MCD)55 Tam Lin46 Troll40 Senri36 Hobgoblin30 Banshee (MCD)26 Elf23 Kelpie18 Rusalka15 Gandharvha14 Cait Sith (MCD)12 Dryad9 Pyro Jack8 Jack Frost6 Goblin2 PixieBeast (N-N)63 Great Pascal (MCD)50 Gryphon43 Cerberus43 Pascal (MCD)40 Rakcharango38 Orthrus35 Tammuz28 Stonka19 Nekomata16 Tanki12 Cu Sith8 SankiTouki (N-N)60 Talos (MCD)52 Yaksa50 Minotaur (MCD)46 Ne Zha40 Mezuki39 Gozuki30 Yaksini14 SpartoiLycan (N-N)41 Werewolf23 Werecat5 WeredogFemme (N-C)69 Kali61 Hariti56 Hel (MCD)54 Rangda49 Scylla45 Dakini39 Gorgon36 Taraka33 LamiaNight (N-C)62 Vampire54 Succubus49 Incubus44 Calon Arang35 Celuluk28 Lilim24 Nightmare14 Cyak7 ImpFallen (N-C)67 Sargatanas (MCD)66 Flauros63 Fleurety60 Abaddon57 Samael51 Marchosias48 Ose42 Decarabia39 Leonard35 Orobas31 Sitri27 Berith18 Forneus12 Gamigin8 AndrasSnake (N-C)61 Pendragon57 Yamata no Orochi53 Itzamna50 Quetzalcoatl46 Yurlungur41 Naga RajaBrute (N-C)49 Shuten-douji44 Turdak38 Ibaragi-douji34 Purski24 Momunofu13 Bogle10 AzumiGaean (N-C)56 Assassin52 Yamihoushi40 Onijorou27 Hakaisou20 Shokei Rider15 TokkoutaiVile (D-L)71 Taotie69 Seth (MCD)66 Orcus62 Tezcatlipoca55 Amon (MCD)44 MishagujiRaptor (D-L)53 Hresvelgr42 Gurr20 Furiae8 Fu XiJaki (D-L)53 Girimehkala51 Cyclops48 Rakshasa45 Barbegazi37 Lakhe28 Wendigo11 Orc8 Donkou5 GremlinMech (D-L)32 T95D25 T95C/P21 T93G15 Bitball11 Bigfoot2 DummyWilder (D-N)62 Fenrir51 Kraken47 Manticore44 Tamamo27 Atsuyu15 NueDead (D-N)18 Corpse10 Army Zombie7 Bodyconian6 Zombie Cop3 Obattallion2 Lady Zombie1 ZombieTyrant (D-C)99 Beelzebub95 Satanachia (MCD)90 Astaroth (MCD)87 Surt (MCD)85 Arioch (MCD)82 Mara80 Asmodeus (MCD)78 Bael77 Pazuzu (MCD)75 Mephisto (MCD)74 DagonDrake (D-C)60 Fafnir58 Midgardsormr (MCD)54 Serpent51 Basilisk43 Wyvern37 Wyrm30 Cockatrice22 WormHaunt (D-C)54 Lich46 Vetala40 Sunni Yaka35 Sawo Bhaku25 Baykok22 Man Eater17 Ghoul7 Oshichi5 PretaSpirit (D-C)44 Legion29 Phantom23 Larva19 Pisaca14 Lemur9 Shade4 GhostFoul (D-C)44 Backbeard32 Black Ooze13 Slime4 Mouryou2 Yakuza1 ThugFiend99 David99 Pale Rider99 DaisoujouBoss (1)10 Orias12 Ame no Sakugami15 Douman28 Gotou30 Thor32 Red Phantom32 Blue Phantom32 Zenki32 GokiBoss (2)43 Take-Minakata48 Arachne46 Nebiros52 Belial58 Security System70 Kazfiel80 Haniel77 Yama72 Nio71 Ladon81 Echidna92 Vishnu69 Ravana81 IndrajitBoss (3)96 Gabriel83 Uriel91 Raphael85 Arioch98 Astaroth100 Surt99 Law Hero99 Chaos Hero80 Lilith108 Beelzebub116 Michael110 AsuraTranslation into EnglishThe full translation patch for Shin Megami Tensei was released by Aeon Genesis on June 30th of 2002. It includes a translation of the game manual which is virtually necessary to play the game.Referenceshttp://www.atlus.com/smt/history.htmlhttp://agtp.romhack.net/project.php?id=smtCheat: A-MODE DDSAfter you save the game for the first time, A-Mode DDS will be unlocked from your main screen, if you choose to go back to the main screen after saving. More options in A-Mode DDS will be unlocked after you beat the game once.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<VideoURL>gnmNHWClXMA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20004</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/583327-shin-megami-tensei</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/shin-megami-tensei</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shin-megami-tensei/3030-19250/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/20004-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/20004-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/45606-shin-megami-tensei-sega-cd-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/20004-1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/20004-2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/20004-3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/screenshots/20004-4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/112552-shin-megami-tensei-sega-cd-screenshot-the-famous-smt-symbol.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/112526-shin-megami-tensei-sega-cd-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/112524-shin-megami-tensei-sega-cd-screenshot-the-insane-computer.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/112525-shin-megami-tensei-sega-cd-screenshot-one-of-the-several-intro.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/112523-shin-megami-tensei-sega-cd-screenshot-another-expressive-picture.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/112527-shin-megami-tensei-sega-cd-screenshot-character-information.jpg</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/20004.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The story is set in Tokyo in the year 199X. Demons from the nether-realm of Makai have found their way back to Earth, and as such have upset the balance of power. A charismatic Japanese leader attempts a coup d'état using these demons as a potent military force, forcing America to intervene with its military. The player, as the hero, becomes involved when sent a Devil Summoning Program via email which allows him to converse with and recruit demons to fight for him, storing them as digital data on his computer. In the aftermath of the ensuing destruction, the hero must decide what kind of world should be created on its ruins. Will he side with the angels and create a kingdom of absolute order that would last for a thousand years, or will he side with the demons and bring about an eternal anarchy, or will he choose neither, and destroy everyone who opposes him?</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c999d7ad-c1d1-4cd6-853f-48574c18d41d.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f601f86e-2dec-47cf-b935-a17d7959d631.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5712d380-3cb7-4aef-b4d4-044413d37d75.jpg</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c5f09292-341e-471d-bad2-7b2c42fc3a1b.jpg</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c7c336c2-a1e3-44c7-899b-1ad55f8b48ed.jpg</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/044986f8-8d25-4da2-9640-4480d68e8aad.jpg</snapshot14>
	<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
</game>