<Game>
	<Name>Shining Force - Resurrection of the Dark Dragon (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Differences from OriginalResurrection of the Dark Dragon is a complete remake of the original Genesis title. It features reworked graphics, audio, and a retranslated script. For the most part the gameplay remains faithful to the original. One substantial difference is that the main protagonist, Max, has dialogue. In the original, Max was a silent protagonist.   Card Quest  Max can also collect character cards that have the different members of both the Shining Force and the game's bosses.  Each card has a specific character or monster on it. These cards can be used by the new character Mawlocke for two inherent features:  Ability and Effect    New Characters Also, there are three new characters:  Narsha, Mawlocke, and Zuika.    Narsha may be the best mage in the entire game. She is very easy to level up, and each of her spells are very useful. She learns Boost, Step,  Attack, and Aura.  Not only is she decked out with powerful spells, she also has high MP, high defense, high magic defense, and average attack. She is tank with the some of the best magical spells in the game. Many believe that she is a broken character. Her only weakness is that her awesome spells cost a ton of MP (some weakness, huh).    Zuika is an average to above average addition to your team. He has good attack power, high speed, and average defense. Zuika has a special ability. When his HP gets low, his attack power is boosted. He is a basic risk/reward character. Most users will find his ability helpful, but there are better characters to bring into battle. Zuika is a weaker version of Zylo with a bonus ability. Mawlocke is a very useful character because he can use the character cards. He can take on the individual stats of the character on the card, he can use the special ability granted by the card, or he can use the card so the character can move two times in one round. </plot>
	<releasedate>6/8/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.4</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>LEzEV74ZMpo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3682</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/918893-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon/3030-11215/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2525249-box_sfrotdd.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/JLZb7Gw.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/59937-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92437-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92439-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92438-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92440-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92441-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92442-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92443-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92444-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92445-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/92446-shining-force-resurrection-of-the-dark-dragon-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3682-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/NakXGay.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3682.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Shining Force is a turn-based tactical RPG. Battles take place in square grids, and each unit occupies one square. Each unit can move up to a fixed amount of squares along the battlefield, determined by its Move statistic. Depending on its location relative to enemies and to allies, a unit can also perform one action: attack, cast a spell, use an item, or search the area. Some commands, such as equipping or dropping items, don't count as actions. The order of turns is determined by the unit's agility score and a random seed. In Shining Force, each allied unit is represented by a character with his or her own background and personality, much like in the Fire Emblem series. Although there are no "generic" units, except on the enemy side, most characters contribute little or nothing to the plot upon joining the player army. Each allied unit also has a class, which defines a set of abilities for that unit and determines the spells and equipment they have access to. A unit can be promoted to another class at any level between 10 or 20. Upon promotion the character's level resets to 1 and statistics are reduced by a fixed amount, although they begin higher if the character had been promoted at a higher level. Battle goals for the player are fairly simple: kill all enemies, kill the enemies' leader, or advance to a town or landmark. The enemy side wins if they kill the player's leader, Max, or if the player chooses to escape the battle by casting Egress. Even if the player army is defeated, the player can recover allies and retry the battle. The Force keeps any experience that is obtained, regardless of the battle's outcome. Thus, there is no Game Over, and the player's army gets stronger even upon its defeat, although Max's death results in the player losing half of their money.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/87661be6-66db-4d51-90d0-e98c8fd431ea.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cc82a0d3-b604-411a-86f1-09af33fd89e7.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6e867bb9-baa2-43b6-8fb8-a50b92f61516.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b8bef19f-fcd2-460c-8b9c-95c3499ec2ea.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>