<Game>
	<Name>Sigma Star Saga (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Ian Recker, a spy for Earth, is sent undercover as a prisoner so that he can become enlisted in the Krill army.  He is suited up with a parasitic suit of armor that gives him enhanced strength and the ability to merge with Krill ships, which are living organisms.  However, he soon discovers that all is not as it seems in this war, and Recker must decide which side he is fighting for.Sigma Star Saga is a hybrid of the side-scrolling shooter and RPG genres.  Players interact with characters and explore the overworld, and are frequently 'summoned' by random ships for battles.  To successfully complete a battle, the player must defeat a preset amount of enemies, and they gain experience with each enemy defeated.  As players explore the overworld, they can also discover Gun Data, which can be used to customize the player's shot with over 15,000 different weapon combinations using abilities such as rapid fire, vertical shot, and experience gain.Cheat: New Game +To unlock New Game +, beat the game and wait through the credits. At the end, the game will prompt you to save. Do so, and the next time you start the game the completed save file will have a gun data icon by it. New Game + allows you to replay the game with all of your old gun data, and gives you access to several new endings.Cheat: New Game +In the final battle with psyme she is in a battle worm and you have to fight her. If you only shoot out the three cannons on top she remains alive to the end. But if you shoot out the eyes on the bottom of the screen she dies, and is out of the last cut scene.Cheat: New Game +Whether Scarlet appears in the ending or not depends if you pick up the Virus while on earth the second time or not. You can find it in the room above the one where Zart and Tierney were working. You cannot return here after you have left, so decide what ending you want here.Only available in New Game +Cheat: New Game +Defeat the game once to unlock the Sigma Ship in random encounters.Cheat: Final Boss trickThe final battle with the overlord can be very difficult. However, there is one trick to beating him. Equip a gun type that can shot at a down-left angle. Then simply fly right in front of his forehead, the only place none of his attacks can reach.Cheat: Final Boss trickOnce you obtain the Girl Wings, you can use them to avoid random battles. You cannot enter a random battle while hovering. So if you repeatedly use the Girl Wings as a means of travel instead of walking normally, you'll never be summoned to play a random level.</plot>
	<releasedate>16/8/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Namco Hometek Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3504</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/925863-sigma-star-saga</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/sigma-star-saga</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sigma-star-saga/3030-3955/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3504-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3504-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/57463-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150581-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-screenshot-nice-graphic.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150582-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-screenshot-outro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150583-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-screenshot-hero-is-kind-of.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150584-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-screenshot-and-from-the-rear.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150585-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-screenshot-talking.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150586-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-screenshot-fighting-on-the.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150587-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-screenshot-kill-all-enem.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150588-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-screenshot-boss-fight.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150589-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-screenshot-stats.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/150590-sigma-star-saga-game-boy-advance-screenshot-equipment.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/X27gTkB.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3504.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>When a double-agent's allegiance begins to waver, the galaxy finds itself in a precarious position. Humanity is struggling to survive against the Krill onslaught. Ian Recker, a decorated pilot, goes undercover to investigate the Krill's secrets, but finds himself trapped in a moral dilemma. The first RPG on Game Boy Advance to combine a deep storyline and well-developed characters with a space-shooter battle engine. Customizable weapons including over 15,000 Gun Data combinations. Branching storyline with four ending and 20+ hours of gameplay.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b28a744b-8ef8-46ef-884c-9662a0e089f7.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1fec9e2b-e0e1-4122-923b-075ea1d6de64.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f52bc5a6-02c8-4abc-a9cc-3ef9c069f286.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ebf4622f-0e2a-43e4-8cc2-d508a1f96b23.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/30fb7a12-4e4b-4635-850b-2ff5c8e7f2e0.png</snapshot12>
	<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d4ad858-04fd-467a-8c2f-b28b85e48cfb.png</snapshot13>
	<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c607f412-3f98-40cc-9752-527a193e76ca.png</snapshot14>
	<snapshot15>http://images.launchbox-app.com/39ff94e6-b37c-4a95-9498-044054660154.png</snapshot15>
	<snapshot16>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2723797c-4872-40a4-81ba-550046dacf69.png</snapshot16>
	<Publisher>Atari</Publisher>
</game>