<Game>
	<Name>Sitting Ducks (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>Welcome to the world of Sitting Ducks, where life is good, food is plentiful, and alligators are lurking in the neighboring Swampwood. You can play as one alligator, Aldo, and his friend, Bill the Duck, as they take on a variety of challenges. In more than 20 different missions, you'll do everything from racing Vespa scooters and ice-skating to playing soccer and water polo. With each event, crowds of ducks (each duck with its own personality) may form around you--but try not to become nervous.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/915089.htmlCheat: Level passwordsEnter the following at the password screen:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Hip Games</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>28207</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/915089-sitting-ducks</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/28207-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/1/4/1/54141_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/5/2/gfs_47630_2_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/8/2/gfs_47630_2_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/3/2/gfs_47630_2_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/2/2/gfs_47630_2_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/9/2/gfs_47630_2_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>Welcome to the whimsical world of Sitting Ducks, where life is good, food's a plenty, and alligators are lurking in neighboring Swampwood. One bird stands out amongst the flock: Bill. He is a quirky, smaller than average duck with a big imagination and a secret fun loving side. Along with his alligator friend Aldo, Bill embarks on 20 different missions in this whimsical action game. Play as Bill the Duck and Aldo the Alligator from the TV series and explore colorful and detailed levels.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9f4325ac-7563-4efa-89bd-5486bb7b5433.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/70b8b7c9-5ab1-4427-9a9a-1fa64caf8b0e.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Hip Games</Publisher>
</game>