<Game>
	<Name>Snood 2 - On Vacation (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>The sequel to Snood keeps the gameplay from the original game but takes it to locations around the world. In this puzzle game players need to line up groups of three or more adjacent Snoods to remove them, similar to the Bust-a-move series. They are launched from the Snood-o-matic cannon at the bottom of the screen. For every Snood launched, the danger level increases and causes the Snoods at the top to move downwards. When the bottom is reached, the game is lost.There are five game modes available: World Tour, Classic, Puzzle, Journey and Armageddon. Four additional bonus games can be unlocked: Snood Ball, Snood Sideways, Snood Grab and Snood Stack, all with small twists on the classic gameplay. Multiplayer is available as well.Cheat: Password.Input the password at the password screen to activate the cheats.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Destination Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>1.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>26176</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929551-snood-2-on-vacation</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/snood-2-on-vacation</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/snood-2-on-vacation/3030-11242/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/561/214428-snood_2.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463307-snood-2-on-vacation-game-boy-advance-screenshot-language-selection.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463308-snood-2-on-vacation-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463309-snood-2-on-vacation-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463310-snood-2-on-vacation-game-boy-advance-screenshot-available.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463311-snood-2-on-vacation-game-boy-advance-screenshot-first-stop.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463312-snood-2-on-vacation-game-boy-advance-screenshot-first-usa.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463313-snood-2-on-vacation-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-the-game.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463314-snood-2-on-vacation-game-boy-advance-screenshot-if-we-take.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463315-snood-2-on-vacation-game-boy-advance-screenshot-level-statistics.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/a/7/gfs_69472_1_1.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>We have arrived at Snoodville and the action is all go, go, go! Classic Snood turned sideways is a massive issue as all the snoods fall to the floor. Once they meet up with three of their own color, all the action starts to happen. Clear the board of all the snoods in time limit and other play modes. No more snoods available !! What do we do now? We fire a grappling hook to hook the snoods and pull them back to snood central! Then fire them to where we want them to be to make them fall from the board. Circular snood will also get you in a spin! Fire the snoods up to the highest levels, but watch out -- there are no straight sides to bounce off! You are in a circular tube and the snoods will bounce and fly everywhere if your angles are wrong. Just when you think you have the game beaten the whole world rotates and leaves you fighting to stay in the game!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6badd5f2-3e69-4183-883a-b376a6f92dbb.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/01309754-cbfc-45bd-b2dc-7afb9c24a814.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2447f942-8340-4585-bb5e-e7a6b5bd252c.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Destination Software, Inc.</Publisher>
</game>