<Game>
	<Name>Sonic The Hedgehog - Genesis (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This is the first of many games starring Sega's premier rodent, Sonic. It's a side scrolling platform game with a difference: speed. Sonic rushes through levels with incredible speed, allowing him to traverse loops and jumps with ease.The plot of the game is simple. The evil Dr. Robotnik has captured many of Sonic's animal friends, and trapped them inside robots. Fortunately, Sonic can free his friends by destroying the robots with his spin attack. Meanwhile, Dr. Robotnik is trying to control the all-powerful chaos emeralds. Sonic must grab them before he does in the 3-d rotating bonus levels.Sonic the Hedgehog is a significant game because it gave Sega it's first real mascot, and established the Genesis as the video game system with "attitude."http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/sonic-the-hedgehogCheat: Completing the Juke BoxIn when you first unlock the juke box only half of it to get the other half read below.Cheat: Completing the Juke BoxBeat the Final ZoneCheat: Completing the Juke BoxBeat the game with all 6 Chaos Emeralds</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA</Developer>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<VideoURL>z8W6MuuKCB8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>21236</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/934134-sonic-the-hedgehog-genesis</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/21236-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/4/5/77945_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/f/5/gfs_77475_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/2/5/gfs_77475_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/9/5/gfs_77475_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/8/5/gfs_77475_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/3/5/gfs_77475_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>In honor of its beloved mascot's 15th birthday, SEGA brings the game that started it all to GBA Sonic The Hedgehog. The game will feature two new additions to the classic 1991 debut, including Sonic's famous Spin-Dash move and a new save ability. Burst the videgame speed barrier wide-open with Sonic the Hedgehog. Blaze by in a blur using the super sonic spin attack. Loop the loop by defying gravity. Plummet down tunnels. Then dash to safety with Sonic's power sneakers. All at a frenzied pace. Sonic has an attitude that just won't quit!</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/de40e44f-1a57-485d-bccc-b10091613586.jpg</boxart3>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>