<Game>
	<Name>Sonic Advance (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Sonic Advance is the first game in the GBA Sonic Advance spin-off series, which is also the first Sonic game to be released on a Nintendo console. As well as Sonic, the player can also select between Knuckles, Tails and Amy Rose.The game was followed by two direct sequels: Sonic Advance 2 and Sonic Advance 3. The game was also converted to the Nokia N-Gage, where it was renamed Sonic N. A Japan-only Android version also exists.Sega's Move to Third-PartySonic plays in a city-themed level.When the Sega Dreamcast had to be discontinued from low sales, Sega changed their plans and became a third-party publisher, announcing to make games for systems other than Sega consoles. The Game Boy Advance was the first console Sega approached, and began work on a brand new Sonic game by hiring the developer Dimps to work under the name of Sonic Team. Dimps previously worked on Sonic Pocket Adventure for the NeoGeo Pocket Color, and its critical reaction deemed the studio qualified to do the game.Gameplay:Sonic Advance returns to the 2D gameplay of the Genesis originals, having Sonic get from the beginning to the end of the stage without dying and going as fast as possible. Enemies and barriers are spread out throughout the levels and Sonic has to collect rings to keep from being killed. Every zone contains at least one hidden 'Special Spring' which will take Sonic to the Special Stage. Completing all 7 Special Stages will unlock the final boss battle and an alternate ending.The levels are arranged into Zones, and in those zones are two Acts. The second act ends with a Boss Fight against one of Dr. Eggman's crazy inventions. Four characters are available to replay the levels, and their different characteristics changes how to approach the level. The biggest addition is the inclusion of Amy Rose, who is the hardest character to maneuver because she is slower and cannot curl into a ball.ZonesNeo Green Hill ZoneNeo Green Hill ZoneSecret Base ZoneCasino ParadiseIce Mountain ZoneAngel Island ZoneEgg Rocket ZoneCosmic Angel ZoneX ZoneThe Moon ZoneCross-Game ConnectivityThe game's Tiny Chao Garden featured linkability with Sonic Adventure 2 Battle and Sonic Adventure DX, both for the Nintendo Gamecube. this allowed the trading of Chao, rings obtained in both games and items for use in either the tiny Chao garden featured in Sonic Advance, as well as Sonic Advance 2.Other FeaturesOther features included a time attack mode, as well as a 2 player mode. This had 2 styles, single cart and multi-cart play.Single cart play allowed players to search for as many rings as possible in a time limit on an enclosed field.Multi-cart play allowed players to race sonic 2-style in all of the levels.N-Gage VersionSonic N is basically a port of the Sonic Advance game that was released on the Game Boy Advance except for the exclusion of the Tiny Chao Garden. The game was a launch title for the Nokia N-Gage game deck. The game itself was on a MMC ROM, so when players saved there data it was saved on the card.The main problem people had was that it was running was a little slower than it should be as well as the resolution which was changed to be taller but not wider like the sonic games are normally displayed.CheatsHave Tails follow Sonic in story modeIn the character select menu, highlight Sonic, and press up, right, down, right, L, right, R, right, A. if entered correctly, the player will hear a chime. Then select any level as Sonic, and Tails will follow him around Sonic 2 style.Cheat: Play with Sonic &amp;amp; Tails in Story ModeGo to game start on the main menu, and select Sonic (don't press A, just make sure he is on your screen.)  When you do this, do the following: Cheat: Play with Sonic &amp;amp; Tails in Story Modeup, right, down, right, L, right, R right, A  Cheat: Play with Sonic &amp;amp; Tails in Story ModeYou should hear a chime like you just collected a ring letting you know the code was right.  Select a course (if you have that option) and have fun.  Cheat: Play with Sonic &amp;amp; Tails in Story ModeOh, by the way, the computer Tails isn't very smart, but it can be helpful.  (He doesn't Die.)Cheat: Duplicate ChaoYou must have a GBA, GBA to GCN link cable, two memory card with Chao garden saves, and this game. Send the Chao you want to duplicate to the GBA. It should say it's making a copy. Once you have the copy go to move. Move the duplicated Chao to the Garden in slot two. Now take the Chao out of the garden and put it in slot 1. Now take the other Chao from slot 2 and transfer it to slot 1. You now have two of the same Chao.Cheat: Duplicate ChaoRun up to the first yellow spring in the level (Just as the ground turns to pavement and grass) and jump to the right side of it. Push yourself against it, face right, and do a spin dash. Release to send Sonic/Tails/Knuckles spinning forward, while holding Right on the control pad, and hold it. You'll go through the two loops, but as you go downhill, your character will fly far right and off the screen. Keep holding Right untill the camera catches up with your character.Cheat: Chao memory tripDuring the chao memory game press the A button as your chao moves a card and it'll trip up. This can stop it from moving the card.Cheat: Chao memory tripNormally the sound test has 39 songs on it.  If you can beat (not just make it to) The Moon Zone, then the Sound Test will Have songs 40 (The Moon Zone), 41 (Sonic has cleared EXTRA), and 42 (Super Sonic Ending).</plot>
	<releasedate>4/2/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>SEGA of America, Inc., THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>yh86Uuj3I_U</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2346</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/516689-sonic-advance</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/sonic-advance</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sonic-advance/3030-14191/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1803644-box_sonica.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/zwWkskE.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/213026-sonic-advance-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24699-sonic-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24707-sonic-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24704-sonic-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-character-selection.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24700-sonic-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro-animation-frame.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24701-sonic-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-tiny-chao-mini-game.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24702-sonic-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-chao-in-action.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24703-sonic-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-amy-in-action.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24705-sonic-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-loopin-on-a-sunday.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24706-sonic-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-finished-well-act.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/2/23093/2714027-sonicadvance001.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2346-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2346-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2346-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2346-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2346-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/SjJMHyY.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2346.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>SONIC IS BACK TO SAVE THE WORLD! The evil Dr. Eggman is at it again, with a brand new scheme to trip up Sonic and his pals. Maneuver your way through obstacles, puzzles and traps to collect the Chao Emeralds and defeat the vile Dr. Eggman before it’s too late! -Play as Sonic, Knuckles, Tails, or Amy -Link up to 4 players on one Game Pak -Zip through levels filled with puzzles and traps at sonic speed -Exchange chao between the Game Boy Advance and the Sonic Adventure’ 2: Battle game on the Nintendo GameCube’</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>Ijgh5WE5K3g</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/f242ae32-8409-4d1f-a62e-d84cc10bbaa8.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/178e1fa1-e2e8-4477-ada5-5e4cd5015051.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1d28718f-59b4-4f4e-89a9-cf6223a0db64.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9883ce51-2fda-4589-ac17-9849c6836399.png</snapshot11>
	<Publisher>Sega</Publisher>
</game>