<Game>
	<Name>Spider-Man (France)</Name>
	<plot>Trouble's ahead for Peter Parker in Spider-Man's first appearance on the Game Boy Color: an explosion at Dr. Curt Conners' lab will lead him into a plot planned by a mysterious villain, involving the alien symbiote and several of Spidey's arch enemies.The game is a platformer, divided into several large levels. Progression is not strictly linear: some of the levels can be freely explored in any order before continuing with the story. Locations include the city, subway and sewers, the docks and a warehouse. The levels are usually crawling with enemies that Spider-Man can beat up with kicks and punches. Defeating them will eventually result in him gaining levels, becoming stronger and learning some new fighting moves.Spidey's special abilities come into play when he swings freely over the rooftops, clings to walls or throws web balls at enemies to immobilize them. His spider-sense will usually alert him when important locations or special obstacles are near.The game includes various boss fights with the likes of Venom, the Lizard and the Hobgoblin.http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-color/spider-man__Cheat: UnlockablesDo the things listed on the right to unlock the things on the left</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2000</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Activision</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3698</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/938109-spider-man-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/spider-man____</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spider-man-3/3030-5614/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3698-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3698-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34018-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-opening-cinematic.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34019-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34020-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-web-swinging.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34021-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-second-level.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177301-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-beating-up-some-thugs.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177303-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-spider-man-is-ready.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177304-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-catching-a-crook-just.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177305-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-get-cinematics.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177308-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-spider-man-can-fight.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/177309-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-does-whatever-a-spider.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3698-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3698-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3698-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3698-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3698.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Spider-Man, the classic comic book co-created by Stan Lee, is now a major motion picture. This conversion of the movie to the video game world takes the major storyline, characters and artwork of the Spider-Man movie and adds a lengthy backstory and new characters. The Green Goblin is the main villian here, and as Peter Parker you must defy gravity using your spider crawl, web-slinging and spider-sense abilities to track down Spidey's nemesis through the skyscapers of New York City. The major inclusion for this title over the previous Spider-Man series (on Playstation also by Activision) is aerial combat. Attack the enemy mid-air while web-slinging, rise and decend while swinging and banking around buildings create a greater emphasis on Spidey's greatest asset, the spider web.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/07d2b85e-3e77-4122-bc7c-a17e952f90fd.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/df6528e3-557c-42ad-9408-d1fc64300050.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/68cae734-8cf9-4617-b4b1-a7f988220596.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>