<Game>
	<Name>Spirits & Spells (USA)</Name>
	<plot>In Spirits and Spells the player takes the role of the two kids Alicia and Greg which visit a spooky old house with their friends. Unfortunately the Bogeyman steals the soles of their friends and turns them into stone - of course the two heroes have to get them back. So they visit the Land of Dead and have to survive a cemetery, a haunted house and the lab of a mad scientist (overall 15 stages).The player can switch instantly (but limited because it costs crystals which can be found in the levels) between the two characters which is often needed to progress in the game: both have distinct advantages and disadvantages. Alicia is disguised as a witch, is strong with the ice element, can attack from a range and doesn't take damage from long falls.  Greg on the other hand is the master of fire, is disguised as imp and has a super jump. Both have also a special attack which also cost crystals to perform. The gameplay is the usual platforming along with fighting enemies.The main difference to the console version is that the whole game is in 2D with different level design and less puzzle elements.Cheat: Level passwordsEnter the password on the password screen and you will be taken to the level listed.</plot>
	<releasedate>24/4/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>MTO Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<rating>3.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>25880</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589576-spirits-and-spells</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/spirits-and-spells</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spirits-and-spells/3030-38735/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/25880-1.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/196759-spirits-spells-gamecube-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/209653-spirits-spells-playstation-2-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2242267-40.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2242265-39.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2242264-37.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2242263-35.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2242262-33.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2242261-31.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2242260-29.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2242259-27.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2242258-25.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2242257-23.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Released in Europe as Castleween by Wanadoo, in Japan as Mahou no Pumpkin by MTO, Spirits &amp; Spells is an inch of horror, a dash of surprise and a whiff of fantasy: Halloween's magic formula. It's Halloween night and Alicia's and Greg's friends have all had a terrible curse put on them: their souls have been stolen! The two will have to cross over into the kingdom of the dead if they want to find their friends and free them from this dreadful spell. Features 20 monsters (skeletons, vampires, witches, devils and others) which you will have to avoid and/or fight, collect life and invincibility bonuses as well as precious gems across 12 levels.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/40fa64fa-ed6f-4d38-bcfd-002913bb26f4.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/396436c3-b795-40f5-abcc-64898ceeb161.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>DreamCatcher Interactive</Publisher>
</game>