<Game>
	<Name>SpongeBob's Atlantis SquarePantis (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Holy algae! SpongeBob and Patrick tumble upon the lost magical amulet that will take them to the legendary city of Atlantis. Players will join them and the rest of their Bikini Bottom pals as they ride on a magical bus for a soaking new adventure. Hoping to uncover the treasures of Atlantis in order to fulfill SpongeBob's dream of finding the "World's Oldest Bubble," players will control whether the city brings everything he desires, or if Plankton's evil plan will burst his bubble.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/939404.htmlCheat: Unlock Everything.First, you turn on the game, then, you go to the password screen in the main menu (you can't miss it) and put in this password. By doing this, you will unlock all worlds, all mini-games, the biggest life bar, the cut-scenes, the sound room, Invincible difficulty, and the credits. After you enter it, you will start at the last world, and will have the unlockables.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2007</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ</Developer>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>29264</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/939404-spongebobs-atlantis-squarepantis</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/29264-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/4/d/gfs_87422_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/9/d/gfs_87422_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/2/d/gfs_87422_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/3/d/gfs_87422_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/8/d/gfs_87422_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>SpongeBob's Atlantis SquarePantis will follow SpongeBob and the rest of the Bikini Gang as they leave Bikini Bottom and journey to the legendary city of Atlantis. Players will discover the treasures of Atlantis, while experiencing new game mechanics and multiplayer features.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/aa669d03-f0e6-4096-a56b-1101be6b9f96.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/06c41b6e-28b5-4a10-adcd-f27e03e0cb3d.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>