<Game>
	<Name>Sports Illustrated for Kids - Football (USA)</Name>
	<plot>A football game aimed at younger kids. Features player development, trading, team management, all mixed into arcade style play. The first multiplayer football game on the Game Boy Advance. Each athlete has three key statistics that define their abilities within the game: Strength, Speed and Agility. The stats can be improved through play, improving team overall. Choose a type of team, a team name, team color and uniform style. You'll see special effects. A player who gets faster will have smoke and flames under his feet when he runs. Dynamic cameras follow the action through entire game play, enhancing the 3D look and feel of the game. Unlock secret bonus stadiums and modifiers.Cheat: Cheat CodesSelect the ''Cheat Codes'' options from the team management menu in seaon mode and enter any of the following codes to add all star players to your team.Cheat: Raise Your StatsAfter you play a game in season mode, go to the newspaper and press A, B, A, A. Then, choose to either raise your offense speed by one, your defense strength by one, or your special teams agility by one. This may be repeated as many times as needed.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/8/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Simulation, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>BAM! Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3701</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/562722-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/sports-illustrated-for-kids-football</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/sports-illustrated-for-kids-football/3030-19324/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3701-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3701-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/155976-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/737715-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/737723-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/737724-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/737725-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/737726-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/737727-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/737728-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/737729-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/737730-sports-illustrated-for-kids-football-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3701-g.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>This is your team, and you can run it any way you see fit! Assemble your squad, come up with a menacing name, choose a style for your uniforms, and then put your athletes through a rigorous training camp in hopes of fielding the best bunch ever to hit the turf! There are no official licenses to stand in the way of the detailed action, leaving the burden on the game to deliver realistic gameplay at every turn. As your players become more experienced, their skill levels will increase and you’ll get a chance to see new special effects. There are tons of hidden bonuses such as power-ups and stadium improvements to be unlocked throughout the season, and each player is rated for speed agility, and strength. A unique rookie card system rewards all-stars with a little bit of fame, and 3D camera work captures all of the excitement from the opening kickoff to the awards ceremonies. Using a link cable, you can match up against a friend to see who has developed the most competitive team. If realistic football sounds like fun to you, give SPORTS ILLUSTRATED FOR KIDS a try.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82723e98-1ce3-43b2-b7a3-63cb56ea674f.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/20fc54db-888b-4e48-a5e3-1a7371037756.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Bam Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>