<Game>
	<Name>Spy Kids Challenger (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Do you have what it takes to become a Spy Kid like Juni and Carmen? Equipped with secret gadgets like spring bots and rocket torpedoes, you will train for top secret SPY KIDS missions. How well you perform in each high flying, deep-sea diving, canyon racing adventures will determine your rank in the OSS.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/569262.htmlCheat: Secret MenuWhen in Juggler, or Dragonfly press SELECT+A+B+R+L at the same time, and you will get access to a secret menu.In Juggler, you can adjust how many points you get for different things in the level, or adjust infinite lives, etc.  HINT: When adjusting points, hold L until the points go past zero, then hold R to get 99,999 points for each thing!WARNING:  Do not adjust "Jump velocity" past 3,500.  Otherwise you will start bouncing around the screen and your character will be uncontrollable.In Dragonfly, you can adjust the frequency that different monsters appear.Cheat: Secret MenuTHIS MENU IS NOT AVAILABLE IN MAGNA RACER</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Disney Interactive</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>26181</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/569262-spy-kids-challenger</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/26181-1.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/f/d/gfs_32412_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/2/d/gfs_32412_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/9/d/gfs_32412_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/8/d/gfs_32412_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/3/d/gfs_32412_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>You've been selected for Spy Training -- complete the fun and challenging trials and help Carmen and Juni out! How well you do in each training challenge determines your rank in the Secret Service known as OSS. The fun continues as long as you can -- with limitless obstacles, enemies, upgrades and power-ups.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/4234ff0d-8bbb-4b55-bb4e-c9942c039075.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e6c53448-affd-45cc-999c-42bd6117d416.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Disney Interactive Studios</Publisher>
</game>