<Game>
	<Name>Spy Hunter (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Evil multinational corporation, NOSTRA are ready to destroy the world and keep what's left, but as the Spy Hunter, it is your job to take them down, using all of the weapons available to you.In this complete remake of the classic 80's arcade game, you must ride through 7 real life locations in your G-6155 Interceptor, the most high tech car ever built. Weapons include built in machine guns, oil slicks, missiles and much more.Two major things happen to the Interceptor: When you hit the water, it transforms into a speed boat. When your shield dips lower then 50%, it transforms into a motorcycle or jet ski.http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/spyhunterCheat: PasswordsEnter one of the following as your name.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Mission Based</genre>
	<Developer>Midway</Developer>
	<rating>7.5</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>9yqDDdt04Ac</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3702</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/560855-spy-hunter</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/spyhunter</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spy-hunter/3030-14843/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3702-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3702-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/4/d/gfs_44926_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/9/d/gfs_44926_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/2/d/gfs_44926_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/3/d/gfs_44926_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/8/d/gfs_44926_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3702-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3702.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>One of history's best-loved arcade games shrinks down to fit in the palm of your hand. From the distinctive music to the climactic boat transformation, this translation does everything it can to replicate the original coin-op adventure, and loses none of the thrills. Driving the lightning-quick G-6155 Interceptor a vehicle that can switch from car to boat to motorcycle you'll try to destroy the N.O.S.T.R.A. organization before it destroys you. You'll use oil slicks, smoke screens, and missiles to knock your foes off the road, out of the air, and below the surface of the water. This version of SPYHUNTER actually serves as something of an update on the original, as there are seven real-world locales to test your resolve, and the gameplay is now mission based. The graphics have also gotten a bit of an overhaul, with visuals taking place in near 3D. Whether or not you had the pleasure of growing up with this game, there's nothing not to love about one of the original white-knuckle spy games.</Notes>
	<nPlayers>2</nPlayers>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7b1ac027-f2be-4723-9a17-dc2cbc2348d2.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a35eb462-4fcd-4108-8d2b-9e2804c84c9e.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a95d39ee-f298-4751-af2e-57120b4dc4e0.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Midway</Publisher>
</game>