<Game>
	<Name>Spy Hunter (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Evil multinational corporation, NOSTRA are ready to destroy the world and keep what's left, but as the Spy Hunter, it is your job to take them down, using all of the weapons available to you.In this complete remake of the classic 80's arcade game, you must ride through 7 real life locations in your G-6155 Interceptor, the most high tech car ever built. Weapons include built in machine guns, oil slicks, missiles and much more.Two major things happen to the Interceptor: When you hit the water, it transforms into a speed boat. When your shield dips lower then 50%, it transforms into a motorcycle or jet ski.http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/spyhunterCheat: PasswordsEnter one of the following as your name.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Driving, Racing, Mission Based</genre>
	<Developer>Midway</Developer>
	<rating>7.5</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>9yqDDdt04Ac</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3702</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/560855-spy-hunter</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/spyhunter</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spy-hunter/3030-14843/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2285699-box_sh.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3702-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/4/d/gfs_44926_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/9/d/gfs_44926_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/2/d/gfs_44926_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/5/3/d/gfs_44926_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/c/8/d/gfs_44926_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3702-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3702.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>SpyHunter is an enhanced remake and sequel of the 1983 arcade game for the PlayStation 2, Xbox, GameCube, Game Boy Advance, Microsoft Windows and Mac OS X. In the original Spy Hunter, a popular arcade game, the player drives a souped-up spy car with Bond fittings. While the original was viewed from high above, Midway revamped it with next generation graphics and a behind the car view.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/556c99d5-ed94-436e-aafb-5bca4dcc5453.jpg</boxart2>
</game>