<Game>
	<Name>Spyro - Season of Ice (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:The main game is played from this perspective Season of Ice is the first Spyro game developed for the Gameboy Advance. Other handheld versions of Spyro have solely been 2D platformers, but Season of Ice is more of an exploration game. The developers said they wanted to create a game that has more similarities to the Playstation versions of Spyro rather than handheld versions.   Plot:The evil Grendor set out on as task to harm Spyro's land. Grendor's original plan failed so he decides to capture all the fairies in the land and encase them in ice. Spyro and Sparx set out on a journey to rescue all the fairies and defeat Grendor.Gameplay: Spyro's flying stagesSeason of Ice is played in an isometric perspective to simulate 3D. Spyro will walk throughout the land in search of fairies and different collectibles. There are some platforming elements which play similarly to Super Mario RPG. The game is also broken down into many different mini games. The most prominent mini games are Spyro's flying stages and Sparx shooting stages. The flying missions are played from behind Spyro's back you basically navigate to collect items and avoid different obstacles. Sparx stages play like an overhead arcade shooter, where you point Sparx in different directions blasting enemies with fire.Levels:As with previous entries in the series Season of Ice continues the tradition of having multiple hub worlds each with their own levels attached to them.Autumn Fairy HomeLevel I: Lava PrairieLevel II: Mermaid CoastLevel III: Market MesaLevel IV: Stone Age SpeedwayLevel V: Ant FarmWinter Fairy HomeLevel I: Hummingbird FortLevel II: Panda GardensLevel III: Honey MarshLevel IV: Ice Age SpeedwayLevel V: Wasp CityLevel VI: Grendor's LairSpring Fairy HomeLevel I: Time Machine LabLevel II: Roman CityLevel III: Twilight Bulb FactoryLevel IV: Aqua Age SpeedwayLevel V: Caterpillar GardensSummer Fairy HomeLevel I: Dusty TrailsLevel II: Star ParkLevel III: Space Age SpeedwayLevel IV: Beetle BurrowsLevel V: Grendor's LairCheat: Cheat CodesAll codes are entered on the title screen:Cheat: More Special Commands for SparxAt the start screen: press Right, Up, Right, Left, Down, Up, Left, Down A. This activates special commands during Sparx worlds, which provides the following controls: -Up+Select= Gives Sparx an Invincibility Shield -Right+Select= Gives Sparx a Smart Bomb -Left+Select= Gives Sparx Rapid Fire -Down+Select= Gives Sparx Homing Bombs -L+Select= Gives Sparx all keysCheat: More Special Commands for SparxYou can play around with the parameters controlling the particles in the menus and credits sequence. In any menu: L + Select - Set all particle parameters to random values L + Left/Right - Rotate direction of particles L + Up/Down - Increase/Decrease particle directionality L + A/B - Increase/Decrease number of particles R + Left/Right - Increase/Decrease particle velocity R + Up/Down - Increase/Decrease gravity R + A/B - Increase/Decrease particle lifespan L + R - Reset all particle parameters to default values During the credits sequence: Start - Pause/Unpause the scrolling of the credits L + Select - Set all particle parameters to random values Up/Down - Increase/Decrease vertical range of particles Left/Right - Increase/Decrease horizontal range of particles L + R + Up/Down - Increase/Decrease vertical speed of particles L + R + Left/Right - Increase/Decrease horizontal speed of particles L + Left/Right - Rotate direction of particles L + Up/Down - Increase/Decrease particle directionality L + A/B - Increase/Decrease number of particles R + Left/Right - Increase/Decrease particle velocity R + Up/Down - Increase/Decrease gravity R + A/B - Increase/Decrease particle lifespan B - Exit creditsCheat: More Special Commands for SparxIn the UK version of Spyro, pressing L+R+START any time before the language selection menu will take you directly to the language selction menu. In all other regions, pressing L+R+START any time before the Spyro logo screen will take you directly to the Spyro logo screen. (L+R+START = Hold down top left and right buttons, and press START)</plot>
	<releasedate>29/10/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Universal Interactive Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>l9As_hXton0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3709</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/516703-spyro-season-of-ice</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/spyro-season-of-ice</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spyro-season-of-ice/3030-10579/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1803995-box_spyrosoi.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3709-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/135101-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253834-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253821-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-game-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253831-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-in-game.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253820-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-screenshot-hunter-talking.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253813-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-screenshot-bianca-says.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253819-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-screenshot-go-for-the.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253835-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-screenshot-using-your.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253830-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-screenshot-talking-to.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253810-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-screenshot-that-s-what.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/253811-spyro-season-of-ice-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-person-asking.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/vYmRGy6.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3709.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Dragons never seem to have had it too easy. They have always had to worry about dragon slayers, plus they usually get a bad rap for being destructive, and let's not even get started on what people say about their breath! Fortunately Spyro has generally avoided such negative opinions, but then again he hasn't always had it easy either. You'd think that after several death-defying adventures on the Playstation over the past few years, which included the defeat of the evil Sorceress, Spyro and his friends would be able to take some time off and enjoy a bit of a vacation at Dragon Shores. But with evil brewing and a new title on the way for the GameBoy Advance, which is due out in November, the gang shouldn't get too comfortable on the beach.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/473e08c8-7815-4cd9-bf71-6306d3bd109b.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/73890845-2fe1-4bae-8e4b-dc3b2d3ff96b.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/252de7c3-009c-4092-a113-2e333a1d0513.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Universal Interactive</Publisher>
</game>