<Game>
	<Name>Spyro Orange - The Cortex Conspiracy (USA)</Name>
	<plot>In Crash Bandicoot Purple: Ripto's Rampage and Spyro Orange: The Cortex Conspiracy, Dr. Neo Cortex--Crash's nemesis--and Ripto--Spyro's nemesis--have accidentally met up through underground portals and are set on taking over the entire universe. Crash and Spyro must team up with each other to discover the identity of the new menace and save the universe from this evil plot. In these side-scrolling adventures, you can link up with three friends for a variety of multiplayer modes, including Party Games, Wager Games, and Card Trading. Connecting both Crash Bandicoot Purple and Spyro Orange gives you the option of unlocking special content and allows you to trade and wager the cards with friends.Cheat: Fun PasswordsAt the game mode screen, press the L and R buttons together to activate the code entry screen.Cheat: Various UnlockablesNOTE: The unlockable levels will pop up when you get close to their location. They are like the bonus portals. Cheat: Crash Party USAHold the L and R buttons while you turn on the power and a secret game will start up instead of Spyro Orange. You get to make Crash dance!Cheat: Crash Party USAAfter you beat the Story Mode select Credits from the menu and instead of the Spyro Orange Logo you will see a slideshow of 5 pieces of what appear to be fan art behind the credit roll.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/6/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Vivendi Universal Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22309</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919869-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy/3030-15249/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1803672-box_spyrootcc.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/2/0/58620_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/160397-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635665-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635666-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635667-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635668-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635669-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2009/213546-fusioncrashjapan.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2009/213543-1510a.png</snapshot8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/yvoBCsd.png</banner1>
</game>