<Game>
	<Name>Spyro Orange - The Cortex Conspiracy (USA) (Rev 1)</Name>
	<plot>Ripto and Dr. Cortex have combined their forces to take over the world once and for all. Right in the middle of it all our the heroes, Crash Bandicoot and Spyro the Dragon.Spyro now finds himself in both familiar and unfamiliar territory, passing through the realms into Crash's world as well as his own to defeat the evil that awaits. Spyro's usual abilities are available as always.Through-out, you'll find a collection of familiar characters from both the Crash and Spyro franchise, mini-games and multiplayer options. Collect the hidden trading cards and trade them with other players to get a complete set, or connect Spyro the Dragon Orange with a Crash Bandicoot Purple cartridge for unique connection options.</plot>
	<releasedate>1/6/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Vivendi Universal Games, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22309</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919869-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy/3030-15249/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1803672-box_spyrootcc.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/2/0/58620_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/160397-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635665-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635666-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635667-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635668-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/635669-spyro-orange-the-cortex-conspiracy-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2009/213546-fusioncrashjapan.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/2009/213543-1510a.png</snapshot8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/yvoBCsd.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Spyro Orange is Vicarious Visions' first Spyro the Dragon title, taking the reigns after Digital Eclipse's GBA trilogy. For Spyro's fourth appearance on the Game Boy Advance, the development team has given the dragon a more traditional side-scrolling environment for his overworld instead of taking him back to his isometric exploits. But the scrolling platformer is only part of the experience. Spyro Orange focuses on dozens of mini-challenges for its gameplay, like a vertical shooter where Spyro floats around blasting sheep or collecting gems, a rapid-button-tapping challenge involving tug-o-war and ice cube creation, or driving around in a tank, or knocking out a series of bad guys in a Breakout-style challenge. The game supports link cable play for multiplayer challenges.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8a31cb46-2776-4105-849c-415e03216ae5.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/48e1420a-c230-431b-8836-908843e36b15.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d1f7ec86-445c-4ae9-ae25-c298246dd105.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>VU Games</Publisher>
</game>