<Game>
	<Name>Star Wars - Episode III - Revenge of the Sith (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>Summary:Released on May 5 2005, Star Wars Episode III: Revenge of the Sith is based directly on the film of the same name. Released on the PlayStation 2, Xbox, Game Boy Advance, and Nintendo DS, players are able to take part in the 17 levels that follow Anakin Skywalker and Obi-Wan Kenobi as the Clone Wars conclude and the rise of Darth Vader begins.Plot:Anakin duels Darth TyranusFollowing the plot of the movie, players take control of both Anakin Skywalker or Obi-Wan Kenobi throughout the game. Like in the movie, Obi-Wan Kenobi's task is to locate and destroy General Grievous, while Anakin Skywalker's story focuses around his fall to the dark side and the destruction of the Jedi Order. The game ends with a dramatic lightsaber battle between Obi-Wan and Anakin on the lava planet of Mustafar.There are some story differences between the game and the movie which it is based on. Most of the differences are just extended sequences of scenes from the movie. Examples include:More death of Jedis in the execution of Order 66Extended scenes leading to the General Grevious fightThe destruction of the Jedi TempleObi-Wan's escape from UtapauObi-Wan and Yoda's investigation of the Jedi TempleOther differences are strange additions and some removed elements that do not closely follow the film. The game adds the death scene of Jedi Jocasta Nu. The game also does not have Padme as a major inspiration for Anakin's betrayal, and other minor changes.Secret endingIn cooperative mode, each player controls one of these two characters.This game features an additional, non-canon ending. The last two stages of the game both are about the duel between Anakin and Obi-Wan. In the first level, you play as Obi-Wan, and when you beat Anakin, you are shown the canon ending as it was seen in the Revenge of the Sith movie. However, if you play the level as Anakin and beat Obi-Wan, the ending plays out differently. Anakin kills Obi-Wan, and when the Emperor congratulates him, he slays the Emperor and proclaims himself the sole ruler of the universe.Bonus MissionsAfter completing missions from the campaign, various bonus missions are unlocked which feature different characters from the main story. They are unlocked by progressing through the main story mode.Episode IV: Death Star MissionGrievous on the RunMustafar Lava ChallengeSize Matters NotThe General's ProtectorOther unlockables include concept art and extra versus mode characters.Multiplayer:The game features four cooperative missions for 1-2 players, where the AI controls the second player in 1 player mode.A duel mode is also available as a two player versus mode. This mode has players fight against each other in a fighting game type setting, but with loose gameplay like in the campaign.Available characters are:Obi-Wan KenobiAnakin SkywalkerCount Dooku (unlockable)General Grievous (unlockable)Mace Windu (unlockable)Cin Drallig (unlockable)Serra Keto (unlockable)Darth Vader (unlockable)Ben Kenobi (unlockable)Alternate costumes are also available if two of the same characters are picked. Some of these are more than simple color swaps and include Sith versions of Jedi characters.Version DifferencesThe Gameboy Advance and DS versions feature sidescrolling gameplay.Two main versions of the game were released - one being shared between the PlayStation 2 and Xbox; and another shared between the Game Boy Advance and Nintendo D.S. The Xbox and PS2 versions of the game are identical, with the player fighting through a series of linear levels in a traditional hack 'n slash style game (strongly reminiscent of the Lord of the Rings games from EA released a few years prior). They also feature co-operative multiplayer, and one-on-one local duels between two players using characters unlocked throughout the course of the game. The Game Boy Advance and Nintendo D.S. versions are also largely identical, being two dimensional side scrolling action games, however the Nintendo D.S. added a strong multiplayer mode (complete with bots) that featured up to four players going head to head in space-craft based dogfighting, resembling the Nintendo 64 Rogue Squadron titles.Critical ResponseThe Xbox and PS2 versions of the game received largely "Average" ratings - totaling scores in the low 60% range on both GameRankings and Metacritic. The Nintendo D.S. and Game Boy Advance versions performed more admirably, garnering reviews in the mid 70% range from both websites. The console versions of the game were criticized for a lack of gameplay variety, and poor multiplayer gameplay. The D.S. version was praised for being a competent, interesting side scrolling action game with a surprisingly entertaining multiplayer component.CheatsAll Bonus' 021282Unlimited Health XUCPHRAUnlimited Force KAIBURRFast Regen BECSAVISUnlock Story KORRIBANUnlock Duel Arenas TANTIVEIVUnlock duel people ZABRAKUnlock all movies COMLINKUnlock all concept art AAYLASECURAAll Powers and Force Moves JAINASuperSaber Mode SUPERSABERS</plot>
	<releasedate>4/5/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ubisoft, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>wMZ0MhzQ2Nc</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3510</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/925150-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith/3030-9200/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/10831/1349753-920420_54117_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3510-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/153113-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181854-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181855-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181856-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181857-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181858-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181859-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181860-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181861-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/181862-star-wars-episode-iii-revenge-of-the-sith-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3510-2.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/zvjM8UC.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>THE ULTIMATE JEDI ACTION EXPERIENCE With the fate of the Republic in your hands, you must master the ways of the Force - and resist its darkest temptations. -Use deadly weapon combos and maneuvers to defeat legendary Star Wars villains, including General Grievous and Count Dooku. -Discover formidable Jedi powers, including the Force Push, Saber Throw, and Jedi Mind Trick. -Pilot Classic Star Wars ships in action-packed four-player wireless dogfights.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e076ae57-59c4-4bd2-b663-1aaa4843d2d4.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/de758017-8cee-4ca0-a5b4-d288b73a6ff9.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/238f2bd6-ec55-4312-9b97-731f19d5ee7d.png</boxart3>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>