<Game>
	<Name>Star Wars - Flight of the Falcon (Europe) (En,Fr,De)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Star Wars: Flight of the Falcon was released as a Game Boy Advance exclusive in November 2003. You pilot one of the most iconic space vehicles of the Star Wars franchise: the Millennium Falcon as well as other Star Wars vehicles. Gameplay:The Millennium Falcon can only go straight. Flight of the Falcon is an on rails shooter where you must eliminate enemies and dodge obstacles to complete your objectives. The A button is used to fire, the B button is used to fire secondary weapons, the L button is used to slow down and the R button is used for a speed boost. And, like in most games, the control pad is used for movement. You have a hud that gives you some important gameplay information (see gameplay picture).Your secondary weapons are missiles and you have a limited number of them. The number of missiles you have left can be seen on the top left of the screen. On the right side of the screenGameplayis your score that gets higher every time you eliminate an enemy. Bottom left is the number of lives you still have. Bottom right are your shields (you can get hit eight times before losing a life). Finally, bottom middle, you have your Mission Objective Counter. If your objective is time based, than it will serve as a timer and count down. If you must destroy a certain number of enemies to complete your objective, it reduces as you destroy enemies. You can pick up different power ups called pickups throughout the game's levels: -Partial Powerup Gives the player a partial (thus the name) health increase -Full Powerup Gives you full health. -Single Missile Upgrade Gives you one extra missile. -Multiple Missile Upgrade Gets you 3 extra missiles. -Extra Life Token As the name suggests, this pickup gives you an extra life. You can export your high score. You can import, export and reset the game's high score tables. If you import a high score table, it overwrites your previous scores. You can export your high score table via a code. Story:The game is set during the original trilogy and spans all three movies.  Episode IVApproaching the Tatooine System After being forced to dump his contraband after being boarded by imperial forces, Han and Chewbacca are called back to Tatooine by Han's employer, Jabba. Unfortunately, the Empire has rounded up some Tie Fighters on the way to the desert planet to stop Han from doing any more smuggling. Despite their best efforts, Han manages to land safely on Tatooine. Mos Eisley Spaceport, Tatooine Han Solo finds himself transporting Luke Skywalker and Obi-Wan Kenobi. But the Imperials are on to their plan to escape the planet and plan to stop them. In this level, Han pilots a landspeeder while dodging Stormtroopers who are taking shots at him. He manages to sell the landspeeder in time to get to the Falcon and take off. Dune Sea, Tatooine The Falcon may have made it out of Mos Eisley, but its not over yet. Imperial Star Destroyers await our heroes in orbit and Han is forced to fly his ship low in the dune sea to avoid detection. The only way to make it off the planet is to destroy the imperial probe droids to avoid detection. Han succeeds and the crew of the Falco finally leave Tatooine. Death Star Approach The rebellion is launching a full scale assault on the Death Star over the moons of Yavin. The player pilots an X-Wing as the rebels plow through waves after waves of Tie Fighters and imperial Star Destroyers. Luke and the rest of the Rebels survive and prepare to destroy the Death Star before it destroys Yavin. Death Star Attack, Battle Station Surface As the X-Wings get closer to the Death Star's only weak point, the fighting grows more intense. Luke must destroy turrets, deflector towers and Tie Fighters on the Death Star's surface so the assault on the Death Star's exhaust port can commence. After taking care of business, the rebels can finally start their final assault. The Exhaust Port, Death Star Trench The final assault has commenced: Luke must go down the Death Star's trenches and shoot a missile down the exhaust port to blow the super weapon to oblivion. By flying through the narrow channel, avoiding obstructions, blasting gun turrets and taking down Tie Fighters, Like destroys the Death Star and saves the galaxy !   Episode VHoth Asteroid Field The Empire has taken Hoth and Han must escape on board of the Millennium Falcon. However, the Falcon's hyperdrive has failed, keeping him from escaping. The Falcon must destroy multiple Imperial fighters, Star Destroyers and Asteroids before it can finally go into hyper speed and escape the Empire. Cloud City, Bespin Han Solo has been turned into frozen carbonite. The bounty hunter Boba Fett has taken him on board Slave 1 and the Falcon gives chase through the cloud city of Bespin. The Falcon takes down the enemy ships shields to access its onboard computer to learn where its going so they'll be able to go and save Han Solo.  Escape the ExecutorThe Falcon attempts to escape the Empire but the Imperials aren't going to let them go without a fight. They send wave after waves of Tie Fighters at our heroes. They also bring out the big guns, the Super Star Destroyer: The Executioner. The Falcon defeats the giant war ship and escapes.  Episode VIBattle of Endor The rebels have run into a trap! Thinking the Death Star's shields were down, they rushed towards the super weapon only to be welcomed by the Empire's Tie-Fighters and a shielded Death Star. The Falcon must defend the rebel starfighters from Tie-Fighters and Star Destroyers as the shields are shut down on Endor. Endor, The Forest Moon In this level, the player who plays as Luke, uses a speederbike through the woods of Endor. Imperial scout troopers have become aware of rebel presence. Luke must use his speederbike to chase down the scouts before they alert their base and ruin the plan to destroy the Death Star's shield generators. Death Star II Surface The shield generator on Endor has been destroyed and the final assault on the Death Star may commence. First, the Falcon must destroy the battle station's turrets and reflector towers so rebel forces can access the station's core reactor and destroy it once and for all! Reactor Core Access Tunnels, Inside the Death Star The Millenium Falcon has managed to punch through the Death Star's defenses. Now it must race through winding tunnels, dodging obstacles and destroying enemies, to destroy the reactor's core. After a long fight, the Falcon succeeds and barely escapes the destruction. The galaxy is saved! Famous Movie Lines Used in the Game"She may not look like much, but she's got it where it counts, kid." - Han Solo "Hokey religions and ancient weapons are no match for a good blaster at your side." - Han Solo "Sir, the possibility of successfully navigating an asteroid field is approximately 3720 to 1!" - C-3PO "Never tell me the odds!" - Han Solo Cheat: Cheat codesAt any time during the gameplay, press start to pause, then hold L and R and press Up, Right, A, Start, A, Down, A, Start, Start. The game will automatically unpause. Press Start again, then press A to quit. Now enter these codes by choosing password from the main menu.Cheat: Cheat codesEnter these on the password screen.Cheat: Cheat codesEnter these on the password screen.</plot>
	<releasedate>18/11/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>1.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22313</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/915386-star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon/3030-10164/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22313-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/9/7/4/54974_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188447-star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188448-star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188449-star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188450-star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188451-star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188452-star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188453-star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/188454-star-wars-flight-of-the-falcon-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8572/420426-star_wars___flight_of_the_falcon__usa__04.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/8572/420425-star_wars___flight_of_the_falcon__usa__01.png</snapshot10>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/22313.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Can you outrun the Empire? At last, you can know what it feels like to pilot the most popular ship in the Star Wars universe -- the Millennium Falcon. If you also want to find out what it feels like to wear super-tight pants and a black leather vest, that's up to you. Star Wars: Flight of the Falcon challenges you to blast your way through the Empire's fleet as you recreate the Battles of Yavin and Endor.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/366dad04-e7a3-498b-8335-4041169b9db1.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a868c6f-5959-4eca-bbcb-d1d74a99ddb3.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/46e617f7-3552-4d9a-b7da-92818bc3a80d.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>