<Game>
	<Name>Star Wars - Jedi Power Battles (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Choose your Jedi (either Qui-Gon Jinn, Obi-Wan Kenobi or Mace Windu) and fight the forces of the Trade Federation through the planet Naboo, facing plenty of droids and Darth Maul himself.Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulTo get all levels and play them with darth maul, enter VMT3XRM in the resume game section. Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulEnter the password  NMH0YQR  to play as Qui-Gon, Mace Windu, Obi-Wan, and Darth Maul on all levels.Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulNow, I am back with more codes.  I don't have ALL the Darth Maul codes, but I only lack 3 of them. Lv.2:VMT3D1K Lv.3:VMT3GFK Lv.5:VMT3JPK Lv.6:VMT3NMK Lv.7:VMT3Q5K I'll be back with 8,9, and 10 level codes after I get through the levels.Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulAll levels, 7 Darth Mauls: 1: VMT3BYJ 2: VMT3D*K 3: VMT3GKL 4: VMT3JTL 5: VMT3L2L 6: VMT3N*L 7: VMT3QKM 8: VMT3STM 9: VMT3V2M 10: VMT3X*M Note: 7 means 7 in reserve.  I should have specified this in my previous 2 posts (Obi-Wan codes &amp; Qui-Gon Jinn codes). Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulGo to resume game and put in MBJ3BYG Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulEnter the code VMT3BYJCheat: All levels with Darth MaulEnter 4MF0ZLP at the resume game screenCheat: All levels with Darth MaulLevel 1:You dont need this because you always start the game at level 1. Level 2: WB1BCPF You have to play as Mace Windu Level 3: VCJMBFF You have to play as Mace Windu Level 4: VC1MBPF You have to play as Mace Windu Level 5: VCJNBYF You have to play as Mace Windu Level 6: VC1DBYF You have to play as Mace Windu Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulV C J O X Y K - Level Select for Mace Windu or Darth Maul V H R 3 B F J - Level Select for Qui-Gon JinnCheat: All levels with Darth MaulHere are codes from level 7 through 10 (since 1-6 have allready been shown) level-7 VCGYCFH =6 LIVES level-8 VCXYCFH =6 LIVES level-9 VCDZCPH =6 LIVES level-10 VCVZCPH =6 LIVES Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulLEVEL 1= ALREADY SHOWN LEVEL 2=VMT3DGK(THIS ONE IS THE SAME as my old one) LEVEL 3=VMT3G0K (I THINK THIS ONE HAS 5 LIVES) LEVEL 4=VMT3J8K (5 LIVES) LEVEL 5=VMT3LHL (5 LIVES) LEVEL 6= VMT3NRL (5 LIVES) The other i submitted has less lives so it might be better to use theseCheat: All levels with Darth MaulHello again! I went to church on Dec.23 and found myself incredibly bored.  So I started playing my Star Wars game and put in the code for Darth Maul.  Well, I played and got through to the seventh level with 6 lives. Here are the new, updated codes I found. LV.2:VMT3D1K LV.3:VMT3JJL LV.4:VMT3LSL LV.5:VMT3N1L LV.6:VMT3QKM I'LL BE BACK SOON WITH THE REST OF THE LEVEL CODES.  I'M WORKING AT IT, BUT IT'S HARD TO KEEP 6 TO 8 LIVES ALL THE WAY THROUGH.Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulAll levels, 7 Obi-Wans:  1: n/a  2: WFJ3BPG  3: XFJ3BYG  4: YFJ3B6G  5: ZFJ3BFH  6: 0FJ3BPH  7: 1FJ3BYH  8: 2FJ3B6H  9: 3FJ3BFJ 10: 4FJ3BPJ Note the patterns... Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulOk I have found these through much tiresome work on the game, but they're worth it. Lv.2:VHN3B6F Lv.3:VML3B6F Lv.4:VR13BFG Lv.5:VW13BPG Lv.6:(the first code gives 3 lives, the other is for experts) V013BYG, expert:V0B3BYF Lv.7:V413BBG Lv.8:VCY3BBG Lv.9:V8Z3BBG Lv.10:(sorry, no extra lives) V0C3BYH (Must be Qui-Gon to use these) Also on a personal note: I found the last code on accident by altering two of the letters on the level 6, Code 1. Cheat: All levels with Darth MaulAll levels, 7 Qui-Gons: 1: n/a 2: VHS3BPG 3: VMS3BYG 4: VRS3B6G 5: VWS3BFH 6: V0S3BPH 7: V4S3BYH 8: V8S3B6H 9: VCT3BFJ 10: VHT3BPJCheat: All Players With 7 Lives On All LevelsEnter the password 5PT80KW to play as Qui-Gon, Mace Windu, Obi-Wan, and Darth Maul on all levels with 7 lives on each and every level.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC, THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22261</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/479407-star-wars-jedi-power-battles</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/star-wars-jedi-power-battles</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/N4zNrTW.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/146395-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/292362-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/292363-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/292364-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-screenshot-options.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/292365-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/292366-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-screenshot-qui.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/292367-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-screenshot-and.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/292368-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/292369-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-screenshot-each.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/292370-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/292371-star-wars-jedi-power-battles-game-boy-advance-screenshot-level.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/hRhuAbB.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Deflect. Defeat. Destroy! Let the Force guide you to victory. Take back the Theed Royal Palace in fast and furious lightsaber assaults as one of three powerful Jedi: Obi-Wan Kenobi, Qui-Gon Jinn, or Mace Windu.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/96cca136-7ae9-49fe-ad3e-f423fc29df40.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a653006f-a62d-433c-9846-99a15146d35d.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>