<Game>
	<Name>Street Jam Basketball (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Street Jam Basketball features intense three-on-three street ball. You'll select your team from a roster of more than 40 different characters--each with a different style, speed, and special dunks. Take your players throughout more than 20 tournaments while climbing from beginner to violence mode. Playground locations include the streets, abandoned buildings, the docks, the park, the sea, the roof, and a skyscraper. Street Jam Basketball also features stamina bars, team managing statistics, and a multiplayer mode.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/917905.html</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Destination Software</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3715</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/917905-street-jam-basketball</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/street-jam-basketball/3030-46218/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3715-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3715-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/6/8/gfs_52025_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/b/8/gfs_52025_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/0/8/gfs_52025_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/1/8/gfs_52025_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/a/8/gfs_52025_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3715-g.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Street Jam is a three-on-three street basketball game for Game Boy Advance. Select your team from a roster of 15 teams and over 40 different characters and enter the world of street-ball. Your aim is to win all illegal tournaments held in various locations of the downtown. The individual players differ in game style, speed, special dunks and graphic presentation. Compete in the arcade mode and win eight challenging matches against the CPU, or partake in the story mode. The latter lets you select your team, and try to rise up in the ranks via five different levels from beginner to violence mode throughout 20 different tournaments with animated story sequences.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9fe724c4-6e9c-4b10-b223-ab838a34cf12.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/9f3c4eb3-8eb6-42fd-9b85-13a7bf7e7172.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5690cdb7-fb23-4129-b06f-4d7d5fd3b2c1.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>DSI Games</Publisher>
</game>