<Game>
	<Name>Summon Night - Swordcraft Story 2 (USA)</Name>
	<plot>You are a male or female apprentice Craftknight and the Edge Fencer.  It is your job to protect the seal trapping Goura, a stray summon creature who is too powerful for anyone to control.  Similar to Summon Night: Swordcraft Story, your father died 3 years ago.  He died trying to trap Goura after a summoner tried to free Goura and take control of him.  Now it is your job to protect that seal, while you are working at becoming a Craftknight.A Craftknight is a person who creates weapons and uses them, similar to an armorer.  However, these weapons are made with the combined power of your hammer and your Guardian Beast.  You will have the ability to choose between 4 Guardian Beasts shortly after starting the game.  Each one has different abilities and will have different conversations throughout the game.  Unlike in the previous game, you do not learn techniques for making weapons, but instead you use shapestones to create a weapon type.  There are 6 weapon types that can be made and you will need at least a basic weapon from each type in order to reach all areas of the game.  The actual weapon you create will be determined by the material you use to create it.  If you make it with Iron Ore, it will be one kind of weapon, while if you make it with Aqua Ore, it will be another kind of weapon.  Later, you will have the ability to upgrade the weapons up to three times each.Battles are the same as in the previous game. You fight in a side scrolling area with up to 4 enemies.  You can use your weapon to attack, or use your Guardian Beast's magic to attack, heal or protect you, or enchant your weapon in some way.  Some weapons will also have special attacks that can do even more damage.  In this game, you'll have battles above and below ground, rather than just in the dungeon and arena.  You also have the ability to Mono Shift, where you will change into a more powerful being.  You can only do this once before recharging the item that allows you to Mono Shift.Cheat: End Game UnlockablesComplete the game and save. Now there will be an extra 'bonus' option in the main menu. Doing the following will unlock the following modes in that menu.</plot>
	<releasedate>17/10/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Atlus U.S.A., Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.1</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>VxvASK5qcD0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3512</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920241-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/summon-night-swordcraft-story-2</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/summon-night-swordcraft-story-2/3030-14817/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3512-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3512-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/D4yF3WL.png</boxart2>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/210427-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/195953-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/195954-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/195955-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/195956-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/195957-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/195958-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/195959-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/195960-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/195961-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/195962-summon-night-swordcraft-story-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3512-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/8rRWPZO.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3512.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In Summon Night: Swordcraft 2, the player is an orphan from the Colthearts clan raised by a Craftknight (a smith/warrior). The character aspires to be a Craftknight as well. The player character, either Edgar Colthearts or Aera Colthearts, who are Edge Fencers, find themselves at the site of an abandoned ruin where a violent Summon Beast named Goura is awakened. In order to protect their new family, Edgar/Aera is bound to a wild Summon Beast (stray summon) and embarks on a journey to reseal the ruins.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dafc5f56-537b-4841-90c4-b0b9b2156b74.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b05a1147-2975-43e8-9433-b30c7f594d03.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ef6647fe-936f-40ce-919b-e195b52ab6a2.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Atlus</Publisher>
</game>