<Game>
	<Name>Summon Night - Craft Sword Monogatari (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Summon Night: Swordcraft Story is an RPG set in the strange world of Lyndbaum, a sacred land linked to four magical dimensions from which Summoners can call forth spirits called Guardian Beasts to do their bidding.Cheat: After ending - Getting Kuhyra and labyrinth floors 50 through 100Once you finish the main portion of the game, traverse to the 50th floor and return to the room with the forge in it.  You will see Kuhyra and if you talk to him, it will allow you to switch your guardian beast to Kuhrya, who can use mystic ore on all weapons.   Also, the door which was previously "closed by a powerful force" is now open, making the final 50 floors of the labyrinth available.Cheat: After ending - Getting Kuhyra and labyrinth floors 50 through 100After completing the game go back to the central tower and speak to the guy guarding the arena. He will ask you if you want to compete in an exhibition match for 1000 Boam. Say yes and you'll enter the boss attack mode were you'll fight all the bosses throughout the game in order.Cheat: Increase Item Drop RateIn order to obtain more item drops from enemies in battle, unequip all weapons and fight using only the hammer. While you are fighting using only the hammer the item drop rate increases dramatically and you will recieve items after nearly every battle fought.</plot>
	<releasedate>26/7/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Flight-Plan</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>oVu2HbwuTsU</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3513</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/583203-summon-night-swordcraft-story</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3513-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3513-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/2/6/gfs_76664_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/f/6/gfs_76664_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/4/6/gfs_76664_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/5/6/gfs_76664_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/e/6/gfs_76664_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3513-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3513-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3513.png</clearlogo1>
</game>