<Game>
	<Name>Summon Night - Craft Sword Monogatari - Hajimari no Ishi (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Third game in the Summon Night "Swordcraft" action-RPG spin-offs. You take the role of a young craftsknight (a combination of knight and weaponsmith) whose master has been recently murdered. His guardian creature appears to you and admits to being responsible for his death, and joins you to try to atone for its sins as you attempt to unravel the conspiracy that caused his death and also finish your training.As the other games in the series the game is a top-down action RPG in which you explore the game world talking to NPCs for items and clues and dungeon-crawl to gather the materials needed to create your weapons. When in combat, the game switches to a side-scrolling view in which you attack and attempt to avoid your enemies attacks in real-time. Additionally you can now summon creatures and control them in all battles to take advantage of their enhanced abilities.Cheat: Battle the little girl and unlock robot wars!You have to have completed the game to do this.Go into the Omake menu (4th option in the screen after the "press start screen), and press "R, left, L, right, down, B, up, select , B, B, B ,start"You'll hear a female voice say something ,and you will be able to fight the yellow haired girl in the village in the electric ruins. Also, you'll be able to use her in the Boss battles and EX battles and such in the Omake menu. Plus, you'll get a robot wars option in the Omake battle option.Cheat: New Game+Complete the game and save. Now reset and you can start a new game but with your previous money, bestiary, weapon levels, special attacks, etc...Cheat: Transferring weapons for New Game+After you complete the game go to the top right corner of the fishing area to find a person there. You can choose 6 of your current weapons to be given to him, and these weapons will be the ones transferred to you when you start a New Game+.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/12/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Banpresto Co., Ltd.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/930200-summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-ishi</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-is/3030-163/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/97089/2523936-box.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/9/6/71696_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465382-summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-ishi-game.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465383-summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-ishi-game.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465384-summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-ishi-game.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465385-summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-ishi-game.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465386-summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-ishi-game.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465387-summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-ishi-game.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465389-summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-ishi-game.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465390-summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-ishi-game.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/465391-summon-night-craft-sword-monogatari-hajimari-no-ishi-game.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/9/97089/2523943-7.png</snapshot10>
</game>