<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario Advance 4 - Super Mario Bros. 3 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Bowser is back, and along with the Bowser kids, he's out to spoil Mario's day once again.This time, along with nabbing the Princess, the Bowser crew have also taken the magic wands from the Kings of each land and turned them into creatures. It's up to Mario and Luigi to get back the magic wands, defeat Bowser, and save the Princess all before the day is done.Old and new power-ups abound in each level for the Mario Brothers, including the return of the Super Mushroom and Fire Flower, plus the new power-ups including the frog suit, the warp flute, and the most important of all, the leaf, which allows you to fly and attack enemies with your tail.http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/super-mario-bros-3Cheat: Many Tanooki SuitsIn World 5 (Cloud World), the first available mushroom house has a Tanooki Suit. Get it and beat levels until you get to the cloud part of the world by beating the spiral tower. The game offers to save your game. Save it, then get game over. When you continue, you keep the Tanooki Suit you got at the mushroom house, and the mushroom house has returned! All of the other levels remain defeated as well, though the spiral tower remains standing, so you cna beat it and save your game, get game over, and get another Tanooki Suit each time! The suits make good replacements for leaves, mushrooms, and useless items (like music boxes) in your item list. Glitch only works for World 5 due to the ability to beat the spiral tower as many times as you want and save after each time.Cheat: 1,000,000 StarFor every 1,000,000 points you earn, a star will appear above the title Super Mario Bros. 3 (where you select between Super Mario Bros. 3 or Mario Bros.) You can earn up to five stars.Cheat: 1,000,000 StarFor each 150,000 points you get in Mario Brothers, a star will appear at the top of Mario Brothers at the game selection screen (where you pick between Super Mario Brothers 3 and Mario Brothers). You can get up to 5 stars maximum.Cheat: 1,000,000 StarTo replay any level, fortress, and castle, beat every level in the game. Not just Bowser, every single level.Cheat: 1,000,000 StarIf you manage to ''beat'' a spade house (by correctly matching the pieces into any of the 3 forms), you can unlock additional houses! In addition, you can create different combos that can get you even more lives! Heart house: Star is replaced with a racoon leaf, and matching it rewards you with 7 lives Club House: Star/Leaf is replaces with the number ''3'', matching this awards you 9 lives Diamond House: All items are replaced with stars..a Guarenteed win! Once you have passed a diamond house, the cycle repeats itself.Cheat: 1,000,000 StarBeat the game clearing every single level (90 in total). Once Bowser is defeated, save and you will be brought to a World Selection screen where you can jump to any of the 8 worlds. All locked doors will have been unlocked and you can freely visit any stage/bonus stage/castle/etc.Cheat: 1,000,000 StarAfter you beat the whole game, special coins at the beginning of the secret levels: Levels and required coins:  1-4, 2-2, 3-8, 4-2, 5-5, 6-7, 7-2 Each will have a number on the bottom of the screen telling you how many coins in that level you need to get a white mushroom popup on the map. Once you achieve that many coins, the white mushroom house icon will show up.Cheat: Behind-The-ScenesIn most levels, there are multi-colored blocks held up by screws. With the white ones, you can drop behind the scenes to escape enemies or find secret exits by holding down on the d-pad for 5 seconds. In World 1-3 towards the end of the level, drop behind from on top the white block and run behind the black curtain. You will uncover a hidden mushroom house which contains a warp whistle.Cheat: Behind-The-ScenesDefeat the Koopaling at the end of an Airship (Worlds 1-7) while wearing either the Frog, Tanooki, or Hammer Bros. suit and receive a special message from the King.Cheat: Get the Magic WhistlesWhistle 1- On Level 1-3 when you get to the end of the course you will find a white block. Hold down while on top of the white block until you go behind the scenery. From here run to the end of the course and you will be transported to a room with a magic whistle Whistle 2- On the World 1 Fortess, when you come across the first Dry-Bones, there will be a [?] block. Hit this to get a leaf. As Racoon Mario, knock out the dry bones and fly up the ledge until you start walking along the top of it. Continue going right whilst on top of the ledge until you stop moving. Press up to be transported to a room with a Whistle Whistle 3- On World 2 after you have collected the Hammer from the Hammer Brothers go to the top right corner of the world map. Use the Hammer to break a rock leading to a secret passge. In here there is a Firs Brothers, beat them to get the WhistleCheat: Get the Magic WhistlesAttract Lakitu to the pit underneath the Venus Fire Trap. Next, launch a Koopa shell between the two wooden blocks. Now, as Lakitu launches Spiny Eggs, the Koopa shell will instantly destroy them. Accumulate enough points, and soon you will receive infinite lives. (NOTE: The max amount of lives you can get is 999.)Cheat: Get the Magic Whistles You need to be Raccoon Mario to do this. When you enter the World 2 Fortress, don't attack the first Dry Bones (the skeletal turtle) you see. Instead, lure it over to the other two Dry Bones a few screens ahead. Now, jump on the first one, and use the raccoon tail to flutter onto the next one, and then the final one. By then, the first one should be back on its feet. Keep repeating the process for infinite lives.Cheat: Get the Magic WhistlesThe N-Spade Memory Game will appear on the world map every 80,000 points you score. There are a select amount of layouts that the game will select from. M=Mushroom F=Fireflower 1=1-Up Chest T=Ten Coins 2=Twenty Coins S=Starman MF2F1S 21MT1F SMSMFS FT1F1M SM2SMT SF2MFS FS1F1M TMFSMT S22MFS F2MS1F 1FTM2S MTSMFS FS1F2M TM21MT SFSMFS MF2MTS F1MT12 SFSMFS 1MTMFS MTS22F S1FMFS MF1FSS 2SMT1F 2MTMFSCheat: Get the Magic WhistlesUse the following procedure to turn the Wandering Hammer Bros. into a Treasure Ship. Note that this only works on Worlds 1, 3, 5, and 6. Get an amount of coins that is a mutiple of 11 Make the number in the tens place of your score the same as the number your using for the mutiple of 11 At the end of the stage before you reach the Wandering Hammer Bros., stop the timer on an even number  Here's an example:  33 coins  score: 1,430  timer: 98</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>-OekXpbdvrA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2350</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589393-super-mario-advance-4-super-mario-bros-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/TERSEgv.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/0isu5xG.png</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/D4Bz7Jq.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/EnnFLvz.jpg</boxart4>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/9/5/gfs_24375_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/7/4/gfs_120946_1_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/a/4/gfs_120946_1_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/1/4/gfs_120946_1_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/0/4/gfs_120946_1_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2350-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2350-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2350-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2350-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2350-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2350-6.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2350-7.jpg</fanart7>
	<fanart8>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2350-8.jpg</fanart8>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/CQV3EkD.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2350.png</clearlogo1>
</game>