<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario Advance 2 - Super Mario World (USA, Australia)</Name>
	<plot>Mario hasn't even had a chance to savor his victory in the original Super Mario Advance, and already he's back for more in Super Mario World: Super Mario Advance 2.This game is a re-creation of the Super NES classic Super Mario World, featuring every last secret exit and all 74 levels of platform-jumping action.Once again, Princess Peach has been kidnapped by the ever-diabolical Bowser, and Mario and Luigi set out on a massive adventure to rescue her.As either Mario or Luigi, you'll solve puzzles, shoot fireballs, fly, and discover the hidden secrets in Dinosaur Island.Cheat: Get stuck in wallsIn a few levels, there will be sets of rotating blocks blocking your path. (Example: Vanilla Dome 2 or Star World 1)Make sure you have a feather equipped. Use your cape to roate the blocks, then stand in right in front of the blocks while they are rotating. Usually the blocks will just push you back into open when they stop moving. However, sometimes the blocks will push you the opposite direction- into the wall. This usually works only in Vanilla Dome 2, but it allows you to walk down the slope of the wall underneath enemies. However, if you are surround by layer after layer of bricks (Star Road 1), you will be pushed into the other blocks, usually resulting in you losing a life.Cheat: Earn Point Stars (Mario Brothers)For each 150,000 points you get in Mario Brothers, a star will appear at the top of Mario Brothers at the game selection screen (where you pick between Super Mario World and Mario Brothers). You can get up to 5 stars maximum.Cheat: Earn Point Stars (Mario Brothers)After filling a ceratin Requirement you give a new look to yoshi's island which is called EXTRA. The shells will look like bubbleheads of Mario, the Pirahnas will have pumpking heads and you can access any stage by pressing SELECT and pressing A on the stage you wish to go to.Cheat: Decorative StarsFor every one-million points you get in Super Mario World mode, a star will appear on the main menu screen next to the ''top score'' display. NOTE: The maximum amount of stars you can get is 5.Cheat: Decorative StarsPlay through the games and as quickly as you can get to the Star Worlds. Now go to Star World 4 and get the yoshi now either complete the mission with Yoshi. Now Go back to that level with yoshi and go back to the egg and get the 1-up and then press START and go back and do then level again to get more lives. Repeat As Needed   Cheat: Decorative StarsIf you find and complete the alternate (key) exits in all Star Road levels, you will unlock a set of special levels accessible from the mountain in the middle of the main Star Road map.Cheat: Decorative StarsWhen your time has twice the same digit repeated at the end and it's the same as the tens of your stars total you'll get a extra life for free!!!Cheat: Decorative StarsExample:With 39 stars, beat the stage with your time ending in 33.Cheat: Decorative StarsGo to the special levels (place with Tubular, Groovy, etc.) Still on the world map, leave the game alone for a few minutres and you'll hear the music change.Cheat: Decorative StarsOnce you complete the Special World, you will be able to save your high scores in the Special World levels.Cheat: Decorative StarsOnce you've cleared all 96 Goals, you will then be able to warp to any point on the map via the Status Screen. On the Map Screen, press Select to access the Status Screen. You will now see a little white arrow to the left of each course name. Choose a course and press A. Mario (or Luigi) will be automatically warped to that part of the world map. This will save lots of time trudging from one part of the map to the next. Enjoy!Cheat: Decorative StarsComplete the special worlds (The world with SPECIAL written across the top) and the Super Famicom logo will appear across the top of the Special World Map. You will have to press L and make the screen scroll up to see the logo. Cheat: Decorative StarsBeat the game (defeat Bowser) and the intro changes from the usual 'find the princess is missing, play scary music' to a sequence where you see the princess riding on a Yoshi with another Yoshi carrying a picnic basket.Cheat: Decorative StarsOnce you beat the game you will be able to re-do Fortresses and Castles.Cheat: Decorative StarsTo change all the Yoshi Coins to Princess Coins, collect all five Yoshi Coins from each level. After you collect them all, watch the in-game movie to see the coins change.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>xzArNQRCxO0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2348</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/472572-super-mario-world-super-mario-advance-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/super-mario-advance</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-mario-advance/3030-5215/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2348-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2348-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/228130-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/404362-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-alternate.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24770-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/545233-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-japanese-title.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/404357-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-game-choose.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24771-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro-screen.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24772-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-player-selection.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24773-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-b-b-big-shy.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24774-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-charged-for.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24775-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-shadow-world.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24776-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-the-clouds.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2348-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2348-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2348-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2348-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2348-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7CkOo4K.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2348.png</clearlogo1>
</game>