<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario Advance 3 - Yoshi's Island (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>When Baby Mario falls from the sky, the big-hearted Yoshis vow to reunite him with his twin brother on the far side of the island.It won't be easy, but you must help them take on a meddling Magikoopa and his entire cast of underhanded underlings.Your journey spans the island's jungles, caves, and snowcapped peaks--each area filled with hidden rooms, secret passages, charming minigames, demented bosses, and all-new pals.Sure, Yoshi looks cute, but he packs some pretty amazing firepower--he can throw eggs, hover, stomp, pound the ground, slurp up enemies, and morph into a toy submarine.Cheat: Alternate Title ScreenSimply beat the game 100% and the next time you boot up yoshi's island the game's title screen will show yoshi's island but it will be night instead of dayCheat: Alternate Title ScreenTo append stars next to the logo at the game's title screen, you must complete every single level in a given world: this includes the extra levels earned by getting 100 points on the other eight levels in the world. One star will appear for each world completed in such a manner, for a total of up to six stars at the title screen.Cheat: Alternate Title ScreenCollect a certain amount of points in a world to get a special surprise. (Note: the first three apply for all 6 Worlds.)Cheat: Get 6 NEW Secret LevelsBeat the game to get a whole new set of 6 levels not found in the original Yoshi's Island.Cheat: Get 6 NEW Secret LevelsAfter you have gone over all the hills there is a pipe that Shy Guys come out of. Ignore them and go past the pipe and get  rid of the Killer Plants in the next two pipes to the right (one above and on the ground). A Kooper is walking between the two pipes on the ground. Jump on the Kooper and send his shell spinning between the two pipes. Shy Guys continue to jump out of the pipe on the left and every time the Kooper shell hits them you will hear a different sound that means youre getting lives! Stand on the pipe on the right and the lives will continue for as long as you stay on this screen.Cheat: Get 6 NEW Secret LevelsIn any World, whenever you get your World Score to 777, you will earn 7 lives.Cheat: Get 6 NEW Secret LevelsWhen entering the arena, do not pass the end of the stone colonade that is at the very edge of the large arena room. This will allow you to see the small pirhanna plant without activating the boss battle.Cheat: Get 6 NEW Secret LevelsFrom here, you can fire an egg at the pirhanna plant and destroy it with one hit. This forces Kamek to appear and say 'OH MY', before fleeing. Having already destroyed the plant and scared Kamek, you will not have to fight the Naval Pirhanna, thus avoiding a potentially difficult boss battle.Cheat: Get 6 NEW Secret LevelsGrab a Melon Bug (the creature that rolls up into a ball) and go to the pipe with Shy Guys jumping out of it. Spit the Melon Bug close to the pipe on the left-hand side. When Shy Guys jump out, after a while you will get a "1-Up" for each time a Shy Guy hits the Melon Bug when it is in its melon form.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.2</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>BDXmjzVVUCo</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2349</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561566-yoshis-island-super-mario-advance-3</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/AMfLWvG.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://i.imgur.com/nPlABe3.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/f/7/gfs_21800_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/2/7/gfs_21800_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/9/7/gfs_21800_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/8/7/gfs_21800_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/d/6/gfs_45094_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-6.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-7.jpg</fanart7>
	<fanart8>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-8.jpg</fanart8>
	<fanart9>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-9.jpg</fanart9>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/4k7zTqy.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2349.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Go for a spin around Yoshi's island. Baby-sitting a whiny newborn is about as fun as a head cold on the first day of summer vacation. But when Baby Mario falls from the sky, the Yoshis seize the opportunity to do a lot more than change diapers. The big-hearted Yoshis vow to reunite Baby Mario with his twin brother on the far side of the island. It won't be easy, but the Yoshis are determined to take on a meddling Magikoopa and his entire cast of underhanded underlings. Brilliant game-designer Shigeru Miyamoto has crammed the island's jungles, caves and snowcapped peaks with one brain-bending surprise after another. Hidden rooms, secret passages, charming minigames, demented bosses and all-new pals await your discovery. Sure, Yoshi looks cute, but he packs some pretty amazing firepower. He can jump, hover, stomp, pound the ground and slurp up enemies. Best of all, he can throw eggs. Heck, Mario even gets to presto-chango into superfast Superstar Mario, while Yoshi morphs into a toy submarine that shoots itty-bitty torpedoes. As an added bonus, Yoshi's Island includes six super-challenging levels developed just for the GBA. You can also take a break from baby-sitting duties to indulge in multiplayer Mario Bros. action. In Super Yoshi's Island: Super Mario Advance 3, the unlikely duo of Yoshi and Baby Mario must together brave a world of infinite surprise and challenge. Richly varied gameplay, brilliant graphics and precision control perfectly meld in an adventure you won't be able to put down!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2a9a5d0a-fddd-4c57-a800-a83560ea000a.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8bfd1fd5-20f0-4abb-a725-f5846141c1b3.jpg</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/57221963-5170-41af-9b44-b9f06a1d8b75.png</boxart4>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/bbb177d8-4e98-4bba-ac7c-d56d9b1d6600.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>