<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario Advance 2 - Super Mario World (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Mario and his brother Luigi are back for this second Super Mario Advance title: the first being a remake of Super Mario Bros. 2. The brothers, along with Princess Peach, are vacationing in Dinosaur Island. Then when they least expect it, Bowser once again kidnaps Peach and takes her to his castle. On the way to rescue her, the plumbers find Yoshi, who tells them that Bowser has also turned his friends into eggs. So the Mario brothers, with the help of Yoshi, must rescue the princess and Yoshi's pals.Mario and Luigi can run and jump through each level. They can also collect power-ups to gain new skills. The Super Mushroom makes them grow and gain more defense. The Fire Flower lets the brothers throw fireballs to defeat enemies. The Starman makes them invincible. The plumbers can gain the ability of flight with the Cape Feather.Yoshi can help Mario and Luigi if they find an egg. The green dinosaur can use his tongue to eat enemies or grab power-ups. He can walk across certain enemies with his shoes. Yoshi can eat differently colored Koopa shells to briefly gain more abilities. For instance, the blue shell gives him wings, red shells let him spit fireballs, and the yellow shell allows him to stomp the ground.This update over the original Super Nintendo version includes character speech (as heard in Mario Advance and Mario Kart Super Circuit). Up to four players can compete in the classic Mario Bros. game, included with the main game.http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/super-mario-world-super-mario-advance-2</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.1</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>xzArNQRCxO0</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>2348</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/472572-super-mario-world-super-mario-advance-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/super-mario-advance</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-mario-advance/3030-5215/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://i.imgur.com/SczXrtj.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2348-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/228130-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/404362-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-alternate.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24770-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/545233-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-japanese-title.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/404357-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-game-choose.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24771-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro-screen.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24772-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-player-selection.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24773-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-b-b-big-shy.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24774-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-charged-for.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24775-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-shadow-world.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/24776-super-mario-advance-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-the-clouds.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2348-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2348-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2348-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2348-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2348-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/7CkOo4K.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2348.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>One of Mario's greatest adventures is in your hands! Bowser and his crew of cruel Koopalings have taken over Dinosaur Island, but luckily, Mario and Luigi are up for some Koopa-kicking. As they ride Yoshi, search for P-Switches, find secret paths, blast fireballs, and soar skyward with the Cape, they'll need to use every trick in the plumber handbook. Dino Rhinos, Chargin' Chucks, and a host of unforgettable enemies await in one of the Mario Bros. biggest and most challenging adventures ever! -All 96 levels in the palm of your hand! Ride Yoshi from the spooky Forest of Illusion to the super-tough Star Road - everything from the Super NES classic is here, powered up with all-new features for the Game Boy Advance. -Luigi's ready, so pick a Bro and go! Now you can play as Mario or his brother, Luigi, who can jump and fly higher than his famous sibling. Which Bro is the best for each stage? -Get linked! Using a single Game Pak, link up four players and play the timeless Mario Bros. arcade game. You can even connect with Super Mario Advance Game Paks for Multi-Pak madness!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3ccb2fde-703d-41af-993d-8851c2002028.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5f312314-d3da-4e35-adea-a99135eeeba8.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a476c08-c33c-44b3-9746-3f397429fc5f.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/82721ec4-c936-4385-8b49-6d0a82a39cbf.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>