<Game>
	<Name>Super Hornet FA 18F (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Super Hornet F/A-18F is a Jet Sim game, developed by UK Magic and published by Majesco Games, which was released in 2004.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/922254.htmlCheat: Unlimited Weapons and FuelTitle ScreenCheat: Ace Level PasswordsThese are the passwords used to skip to a different level in ACE difficulty. Go to the password screen, and type in the password. Upon entering the password, you\'ll be directed to the corresponding level automatically.Cheat: Ace Level PasswordsThese are the passwords that you use to skip to a different level in NOVICE difficulty. Go to the password screen, and type in the password. After entering the password, you'll be directed to the corresponding level automatically.Cheat: All Enemy Fighters Are UFOsGo to the password screen and enter 'NHDCDKPM'. Directly after completing the password, press start. Now choose New Game on the Main Menu. All of your enemies will now be Alien UFOs. These UFOs will shoot giant green balls at you. Also, on the cockpit view, the computer screen will show a UFO being shot in a game of Space Invaders, instead of the usual jet getting destroyed be a missile.Cheat: All Enemy Fighters Are UFOsGo to the password screen and enter 'LCMLFLTC'. Directly after entering the password, press start and select New Game on the main menu. Now all of your enemies will be flying the "Red Baron" Fokker DR.111 triplane. Now on the computer screen in the cockpit view, when you hit a "Red Baron" with a missile, the screen will show a World War I fighter plane crashing into the ground rather than the usual jet being destroyed by a missile. The symbol for the enemy planes will also change to a WWI plane.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
	<Developer>Majesco Games</Developer>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22315</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/922254-super-hornet-f-a-18f</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22315-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/c/d/gfs_57750_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/1/d/gfs_57750_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/a/d/gfs_57750_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/b/d/gfs_57750_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/0/d/gfs_57750_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<Notes>In F-18 Super Hornet, players will take to the sky for more than 19 different land and sea missions in real Iraqi cities, to defend the coalition and defeat the insurgent forces with an array of high-powered weaponry.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ab17498c-db9c-452c-878e-3e5de0d989fa.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Majesco Games</Publisher>
</game>