<Game>
	<Name>Super Robot Taisen J (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Super Robot Taisen J is a Strategy game, developed by AI and published by Banpresto,which was released in Japan in 2005.Cheat: Deploy more units at startBoth Dancougar and Tekkaman blade have a seperate ability that splits them into two, less powerful units.  When these units get this ability, split and send them into a battleship.  Simply swap them out for the desired units.  It's basically a two for one dealCheat: Ahmos Gale with Graimkaiser or Julia Asuka with BloodykaiserFor Gale, in Stage 3, Eiji must convince with him. In Stage 4, agree the choice (1st choice). After Stage 10, pick Archangel's route. Finally, in Stage 14, have a battle encounter between Eiji &amp; Gale.Cheat: Ahmos Gale with Graimkaiser or Julia Asuka with BloodykaiserFor Julia, in Stage 20, Eiji must convince "???". In Stage 27 &amp; Stage 35, don't destroy Bloodykaiser.Cheat: Ahmos Gale with Graimkaiser or Julia Asuka with BloodykaiserYou can pick one of them only after Stage 39. If you have Gale in your team, you won't have Julia even you have the requirement to recruit her.Cheat: Ahmos Gale with Graimkaiser or Julia Asuka with BloodykaiserOn stage 24, defeat Takuma with Sousuke.  On stage 29, defeat Zaied with Sousuke.  On sage 30, defeat Gauron with Sousuke.  You should get him on stage 34.Cheat: Ahmos Gale with Graimkaiser or Julia Asuka with BloodykaiserDo not use Zeorymer unless the game forces you to.  Go with the Nadesico on stage 11 and let Zeorymer destroy Lanster of Wind.  On stage 21 go with the Archangel and let Zeorymer destroy Briest of Fire and Gallowin of Water.  On stage 29 let Zeorymer destroy Rose C\\\'est La Vie of Moon.  On stage 32, let Zeorymer destroy Dinoderos of Earth, Burrstone of Mountain and Omzack of Lightning.  Afterwards, Great Zeorymer will come.  Destroy it with Zeorymer.  You should get Great Zeorymer on stage 36.  After this point, you may use Great Zeorymer whenever you want.</plot>
	<releasedate>15/9/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Turn-Based, Sci-Fi</genre>
	<Developer>AI</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>9.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>hDIDZXu4RJE</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>32152</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929355-super-robot-taisen-j</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-robot-wars-r/3030-23082/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/10588/513413-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/7/0/70270_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/e/7/gfs_69087_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/7/a/gfs_69087_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/a/a/gfs_69087_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/1/a/gfs_69087_2_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/0/a/gfs_69087_2_4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/YKTpoRE.png</banner1>
	<Notes>Super Robot Wars J , is a tactical role-playing video game released for the Game Boy Advance by Banpresto. The last installment of the Super Robot Wars series for the Game Boy Advance. Notable for its battle animations, which are arguably on the level of the Playstation 2 versions of the series. A list of the anime series which are featured in the game. Series that premiered in the Super Robot Wars series in this game are marked with "(new)". Mobile Fighter G Gundam Mobile Suit Gundam SEED Blue Comet SPT Layzner Brain Powerd Martian Successor Nadesico Space Knight Tekkaman Blade (new) Full Metal Panic! (new) Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu (new) Mazinkaiser (Anime OVA version) Mazinkaiser vs. The Great General of Darkness (new) Super Electromagnetic Robot Combattler V Super Electromagnetic Machine Voltes V Super Beast Machine God Dancougar Hades Project Zeorymer Banpresto Originals (Original characters created for the game)</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>1BI4vOydGu8</VideoURL1>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/cab682f1-c4f0-4d92-ab8f-87953cd592ca.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8d526cba-3ad9-44b7-b03e-ed15b74d7e09.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Banpresto</Publisher>
</game>