<Game>
	<Name>Super Donkey Kong (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Welcome to Donkey Kong Country, a place where ostriches wear running shoes, apes wear neckties, and rhinoceros gracefully leap across gaping canyons with a style and flair that would make the great Evel Knievel envious.This remake of the SNES classic revamps the Donkey Kong Country gameplay with new minigames, a new Attack mode, and the ability to save your progress anywhere.Whether you're looking for a nostalgic stroll through the jungle or you're new to the Donkey Kong world, Donkey Kong Country keeps you on your toes with platform challenges, dance minigames, and unique enemies.Cheat: Bonus StageTo see the sound test menu and listen to music from the game, at the start screen, hold select button, then press B,A,L,L,A, Down. Now, youll see the Sound player.Cheat: Bonus StageAt the file select screen, go down to the erase command at the bottom of the screen. Hold select, and input the following buttons. Diddy will say ''Not Bad''. Now, load any of the three game files, and you will automatically start with 50 lives. You do not have to input this code again as long as you save.Cheat: Alternate DK Attack BackgroundUnlock photos in the picture album by finding the camera pieces in the various levels.Cheat: Exit Previously Beaten LevelsOnce you've beaten a level you can press Start and then Select in the level to exit it.Cheat: Exit Previously Beaten LevelsRight after the part where you get the frog, drop down to the ledge on the right. You will be back in the same room and you can collect the +5 multiplier again. Rinse and Repeat for as big of a time bonus as you want!</plot>
	<releasedate>9/6/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Rare Ltd.</Developer>
	<rating>8.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>PeVJq3phR6w</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3391</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589452-donkey-kong-country</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/donkey-kong-3</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3391-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3391-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/37489-donkey-kong-3-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263686-donkey-kong-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263687-donkey-kong-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-start.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263688-donkey-kong-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-shooting-pesticide.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263690-donkey-kong-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-incoming-bugs.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/3/c/gfs_47225_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/d/5/gfs_52792_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/0/5/gfs_52792_1_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/b/5/gfs_52792_1_3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/a/5/gfs_52792_1_4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3391-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3391-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3391.png</clearlogo1>
</game>