<Game>
	<Name>Super Donkey Kong 2 (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The Donkey Kong Country series returns to the Game Boy Advance in a sequel that features Dixie Kong. She and Diddy Kong must team up to rescue Donkey Kong from the evil Kaptain K. Rool. You'll play as both Diddy and Dixie, and master their different attacks. Test your skills and beat the clock in Diddy's Dash, or race against your friends to see who's the fastest. You can play the game solo or challenge your friends in new bonus games such as Funky's Flights and Bag a Bug.Cheat: CodesEnter these in the Cheats Menu.Cheat: Invincible in Funkys KongstructionDuring Funky's Challenge "Kongstruction" there are annoying Flitters everywhere that hurt you if you bump into them. At the start bump into them until you explode. When the screen says "give up?" say no and continue. Now when you bump into Flitters you won't get hurt. The only way you can get hurt is by bumping into walls. This will make the event easier.Cheat: Lost WorldTo unlock the lost world you must pass the first world. In all the other worlds, you will start to find a "Klubba's Koisk" in each world. When you visit one, a kremling named klubba will ask you to give him 15 Kremcoins. When you do you will go to the lost world. For every world their  will be a level in the lost world.Cheat: Crankys Video Game HeroesWhenever you are walking between levels (not when you are on the Gyrocopter) Press L and R at the same time, the screen should star wipe, and you will be at Cranky's Video Game Heroes hall of fame. This is where you can see your ranking with medals, against all time Nintendo heroes.Cheat: Gangplank Galley Level WarpIn the level Gangplank Galley, jump up the first barrels at the start, up where the first Bonus Barrel is. Instead of jumping inside the Bonus Barrel, jump up to the right of it, where the sun is in the background. You'll disappear and hear a sound effect, then you are taken to a "Level Warp!"-Screen. Just go into the right door. You are now directly before the end of this level!Cheat: Gangplank Galley Level WarpOn the world Gloomy Gulch, the level ghostly grave you can easily get 99 lives. For this to work you need both kongs.Cheat: Gangplank Galley Level WarpRight at the start of the level before you move press the 'R' to make one of the kongs jump on the other. Throw the kong upwards killing the enemy. Then press 'R' again and jump and throw the kong up and left. You will land on a cliff off the screen and gain 3 lives. After you do this press 'start' then press 'select' to exit the level. Repeat as many times as needed to get 99 lives.Cheat: Gangplank Galley Level WarpNote: you must beat this level atleast once for this trick to work.</plot>
	<releasedate>15/11/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Platform, 2D</genre>
	<Developer>Rare Ltd.</Developer>
	<rating>8.8</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>3392</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919611-donkey-kong-country-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/donkey-kong-3</mobygames_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3392-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3392-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/37489-donkey-kong-3-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263686-donkey-kong-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263687-donkey-kong-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-start.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263688-donkey-kong-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-shooting-pesticide.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/263690-donkey-kong-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-incoming-bugs.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/3/b/gfs_54950_1_1.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/e/b/gfs_54950_1_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/5/b/gfs_54950_1_3.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/4/b/gfs_54950_1_4.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/f/b/gfs_54950_1_5.jpg</snapshot9>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3392-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3392-g.jpg</banner1>
</game>