<Game>
	<Name>Super Mario Bros. (Japan) (Hot Mario Campaign)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Mario Bros. title screen.Super Mario Bros. is a fantasy platformer created by  Shigeru Miyamoto, and published by  Nintendo. The game was released in 1985 for the  Nintendo Entertainment System. Super Mario Bros. has gone on to be considered by many to be one of the best platformers ever created. The  Guinness World Records Gamer&#8217;s Edition, a record keeping organization, declared Super Mario Bros. for the NES as the  best selling video game of all time with more than 40 million copies sold worldwide.Super Mario Bros. has two direct sequels, numerous spin-offs, and has also crossed mediums--most notably into television and movies. Super Mario Bros., the movie, was the first  movie to be based on a video game.  Mario, the main character of the game, is one of Nintendo&#8217;s most recognizable mascots, and has become so famous that he is recognized worldwide.The game has been released in a variety of forms. It has been released on the  Game Boy Advance,  Super Nintendo Entertainment System,  Nintendo Entertainment System,  Wii Virtual Console, and has been featured in  Animal Crossing as a game that can be obtained through use of an  Action Replay. The game was later repackaged in  Super Mario All-Stars, along with several other early  Super Mario games.The music for the game is composed by  Koji Kondo, also well known for his compositions in games such as  The Legend of Zelda. The game's iconic "Ground Theme" has been used in dozens of games since, and it is now considered the "theme song" of the  Mario series. The game's other songs, such as the Starman theme, underwater, underground, the game over jingle, and the castle themes have also been featured in dozens of future games, not limited to the Mario series.Story: The Mushroom Kingdom is invaded by the  Koopas. The Koopas are a tribe of turtle-like creatures versed in the ways of black magic. Using their black magic abilities they have turned all the Mushroom people into various objects like stones and bricks. Their leader, the evil Koopa King  Bowser, has kidnapped the only person who can undo the black magic that has trapped the Mushroom people,  Princess Toadstool. Mario hears of the plight of the Mushroom people, grabs his brother  Luigi, and sets out on a quest to free Princess Toadstool.Gameplay:The gameplay of Super Mario Bros. is simple. The game has eight worlds, and each world has four sub-levels. Basically, Mario must travel through all eight worlds, avoiding obstacles and enemies along the way. At the end of each world is a castle, in which Mario must fight one of Bowser&#8217;s evil minions; with the exception of the last castle in which Mario fights Bowser himself.Mario swims through World 2-2.There were also several chances to  Warp ahead and skip levels. World 1-2 had the ability to warp to Worlds 2, 3 or 4, and World 4-2 had the ability to warp worlds 6, 7 and 8. This allowed for the  Speedruns to become common.The weapons in Mario's arsenal are not vast by any means. Mario can  jump on enemy&#8217;s heads, shoot  fireballs (by picking up a Fire Flower) at them, or use &#8220;Star Power&#8221; by picking up a Starman, which makes him an  invincible machine of destruction, laying waste to everything in his path. Mario can also use the occasional  Koopa shell to kill enemies. This four pronged offensive is how Mario will dispatch of most enemies, with the exception of Bowser and his castle minions. When it comes to the bosses of the game there is another way of dealing with them that is presented. Jumping on their heads will only get Mario killed, and there are no Starmen to be had during these instances. They can be killed with fireballs, if Mario somehow makes it to the end of the level with with that ability; but if Mario doesn't, there aren't many other approaches to dispatching these enemies.Mario begins the game with 3 lives, and can earn more by obtaining 1-up mushrooms, collecting 100  coins, or by jumping on multiple enemies (or a single enemy multiple times) without touching the ground. It is possible to earn many lives very quickly by using exploits such as repeatedly jumping on a Koopa shell, kicking it into a block, and jumping on it again as it returns. If Mario loses all his lives, the player is returned to the start screen.All of the the bosses in the game are standing on bridges over pits of lava, blocking the way to the end of the level. At the end of each bridge is an ax. Using a platform above the boss or running underneath the boss when he jumps, and then touching the ax at the end of the bridge will cause the bridge to collapse, sending the boss into the lava below.After each one of the &#8220;boss&#8221; battles a mushroom retainer (aka  Toads) is saved who says this  famous line, &#8220;Thank you Mario! But our princess is in another castle!&#8221; The exception is, of course, when Mario finally beats Bowser in World 8-4 and rescues  Princess Peach.Characters: Mario - Main character of the game. The character the player assumes when playing the game in single player mode, and the character used by player one in two player mode. Bowser - King of the Koopas and the main boss of the game. Luigi - Secondary character of the game. Mario&#8217;s brother and character used by player two when in two player mode. Mushroom Retainer (Toads) - The mushroom person that is saved in the castles at the end of each world, with the exception of the last castle. Princess Toadstool - Princess of Mushroom Kingdom and the only one who can undo the Koopa&#8217;s black magic.Enemies: Blooper &#8211; Underwater squid-like creatures that must be killed with fireballs. Bullet Bill &#8211; Bullets that are fired, either with a cannon, or off-screen, at Mario. Buzzy Beetle &#8211; A tough beetle-like creature with a hard, outer shell that cannot be hurt by fire. Cheep Cheep &#8211; Red and yellow fish with white undersides. Under water this enemy must be killed using fireballs. Out of water they can be killed by fireball, jumping on them, or touching them when the player possesses "Star-Power." Goomba &#8211; A small mushroom like enemy with feet that is susceptible to any of the four main attack methods. Koopa Troopa &#8211; A turtle-like enemy. Jumping on this enemy will cause it to go into its shell, and if the shell is then jumped on it will send it traveling either right or left and take out any enemies in its path. This enemy is susceptible to any of the four main attack methods. Lakitu &#8211; A koopa who rides on a cloud, showering Mario with spiny eggs. These eggs turn into Spinies (see below). Paratroopa &#8211; Basically Koopa Troopas with wings. When jumped on, they lose their wings and turn into Koopa Troopas. This enemy is susceptible to any of the four main attack methods. Spiny &#8211; These koopas are thrown by Lakitu, and come covered in spikes. They can be hurt by fireballs, or when touched by a player possessing "Star-Power."Power Ups 1-UP &#8211; A green mushroom that grants Mario an extra life. Fire Flower &#8211; Gives Mario the ability to shoot fireballs. Mario must already be in the &#8220;Super&#8221; form to gain the fireball ability; otherwise it has the same affect as the Super Mushroom. Starman &#8211; Makes Mario or Luigi invincible, with the exception of falling into holes, and grants the ability to kill enemies just by touching them. Normally Mario must jump on an enemy, shoot it with fireballs, or use a Koopa shell to kill them. Super  Mushroom &#8211; This makes Mario bigger. In essence it transforms Mario or Luigi into &#8220;Super Mario&#8221; or &#8220;Super Luigi.&#8221; It also gives them the ability to take an extra hit; however, when hit they lose the &#8220;Super,&#8221; and are reduced to regular Mario or Luigi.Notable Ports and Remakes Vs. Super Mario Bros. All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. Super Mario Bros. Special Super Mario Bros. Deluxe Super Mario All-Stars Super Mario All-Stars &amp; Super Mario World Classic NES Series: Super Mario Bros. Super Mario Bros. / Duck Hunt Super Mario Bros. / Duck Hunt / World Class Track MeetReception:In November 1986, the Milwaukee Journal described the original NES version of Super Mario Bros as "the best video game this year".In the March 1986 issue of Computer and Video Games, Clare Edgeley gave the arcade version, Vs. Super Mario Bros, a positive review.Legacy:Super Mario Bros. (and the Nintendo Entertainment System) were released at a major turning point in video game history, shortly after the infamous video game market crash in 1983 (caused by oversaturation of the market with budget, low-quality games). Marketed as more of a toy than a "video game console," the NES was able to find its success due, in part, to Super Mario Bros., which was offered along with a purchase of a new console, rendering it one of the best selling games of all time.The game popularized the "side-scrolling platformer" genre, inspiring clones and lookalikes for several generations following its initial release. Even the NES itself found dozens upon dozens of side-scrolling platformers released for it, indicative of Super Mario Bros.'s effect on game development.Since its release, Super Mario Bros. has been regarded as one of the most influential games of all time. It is consistently placed on official "top games of all time" lists, including lists from publications such as Nintendo Power, Electronic Gaming Monthly, IGN, Screw Attack, Game Informer, and many, many more.Release Date ControversyThere is minor controversy regarding the actual date of Super Mario Bros.'s release. While the game's official release date in Japan is recorded and well known, its release date in North America is highly disputed, and even the year is uncertain. Several sources cite the release date as 1986, including video game historian Steven Kent.Official Nintendo sources state the release date is October 18, 1985, which is reciprocated in  Super Smash Bros. Brawl's "Chronicle" section. Supposedly, the game was released coinciding with the release of the NES, however, its original release date is also lost. Other possible release dates include October 12, October 19, and another official Nintendo provided date of November 17, 1985.Cheat: Shoot Fireballs as Small Mario:Go to either 1-4, 2-4,3-4, etc. and get to Bowser. Make sure you are Big Mario and try to jump over Bowser or run under him. Stand near the Axe and Bowser will start to walk towards you. As he gets near you, jump high, and touch Bowser and the Axe at the same time. If you do it correctly, you will hear the sound as if you were to shrink, but you will just flash and stay as Big Mario. Go to the next stage, and get a Mushroom. (Yes, there will be a Mushroom instead of a Fire Flower.) When you touch the Mushroom, you will shrink. Then get a Fire Flower, and you'll have Fire Power as Small Mario. (Note: after you do the Bowser/Axe trick, enemies that touch you will be able to kill you when you are Big Mario. When they touch you while you are Small Mario after getting the Mushroom or Fire Flower, you will turn back into Big Mario.) Cheat: Shoot Fireballs as Small Mario:In World 1-2, execute the Minus World glitch as described below. However, rather than enter the leftmost warp pipe, enter the one in the middle of the three that are normally there. This would normally take you to World 3 - however, it will now bring you to World 5.Cheat: World SelectAfter beating the game, if you do not turn off the console, you will return to the title screen. There, you can press the B Button to start as desired in World 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, or 8.Cheat: Minus WorldGo to world 1-2. At the end of the level, there is a pipe, and some bricks. You must smash the second to last brick and the third to last brick as seen to the left.Now you must stand on the edge of the pipe, duck, and face leftNow jump to the right towards the one block that you didn't break, while facing leftYou should slide right through the bricks, go into the first pipe when you get to the other side.Cheat: Minus WorldYou should be warped to the minus world, the level is -1.Cheat: Continue Game after a Game OverIf you ever find yourself with a Game Over, and you would like to continue from what world you were on, wait for the 1/2 Player select screen, then hold A and press Start. Now you will start at the first level of the World in which you obtained the Game Over from. For example, if you got the Game Over from 7-3, you will start over again at 7-1!Cheat: Continue Game after a Game OverIn order to get fireworks to go off after you beat a level, simply finish the level when the last number in the Time is either a 1, 3, or 6. The number of fireworks you get depends on that number. So finish a level with 106 remaining, and you'll get 6 fireworks to explode. Plus, you get bonus points for each firework that goes off.Cheat: Continue Game after a Game Over               In world 4-2 you will come across a moving platform.  Jump past the platforms until you see a ledge with three blocks.  Go just left of the first block and jump, you will reveal a secret block.  Go over under the second block and jump (rember to leave the space under the first block empty) and jump under the third block to reveal another hidden block.  Jump on top of the blocks and start destroying the blocks until you find a vine growing out one of them.  Climb up the vine to reach an area with lots of coins. go right until you find some stairs.  jump on top of them and walk rigth.  Now you can warp to levels 6, 7, and 8.Cheat: Continue Game after a Game OverDuring World 1-2, go to the end of the level and get on the rising platforms. Now jump onto the TOP of the level and go right until you reach three pipes. You can now warp to either World 2, 3 or 4.Cheat: Continue Game after a Game OverAt the end of World 4-2, jump onto the top of the screen and keep walking until you drop into a room with a warp pipe.  It leads to World 5.</plot>
	<releasedate>7/6/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>MrtGe_UrZLA</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>22227</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919774-classic-nes-series-super-mario-bros</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/super-mario-bros</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-mario-bros/3030-15544/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22227-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/104936-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-back-cover.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/104937-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464557-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/696790-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-screenshot-first-world.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/696791-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-screenshot-game-starts.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/696792-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-screenshot-secret-room.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/696793-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-screenshot-level-completed.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/696794-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-screenshot-underground-level.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/696795-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-screenshot-koopa-troopa.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/696796-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-screenshot-moving-platform.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/696797-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pretty-hard-jumping.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/696798-super-mario-bros-game-boy-advance-screenshot-life-lost.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/sb2lwsJ.jpg</banner1>
</game>