<Game>
	<Name>Super Street Fighter II Turbo - Revival (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Super Street Fighter II: Turbo Revival is the first Street Fighter game to be released on the Game Boy Advance and features all 17 characters from Super Street Fighter II Turbo. Some new stages were introduced exclusively for this version as well as bonus modes like survival. Since the Street Fighter games have relied on a 6-button pad layout, the overall control was significantly altered on this Game Boy Advance version to only four buttons of weak and strong punches and kicks.Characters:AkumaRyuKenE. HondaChun-LiGuileZangiefDhalsimBlankaBalrogVegaSagatM. BisonCammyDee JayT. HawkFei-LongCritical ReceptionGame Informer gave the review scores of 9 and 8.75 out of ten. Justin wrote, "...The sprites are very detailed, and show up clearly on the GBA screen, even in less than optimal lighting... Amazingly, gameplay is near perfect, even with only four buttons. It's kind of tough to quickly tap a button for medium attacks, but you get used to it. Quarter-circle and charge specials are pulled off without problem."Reiner wrote, "...it's just as amazing as any of the SNES SF ports. The bonus options add some replay value, but as a while, this fine release is purely nostalgic."Cheat: Have Akuma challenge youWhen playing through the one player mode, get at least 3 perfect victories. After you beat Sagat, instead of the "your fighter vs. M.Bison" screen it will have "your fighter vs. Akuma" instead.Cheat: Have Akuma challenge youTo have your character wear its original colors from Street Fighter 2 (for example Ryu with a red bandana and white outfit, or green Blanka), select your character by pressing the A and B buttons at the same time.Cheat: Have Akuma challenge youThere are nine colors in this game for every character, which include nearly every color in the Street Fighter II series. A: Default color, corresponds to the classic Street Fighter II color or Super Street Fighter II Jab L: Alternate color, Champion Edition, SSF2 Strong R: Turbo, SSF2 Fierce B: SSF2 Short Select + A: SSF2 Forward Select + L: SSF2 Roundhouse Select + R: SSF2 Start Select + B: SSF2 Secret, also the color you get if you hold down any other button for a few seconds Start: Super Turbo Jab color Even Akuma and Shin Akuma have all nine colors, which means they have new colors in this version not in the arcade original!</plot>
	<releasedate>31/10/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Capcom Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>3.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>H3-L0Vjr-Z8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3729</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/472721-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival/3030-9726/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/1791312-box_ssf2tr.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3729-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/210382-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34141-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/546527-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34142-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34143-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34144-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/34145-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/80240-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/80241-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/80242-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/80243-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-revival-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/zDqjLrl.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3729.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Capcom's timeless Street Fighter masterpiece conquers the Game Boy Advance system. Choose from over 16 brawlers from the Street Fighter universe and execute special moves, and super combos to wreak havoc on your opponent and become the best street fighter in the world. Lightning fast animation, unbelievable graphics and Capcom's signature gameplay make Super Street Fighter II Turbo the most respected fighting game of all time.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/60fdd22f-66e4-461a-8cca-5d1ceb90ea4c.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d8af90dd-1e0a-4ac9-8e89-0a9f988cf45e.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a03fcf18-ff3a-44bb-aeb7-3423a50084b1.png</boxart3>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0e9c4f33-64da-48ab-86ec-08d8d6778f62.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>