<Game>
	<Name>Tak 2 - The Staff of Dreams (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Plot:Tak had been asleep for 16 days since his last adventure. He had a dream when the Dream Juju told him to defeat the Dream Guardian, take the Staff of Dreams and rescue the princess. Tak was later guided to a rift. He was woken up by Lok's smelly armpit BO. Jibolba tasked Tak to find his brother JB and he transformed into a flea. Lok wanted to come too. Tak and Jibolba reached a dead end and summoned the Belly Juju for making a raft. But first, Belly Juju wanted a barrel of candy. Tak later used the barrel as a raft. At the rapids, Tak returned to the Dream World. Tak went into another rift. Tak let Lok provide a distraction to the Woodies. Tak summoned the Mind-Reader Juju who told him to find 3 magic stones as bolas. Tak was later knocked out and sent to the Dream World. Tak was sent to a rift and woke up in the Gloomleaf Arena. Caged Juju asked Tak what is in the box. Tak guessed many times until he thought there was nothing in the box. Inside the box was Lok. Tak took a key to battle 4 waves of woodies. He uses a catapult to escape. In the swamp, Tak saw Dead Juju being harrassed by woodies who took his tiki. Tak goes back to the arena and steals the Tiki back from the Woodie King. Dead Juju agrees to go with Tak, Jibolba and Lok. At the exterior of JB's Planetarium, Tak and his friends were sleeping due to the flowers. At the Dream World, Tak uses a catapult to break the Dream Guardian's tower. He went back to a rift and woke up. Tak and Jibolba left Lok and Dead Juju behind. At JB's planetarium, JB needed help with the Power Parasites. After the battle, JB helped Tak go to sleep but never heard of a Dream Juju. At the tower in the dream world, Tak defeated the Dream Guardian and rescued the princess. But the princess was actually Pins and Needles. The Dream Juju was also revealed to be Tlaloc (in his sheep form). Tlaloc used Tak to defeat the Dream Guardian so he can steal the Staff of Dreams. Tak and Pins and Needles struggled for the staff but it broke into two and they were sent into the real world. Needles used the Staff of Nightmares to create a rift. Tak was later knocked out. In his dream, he was met by the Moon Juju to pick one of four spirit animals. She was about to say the best one (which is jaguar), but lost connection. Tak picked an animal and woke up with new powers. Tak met the Giant Misunderstanding Juju to open a rift. The Juju thought he wanted to talk to Rick. Rick told Tak to ask him if he wants to talk to Rick. The Juju finally opened a rift. Tak told him goodbye but the Juju decided to sing a song. Moon Juju's daughters, Flora and Fauna gave Tak the power to transform into a bear, a squirrel, a boar and a frog. Tak chased Pins and Needles constantly until Tak went into the Dream Fortress. When Tak defeated Pins and Needles, Lok grabbed the Staff of Nightmares and unintentionally gave it to Tlaloc. Tak battles Tlaloc but both became Dream Guardians. After the battle Tak apologizes to the Dream Guardian and gives the full Staff of Dreams back. The Dream Guardian helps Tak return to reality. Dead Juju, Lok and Tak give Tlaloc the final blow. It has been revealed that the events are a dream. Tak slept for 16 days and told Jibolba and Lok about the story. Tlaloc's evil black sheep came running towards them. It has been implied that the events will happen.Features:OldJujus that help Tak on his questAnimals on enviorments.Comedic scenesNewGoing from the Dream World to the Real World4 new jujus.Shapeshifting into 4 different animalsThrowing Jibolba (flea form) at enemies or animalsDinky Temple: A minigame marathon with different characters to play as. The minigames were based off of the Tak and the Power of Juju game.New enemy types including Woodies and Nightmare Creatures.Tak can glide.No hub worlds.Making Juju potions by using Recipe CardsRecipe Cards give the amount of Bugs, Crystals and Fruit.Juju Potions unlock extrasCharacters:Tak: The warrior of the Pupanunu people's prophecy.Jibolba: The great shaman who shapeshifts into a flea to help Tak.Lok: Tak and Jibolba's friend who wanted to come with them.JB: Jibolba's brother who is an expert in the Dream World.Tlaloc: 16 days ago, he was transformed into a sheep by Tak.Pins: A minion of Tlaloc.Needles: A silent minion of Tlaloc.Rick: A man who was unintentionally summoned by the Giant Misunderstanding.Dream Guardian: Protector of the Staff of Dreams.JujuBelly Juju: A juju who uses his belly to talk.Mind-Reader Juju: A juju who reads minds.Caged Juju: A demon sealed in a cage for 10,000 years.Dead Juju: A skeleton juju who likes to party.Flora: Daughter of the Moon Juju.Fauna: A rowdy daughter of the Moon Juju.Moon Juju: A female juju who gives Tak the choice of 1 of 4 Spirit Animals.Dinky Juju: The host of the Dinky Temple games.Giant Misunderstanding Juju: A giant who cannot hear from far away.Dream Juju: A juju that guides Tak in the Dream World.Cheat: The Yorbel Game TrickAll you have to do is first start the yorbel game. On the screen which has 'SPIN?' written on it , select 'YES' . After selecting 'YES" a big triangular dial will start revolving. To get the dial to stop at your desired 'item' , then while the dial is spinning press the A button on the item directly opposite to the desired item........If done correctly, the dial will stop on the item you wanted! </plot>
	<releasedate>11/10/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>THQ Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4040</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920452-tak-2-the-staff-of-dreams</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/tak-2-the-staff-of-dreams_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tak-2-the-staff-of-dreams/3030-1274/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/4040-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4040-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/160139-tak-2-the-staff-of-dreams-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/409566-tak-2-the-staff-of-dreams-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/409567-tak-2-the-staff-of-dreams-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/409568-tak-2-the-staff-of-dreams-game-boy-advance-screenshot-opening.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/409569-tak-2-the-staff-of-dreams-game-boy-advance-screenshot-starting.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/409570-tak-2-the-staff-of-dreams-game-boy-advance-screenshot-i-need.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/7/e/gfs_54150_1_1.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/a/e/gfs_54150_1_2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/1/e/gfs_54150_1_3.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/0/e/gfs_54150_1_4.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/6/b/e/gfs_54150_1_5.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/4040-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/4040.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The gameplay is almost identical to the original Tak Game, whereas Tak's weapon is always on hand and mana is represented by feather count and not a meter. The game takes place in various locations, such as tropical forests, canyons, volcanic areas, snowy tundras and other harsh environments. There are also a number of dimensional stages, in the Dreamworld. Tak gets aid from animals, a number of which did not appear in the first game. In this game, Tak's juju magic is triggered by holding down one button and pressing combos of other buttons. Tak also earns juju powers gradually throughout the game instead of having to seek them out.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6068e140-5942-4e7a-92f4-4d80717af577.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e588caf5-cedb-408d-bfd9-30beb2f20cf4.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/e079f1be-77fe-48e3-8ef4-c1c1178b75fa.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>THQ</Publisher>
</game>