<Game>
	<Name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Double Pack (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Run with the Turtle dudes as they show off their Ninja abilities against feirce opponents. Only the best can turn chaos into control with simultaneous play for up to four players in both cooperative and head-to-head modes on TMNT 2. Combine different movements for a wide range of actions, including Ninja kicks and jumps.Cheat: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Unlock Very Hard ModeAt the title screen enter in the following button combination to unlock Very hard mode.Cheat: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2: Battle Nexus: Extra Race &amp;amp; Battle Level PasswordsFor the passwords below,L = LeonardoM = MichaelangeloD = DonatelloR = RaphaelS = SplinterCheat: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2: Battle Nexus: Extra Race &amp;amp; Battle Level PasswordsFor the passwords below,L = LeonardoM = MichaelangeloD = DonatelloR = RaphaelS = SplinterCheat: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2: Battle Nexus: Extra Race &amp;amp; Battle Level PasswordsFor the passwords below,L = LeonardoM = MichaelangeloD = DonatelloR = RaphaelS = SplinterCheat: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Shredders Tower levelComplete all levels on Normal mode to unlock Shredder's Tower secret level.Cheat: At the title screenCheat: In password menu enter this password to unlock each courseCheat: This is a little "exception" glitch I found while fighting Casey Jones with Raphael.Cheat: Simply put, if you beat on Casey without knocking him down, he's never whip out his baseball bats after he gets down to half his health.Cheat: Complete all levels on Normal mode to unlock Shredder's Tower secret level.Cheat: Enter these codes at the password screen:Cheat: At the title screen, press:Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Left, Right, B, A</plot>
	<releasedate>6/6/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Compilation</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>20887</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/932259-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-double-pack</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/1/1/74211_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/2/1/2/74212_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/0/9/gfs_74012_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/d/9/gfs_74012_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/d/1/gfs_74579_1_1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/0/1/gfs_74579_1_2.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/b/1/gfs_74579_1_3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/a4QCCpT.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>With the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2-Pack, you'll get a double-shot of classic ninja-bustin' action with Leonardo, Michaelangelo, Donatello and Raphael! Run with the Turtle dudes as they show off their new Ninja abilities against all-new opponents. Features Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Battle Nexus &amp; Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Mutant Melee.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7a28cf6b-adf2-4a20-b23e-39922c27ecda.jpg</boxart3>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>