<Game>
	<Name>Three Stooges, The (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Save the Orphanage!The Three Stooges was originally released in 1987 for several different systems. It has been ported and remade for numerous other times in the future. The remakes never changed the core gameplay, but usually updated the graphics. The most recent remakes were for the Gameboy Advance and Playstation in 2002. Plot:An evil banker wants to shut down an orphanage in a greedy scheme to make money. The only way to save the orphanage is to pay the banker the money he demands. The Three Stooges step in and take on the task by doing odd jobs to make money. Failure to meet the bankers price means the orphanage is lost. Gameplay:Levels are based on classic slapstick comedyThe Three Stooges is made up of several mini games that put the player in control of classic Stooge moments. The game covers several genres of gameplay with action, platform and trivia levels. You have thirty days to make enough money and on each day you complete a game. You are never able to choose the game because it is randomly picked for you. Levels may have you going through grocery stores and hospitals causing havoc, working in a restaurants, or retrieving a violin to play curly pop goes the weasel. Other games will allow you to answer classic Three Stooges trivia. There are also bad levels that will have paying the banker taxes or bills. There are several endings to the game depending on the amount of money you make. These endings give the player incentive to keep playing the game in order to see them all. The failed ending will have the banker taking the orphanage, but the rest are different win scenarios. </plot>
	<releasedate>31/3/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Metro3D, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.3</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4030</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561079-the-three-stooges</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/three-stooges</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-three-stooges/3030-7201/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/4030-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4030-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/461383-the-three-stooges-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-stooges.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/461384-the-three-stooges-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/461385-the-three-stooges-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/461387-the-three-stooges-game-boy-advance-screenshot-product-placement.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/461389-the-three-stooges-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/461390-the-three-stooges-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/461391-the-three-stooges-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-general.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/461393-the-three-stooges-game-boy-advance-screenshot-found-some-money.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/461394-the-three-stooges-game-boy-advance-screenshot-trivia-game.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/461395-the-three-stooges-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-trivia-question.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/4030-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/4030-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/4030.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Moe, Larry &amp; Curly starring in their own Cinemaware Interactive Movie? Why coitanly! Nyuk. Nyuk. Nyuk. Join those zany masters of mirth as they try to save an old lady and her 3 beautiful daughters from the clutches of an evil banker. You'll love the eyepopping graphics and animation. And the voices and sound effects digitized from their classic films! You'll maneuver the Stooges through prizefighting, pie throwing and medical madness in the famous "Calling Dr. Howard, Dr. Fine, Dr. Howard" scene. It's like starring in a Stooges movie!</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c009049e-9723-4deb-8991-855aae5de783.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b63dce72-3c89-4e4c-8d1b-f8f03570f1da.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/77a5dec3-b7fd-42db-8944-6969007746c4.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Metro3D</Publisher>
</game>