<Game>
	<Name>Tiny Toon Adventures - Wacky Stackers (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>A Tiny Toon themed drop-down puzzle game comparable to Tetris and Columns. The player has to create clusters of equally colored eggs which cause explosive chain reactions, trying to clear the screen. Playable against computer or against up to four human competitors via Link Cable. Particularly effective moves cause additional elements to be send to the other players screens. The player can also invoke special moves to be executed by Tiny Toon characters by collecting coins.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2001</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Swing! Entertainment Media AG</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>26154</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/520728-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers/3030-3587/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2280534-box_ttaws.png</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/69370-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/69371-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/69372-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/69373-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/69374-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/69375-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/69376-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/69379-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/69377-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/69380-tiny-toon-adventures-wacky-stackers-game-boy-advance-screenshot.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>What happens when you take classic puzzle gaming and toss in some of the most lovable characters in cartoon history? You get one undeniably awesome game. Buster Bunny, Plucky Duck, and the rest of the TINY TOONS crew are ready for fun, and you're in the driver's seat. The basic premise of this addicting, original title is to arrange pairs of colored eggs, dropping them onto the screen to create combinations. Of course, there are numerous obstacles and would-be detractors to make things more difficult (UFOs, Tasmanian Devils), and time is never on your side. There are plenty of characters from the animated series along for the adventure including Hampton J. Pig and Fifi La Fume and each is prepared for puzzle-style battle. As many as four players can link up to see who has the quickest reflexes, and there are plenty of single-player modes to keep you busy as well. If you're a TINY TOONS fan, this one is a must-have. If you're not a fan well, you should be.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0a1d8b2d-2601-4841-b549-588d4d4784d5.jpg</boxart2>
	<Publisher>Conspiracy Entertainment</Publisher>
</game>