<Game>
	<Name>TMNT (USA) (En,Fr,Es)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:TMNT is a single player action/adventure video game starring the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles. It is based on the 2007 CGI movie. The game was released for the Xbox 360, Wii, PlayStation 2, and Nintendo GameCube consoles, as well as for the PC on March 20, 2007. Versions where also made for the Game Boy Advance, PSP, and Nintendo DS. The PlayStation 3 version of the game was canceled.Story:The story closely follows the plot of the 2007 animated film, adding various game lengthening objectives like many movie-game tie-ins. At the start of the game, the turtles aren't currently fighting crime, but essentially off on their own. Leonardo is in the jungles of Central America, searching for a mystical artifact (this artifact will later allow him to phase through solid objects). Raphael is a motorcycle riding, chain-wielding vigilante known only as Nightwatcher. Donatello and Michelangelo are both working real jobs (Don is Tech Support, Mikey is a party clown). The initial levels follow a single turtle, acting as a tutorial on each turtle's play style. After completing each turtle's level, the story pushes forward and the turtles are once again reunited, allowing the player to control all four turtles at will.The main story line involves a warlord from 3,000 years in the past, opening a gate to an alternate dimension with his four generals. When the gate opens, the general becomes immortal, his generals turned to stone, and 13 monsters are let loose into the world. As the story progresses, the turtles must fight the four stone generals, and various monsters.Gameplay:The gameplay in the console, Nintendo DS, and PSP, TMNT contains many acrobatic segments similar to Ubisoft's Prince of Persia, though these segments are more streamlined and easy to do. The game features sixteen levels, after completing a story level, a corresponding challenge level is unlocked. The game also features five playable characters, each with their own unique fighting style and abilities. Michelangelo can use his nunchuks as makeshift helicopter propellers to hover over long pitfalls, Donatello can jump over long gaps using his bo staff as a pole-vault. Raphael can use his sais to climb certain walls, and Leonardo can phase through certain obstacles. The fifth character is Nightwatcher, who is just Raphael in a vigilante costume, and uses the same move set. At the end of each level you&#8217;re given a grade, and the coins you collect in each stage can be used to buy extras like artwork, challenge levels, videos, and a big head mode.The Game Boy Advance version of TMNT is different from the console, Nintendo DS, and PSP versions. Instead of a platformer, it is a brawler similar to the  the  two Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle arcade games. The player can pick up money dropped by enemies to purchase new moves. Some levels also include mini-challenges hosted by  Casey Jones or  Splinter.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/3/2007</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ubisoft, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>o82Ll_qOU00</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4032</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/937405-tmnt</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/tmnt_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tmnt/3030-4443/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/4032-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4032-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/84975-tmnt-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/229270-tmnt-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/229271-tmnt-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-have-three-game-slots.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/229272-tmnt-game-boy-advance-screenshot-there-are-several-stages.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/229273-tmnt-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-game-tells-its-story.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/229274-tmnt-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-cutscenes-feature-snapshots.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/229275-tmnt-game-boy-advance-screenshot-your-turtle-poses-dramatically.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/229279-tmnt-game-boy-advance-screenshot-these-street-bums-are-the.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/229284-tmnt-game-boy-advance-screenshot-some-of-them-throw-rocks.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/229286-tmnt-game-boy-advance-screenshot-gratuitous-destruction-of.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/229291-tmnt-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-guy-can-block-most-of.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/4032-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/wElOBkl.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Over the top Ninja Action! Use acrobatic moves and extreme fighting skills to unite the Turtles and save the City. Use special weapons, such as deadly ninja starts, and unique tag-team moves. Play the famous TMNT characters, each with his own fighting style. Take on the big bosses from the TMNT movie.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2ef9e051-8615-452f-bfe6-716694d51d2e.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/35f534ee-5691-4e8e-919e-1b65c033d9b3.jpg</boxart2>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3d49c745-3294-47e1-a609-3a20b1912e11.png</boxart3>
	<boxart4>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0f2707f0-036e-47ad-895b-02b035560991.jpg</boxart4>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3afa81ef-dc73-400b-b9f2-88fdb7473bf0.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>