<Game>
	<Name>Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Pandora Tomorrow (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell: Pandora Tomorrow is the sequel to Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell and the second game in the franchise. It was developed and published by Ubisoft Shanghai while Ubisoft Montreal, the creator of the original Splinter Cell was working on the third game in the series Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell: Chaos Theory. Aside from making improvements to the single-player AI and lighting system, it was also the first game in the series to feature the Spies vs Mercenaries multiplayer mode that would be refined and featured in many of the later entries in the franchise.Single PlayerThe Stealth Action formula remains largely unchanged from the first game, although Fisher gains many new gadgets and maneuvers such as the SWAT turn and a new split jump that works in narrower spaces.The Single Player campaign begins with Sam Fisher being called in again by Third Echelon to rescue hostages in a United States Embassy in East Timor. They are being held by Suhadi Sadono, leader of the Indonesian militia organization Darah Dan Doa.Although Sadono is able to evade capture during Fisher's Embassy operation, Fisher is able to gather intel on Sadono's terrorist plan "Pandora Tomorrow." Third Echelon discovers that Sadono has hidden biological bombs equipped with smallpox throughout the United States that will detonate if Sadono is killed or detained.Because of the sensitive nature of this operation, Fisher has to infiltrate various Darah Dan Doa strongholds to interrogate other leaders of the organization, and intercept phone calls placed by Sadono to learn the locations of the Smallpox bombs.When Fisher learns the locations of all of the bombs, Third Echelon dispatches small teams of Shadownet spies into the United States to defuse them, which ties into the action in the Multiplayer campaign.Campaign MissionsDili, TimorParis, FranceParis-Nice, FranceJerusalem, IsraelKundang Camp, IndonesiaKomodo, IndonesiaJakarta, IndonesiaLos Angeles, CA, USAMultiplayer:Spy taking advantage of a MercPandora Tomorrow raised the bar for espionage themed team objective based multiplayer. Ubisoft thrived to create a unique and intimate multiplayer experience. Two teams of two, (Spies Vs Mercs), made the in-game voice chat almost a requirement for strategy and victory. Having a great partner for Spies and Mercs is essential to win almost every match. Teams must constantly fill each other in on new information such as, the location of an enemy, location of mines, sticky cams, and most commonly noise. The Mercs have excellent hearing, and arrows pop up on their hud to indicate them of nearby Spies.Spies (Stealth)Sam doing his job (Single Player)Most notably of the multiplayer is that players control Spies in third person, very similar to how Sam Fisher is controlled in the single player campaign. Instead of a pistol or rifle however, they are given long ranged tasers that can stun Mercs and disrupt their radar. These come in handy when trying to escape or to help your fellow spy from getting shot down by a raged Merc. They can also be used to explode motion sensing mines, trip mines, motion detectors. Spies can kill Mercs in a variety of ways. Luring the opponent towards an area and then have your partner come out of the shadows to grab him and snap his neck. The player can Jump on a Merc once to knock him down for a few seconds, and twice for a kill. They can also use their long ranged tasers to shoot wall mines and explode Mercs nearby.The object of the game is simple, (Neutralization), hack a terminal before a Merc kills you or the time runs out. However, their are other game modes such as, (Extraction), steal glowing tubes, and (Sabotage). Sabotage was too difficult for inexperienced players and was not popular among the online community. It is the same feeling people have about Gears of War's Assassination mode. On the Optimatch you will mostly want to try to find Neutralization since it is the most mun and balanced. Speaking of balancing issues, Ubisoft manages to give a pretty frustrating life count for both Mercs and Spies. This issue will only affect newcomers to the online multiplayer and "bad" players alike. Mercs are given three lives to start, and Spies are given four. It takes a while getting use to, however the balancing seems alright once you find a consistent friend to play along side with you.EquipmentSmoke GrenadeFlashbangChaff GrenadeSticky CameraSpy BulletAlarm SnareMercs (Run and Gun)Very similar to your typical online shooter in that it is in first person. This concept is to give Spies more a chance during multiplayer consider that spies can only use non-equipment. On the other hand, Mercs have guns, loud guns. Actually it is just one machine gun that can zoom in for a sniper shot and It can also be set to fully automatic or burst. Almost every piece of equipment is lethal, mines, tazor, and melee. Mercs can rush up on spies and tackle them down. A good Merc will know that carefully placed motion sensing mines is the best way to kill spies. Grenades work quite well, and trip mines are a must near vent shoots. Sniping is another way to take out a spy if he is hacking a terminal too far to reach in time.The Mercs objective in all game modes is to kill Spies. Taking out all of the Spy team's lives will result in victory. Similarly, Spies can win if the Merc team's lives run out.EquipmentFrag GrenadeMinePhosphorescent GrenadeSpy TrapFlareTaserMultiplayer LevelsCinema (Community favorite)Deftech-Blew (Pros only)Krauser Labs (Pros only)Mount Hospital (Community favorite)Museum (Community favorite)Schermerhorn (Pros only)Vertigo Plaza (Community favorite)Warehouse (Majority favorite)Ranking SystemLevel 1: 0 pointsLevel 2: 60 pointsLevel 3: 180 pointsLevel 4: 360 pointsLevel 5: 600 pointsLevel 6: 1000 pointsLevel 7: 1500 pointsOriginal System RequirementsMinimum:Supported OS: Windows&#174; 98/ME/2000/XP (only)Processor: 1 GHz Pentium&#174; III or AMD Athlon&#8482; processorRAM: 256 MBVideo Card: 64 MB DirectX&#174; 8.1-compliant video card (see supported list*)Sound Card: DirectX 8.1-compliant audio cardDirectX Version: DirectX 8.1 (DirectX 9.0 included on disc)CD-ROM: 8X CD or 4X DVD (16X CD recommended)Hard Drive Space: 3 GBPeripherals: Windows-compatible mouse and keyboard required (Game pads and joysticks not supported)Multiplay: Broadband modem, 64 Kbps uploadRecommended:Supported OS: Windows XPProcessor: 1.8 GHz Pentium 4 or equivalentRAM: 512 MBVideo Card: 128 MB DirectX 8.1-compliant video card (see supported list*)Sound Card: DirectX 8.1 compliant and EAX&#8482;DirectX Version: DirectX 9.0 (included on disc)CD-ROM: 16X CDHard Drive Space: 3 GBPeripherals: Windows-compatible keyboard and mouse with wheel; headset optional (Game pads and joysticks not supported)Multiplay: Broadband modem, 128 Kbps upload*Supported video cards at time of release: ATI&#174; 8500/9000 families NVIDIA&#174; GeForce&#8482; 3/4/FX familiesCheat: Disable TurretsCut the colored wires in the displayed order to disarm the turrets. These sequences only effect the turrets with only those colored wires.Cheat: Disable TurretsEnter these when hacking a computer:</plot>
	<releasedate>23/3/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Ubisoft, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>5.0</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>XiDVypTWSko</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>3700</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919789-tom-clancys-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/tom-clancys-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tom-clancys-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow/3030-15549/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2280528-box_tpscpt.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3700-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/299031-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464206-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464207-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464208-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464209-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464210-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464211-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464212-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464213-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464214-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464215-tom-clancy-s-splinter-cell-pandora-tomorrow-game-boy-advance.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3700-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/3700-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ualLCtN.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/3700.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>The gameplay of Pandora Tomorrow is largely unchanged from the original Splinter Cell. The game features some moderate graphical improvements, as well as minor gameplay changes such as the fact that health kits are no longer an inventory item, and the addition of a laser sight to Sam's pistol that allows the player to know exactly where the rounds will strike, even when moving around. Also, Sam can now open doors while carrying a body, shoot while hanging upside down, SWAT turn past doorways unnoticed, and perform a half split jump.</Notes>
	<VideoURL1>XiDVypTWSko</VideoURL1>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/18008e5a-93d7-454c-ac3d-3b78585b8fa0.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5097b4f2-fb21-49cb-aaad-cf77ed9ab078.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/01978a4d-4cdc-40ad-be25-c29a1a7e9488.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Ubisoft</Publisher>
</game>