<Game>
	<Name>Tony Hawk's Underground 2 (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Nothing weird going on here...Tony Hawk's Underground 2 is a skateboarding game developed by Neversoft and published by Activision or the PlayStation 2, Xbox, GameCube, and PC on October 4, 2004. The sixth installment of the long-running Tony Hawk franchise, the game features a new story mode starring the player's custom skater (similar to its predecessor, Tony Hawk's Underground). In the story, the player is kidnapped by professional skaters Tony Hawk and Bam Margera, only to find that they are staging a "World Destruction Tour", a crazy unpublicized around-the-world skateboarding tour (complete with intense vandalism and complete havoc, similar to the Jackass franchise) where the skaters (both professional and novice) are split up into two teams: Team Hawk and Team Bam. As part of Team Hawk, players try to complete crazy objectives in each location to earn "points" for their team.Along with the new Story Mode, the game includes a new Classic Mode, which replicates the Career Mode from the first three Tony Hawk games (consisting of ten-goal, two-minute sessions), complete with the return of Stat Point pickups. Along with the levels from Story Mode, Classic Mode includes levels from the first three Tony Hawk games: School and Downhill Jam from Tony Hawk's Pro Skater, Philadelphia from Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2, and Airport, Canada, and Los Angeles from Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3. Warehouse from Tony Hawk's Pro Skater is also expanded in both Classic Mode and Story Mode as the game's tutorial level.Two handheld versions of the game were released: one for the Game Boy Advance (developed by Vicarious Visions) and one for the PSP. The Game Boy Advance version, released at the same time as the console versions, maintains the 2D isometric gameplay from the handheld versions of the previous five installments of the franchise. The PSP version, released on March 15, 2005, is titled Tony Hawk's Underground 2 Remix and features four new levels.Tony Hawk's Underground 2, like previous installments in the series, features crossover characters from different franchises as hidden playable skaters: Shrek (a cartoon ogre from the DreamWorks franchise of the same name) and an American World War II soldier from the Call of Duty franchise. Players can also unlock the Tony Hawk model from the original Tony Hawk's Pro Skater as a playable skater.Story ModeYou begin the game by creating a character, or using the default created skater. The game starts when your created skater (or the default) is seen ripping it up at a local spot, and is promptly grabbed and tossed into a black van. Inside you find other skaters who have been kidnapped. Then, Bam Margera and Tony Hawk explain their plans for the first annual World Destruction Tour, a "sick-as-hell" around-the-world skateboarding tour. The main goal of the World Destruction Tour is to create havoc, and have a good time. The skaters then split into two teams, Team Hawk and Team Bam, and you are picked last out of the group, but join Team Hawk. The tour goes to real world locations like Boston, Spain, Australia, New Orleans, and more, with the two teams competing for points by doing silly and dangerous stunts. The story is very lighthearted and just plain silly at times, featuring such characters like Big Foot, and skeletons doing the bidding of the dead. You briefly join Team Bam but it doesn't work out, and you rejoin Team Hawk. Later in the game, the teams meet Nigel Beaverhausen, a strange documentarist, who wants to film the tour for the public. Both teams refuse, and instead play a joke on him. After meeting with him the second time they agree, but only because he promises to pay for the whole trip. The game ends at Skatopia, a skaters heaven. Here, your character ruins Bam's planned firework destruction of the place when he gets out of control, thus ending the Destruction Tour.Gameplay:Damn kids!You can skate around in a 3D environment modeled after various cities and attempts to complete various goals. Most goals involve skating on or over various objects or performing combos. In this game you can play as mutiple characters in the story mode as you find them and not all of them use skateboards so you get to ride new vehicles (like a battery powered wheelchair). New features have been added to the series such as new tricks like flips and rolls. Another new feature is a graffiti spray mechanic, that allows you to create a tag and spray it wherever you desire. When you fall off of your board you can perform a 'freak out' where you get angry and get points which then can be used for a combo. You can also climb up ledges and shimmy, creating more opportunities for skating.Soundtrack:25 ta Life - Over the Years3 Inches of Blood - Deadly SinnersAesop Rock - No Jumer Cables (DJ Pawl Remix)Atmosphere - Trying to Find a BalanceAudio Two - Top Billin'Brand Nubian - Punks Jump Up to Get Beat DownCamaros - CheesecakeThe Casualties - Unknown SoldierCut Chemist - Drums of FireThe D.O.C. - Whirlwind PyramidDas Oath - Awesome RapeDead Boys - Sonic ReducerDead End Road - Sin CityThe Distillers - Beat Your Heart OutDisturbed - LiberateDiverse - CertifiedThe Doors - Break on ThroughThe Explosion - Here I AmFaith No More - Midlife CrisisFear - I Love Livin' in the CityFrank Sinatra - That's LifeThe Germs - Lexicon DevilGrand Puba - I Like ItHandsome Boy Modeling School - Holy Calamity (Bear Witness II)This Hiss - Back on the RadioJimmy Eat World - PainJohnny Cash - Ring of FireJoy Division - WarsawLamb of God - Black LabelLess Than Jake - That's Why They Call it a UnionLibretto - VolumeThe Living End - End of the WorldLiving Legends feat. Slug - Night ProwlerMelbeatz feat. Kool Savas - Grind OnMelvins - Sweet Willy RollbarMetallica - WhiplashMike V. &amp; The Rats - Never Give UpMinistry - NoNebula - So It GoesOperatic - Interested in MadnessPete Rock &amp; CL Smooth - Soul Brothers #1Ramones - Rock 'n' Roll High SchoolRancid - Fall Back DownRed Hot Chili Peppers - The Power of EqualitySteel Pulse - Born fe RebelThe Stooges - 1970The Sugarhill Gang - Rapper's DelightThe Suicide Machines - High AnxietyUltramagnetic MC's - Ego Trippin'Violent Femmes - Add It UpUnlockablesTony Hawk's Underground 2 features many unlockables. Most characters are unlocked by being discovered in story mode, but some are unlocked upon completion of the game, on different difficulty settings. There are also levels that can be unlocked upon completing Story Mode.Secret Characters:Benjamin FranklinBull FighterGraffiti TaggerJesse JamesJesterNigel BeaverhausenPaulie "Wheels Of Fury" RyanRyan ShecklerPhil MargeraShrimp VendorAlienAlien DoctorShrekGeeky KidSpace MonkeyPro Skaters:Tony HawkBob BurnquistEric KostonBam MargeraRodney MullenChad MuskaMike VallelyLevelsTraining (An expanded version of a level called "Warehouse" in THPS 1)BostonBarcelonaBerlinAustraliaNew OrleansSkatopiaPro SkaterThe TriangleSanta Cruz (THUG 2 Remix only - Would later appear as a Classic Mode level in Tony Hawk's American Wasteland)Atlanta (THUG 2 Remix only - Would later appear as a Classic Mode level in Tony Hawk's American Wasteland (For PS2 Special Edition Only)Kyoto (THUG 2 Remix only - Would later appear as a Classic Mode level in Tony Hawk's American Wasteland)Las Vegas Casino (THUG 2 Remix only - Would later appear as a run down Casino in Tony Haw's American Wasteland)Classic Mode Levels:School (of THPS1)Downhill Jam (of THPS1)Philadelphia (of THPS2)Canada (of THPS3)Airport (of THPS3)Los Angeles (of THPS3)Suburbia (of THPS3)Cheat: Graffiti editorBeat Level 1 - 2 of the Tagging minigameCheat: Misc. CheatsTo unlock these cheats, play the Stylin' Mini-gameCheat: Misc. CheatsTo Unlock Skaters Arcade Mode you must play play Tennis shooter in Story mode at least once.Cheat: MinigameOnce you unlock Bam's character on the map, talk to him. Knock down the rollerbladers, then go back. He'll give you the Tennis Shooter minigame. Once you've completed three levels, save your game to access Tennis Shooter at any time from the main menu.</plot>
	<releasedate>4/10/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Activision Publishing, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>4.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4123</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920874-tony-hawks-underground-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/tony-hawks-underground-2_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tony-hawks-underground-2/3030-1492/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/4123-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4123-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/108474-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463871-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463872-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-selecting.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463873-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-entering.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463874-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-customizing.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463875-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-hawk.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463876-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-first.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463877-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-trying.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463878-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-fall.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463879-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pause.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463880-tony-hawk-s-underground-2-game-boy-advance-screenshot-text.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/4123-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/4123-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/g727HzV.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/4123.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>You've been chosen by Tony Hawk to compete against Bam Margera's team in the World Destruction Tour. In an all-new storyline, Tony Hawk's Underground 2 takes you to skateparks around the world, where you can spray your custom tag, slap stickers, and even create new skate lines. Now you can play as yourself, as your teammates, or as more than 20 special skaters. If you're feeling nostalgic for older Tony Hawk games, you can try Classic mode, which challenges you to accomplish your favorite goals, such as Secret Tape and High Score.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3d91d6b4-9810-4070-879a-9f6da21200e2.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2aee35e7-1efe-4c1c-b895-75ec11cb6ef7.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/46fb9fc3-2fab-49c7-a713-a7226b02ae47.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>