<Game>
	<Name>Tony Hawk's Underground (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Take your custom skater around the world and rise as a pro skater!Tony Hawk's Underground (known in Japan as Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2003) is a skateboarding game developed by Neversoft and published by Activision or the PlayStation 2, Xbox, and GameCube on October 27, 2003. The fifth installment of the long-running Tony Hawk franchise and the sequel to Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4, Tony Hawk's Undergound is the first main game in the franchise to disband the "Pro Skater" name, adding a brand new story mode (in which the player's custom skater rises from a local unknown to a superstar). The game also introduces the ability to travel on foot (allowing players to navigate certain areas easier, either in or out of a combo chain, while allowing them to climb to places unreachable by skating), ability to wallplant and wallpush (pushing your skater off the wall when approaching it straight on), and limited vehicle gameplay.The game also introduces enhanced character creation, as players can create tricks using the Create-A-Trick mode and map custom faces to their skaters (PlayStation 2 version only). Players can also create custom objectives for both regular and custom maps using the new Create-A-Goal mode.This game was ported to the PC (in Australia only) by Beenox sometime in 2004. A handheld version was also developed for the Game Boy Advance by Vicarious Visions, maintaining the 2D isometric gameplay from the handheld versions of the previous four installments of the franchise.Tony Hawk's Underground, like previous installments in the series, features crossover characters from different franchises as hidden playable skaters: Gene Simmons (the bassist from the band KISS) and Iron Man (a superhero from the Marvel franchise of the same name). Players can also unlock three levels from Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2: Hangar, School 2, and Venice Beach.Changes from previous GamesNew features for the game included the ability to get off of the skateboard (to walk around the level, or in the middle of a combo for a few seconds), the ability to drive cars, and the ability to create your own tricks, skateboard decks, clothing, and custom goals and share them online. Another new online feature was the ability to upload a picture of yourself and then map it on your created skater's face. Also included were a few new skateboarding moves - the "wall push", the "wall plant", the "hip transfer", and the "acid drop". The amount of tricks per skater was increased with double-tap grinds and more assignable slots for special tricks.Storyline:The game's story centers around a player created character and his friend Eric Sparrow. Both are up and coming skateboarders looking to become sponsored pros. Throughout the game, the player's character travels to different cities (each a different level in the game) and performs a series of tasks for different people (which in turn advances the story). Each level also includes a professional skater who can be approached and will give the player the ability to do a new "special trick" if their goal is accomplished.Levels:New JerseyManhattanTampaSan DiegoHawaiiVancouverSlam City JamMoscowHotter Than HellHangarSchool 2Venice BeachSoundtrack:Aceyalone - "Rapps on Deck"Anacron - "A Prototype"Busdriver - "Imaginary Places"Cannibal Ox - "Iron Galaxy"Dan the Automator - "A Better Tomorrow"Deltron 3030 - "Positive Contact"DJ Q-bert - "Cosmic Assassins"Frog One - "Blah Blah"J-Live - "Braggin' Writes Revisited"Juggaknots - "The Circle Pt. 1"Jurassic 5 (ft. Big Daddy Kane and Percee P) - "A Day at the Races" (THUG trailer song)LA Symphony - "King Kong"Living Legends - "War Games"Mr. Dibbs - "Skin Therapy"Mr. Lif - "Phantom"MURS - "Transitions as a Ridah"Nas - "The World Is Yours"People Under the Stairs - "The Next Step II"Quasimoto - "Low Class Conspiracy"R.A. The Rugged Man - "King of the Underground"Supernatural - "Internationally Known"The Herbaliser (feat. MF DOOM) - "It Ain't Nuttin'"Wildchild - "Secondary Protocol"Alkaline Trio - "Armageddon"Angry Amputees - "She Said"Assorted Jelly Beans - "Rebel Yell"Authority Zero - "Everyday"Bad Religion - "Big Bang"Blue Collar Special - "Don't Wait"Bracket - "2 Rak 005"The Clash - "White Riot"Dropkick Murphys - "Time to Go"Electric Frankenstein - "Annie's Grave"The Explosion - "No Revolution"Flamethrower - "I Want It All"GBH - "Crush 'Em"Hot Water Music - "Remedy"Mike V. and the Rats - "The Days"The Adicts - "Viva La Revolution"The Browns - "American Werewolf in Calgary"The Midnight Evils - "Loaded and Lonely"NOFX - "Separation of Church and Skate"Paint It Black - "Womb Envy"Refused - "New Noise"Rise Against - "Like The Angel" (incorrectly noted as "Like the Angels")Rubber City Rebels - "(I Wanna) Pierce My Brain"Social Distortion - "Mommy's Little Monster"Stiff Little Fingers - "Suspect Device"Strike Anywhere - "Refusal"Sublime - "Seed" *Transplants - "California BabylonBlind Iris - "Drive"Camarosmith - "It's Alright"Clutch - "Impetus"Crash and Burn - "Crazy and Stupid"Entombed - "To Ride, Shoot Straight, and Speak the Truth"Five Horse Johnson - "Mississippi KingFu Manchu - "California Crossing"High on Fire - "Hung, Drawn and Quartered"In Flames - "Embody the Invisible"Jane's Addiction - "Suffer Some"Kiss - "God of Thunder"Kiss - "Lick It Up"Kiss - "Rock and Roll All Nite"Lamont - "Hotwire"Mastodon - "Crusher Destroyer"Nine Pound Hammer - "Run Fat Boy Run"Orange Goblin - " Your World Will Hate This"Queens of the Stone Age - "Millionaire"Smoke Blow - "Circle of Fear"Solace - "Indolence"Stormtroopers of Death - "Milk"Superjoint Ritual - "It Takes No Guts"The Hellacopters - "(Gotta Get Some Action) Now!"The Hookers - "The Legend of Black Thunder"Unida - "Black Woman"Cheat: Skip TutorialEnter this code at the Main Menu:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Activision</Developer>
	<rating>6.8</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4122</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/915078-tony-hawks-underground</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/tony-hawks-underground_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tony-hawks-underground/3030-14896/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/4122-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4122-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/573522-tony-hawk-s-underground-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/573523-tony-hawk-s-underground-game-boy-advance-screenshot-enter.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/573524-tony-hawk-s-underground-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-can.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/573525-tony-hawk-s-underground-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/573526-tony-hawk-s-underground-game-boy-advance-screenshot-select.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/573527-tony-hawk-s-underground-game-boy-advance-screenshot-making.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/573528-tony-hawk-s-underground-game-boy-advance-screenshot-grinding.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/3/39162/2444309-tony-hawk.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/3/39162/2444308-_-tony-hawks-underground-ps2-_.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/3/39162/2444307-_-tony-hawks-underground-gamecube-_.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ARgkChg.png</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/4122.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Activision's definitive skateboarding game returns on the PlayStation 2, GameCube, Xbox, Game Boy Advance and PC with Tony Hawk's Underground. In a departure from former games in the series, Underground gives players the chance to take an ambitious non-pro skater from an unknown, to superstar status. For the first time in the series, players will be able to get off their board and explore the expansive levels on foot, or in a vehicle. Customize the look of your skater, your skater's tricks, and even create custom skateparks. Tony Hawk's Underground features nine sprawling courses, as well as a level of freedom and customization that is unprecedented in the popular series.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1e86094d-968f-4b8e-be3b-4a15f53379ae.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/10201f2f-e2e4-4f9d-9545-04a3c6e26405.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/67a465eb-05d6-4000-b62a-b656c830465f.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>