<Game>
	<Name>Top Spin 2 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Top Spin 2 is the first Xbox 360 game for the franchise. Top Spin 2 is a tennis video game published by 2K Sports and was released in 2006. It is the follow-up of (can you guess?) Top Spin.Career ModeTop Spin 2 features a Career mode that spans the course of 5 years, in which you create a player and increase their ranking from 200 to the number 1 Tennis pro. In addition to increasing your ranking, you will have to balance a hectic schedule of training, special events and sponsorship games.Throughout the course of the career you also develop a rivalry with one of the players, who will frequently consider your achievements as nothing to what they have done.Featured Tennis StarsMale PlayersAlex KuznetsovAndy RoddickBrendan EvansCarlos Moy&#225;Guillermo CoriaJames BlakeLleyton HewittMax MirnyiRoger FedererTim HenmanTommy HaasFemale PlayersAi SugiyamaAlicia MolikAm&#233;lie MauresmoAnastasia MyskinaAngela HaynesCorina MorariuElena DementievaJamee JacksonLindsay DavenportMaria SharapovaSvetlana KuznetsovaVenus Williams</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>2K Sports</Developer>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22330</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/928317-top-spin-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/top-spin-2/3030-17111/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/22330-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/4/8/0/68480_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913189-28.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913188-27.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913187-26.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913186-25.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913185-19.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913184-24.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913183-18.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913182-23.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913181-17.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913180-22.jpg</snapshot10>
</game>