<Game>
	<Name>Top Spin 2 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Top Spin 2 is the first Xbox 360 game for the franchise. Top Spin 2 is a tennis video game published by 2K Sports and was released in 2006. It is the follow-up of (can you guess?) Top Spin.Career ModeTop Spin 2 features a Career mode that spans the course of 5 years, in which you create a player and increase their ranking from 200 to the number 1 Tennis pro. In addition to increasing your ranking, you will have to balance a hectic schedule of training, special events and sponsorship games.Throughout the course of the career you also develop a rivalry with one of the players, who will frequently consider your achievements as nothing to what they have done.Featured Tennis StarsMale PlayersAlex KuznetsovAndy RoddickBrendan EvansCarlos Moy&#225;Guillermo CoriaJames BlakeLleyton HewittMax MirnyiRoger FedererTim HenmanTommy HaasFemale PlayersAi SugiyamaAlicia MolikAm&#233;lie MauresmoAnastasia MyskinaAngela HaynesCorina MorariuElena DementievaJamee JacksonLindsay DavenportMaria SharapovaSvetlana KuznetsovaVenus Williams</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Developer>2K Sports</Developer>
	<rating>7.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>22330</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/928317-top-spin-2</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/top-spin-2/3030-17111/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2266554-box_ts2.png</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/4/8/0/68480_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913189-28.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913188-27.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913187-26.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913186-25.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913185-19.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913184-24.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913183-18.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913182-23.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913181-17.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/3009/913180-22.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Head to the court and compete against some of the biggest names in tennis with 2K Sports' TOP SPIN 2 for the Game Boy Advance. The game contains exciting tennis gameplay, a number of different modes, and a lot of fun. Career mode, the main mode of the game, has players creating a male or female character from scratch using the game's fairly deep customization mode. Once their player is created and named, gamers move to the court. First comes several training rounds with the coach, who will teach players everything then need to know about controlling their character, serving, and returning the ball in TOP SPIN 2. However, each lesson costs money, so players will need to quickly enter a low-level tournament to earn some cash. Many of the tournaments won't be available at the beginning, but as players win matches and earn rankings, more difficult tournaments will open up. Eventually, players will find themselves facing off against big name tennis stars like Andy Roddick, Venus Williams, Roger Federer, Maria Sharapova, Lindsay Davenport, and Lleyton Hewitt. Gamers can also play quick games as either singles or doubles, play an exhibition match, play three different mini-games in party mode, and take on friends using the Game Boy Advance link. Overall, players who love tennis and the challenge it brings will love TOP SPIN 2.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/8306ac7a-a00a-4496-b14d-0f0df0b9f7ae.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/2d93ec5c-768d-4da4-b1c9-06ca72bbd93c.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>2K Sports</Publisher>
</game>