<Game>
	<Name>Tottoko Hamutarou 4 - Nijiiro Daikoushin Dechu (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>The rodent ragamuffins are back on Nintendo Game Boy Advance! Hamtaro and friends must work together as a team as they attempt to locate the ingredients necessary to produce a rainbow. Track down Ham-Ham pals like Boss, Oxnard and Pashmina and control them as a single unit as you complete numerous kooky goals and take part in over a hundred mini-games.You can also hunt down sticker cards which can be traded with fellow Hamtaro fanatics using the Game Boy Advance Game Link Cable. Whod have thought the secret life of a hamster would be so exciting...Cheat: Get hidden Does She Know? coloringGet to the hamster that begins "Crazy Cap Catch" ham-game at Clover Elementary(as you enter,go one screen up,two screens right and one up to find that hamster).behind that hamster is a shogun wig,talk with it(you need to completely end the conversation)then immediately press  L,A,B,L,R.Cheat: Get hidden Does She Know? coloringGo to Rainbow Land,go up with the cloud,go a screen up using the stairs,go to the right/left screen and go up using those disks on the floor.talk with the green poster behind Bo(you need to completely end the conversation)then immediately press  L,A,L,B,A,B,R,R.Cheat: Get hidden Does She Know? coloringEnter Tip-Top Fair and go one screen left,there will be a big stage in that screen.in that stage there is a picture of Howdy and Dexter,talk to it(you need to completely end the conversation)then immediately press R,L,A,R,B.Cheat: Get hidden Does She Know? coloringGo to Hamstarr Manor. Behind Seed Pig-Out (the one with Mean Oxnard) there are three hamsters sitting behind a table. Talk to the middle hamster ONCE. Then, press the following buttons in order: B, L, A, B, A, R. You will receive the picture 'Too Much Good Stuff'.Cheat: Get hidden Does She Know? coloringStand in front of the blackboard in the Clubhouse and press the A button. After reading the message, press the L, R, A, B buttons in this order and you'll receive a secret coloring picture.</plot>
	<releasedate>29/10/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG</genre>
	<Developer>Graphic Research</Developer>
	<rating>10.0</rating>
	<VideoURL>LPRq9jjSFCc</VideoURL>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/582378-hamtaro-rainbow-rescue</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/4/0/43740_front.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/7/4/1/43741_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/b/8/gfs_25675_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/0/2/5/gfs_25675_2_1.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/a/f/5/gfs_25675_2_2.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/4/5/gfs_25675_2_3.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/f/5/5/gfs_25675_2_4.jpg</snapshot5>
</game>