<Game>
	<Name>Tron 2.0 - Killer App (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Tron 2.0: Killer App is an  Xbox-exclusive  adaptation of the PC game  Tron 2.0 with  additional emphasis placed on the multiplayer component. The single  player component received a large number of modifications as well,  primarily through having levels restructured and edited. Despite this,  the core storyline remains the same as the PC game on which it is based.Full  usage of  Xbox  Live's capabilities were central to Tron 2.0: Killer App. It was "Live Aware",  supported MSN Messenger, voice chat, match making, player lists, per  user data, teams, content download, auto updates and web services.There  was a planned port of Tron 2.0 Killer App to the  Gizmondo handheld  console, though it was canceled while in development. A  Game Boy Advance  title of the same name exists, though it contains an entirely new  adventure. Additions to MultiplayerTen new multiplayer mapsoverRIDE mode - A deathmatch mode where the players can enter and  exit light cycles at any point throughout the match.Hard Ware mode - Class-based team multiplayer. Players choose from  among six classes while playing against opposing teams in  objective-based missions.Support for up to four players via splitscreen or 16 players via  system link.Cheat: Cheat CodesAt the title screen -when the words "PRESS START" are flashing -enter any of the following code and you'll hear a sound to confrim each code:</plot>
	<releasedate>20/10/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Driving, Racing, Strategy</genre>
	<Developer>Buena Vista Interactive</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.6</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4126</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920699-tron-20-killer-app</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/tron-20-killer-app</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/tron-20-killer-app/3030-375/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/4126-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4126-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111530-tron-2-0-killer-app-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111531-tron-2-0-killer-app-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111532-tron-2-0-killer-app-game-boy-advance-screenshot-as-in-every.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111533-tron-2-0-killer-app-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose-your.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111534-tron-2-0-killer-app-game-boy-advance-screenshot-alan-badley.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111535-tron-2-0-killer-app-game-boy-advance-screenshot-this-recharge.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111536-tron-2-0-killer-app-game-boy-advance-screenshot-tron-fires.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111551-tron-2-0-killer-app-game-boy-advance-screenshot-datacubes.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111538-tron-2-0-killer-app-game-boy-advance-screenshot-riding-in.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/111553-tron-2-0-killer-app-game-boy-advance-screenshot-an-enemy-tank.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/4126-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/4126-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/l9GzscK.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/4126.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>Developed for the Game Boy Advance by Digital Eclipse, players can assume roles of digital warriors Tron or Mercury, each with their own storylines, weapons and game modes, as they battle against The Corruptor, an evil computer program attempting to create the ultimate virus. Based on the classic Disney movie, the game features more than 30 levels of action-packed game play, including third-person isometric digital action, first-person vehicle combat and light cycle racing. Command the action over a dozen maps of Light Cycle, Tank and Recognizer battle modes; either in single player or with up to four players in multiplayer mode. Collect 100 upgrade chips to customize characters and unlock secrets. Test your skills in 6 challenging bonus games including Firewall, DeFrag and Security and play original TRON arcade games, Tron: The Arcade Game and Discs of Tron, for the ultimate retro experience.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c44a774d-1cbd-49d1-81b7-7c550616ed47.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7fd5f515-d406-4bc5-b66c-4cfc9d412e3e.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/22c5ee16-4b7c-40df-8500-e252db5da929.png</clearlogo2>
	<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0d0682e0-ee93-4b1c-b73b-a71b629011d4.png</snapshot11>
	<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/433410a2-2d84-4605-af8b-9d3031471d04.png</snapshot12>
	<Publisher>Buena Vista Games</Publisher>
</game>