<Game>
	<Name>Tsuukin Hitofude (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>As a new and improved tile-flipping puzzler, Polarium Advance, for the Game Boy Advance, offers all new features that sharpen the brain and accelerate reflexes. Fans of Polarium Advance's predecessor, Polarium DS, will notice you can now use the control pad to move the cursor and also switch to new color schemes...no more black and white. In addition, Polarium Advance has improved playability by utilizing the action buttons and control pad as opposed to only using a stylus. So easy, you can play with only one hand... perfect for gamers on the go. Polarium Advance also features a totally new variety of tiles, making it one of the trickiest, skill-filled, puzzle games of all time.Cheat: 3 Special PuzzlesYou need to complete Daily Polarium for at least two "full" months (i.e. your first month would not count unless you start on the first day of any month). You will unlock either a tile or cursor set on the first day of the following month, depends on the month (see below). The last set will be unlocked when you finish a year in Daily Polarium.Cheat: 3 Special PuzzlesNote that you don't need to complete the secondary objectives (e.g. start and end on specific point etc) to unlock these. Once unlocked, these can be chosen in the option menu.Cheat: 3 Special PuzzlesThese sets can be chosen in teh options menu, once unlocked.Cheat: 3 Special PuzzlesOnce unlocked, this mode is accessible from the Time Attack menu.Cheat: 3 Special PuzzlesInsert your copy of Polarium Advance into the DS GBA Slot when playing Actionloop (Puzzloop) and you will unlock an extra Tile set on Polarium Advance.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/11/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Puzzle</genre>
	<Developer>Mitchell</Developer>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>3491</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929333-polarium-advance</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/3491-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/3491-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/b/f/gfs_69019_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/6/f/gfs_69019_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/d/f/gfs_69019_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/c/f/gfs_69019_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/7/f/gfs_69019_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/3491-g.jpg</banner1>
</game>