<Game>
	<Name>Ultimate Spider-Man (Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Ultimate Spider-Man takes the free roaming style of gameplay from the Spider-Man 2 movie adaptation and creates its own unique experience. The game is completely based off of the comics with the same title and continues young Peter Parker's adventures as Spider-Man. Players will encounter villains such as Rhino, Shocker, and Venom through as the game unfolds. The visuals were created along with the artists who worked on the comic series and offers a distinct art style.The Nintendo DS version of the game was a 2.5D platformer that incorporates animated cutscenes with voice acting. This version of the game was well received.Gameplay:Playing as Spider-Man wasn't enough for some gamers so the developers decided it would be a great idea to allow players to play as Venom. While playing as Venom you are able to jump high and do mainly all power attacks. Also as Venom the player is able to absorb enemies by sucking them inside of Venom using his tendrils and recharge his life while draining the victim's. Contrary to playing as Venom, while playing as Spider-Man you are more agile and can do a lot of tricks with your web. The way you swing from building to building is similar to the way you do in Spider-Man 2. You have to swing off of actual buildings unlike the original Spider-Man game.DevelopmentThe storyline and art style for Ultimate Spiderman is based off of the comic book series of the same name. Series writer Brian Michael Bendis provided input into the overarching storyline for the game, as well as all of the original spoken dialogue. Original series artist Mark Bagley designed all of the characters in the game, providing both character models for previously created characters, as well as the designs for all new characters who first appear in Ultimate Spider-Man. The duo eventually adapted and expanded the game's storyline into the ongoing comic series. The story appears in issues 123-128, in a storyline entitled "War of the Symbiotes."Trivia:The game claims that its story would affect the comic book in a major way. However, Silver Sable unmasks Spider-Man in both the comic and the game, and fails to recognize him both times.System RequirementsMinimum:Pentium III 1.2 GHz or Athlon 1.2 GHzWindows 2000/XP 256MB RAM64MB RAM 3D DirectX 9 compatible cardRecommended:Pentium IV 1.4 GHz or AMD equivalentWindows 2000/XP 512MB RAM128MB RAM 3D DirectX 9 compatible card</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Beat-Em-Up</genre>
	<Developer>Activision</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>6.0</rating>
	<ESRB>E10+ - Everyone 10+</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>VWiB9pDFvhY</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>20823</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/928440-ultimate-spider-man</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/ultimate-spider-man__</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ultimate-spider-man/3030-7593/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2280536-box_usm.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/20823-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/728307-ultimate-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-menu.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735922-ultimate-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-story.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735923-ultimate-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-issue-1.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735924-ultimate-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-get-rid-of.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735925-ultimate-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-searching.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735926-ultimate-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-on-the-side.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735927-ultimate-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-swinging-through.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735928-ultimate-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-careful-of.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735929-ultimate-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-fighting-a.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735930-ultimate-spider-man-game-boy-advance-screenshot-thug-below.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/20823-g.jpg</banner1>
</game>