<Game>
	<Name>Ultimate Beach Soccer (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Pro Beach Soccer is the first game based on the Summer variation of football, played by five players aside on a sandy surface. The game includes 32 national teams (some with their real stars) plus 6 all star teams to be unlocked in 3 game modes (Exhibition, Pro Beach Soccer Tour and Tournament)  played in Bangkok, Rio de Janeiro, Marseille or Venice Beach.Gameplay: is classic arcade, with one button to pass, another to juggle the ball and another to shoot. One of the key aspects is the "State of Grace"; by making fancy moves (such as overhead kicks, heel passes or heading the ball back and forth) and scoring goals, a power bar starts filling, and when it's full, all team attributes are maxed up and the players are given the ability to quickly run with the ball.</plot>
	<releasedate>4/11/2003</releasedate>
	<Developer>DreamCatcher Interactive Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>26122</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/578718-ultimate-beach-soccer</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/ultimate-beach-soccer</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/ultimate-beach-soccer/3030-10790/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/26122-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/146566-ultimate-beach-soccer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/146565-ultimate-beach-soccer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-taking-a.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/146567-ultimate-beach-soccer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-if-a-plyer.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/146568-ultimate-beach-soccer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-there-are.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/146569-ultimate-beach-soccer-game-boy-advance-screenshot-taking-a.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275033-71.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275032-69.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275031-65.png</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275030-61.png</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/7/73970/2275029-59.png</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Billed as the first Beach Soccer video game designed especially for fans of soccer and extreme sports, Ultimate Beach Soccer offers five-on-five action with lots of aerial passes, special moves, combos, intense shooting and scoring, spectacular goals and saves. Set in unique and exotic locations spanning the globe, including Rio, France, Japan and Venice Beach, California, Ultimate Beach Soccer offers detailed and exotic stadiums, with daytime and nighttime games, including spectacular pitch-side shows with DJs, cheerleaders and commentators all fully modeled and animated in-game. Game modes range from quick match to long-term competitions and custom tournaments. The game sports the Official Beach Soccer Federation License - Real Players, Real Teams and Real Locations.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/eb5871c9-d0db-4a9b-b9cc-cf4eb3eecb41.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5d6dbb59-f279-436b-b0d8-22e6123ebd87.png</clearlogo1>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<Publisher>Wanadoo</Publisher>
</game>