<Game>
	<Name>Wade Hixton's Counter Punch (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>SynopsisYou play as Wade Hixton, an average dude who's only claim to fame is that he can fix anything with duct tape, as he breaks down on Route 27. Luckily for Wade and the development of the plot, a tow truck shows up to take him to the local town of Big Piney. Wade get's to Big Piney and heads to the bar to get a grape soda while his car is getting fixed. Unfortunately, he sits in the seat of the town trashman Rocco McScrub who then challenges him to a fight to "take out the trash".Fights/CharactersRocco McScrubRocco McScrub is the first opponent you face in the game and he is the easiest one as well. He has the appearance of a hobo-biker and his special attack involves him jumping back into a three-point stance and then jumping forward to throw a raccoon out of his trash bag at you.SweetnessSweetness is the pimp who runs Club sweetness. His special attack is a backhanded slap.Gameplay:The gameplay is heavily centered around the left and right side of both fighters. Unlike Super Punch-Out!!! you cannot dodge either way to avoid punches thrown by your opponents. You have to dodge towards the character and away from his punch to successfully dodge the punch. Some characters will also sway back and forth forcing you to alternate between left and right punches.Cheat: Debug MenuPause the game and press:Select, L, R, Select.</plot>
	<releasedate>15/3/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Sports</genre>
	<Developer>Destination Software, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.8</rating>
	<ESRB>T - Teen</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>9-fGQ_2W4Q8</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>5487</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/918996-wade-hixtons-counter-punch</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/wade-hixtons-counter-punch</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/wade-hixtons-counter-punch/3030-1928/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/5487-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/5487-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/161177-wade-hixton-s-counter-punch-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735656-wade-hixton-s-counter-punch-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735661-wade-hixton-s-counter-punch-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735657-wade-hixton-s-counter-punch-game-boy-advance-screenshot-fight.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735662-wade-hixton-s-counter-punch-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735658-wade-hixton-s-counter-punch-game-boy-advance-screenshot-took.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735663-wade-hixton-s-counter-punch-game-boy-advance-screenshot-fighting.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735653-wade-hixton-s-counter-punch-game-boy-advance-screenshot-being.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735654-wade-hixton-s-counter-punch-game-boy-advance-screenshot-super.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735659-wade-hixton-s-counter-punch-game-boy-advance-screenshot-knocked.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/FHufM9g.jpg</banner1>
	<Notes>Poor Wade Hixton. On his way home from the monster truck rally in Albuquerque when his car manages to break down. Yet again. Luckily for Wade, he isn't far from the little known boxing town of Big Piney. And this is where our adventure begins. Help Wade fight his way through eight opponents on his quest to fix his car and get back home. Counter Punch is a non-linear boxing adventure game that lets you star as the dumb witted Wade Hixton. But it doesn't end there. On your journey through Big Piney you'll meet the local towns folk, learn new moves, payoff thugs to lend a helping hand a whole lot more. In other words, it be real fun I gar-ron-tee!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/3a8dfbe4-289c-4738-8d85-cdb7d52ad7da.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/afe79f26-8c76-4a02-973d-827e820cad09.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Destination Software</Publisher>
</game>