<Game>
	<Name>Whac-A-Mole (USA)</Name>
	<plot>This is an adaption of the arcade game Whac-A-Mole, for Nintendo's handheld devices. At the screen you have a 5x4 grid of holes (3x3 in the GBA version). As the game begins, moles will randomly pop up their heads in the holes. Now you have to hit them before they disappear again. DS users will use the stylus and tap the moles, while GBA users will have to use the directional pad to move a marker around the screen.The game comes with three different game modes. The first is the arcade mode, were you for each level has to reach a certain amount of points before the time goes out. Different types of mole will show up. In addition to the standard mole, there's the golden mole which gives four times as much points as the standard one, and the plush one which gives minus points. Later in the game, you will also meet moles that attack your score, for example ninja and bazooka moles. Various power ups are also available. We have the multipliers, which  once active will give you double points for each mole, clocks that slows the time and bombs that do the opposite. Seven worlds are available, each with it's own graphical theme.The second mode is the puzzle mode, which isn't the same on both platforms. In the DS version you have to recreate a shape that is shown on the upper screen. This is done by tapping moles of different colors. The GBA version has two puzzle games. One is a Tic Tac Toe where you have to hit three moles in a row before your opponent does so. The other is the Peg Puzzle where you have to empty the field from all moles. For each mole you remove, more moles will appear on the screen. The moles will have arrows around them, indicating where the new moles will pop up. However, there won't come any new moles if there already is a mole in that location.The third mode is a simple quick play mode where you just specify how many levels you want to play and with what difficulty and then try to be successful. The DS version also supports a multiplayer mode.</plot>
	<releasedate>28/9/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Activision Value Publishing, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<thegamesdb_id>26144</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/929538-whac-a-mole</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/whac-a-mole</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/whac-a-mole/3030-17268/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/26144-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/26144-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/202540-whac-a-mole-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/202541-whac-a-mole-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/202542-whac-a-mole-game-boy-advance-screenshot-what-you-have-to-do.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/202543-whac-a-mole-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-moles-start-popping.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/202544-whac-a-mole-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-normal-mole-is-worth.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/202545-whac-a-mole-game-boy-advance-screenshot-a-golden-mole-is-worth.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/202546-whac-a-mole-game-boy-advance-screenshot-for-this-one-you-ll.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/202547-whac-a-mole-game-boy-advance-screenshot-stage-results.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/202548-whac-a-mole-game-boy-advance-screenshot-in-the-desert.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/202549-whac-a-mole-game-boy-advance-screenshot-with-this-power-up.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Whac-A-Mole enlists players to whac, zap and crush 10 new challenging breeds of moles including Pilot Moles that fly planes, Racer Moles that drive cars, Ninja Moles that attack with throwing stars, Soldier Moles that shoot bazookas and Electric Moles that try to shock gamers throughout seven unique worlds. Whac-A-Mole feature two modes of play -- Arcade Mode, where players race against the clock to complete goals in a world that is layered with power-ups, combats and challenging mole enemies and Quickplay mode, which allows players to customize their experience by choosing from game types, number of rounds and difficulty levels, resulting in a randomly generated mix of puzzle and arcade levels. The Game Boy Advance version includes a Classics mode, featuring such mini games as Tic-Tac-Toe and other favorites.</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/20f51047-36cc-4356-9e16-5f6039f25cc4.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/12acfdaf-a7f9-43ad-9925-914533e38bc7.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>