<Game>
	<Name>WinX Club (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Winx Club is an action adventure game based on the Italian cartoon series of the same name. The story is similar to that of Harry Potter, only this time the main character is a fairy. She gets to go to a fairy school in fairytale world called Magix where she has to find her true self. This game is similar to the Windows and Playstation 2 versions, except that instead of a 3D third person perspective it features a 2D top-down perspective of the game world.This game loosely retells the story of the first season of the television series.There are "action" and "adventure"levels. In the adventure levels gameplay consists of finding items for specific NPCs and playing various mini-games. In the action levels the player has to jump, climb and fight enemies. The main character, Bloom, has a magic shield and two attacks that improve during the game. She can also cast a number of spells that can aid her in finding the items she needs. During boss battles Bloom changes to her Winx form in which she is more powerful and can fly. During the levels there are various items to be picked up which improve Blooms health or attacks or unlock new outfits that can be worn.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/11/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
	<Developer>Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
	<thegamesdb_id>27893</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/928439-winx-club</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/winx-club_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/winx-club/3030-23615/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/112/610826-cover.jpg</boxart1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464414-winx-club-game-boy-advance-screenshot-loading-screen-yes-a.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464415-winx-club-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-game-shows-short.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464416-winx-club-game-boy-advance-screenshot-language-selection.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464417-winx-club-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464418-winx-club-game-boy-advance-screenshot-start-of-the-game.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464419-winx-club-game-boy-advance-screenshot-talking-to-a-gardener.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464420-winx-club-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-inventory-is-still.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464421-winx-club-game-boy-advance-screenshot-found-an-item.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464422-winx-club-game-boy-advance-screenshot-progress-in-the-game.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/464423-winx-club-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-blue-crystals-are.jpg</snapshot10>
	<Notes>Join the Winx Club and prepare for an interactive adventure of fairies, fantasy, fashion and magic! Take on the role of Bloom, a 16 year-old Earth girl, who discovers she is a magical fairy! Meet Bloom's fairy friends, Stella, Flora, Tecna and Musa and battle with them against the evil witches in this most exciting girls adventure ever! Featuring a wide range of community-based activities and collectibles, The Winx Club will whisk you away on an unforgettable adventure!</Notes>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/33187b51-6610-4e90-ab5f-2fb582a3687d.png</boxart2>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1089fa11-bc8d-4691-b788-ffa2306d3136.png</clearlogo1>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>