<Game>
	<Name>X2 - Wolverine's Revenge (USA, Europe)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Written by famed comic book writer Larry Hama, Wolverine's Revenge follows Wolverine on his quest to find the cure for the Shiva Virus. He has been infected with it and we learn more about his past. Wolverine's Revenge is the first game to have Wolverine as the single playable character since 1994's Wolverine: Adamantium Rage.Gameplay:You play the game from a third person perspective. You can go into a stealth mode that makes you silent to the enemies and with the help of your enhanced senses you can sneak up on enemies and kill them with Stealth Strikes. Wolverine can also retract his claws at will allowing him to do different sets of moves and allowing him to perform special Combat Strike Moves which trigger a short cut-scene showing him dispatch his enemies. Depending on how many enemies are surrounding you Wolverine will do different Strike Moves. Wolverine also has regenerating health and if you sustain enough damage he'll go into Feral Rage Mode making him deadlier and faster. Mark Hamill provides the voice for Wolverine and Patrick Stewart reprises his role as Professor Charles Xavier.The claw swipeOne of Wolverines Strike MovesBoss fight with WendigoPC System RequirementsMinimum System Requirements:Windows 98/ME 2000.XPPentium III 500MHz Processor128MB RAM1.5GB Hard Disk SpaceDirectX 9.032MB DirectX compatible 3D Accelerated Video CardDirectX compatible Sound Card6X CD-ROM DriveCheat: Cheat CodesAll codes below are to be entered on the Slot Select screen:Cheat: Unlock Secret GalleryTo unlock Secret Gallery, complete Super Hero mode.Cheat: Unlock Secret GalleryTo unlock Super Hero mode, complete Normal mode. It is harder difficulty and tough bosses. And final boss is not Magneto, but Phoenix-X a.k.a transformed Jean Grey.</plot>
	<releasedate>15/4/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Activision Publishing, Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>2.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>Zx2D58S5JhI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4143</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/562382-x2-wolverines-revenge</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/x2-wolverines-revenge_</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/x2-wolverines-revenge/3030-2113/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/4143-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4143-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107847-x2-wolverine-s-revenge-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107835-x2-wolverine-s-revenge-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-game.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107836-x2-wolverine-s-revenge-game-boy-advance-screenshot-after-this.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107837-x2-wolverine-s-revenge-game-boy-advance-screenshot-you-ll.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107848-x2-wolverine-s-revenge-game-boy-advance-screenshot-wolverine.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107838-x2-wolverine-s-revenge-game-boy-advance-screenshot-various.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107839-x2-wolverine-s-revenge-game-boy-advance-screenshot-box-destroyed.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107849-x2-wolverine-s-revenge-game-boy-advance-screenshot-one-simple.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107840-x2-wolverine-s-revenge-game-boy-advance-screenshot-fatal-claws.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/107841-x2-wolverine-s-revenge-game-boy-advance-screenshot-put-speed.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/4143-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/mNkhOG5.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/4143.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>X-Men: Wolverine's Revenge lets players take on the persona of Wolverine as they explore the mysterious past and deadly future of the most popular X-Men character. Unleashing Wolverine's awesome mutant powers and enlisting the aid of Charles Xavier, players must face off against arch enemies as they discover the truth about the Shiva-Virus and the secret behind the ruthless Dept. H organization that made Wolverine into the deadly killing machine that he is today.</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/dbd525a5-3a5b-40ce-84ca-613cbcf54792.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/ad231caa-932a-477d-aeaf-2eb2b1c13faa.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0bbd4dea-dd38-497a-85e9-f01337c8b37a.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Activision</Publisher>
</game>