<Game>
	<Name>Yaoxi Dao (China)</Name>
	<plot>Super Mario World 2: Yoshi's Island was ported by Nintendo R&amp;D2 to the Game Boy Advance as Yoshi's Island: Super Mario Advance 3 with added features.A stork carries two babies across the sea, but the evil Magikoopa Kamek emerges, and steals Baby Luigi, and Baby Mario falls onto an island in the middle of the sea, called Yoshi's Island, home to all Yoshis. He lands on a green Yoshi, who was apparently taking a walk and Mario and the rest of the Yoshi gang must journey through the game's six worlds to rescue Baby Luigi and the stork back from Baby Bowser and Kamek. Throughout the quest, Kamek tries to stop Yoshi by transforming normal enemies with his magic, thus setting the stage for several boss fights.When he finally reaches Bowser's Castle, Kamek demands that Yoshi gives back Baby Mario. Suddenly, Baby Bowser wakes up and tries to ride Yoshi, but Yoshi knocks him off. Kamek then enlarges Baby Bowser to a gigantic size, destroying most of the castle in the process. After fighting and defeating him, Bowser is reverted to his normal size and is unconscious. Kamek is horrified and says that they will return before flying off with Baby Bowser into the night.Yoshi then frees the stork and Baby Luigi. The stork then flies the reunited twins far away to the village where their parents live. Here, it shows that Mario and Luigi's parents live in the Mushroom Kingdom in a house which is incidentally shaped like a Mushroom. Their parents then emerge from their home at dawn to see a pair of not quite new-born babies at their porch.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/9/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>5.6667</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>2349</thegamesdb_id>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2349-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2349-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-6.jpg</fanart6>
	<fanart7>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-7.jpg</fanart7>
	<fanart8>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-8.jpg</fanart8>
	<fanart9>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/2349-9.jpg</fanart9>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/2349-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2349.png</clearlogo1>
</game>