<Game>
	<Name>Yoshi - Topsy-Turvy (USA)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Yoshi Topsy-Turvy is a platformer that is developed by Artoon and published by Nintendo. It is part of the Yoshi series. This game is one of the few games that features tilt control that is possible by a tilt sensor in the GBA cartridge. This allows the player to tilt the game boy and the environment on the screen is affected.Gameplay:Tilting in the gameYoshi Topsy-Turvy has controls like any other platformer. Yoshi can walk and jump, but, with the tilt sensor cartridge, Yoshi can run up vertical walls and he can even slide down hills. Also with the tilt sensor technology the enviorment around Yoshi changes. If the player tilts the Game Boy right all the enemies and objects move to the right, and vice-versa for the left. When you tilt the Game Boy Advance, Yoshi leans the opposed direction.Plot:The Plot is comparable to Yoshi Story on the Nintendo 64. Bowser starts causing dilemma on Yoshi&#8217;s Island, and then a sprit named Hongo traps Yoshi and Yoshi&#8217;s Island in a storybook. Capturing Bowser can only persuade Hongo to release Yoshi&#8217;s Island from the storybook; he then starts to go through the chapters of the said storybook.Each of the levels is controlled by a sprit. The first sprit Yoshi encounters is a sprit who loves cute things. As Yoshi progresses though the story he meets more sprits. One loves money, one loves speediness, another loves being strong, and numerous more. Each one of them will set goals for the stage for the player to complete. For instance, the player must gather a certain amount of fruit to free Egglings, collect a number of coins, or finish a level in time. By fulfilling the spirit's requirements, the player surpasses on to the next course.Cheat: Unlock Challenge ModeDefeat Bowser for the 2nd time in story mode to unlock challenge mode and challenge number 1.Cheat: Unlock Challenge ModeTo unlock these complete the Egg Gallery in story mode by eating all the Cherries.Cheat: Unlock Challenge ModeTo Unlock the Final Challenge Marble just get EVERY Gold Medal in Story Mode.Cheat: Easier chance at getting a bonus minigameIf you collect a Gold Medal at the end of the level your chance of winning the bonus roulette will double.</plot>
	<releasedate>13/6/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo of America Inc.</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>3.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4036</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/924381-yoshi-topsy-turvy</gamefaqs_url>
	<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/yoshi-topsy-turvy</mobygames_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yoshi-topsy-turvy/3030-1307/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/4036-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4036-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/210422-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
	<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/156672-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735550-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-screenshot-intro.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735554-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-screenshot-chapter-one.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735555-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choose-a-level.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735556-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-screenshot-lets-go.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735557-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-screenshot-rolled-out-the.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735558-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-screenshot-sliding-down.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735559-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-screenshot-apple-up-there.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735560-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-screenshot-good-jumping.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/735561-yoshi-topsy-turvy-game-boy-advance-screenshot-play-some-notes.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/ux2baNK.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/4036.png</clearlogo1>
	<Notes>In Yoshi Topsy-Turvy, Yoshi Island has been turned into a picture book. Yoshi will not stand for this outlandish attempt at flattening his world, and he heads off on an adventure to return things back to their original state. To help in on his quest, a group of spirits who like to surprise people give Yoshi the ability to rotate the world to his liking. The big catch with Yoshi Topsy-Turvy is its use of a motion sensor, similar to the one set to be featured in the second Wario Ware GBA game. The game cartridge includes a built in motion sensor which detects how you move the GBA system. By turning the system, you make the world rotate. A meter on the upper right corner of the screen shows which way the system is being held at any time. Rotate the system to help Yoshi stay on the path and make it past perils and through the varied stages. Go full tilt! By tilting your Game Boy Advance, you'll tilt the environment around Yoshi, knocking over enemies, swinging pendulums, and letting Yoshi run up walls and leap huge pits! Will this ending be happy? All of Yoshi's Island is trapped in a storybook, and only by meeting the challenges of each chapter will you succeed. Collect coins, defeat enemies, or race for the finish to satisfy each course's conditions</Notes>
	<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/d6d38b3d-e0d2-4662-8bba-7483095d18f8.jpg</banner2>
	<boxart2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7018c813-99ff-452d-90db-57342f753f45.jpg</boxart2>
	<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/7e2f6395-b7a8-41c5-8140-429166b59309.png</clearlogo2>
	<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>