<Game>
	<Name>Yu-Gi-Oh! Duel Monsters Expert 3 (Japan) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Find out who's the best card-battle player in Yu-Gi-Oh! World Championship Tournament 2004.Construct your monster cards, spell cards, trap cards, and special summon cards into three separate decks for different dueling strategies.You can conquer the tournament solo or link up with a friend in a multiplayer battle.With over 1000 game cards and dozens of popular characters from the Yu-Gi-Oh!TV series, the excitement and exhilaration of the Yu-Gi-Oh trading card game is captured in full force.Cheat: All CardsTo do this, you must have already viewed the staff credits at least once. To view the credits again, input the old famous Konami code by pressing Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Left, Right, B, A at the selection menu.Cheat: Dark Ruler Ha Des GlitchIf you attack and destroy a Slate Warrior with a Fiend type monster on your side of the field when you have a Dark Ruler Ha Des face up on your side of the field, the slate warrior will still weaken your monster, even though the effect of Dark Ruler Ha Des should prevent that from happening.Cheat: Dark Ruler Ha Des GlitchHave Solemn Wishes active on your side of the field and then filp summon Fiber Jar activating its ability, when you go to draw your cards although Solemn Wishes isn't on the field you still gain 2500 life points!Cheat: Dark Ruler Ha Des GlitchThe Graverobber card states that you can take a spell card from your opponent's graveyard and it will only work if you activate the spell card you took during your turn, but you have to pay 2000 life points to activate it.Cheat: Dark Ruler Ha Des GlitchYou can play the card you took without paying the 2000 life points by first placing it on the field and then activating it while its on the field. The game somehow forgets the card is in play because of Graverobber and normally plays out the card. You will however end up paying the 2000 life points if you play the card you took while its in your hand, so make sure you place the spell card on the field first before you play it so to avoid the 2000 life point penaltyCheat: Dark Ruler Ha Des GlitchThunder Nyan Nyan is a powerful 1900 ATK Light element monster that is immediately destroyed if you have a non-Light element monster face-up on your side of the field. However, if you use Snatch Steal to take a monster from your opponent, it doesn't count as a monster on your side of the field, and therefore Nyan lives. This doesn't work with Change of Heart.Cheat: Dark Ruler Ha Des GlitchSpirit Reaper's effect states that it cannot be destroyed as a result of battle, making it a perfect shield, but if it is targeted by a magic, trap, or monster effect card, then it is destroyed immediately (this includes equip magic cards such as United We Stand or Axe of Despair). However, if you use an equip card on Spirit Reaper, the equip magic card will be destroyed, but Spirit Reaper will remain on the field.Cheat: Unlock BoostersTo unlock these boosters, you must have ten wins against the specified duelist. Cheat: Unlock BoostersFollow these instructions to unlock more duelists.Cheat: Unlock BoostersTo unlock the limitation option, get 100% completion by collecting every single card in the game. Now you can choose to have restricted cards to be no longer restricted.Cheat: Faster Duel SpeedWhen choosing a duelist, hold down L until the duel starts. The gameplay speed will be twice as fast.Cheat: Faster Duel SpeedCertain duelists have extra requirements to unlock. You must constantly meet these requirements, or they will vanish from the selection screen. If you defeat a duelist with special requirements ten times, they will be permanently selectable, regardless of their past requirements. For example, if you beat Joey ten times, you can then duel him even if you have a Jinzo card in your deck. Losses and ties don't count against your total wins.</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2004</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Card Battle</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>5.5</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>4150</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/919562-yu-gi-oh-world-championship-tournament-2004</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yu-gi-oh-world-championship-tournament-2004/3030-17067/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/4150-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4150-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2728514-yu-gi-oh%21+world+championship+tournament+2004+9.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2728513-yu-gi-oh%21+world+championship+tournament+2004+7.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2728512-yu-gi-oh%21+world+championship+tournament+2004+6.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2728511-yu-gi-oh%21+world+championship+tournament+2004+5.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2728510-yu-gi-oh%21+world+championship+tournament+2004+4.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2728509-yu-gi-oh%21+world+championship+tournament+2004+3.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/10/103881/2728508-yu-gi-oh%21+world+championship+tournament+2004+2.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/1/10359/363046-yu_gi_oh.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/3/e/7/gfs_52187_1_1.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/9/3/7/gfs_52187_1_2.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/4150-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/4150-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/4150.png</clearlogo1>
</game>