<Game>
	<Name>Yu-Gi-Oh! Duel Monsters International - Worldwide Edition (Japan) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Yu-Gi-Oh! Worldwide Edition: Stairway to the Destined Duel is a Miscellaneous game, developed by KCEJ and published by Konami,which was released in 2003.Cheat: Misc. PasswordsOn the main map, press R, then go to the Misc Menu.  Select Password and enter these codes to unlock the corresponding card for your deck.Cheat: Change your target week targetIf you don't like your target week targets press START to bring up the language menu. Then leave the language alone and press B the guy will anounce target week again and give you two new targets.Cheat: Change your target week targetIf you press any button when you or your opponent uses Graceful Dice or Skull Dice then the game will freeze Cheat: Change your target week targetFighting Espa Roba the day before a Challenge Cup makes it not happen, for some reason.Cheat: Change your target week targetWhen Bandit Keith activates "Gamble", and calls it wrong, you better hope to finish him off that turn, or stop his card with anything you have, because when the game tries to go to his turn, it skips it, which ends the duel, (which it shouldn't, as it should let you start another turn) resulting in a DRAW, no matter how badly you were beating him.Cheat: Change your target week targetNormally this card has to be face-up on the field for 3 full turns for its double ATK/DEF effect to work, but if you use "Call of the Haunted" to revive it during your opponent's turn, on your turn following the opponent's, it's effect is applied, even though it's only the second turn.Cheat: Change your target week targetUse Polymerization of a Witch of the Black Forest on the field along with a fusion substitute monster to Fuse them into the Musician King and trigger the effect of the Witch twice (excellent search tool for fusion and/or Exodia decks)Cheat: Change your target week targetIf you use 2 "Change of Heart" Magic cards, on 2 different monsters (that are beside each other), when you end your turn, the first card will return normally, but when the second returns, it overlaps the first, never to be seen again anywhere that duel.Cheat: Change your target week targetWith Sangan if you use Pre-Mature Burial on it then use Dark hole you et to use Sangan's effect twice instead of once (useful glitch for Exodia Decks) If you or your opponent uses dice the game will freeze on the dice roll normally you CAN! get by this by pressing the A button to skip the cutscene sequence that freezes the game Cheat: Change your target week targetTry reviving The Immortal of Thunder face down with Spear Cretins effect,if your opponent attacks and kills it you get 3000 LP for the flip effect and they lose 5000 LP when the copy of Immortal is put in [I]their[/I] graveyard.Cheat: Change your target week target(Spear Cretin just creates copies of cards from the graveyards that,once [I]destroyed[/I] end up in the wrong graveyard)Cheat: Card BoostersTo unlock these boosters, do the following.</plot>
	<releasedate>8/4/2003</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Card Battle</genre>
	<Developer>KCEJ</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>7.7</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<thegamesdb_id>2355</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/589651-yu-gi-oh-worldwide-edition-stairway-to-the</gamefaqs_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/2355-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/2355-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/d/8/1/gfs_53915_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/5/1/gfs_53915_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/e/1/gfs_53915_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/f/1/gfs_53915_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/4/1/gfs_53915_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/2355.png</clearlogo1>
</game>