<Game>
	<Name>Yu-Gi-Oh! - Ultimate Masters - World Championship Tournament 2006 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:Yu-Gi-Oh! Ultimate Masters: World Championship Tournament 2006 is a card battling game developed and published by Konami for the Game Boy Advance platform.Gameplay:Yu-Gi-Oh! Ultimate Masters: World Championship Tournament 2006 uses the same rules (as of the games release) as the physical Yu-Gi-Oh! card game.There is no story mode in Championship Tournament 2006, in its place is a free duel mode in which the player can choose the opponent to duel. The opponents can be dueled as many times as wanted.There is also a duel challenge mode in which the player can either try and solve a puzzle, try a theme duel, or try and survive in a survival duel.Duel PointsDuel points can be earned by defeating opponents in free duel mode or duel puzzle mode. These duel points can be used to "buy" in game packs of cards. Many of the packs in this game are digital counterparts to the real life packs.Cheat: Card passwordsEnter these 8 digit passwords in the PASSWORD screen to receive the cards for DPCheat: Card passwordsFirst choose the "Forb/Ltd Card Lists" section from the main menu so that it will bring you to the Forbidden / Limited List and then amongst the options there should be one to enter a password.Cheat: Card passwordsNote: In the password, replace the "*" with the circle symbol, the "^" with the triangle symbol, and the "(STAR)" with the star symbol found at the lower right of the keyboard where you type in the password.Cheat: 5 extra duelists for Free DuelComplete a certain amount of the challenges to desire duelist.Cheat: 5 extra duelists for Free DuelWith 20 wins in Survival, you will unlock the events below:Cheat: 5 extra duelists for Free DuelGet the following number of wins in "Free Duel" to desire event.Cheat: 5 extra duelists for Free DuelBy having certain cards extra theme duels can be unlocked.Cheat: 5 extra duelists for Free DuelHave the following cards in your deck in order to unlock the desire event.Cheat: 5 extra duelists for Free DuelThis will unlock everything except the Last 3 Tier 5 Monsters and The Special Tier</plot>
	<releasedate>20/1/2006</releasedate>
	<genre>Strategy, Card Battle</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-2 Alt</nplayers>
	<rating>8.2</rating>
	<thegamesdb_id>26242</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/930982-yu-gi-oh-ultimate-masters-world-championship</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yu-gi-oh-ultimate-masters-world-championship-tourn/3030-34914/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/26242-1.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxart2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/box/6/9/3/72693_back.jpg</boxart2>
	<snapshot1>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/4/9/f/gfs_72492_1_1.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/e/4/f/gfs_72492_1_2.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/7/f/f/gfs_72492_1_3.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/e/f/gfs_72492_1_4.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/2/5/f/gfs_72492_1_5.jpg</snapshot5>
	<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/pO1PClO.png</banner1>
	<Notes>The next installment in the World Championship Tournament series adds more cards and more replay value than ever before. The official software of the 2006 Yu-Gi-Oh! World Tournament has the most cards in any Yu-Gi-Oh! handheld game, over 2,000 to choose from. New modes will test your dueling skill with games such as limited Life Point duels, dueling with an 80 card deck, and more.</Notes>
	<boxart3>http://images.launchbox-app.com/38668667-ccc3-49cd-9620-c41ed31ec5a6.jpg</boxart3>
	<clearlogo1>http://images.launchbox-app.com/a5a8447c-b6a1-43bd-ab50-16dbbb07512d.png</clearlogo1>
	<snapshot6>http://images.launchbox-app.com/690a0ff4-d567-4feb-b2ad-98f3eac11baf.png</snapshot6>
	<Publisher>Konami</Publisher>
</game>