<Game>
	<Name>Yu-Gi-Oh! - Day of the Duelist - World Championship Tournament 2005 (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It)</Name>
	<plot>Light and dark clash in a town where everyone waits to duel. Battles take the place of words and only the best will win tournaments where glittering trophies await the victor.http://www.gamefaqs.com/portable/gbadvance/home/925904.htmlCheat: Changing the title screenIf you haven't beaten the game, the color of the title screen is normally blue. But after you beat the game, the color switches to purple. You can change it back to blue by pressing Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Left, Right, B, A at the title screen. Input the same code to change it back to purple.Cheat: Changing the title screenTo do this, you need to beat the game first. Then at any time, press Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Left, Right, B, A and you'll get to see the credits again.Cheat: card passwordpress R at the password machine and enter password to get cardCheat: Exodia Draw GlitchWhen playing with an Exodia Deck, If your hand contains, for instance, three of the necessary pieces and Graceful Charity, and you activate Graceful Charity, If you get the final two pieces before you have to discard according to Graceful Charity's effect, and you discard Exodia pieces, the animation for an Exodia victory will play, but the match will be considered a Draw.  Weird, huh?Cheat: Exodia Draw GlitchWhen you play this card, normally you destroy your opponent's monster with the highest DEF, but if their monster has 0 DEF, it will actually destroy an empty field zone (Which basically means you wasted it...).Cheat: Exodia Draw GlitchWhen you activate Swords of Revealing light in real life, normally you would flip all face down monsters face up and if they had an effect their effect would still activate. In the video game, when you activate this card, the monsters that are flipped face up and have flip effects are not activated when they should.Cheat: Exodia Draw GlitchNormally this card increases one selected Beast or Beast-Warrior's ATK by its current DEF, but the game actually gives all your Beast and Beast-Warriors their original DEF added to their ATK.Cheat: Tournaments and TrophysThis is just a chart of unlocking the tournaments.Cheat: Tournaments and TrophysTo unlock these characters, you must win the Weekend Tournament, KC Cup, Limitation Tournament, Premiliaries-Challenge, and the National Tournament.Then, go outside your home after a big scenario and go to the Area/Locations choosings.You will notice that the screen goes a little higher than usual.Go to the top of the screen to the new area.It is called "???".You can now duel these rashinal characters.Cheat: Dueling Grandpa Yugi outside the card shopEvery Tuesday, the card shop closes. But every other tuesday, you can find Grandpa Yugi wandering around a random area. You can duel him and his exodia deck at that time. Cheat: Dueling Grandpa Yugi outside the card shopTalk to Weevil Underwood with a deck where the only monsters are insectsCheat: Dueling Grandpa Yugi outside the card shopOccasionaly the scrolling bar will say "Where is Joey?". When it says this go find Joey and talk to him (Not challenge), and if you own a Time Wizard you will face him in a pure luck duel with weak monsters, dice cards, and Time WizardCheat: Dueling Grandpa Yugi outside the card shopLook for the Scrolling bar to ask if Harpie types are Mai's alone.  Construct a deck that contains no monsters with Harpie in their name and no spell cards and she'll duel with you.Cheat: Dueling Grandpa Yugi outside the card shopMake an Exodia deck your current deck. Go to the card shop. Talk to Grampa and he will ask you to duel against him using an Exodia deck. Both of the lifepoint scores will start at 10. The only way to win is to get all five pieces of Exodia into your hand. Bringing either players' lifepoints to zero will end the duel in a tie.Cheat: Dueling Grandpa Yugi outside the card shopAs soon as possible, go to grandpas shop, duel and win agains everyone inside his store, talk to him, he will say that you are an impressive trainer and invite you to a mini-championship to sponsor his shop, it's pretty easy, 2 battles against the anime duelists.Cheat: Dueling Grandpa Yugi outside the card shopSometimes on the scrolling bar on the top of the screen, it will say that mako is not feeling okay.  If you talk to him equipped with an umi deck (a deck with umi and lots of water creatures) you can duel him in a sea battle.  If you win he will give you a ton of water collection packs.</plot>
	<releasedate>15/2/2005</releasedate>
	<genre>Miscellaneous, Card Battle</genre>
	<Developer>Konami</Developer>
	<nplayers>1</nplayers>
	<rating>5.4</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>hWQeIQI58vI</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>4148</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/925904-yu-gi-oh-7-trials-to-glory-world-championship</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/yu-gi-oh-7-trials-to-glory-world-championship-tour/3030-26976/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/8/87790/2210244-box_ygowct2k5.png</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/4148-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/42389/1049141-yu_gi_oh____day_of_the_duelist___world_championship_tournament_2005__europe___en_ja_fr_de_es_it_6.png</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/42389/1049140-yu_gi_oh____day_of_the_duelist___world_championship_tournament_2005__europe___en_ja_fr_de_es_it_5.png</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/42389/1049139-yu_gi_oh____day_of_the_duelist___world_championship_tournament_2005__europe___en_ja_fr_de_es_it_4.png</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/42389/1049138-yu_gi_oh____day_of_the_duelist___world_championship_tournament_2005__europe___en_ja_fr_de_es_it_3.png</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/42389/1049137-yu_gi_oh____day_of_the_duelist___world_championship_tournament_2005__europe___en_ja_fr_de_es_it_2.png</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/42389/1049136-yu_gi_oh____day_of_the_duelist___world_championship_tournament_2005__europe___en_ja_fr_de_es_it_1.png</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/4/42389/1049135-yu_gi_oh____day_of_the_duelist___world_championship_tournament_2005__europe___en_ja_fr_de_es_it_.png</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/b/2/3/gfs_62017_1_1.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/1/f/3/gfs_62017_1_2.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://img.gamefaqs.net/screens/8/4/3/gfs_62017_1_3.jpg</snapshot10>
	<banner1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/banners/graphical/4148-g.jpg</banner1>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/4148.png</clearlogo1>
</game>