<Game>
	<Name>Zelda no Densetsu - Kamigami no Triforce & 4tsu no Tsurugi (Japan)</Name>
	<plot>Overview:A remake of the SNES classic for the Game Boy Advance originally released on the second of December 2002 in North America and then later released in early 2003 in Japan and Europe. The game was co-developed by Capcom and Nintendo and at the time of release the Four Swords portion of the game was considered the earliest in the chronology, though this is no longer the case. This remake is notable for having the first ever multiplayer mode in a Zelda franchise. The single-player game is a port of the original Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past game though there are some slight additions, such as new sound effects from the N64 Legend of Zelda games. If you complete the Four Swords section of the game and then play A Link to the Past you can access a brand new Four Swords temple that will give you a new secret ending. The riddle quest is another new addition that unlocks only through playing the Four Swords portion of the game and completing it will unlock the hurricane blade. A feature of the game was any sword techniques you learned while playing A Link to the Past would carry over to the Four Swords part of the game. The story of the A Link to the Past portion of the game is unchanged apart from the extra hidden unlockable ending.Four SwordsFour Swords is the multiplayer component of the game for two to four players, there is no single player mode for this story so a game link cable is required if you want to play. Unlike in Four Swords Adventures it is not required that there be four Link's, if only two people are playing then the game will make sure that there are no impossible puzzles that require more over two players for example. When you start the game player one is the green Link, two is the red, three is blue and four is purple. In this game there is not an option for you to name your character, he is auto-assigned the name of Link. There are 3 levels each with two stages and a boss stage and then there is a final Vaati boss level that will unlock after you have completed the original 3 levels. In order to complete levels you must make sure you collect enough Rupees, if any of the players die you will collectively lose 50 Rupees and this amount increases each time a player is revived. The player is rewarded if he finishes a stage with the most rupees and also a player gains a heart container if he is the first to reach the portal at the end of the level. The gameplay is very unique as it does not feature an overworld and unlike in Four Swords Adventures the dungeons are randomly generated so that the enemies are never in the same place. The player who does the best on a stage will be awarded the medal of courage which is needed to unlock a secret technique in the Link to the Past portion of the game.The first time you play through the game you will need to collect 1000 rupees to complete each stage, after you have completed the stage the players will be awarded with silver keys. Once you have the silver keys you can opt to play harder versions of the stages which require 3000 rupees per stage, if you can make it through these stages you will unlock the gold keys. Now you have the gold keys you can play through once more, this time you need to collect 5000 rupees a level and there is 4 boss battles on Vaati's stage instead of one. Each time you play through the game you get a different ending so if you want to see all of them you will need to play the game to completion at least 3 times.StoryThe game takes place many years after the events at the end of Minish Cap and many years before Four Swords Adventures. You are told a legend of a young boy who managed to defeat a powerful magic wizard called Vaati through the use of a magical blade referred to by the villagers as the Four Sword. Legend has it that when the boy defeated Vaati he trapped his soul within the sword, Zelda was assigned the task of guarding this sword. Villagers would ask how a boy could beat such a mighty villain and they would tell tales that the blade could create four duplicate copies of the user. When there is strange happenings and disturbances at the shrine, Zelda calls on Link to help her investigate these peculiar happenings. Zelda warns Link not to touch the blade but as she does this Vaati breaks free from his prison, steals the princess away to make her his bride and knocks Link unconscious. When Link awakens he is greeted by three fairies who instruct him to draw the blade and split in to four, they inform him that to gain access to Vaati's palace Link must collect rupees scattered across Hyrule to prove his courage to the great fairies, if he can do this they will grant him keys to the palace. Once Link manages to gain access to the palace he will do battle with Vaati and once again seal him within the sword, after he has rescued Princess Zelda he will return the sword back to the sanctuary and become his original self again.DSiWare ReleaseDuring Nintendo's E3 2011 press conference they revealed that in honor of Zelda's 25th anniversary the Four Swords game that was apart of A Link to the Past's GBA re-release would be available for download, for free, on DSiWare for Fall 2011. The game was reworked to include a singleplayer mode including new enemies, maps, and puzzles. The game was released on September 29, 2011.Cheat: Change color of Agahnims skin/clothesDuring the Light World fight with Agahnim, he turns into a shadow, and moves around like that. If you bring up the map exactly when he is turning from shadow to real form, his colors will be really distorted, or he will look transparent, just like the 2 fake ones during the second fight. If you keep doing it, his colors will keep changing.Cheat: Change color of Agahnims skin/clothesOn any part of the Light World Death Mountain that is on top of the mountain (level with the Tower of Hera, or Mountain Tower) freeze one of the tekktites (those blue or red spidery jumping things) with the ice rod (the Ether Medallion will just kill it) and pick it up using the power glove. not jump off the edge of the mountain that leads to the ground level. The tekktie will suddenly disappear and when you land on the ground you will be holding thin air and you will walk at normal speed with nothing weighing you down. The only problem is, you can't use any items, including your sword, shield or pegasus boots, and you cant throw away the air that you're holding. The only way you can stop this is by entering a cave or by getting hurt. you can also pick up a green stone and do the same thing, but I can't guarantee it will work. Sometimes you may have to repeat the trick several times in order for the item you're holding to disappear. You can also do this in the Dark World Death Mountain where you enter the portal near Spectacle Rock. Pick up a flower, and jump off the cliff. In the Dark World it doesn't work that much, but if you try again it will work.Cheat: Change color of Agahnims skin/clothesIt is indeed possible to swim anywhere in Hyrule. Call the flute bird and go to warp point 4 (your house). Go down one screen and kill all the monsters. Face the pool of water to your left, and call the flute again. Immidiately pegasus boot into the water. After you automatically stop at the water's edge, the flute bird will pick you up. Cancel the flight and when it sets you down you will still be on land --- but swimming! You can freely visit anywhere in Hyrule, but if you get injured or jump off a ledge you lose this ability. You also cannot access any items. Have fun!Cheat: Change color of Agahnims skin/clothesIn most areas of the game this glitch is possible. It allows Link to walk through walls, but in some areas the game, will glitch, and Link will be "frozen", or, unable to move in any direction at all. All you need are the Pegasus Boots and the Magic Mirror. One example is in the East Palace. Once you enter, pick up the pot and throw it. Then step on the switch. The door in front of Link should open. Go through the door, step on the switch, and dash threw the enemies through the next door. Then attempt to jump off the ledge to the left. But as Link's jumping off, before he's in mid-air and as soon as he makes the "hup" sound when leaping off, use the Magic Mirror to make Link appear back at the dungeon's entrance. Then repeat the first two steps untill you're back in the room with the ledge. If you've done the glitch correctly so far, when you dash into the statue on the right, Link should turn invisible when he lands back on the ground. This make take a few tries. NOTE: When Link attempts to walk out of the walls, he will jump back on to normal ground again and the glitch will have to be redone.Cheat: Change color of Agahnims skin/clothesCall up the Flute Duck and fly to point 7 on the map, which is the light world watergate. go up one screen to the place where the water portal is. now go up to the top right corner of the screen in the shallow water. call the flute duck again but this time before it comes aim a correctly timed pegasus charge at your left side. if you time it right, the duck will pick you up when your sword is sticking out while you're dashing. When you enter the map screen, press B to cancel and the duck will put you back down on the ground. Here you will start walking funny and when you touch a solid surface, you will bounce off of it. now go up to the right-most green totem statue so you're facing up. walk into it and bounce off into the deep water. (if you just go directly into the water the trick won't work) Swim towards the water portal and get transported to that place east of the graveyard. If done correctly, you should be standing on the water instead of swimming. Here you can walk around any screen you like and still be walking, but do NOT jump onto one of those green platforms or the trick will stop immediately. And also, it is okay to use the Pegasus Boots, but if you crash into something, you will start swimming again. and if you call up the Flute Duck and press B to cancel the map selection, you'll be swimming.Cheat: Unlock the level Palace of the Four Swords in Single Player mode.In order to unlock this level, you must beat both A Link to the Past and The Four Swords. Then get 20 Rupees, and go into the hole in the Pyramid of Power. Give the creature 20 Rupees, and he will dissapear, allowing you to pass. Beat this level to get a neat secret ending.Cheat: Unlock the level Palace of the Four Swords in Single Player mode.Unlockables using Four Swords.Cheat: Different Statues in Links houseAfter you get all the statues from completing the riddles go into your house and select the magic powder. Sprinkle it on the statues and they will sparkle. Sprinkle magic powder on them again to get them in color. Sprinkle them one final time to get Bunny Link, skinless chicken, and Zelda as an old lady.Cheat: Different Statues in Links houseIn the light world, go to where you recieved the flute. Go down one screen. To the right where there are two trees. Stand next to the top tree and use the Ether medalion. Walk away from the tree and ram into it with Pegasus Boots and a head like Blind in her human-ish form will fall down and explode as if it were a bomb.Cheat: Different Statues in Links houseIn the Light World, go south of Link's house into the swamp. There you will find a blue rabbit jumping up and down in the grass. When it jumps up, cut up the grass below it, then when it comes down, go over to it and touch it. It will give a random item, such as 1 to 300 rupees, or a fairy. This can only be done before you reach the Dark World for the first time.Cheat: Different Statues in Links houseGo to the Treasure chest shop in the dark world in the Village of Outcasts.  In the very back of the house, a picture of mario is hanging on the wall.Cheat: Different Statues in Links houseThe Chickens found in Kakariko Village and other areas have a vendetta against you; that is, of course, if you attack them. Hit a chicken enough with your various weapons, whether it be sword, arrow, bomb, whatever, and the chickens will come from all directions to peck you! Cheat: Easy MoneyAfter you've gotten the Power gloves go to the desert area in the game. Once there find the man thats sitting next to his sign. Go a little bit south and to the left where you should find two large rocks. Lift up the rock below the top one and a secret area will be opened. Once inside you'll notice a thief and 10 different pots that each hold a blue rupee, break open each pot and take all the money. You'll be able to do this as much as you please because the blue rupees come back every time you leave and reenter the area. It should only take a few minutes to get the maximum amount of rupees.Cheat: Easy MoneyOnce you've gotten the super bomb and already blew up the wall blocking the dark worlds fairy go inside and make sure you have at least one empty bottle with you. Go up to the Mysterious pond and it will ask you to throw something in. Scroll through your items until you come across an empty bottle, then throw it in the water. The Fairy will come out and ask you if you droped it. Answer yes and the fairy will say she likes such an honest person and will fill your bottle with green potion. You can do this as many times as you want.Cheat: Easy MoneyAfter you get the Zora flippers, find the big waterfall in the light world. It should be near the area where you got the flippers. Once you see the waterfall walk right into it and you'll be able to go inside of it. Once your inside you'll see a pond and it will ask you to throw something in. Choose to throw your small shield in and a fairy will ask if it is yours. Answer "YES" and she'll give you a red shield.    Cheat: Easy MoneyGo to the cave with the Ice Rod, and go into the non-secret entrance, not the one leading to the Ice Rod. Dash into the statue at the end of the passage, and a Golden Bee will pop out. Catch it, and take it to the guy who refuses to sell you the Golden Bees. He will say that they are not as rare as he thought they were and will begin selling Golden Bees.Cheat: Easy MoneyObtain ten medals in the Four Swords multiplayer mode, and you can start a riddle quest with the Lumberjack in Link to the Past. Complete the Riddle Quest to obtain the Hurricane Blade special move.Cheat: Easy MoneyWhen you are in the light world, go to the dungeon where you get the Ice Rod. To the left, you will see a little fish flopping around. If you catch it with the right button, you can go up one screen and throw it into the water. It will thank you with 20 ruppees.</plot>
	<releasedate>2/12/2002</releasedate>
	<genre>RPG, Action</genre>
	<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
	<nplayers>1-4 Sim</nplayers>
	<rating>8.9</rating>
	<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
	<VideoURL>vBUv85g3o84</VideoURL>
	<thegamesdb_id>8705</thegamesdb_id>
	<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/561559-the-legend-of-zelda-a-link-to-the-past</gamefaqs_url>
	<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/the-legend-of-zelda-a-link-to-the-past-four-swords/3030-35064/</giantbomb_url>
	<boxart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/front/8705-2.jpg</boxart1>
	<boxback1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/boxart/back/8705-1.jpg</boxback1>
	<snapshot1>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112517/1782058-boss_fight.jpg</snapshot1>
	<snapshot2>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112517/1782055-gfs_53585_2_9.jpg</snapshot2>
	<snapshot3>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112517/1782054-gfs_53585_2_7.jpg</snapshot3>
	<snapshot4>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112517/1782053-gfs_53585_2_6.jpg</snapshot4>
	<snapshot5>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112517/1782052-gfs_23204_3_3.jpg</snapshot5>
	<snapshot6>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112517/1782051-gfs_23204_3_2.jpg</snapshot6>
	<snapshot7>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112517/1782050-gfs_23204_3_1.jpg</snapshot7>
	<snapshot8>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112517/1782049-gfs_23204_2_55.jpg</snapshot8>
	<snapshot9>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112517/1782048-gfs_23204_2_54.jpg</snapshot9>
	<snapshot10>http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/11/112517/1782047-gfs_23204_2_29.jpg</snapshot10>
	<fanart1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8705-1.jpg</fanart1>
	<fanart2>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8705-2.jpg</fanart2>
	<fanart3>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8705-3.jpg</fanart3>
	<fanart4>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8705-4.jpg</fanart4>
	<fanart5>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8705-5.jpg</fanart5>
	<fanart6>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/fanart/8705-6.jpg</fanart6>
	<clearlogo1>https://cdn.thegamesdb.net/images/original/clearlogo/8705.png</clearlogo1>
</game>