<Game>
<Name>Pokemon - Emerald Version (USA, Europe)</Name>
				<plot>Pok?mon Emerald is the fifth Pok?mon game of the advanced generation, after its predecessors Ruby, Sapphire, FireRed, and LeafGreen. It takes place in the world of Hoenn but can also connect with Kanto-based games FireRed and LeafGreen as well. Like Pikachu and Suicune were for Yellow and Crystal respectively, Rayquaza plays a vital role in this game along with the other Legendaries, Groudon and Kyogre. Though similar to the original storyline that occurs in Hoenn, Emerald offers more changes than Yellow and Crystal.In terms of gameplay, there have been several alterations to the game:Legendaries- Ability to catch Rayquaza before the Elite Four, as well as both Groudon and Kyogre after it.- Changes to catching the Regis.- Ability to catch either one of Latios or Latias.Graphics- New outfits for the characters.- New Pok?mon animations.Features:- Ability to enter the Safari Zone Extension, where you can catch Johto (the world of Pok?mon Gold, Silver and Crystal) Pok?mon like Houndour and Miltank.- The Battle Frontier, an island full of different battle stadiums.- Ability to get both of the Claw and Root fossils.These are of the changes you might notice at first while playing Pok?mon Emerald. However, there are lots of other improvements apart from the new storyline that separates this game from its predecessors.http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/pokmon-emeraldCheat: Level Up Unhatched PokemonTo do this glitch, you must first execute the Pomeg Berry Glitch, which is done by using a Pomeg Berry on a Pokemon with 1 or 2 HP so that its HP loops to 65,535 (displayed as ?35 in-game). Do so, however, with only one Pokemon and an Egg in the party, with the Egg in the top-leftmost slot of the party in the Pokemon menu. After executing the glitch, you will now be able to enter battles and use the Pokemon Egg as if it were a normal Pokemon. It will function as a normal Pokemon - you can view the stats it will have upon hatching, it can level-up by beating Pokemon, it can learn new moves, it can even evolve. This means that you can alter the Pokemon inside the Egg in otherwise-illegitimate ways. For example. Pikachu cannot normally know Thunder when hatching from an Egg at Level 5; through this glitch, Pikachu can. Similarly, you can hatch Eggs with fully-evolved Pokemon such as Typhlosion, Meganium, and so on, inside.Cheat: Level Up Unhatched PokemonFor this glitch to work properly, you must have a Pomeg Berry and a Pokemon who has not had their HP lowered as much as possible already through Pomeg Berries. (If the latter is the case, the use of HP Ups on the Pokemon will suffice.) Get the Pokemon to a severely low level of HP (1 or 2 HP). Once you do so, in the field, use the Pomeg Berry on the Pokemon. This will in turn cause the data in their HP to cycle back to the top of the counter, giving the affected Pokemon 65,535 HP - over 90 times the otherwise possible maximum in the game.Cheat: Altering CaveYou can go to Altering Cave after you beat the Elite Four. It is located on Route 103. Cheat: Altering CaveOnce you beat the game, you can go to the Battle Frontier.Cheat: Altering CaveTell the Berry Master's Wife certain phrases to receive the following berries. You can only tell her one of these each day.Cheat: Altering CaveAfter you defeated the Elite Four, go to the Upgraded Safari Zone. In the Safari, you can catch some GSC Pokemon such as Houndour, Aipom, Stantler, Mareep, Miltank, and more GSC Pokemon. This Unlockable works only in Pokemon Emerald.Cheat: Altering CaveTo get the old rod, go to dewford town and talk to the fisherman near the gym. He will give you a old rod. To get good rod, talk to the fisherman on route 118, east of  mauville city. You must need surf to reach him. Talk to him and you will get good rod.To get super rod, go to mossdeep city and go north of the space center and go into the house. The man inside will give you super rod.Cheat: Altering CaveOn Route 113, to the right of Fallobour Town, is house in which a man will make you items if you bring him ash.  To collect ash, walk through the ash covered grass.  Then bring it to the glass item maker.Cheat: Altering CaveTalk to Scott in his house in the Battle Frontier, he'll give you certain decorations/berries depending on your accomplishments in the Battle Frontier. Cheat: Altering CaveThere are certain pokemon that can only be caught when you trigger certain events, like castform.Cheat: Altering CaveAs you accomplish more along your journey, your Trainer Card will change colors and rise in rank, depending on completing certain tasks. After completing one task, it will rise in one rank, but there are some tasks that cannot be completed until beating the Elite Four. You must do these tasks:Cheat: Altering Cave-Become Pokemon league Champion-Complete the Hoenn Pokedex-Collect all the gold symbols in the Battle Frontier-Win one ribbon in all five of the Master Rank Pokemon Contests.Cheat: Altering CaveTo unlock Trainer Hill, you must beat the Elite Four.       Cheat: Getting Latias Or LatiosAfter you defeat the Elite Four, go to your house and watch the television downstairs. After you watch it, your mom will ask you what color the Pokemon is. If you say Red, you will find Latias. If you say Blue, it will be Latios.Cheat: Getting Latias Or LatiosTo get the other Lati (Latios or Latias), Mix Records with a Pokemon Ruby/Sapphire game that used the Eon Ticket.  You can then get to a hidden island via the SS Tidal where you can find the Lati you didn't choose.Cheat: Getting Latias Or LatiosEvery time you encounter a pokemon you have a 1/8192 chance of the pokemon being a different color, this is called a shiny pokemonCheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.After beating the Elite Four, a new part of Meteor Falls opens up. It is in the northwestern corner where you found Iron Tail. A new cave was made and you'll find Steven in it. His Pokemon are in the high 70's.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.If you have a Pokemon with Compound eyes 1st in your Party it will drw Wild Pokemon that has held Items more often.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.Have a Pokemon use CUT to remove grass where wild Pokemon live.  It will remove the chance of encountering wild Pokemon. The grass will regrow once you leave the area or enter a building.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.If you have  a Pokemon with Cute Charm 1st in your Party it will more likely draw Wild Pokemon with the opposite gender of the Pokemon with Cute Charm.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.Simply put a pokemon with the ability Flame Body or Magma Armor on your team to cut the amount of steps needed to hatch an egg in half.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.In one of the treehouses in Fortree City is a man with a Wingull. Talk to the Wingull, and it will fly off out of the treehouse.  When you get to Mossdeep City, you will see a person with a Wingull.  Talk to it and it will fly off as well.  Then go back to Fortree City and into the treehouse where you talked to the first Wingull.  Talk to the man next to the Wingull, and he will give you the Mental Herb, and item which is a hold item that prevents attraction on the Pokemon that is holding it.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.If you have a Pokemon with Hustle 1st in your Party it will draw Wild Pokemon that has a Higher Level than the Pokemon that has Hustle.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.To do this you need an Everstone.  To get one, search in Granite Cave for a lone rock on top of a plateau.  Once you get an Everstone, let the a Ditto or a female Pokemon that you are breeding hold on to it.   Once you receive and hatch the eggs, the offspring will have a 50% chance of inheriting the Nature from the Pokemon holding the Everstone. Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.If you put a Pokemon that has intimidate or Keen Eye 1st in your party the chances of wild Pokemon encounter is reduced by 10%.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.If you have a poke'mon with lightningrod as an ability, you will get calls from registered trainers more often.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.If you have a pokemon with the Magnet Pull ability in front of your party, it increases the chances of finding wild steel-type Pokemon. This is very useful for finding rare steel types, such as Mawile.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.Mirage Island is an invisble Island located on Route 130.  Most of the time it will be invisible but on rare cases, the island will be visible.  To find out if the island is there or not, go to Pacifidlog Town and talk to the old man in the bottom right house looking out the window.  He will tell you wheter the island is there or not.   The cause is unknown so a bit of luck is needed to find it.  On the island you will find the rare Leichi Berry that powers up your Pokemon's attack in battle when it gets weak.  In the grass, you will only find Wild Wynauts.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.To unlock mystery gift, go to a pokemon mart and press A on the piece of paper on the counter.  Then insert the words LINK TOGETHER WITH ALL. Press select to easily find the words.  After this the store lady will talk to you and tell you that mystery gift is now unlocked.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.If you have a pokemon with the Static ability in the front of your party, it increases the chance of finding a wild electric type pokemon.  This is EXTREMELY useful for finding rare electric types, like Pikachu in the Safari Zone.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.If a poke'mon in your party has suction cups/sticky hold as an ability, then you will have an easier time fishing for wild poke'mon.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.The Pokemon ability Swarm has 2 effects. It raises Bug-type attacks by 150% when the user is weak, and, new to Emerald, it makes pokemon cry in the background more often. For example, in caves outside of battle, you will hear a Pokemon screech more often.Cheat: Battle Steven, the former champion.If you have a poke'mon with synchronize as an ability, you will encounter more poke'mon with the same nature as the poke'mon with sychronize. Note that the poke'mon with this ability must be in the front of your party.</plot>
				<releasedate>20/1/2005</releasedate>
				<genre>RPG</genre>
				<Developer>Nintendo</Developer>
				<nplayers>1-4 Alt</nplayers>
				<rating>3.9</rating>
				<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
				<VideoURL>bvk_qwpu2v8</VideoURL>
				<thegamesdb_id>2365</thegamesdb_id>
				<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/921905-pokemon-emerald-version</gamefaqs_url>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/pokmon-emerald-version</mobygames_url>
				
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2365-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2365-1.jpg</boxback1>
				<boxart3>http://i.imgur.com/x0WNbFZ.png</boxart3>
				<boxart4>http://i.imgur.com/XZEvFaD.png</boxart4>
				<boxart5>http://i.imgur.com/eVVI04S.png</boxart5>
				<boxart6>http://i.imgur.com/cTnvNRo.png</boxart6>
<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/87488-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/111082-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/179223-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/202440-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
				<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/109700-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/697223-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-beginning.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/109701-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-choosing.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/109702-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-healing.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/109703-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pokemon.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463796-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pokedex.jpg</snapshot6>
				<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463797-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pokemon.jpg</snapshot7>
				<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463793-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-bag-showing.jpg</snapshot8>
				<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463795-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-pokemon.jpg</snapshot9>
				<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/463794-pokemon-emerald-version-game-boy-advance-screenshot-trainer.jpg</snapshot10>
				<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2365-1.jpg</fanart1>
				<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2365-2.jpg</fanart2>
				<fanart3>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2365-3.jpg</fanart3>
				<fanart4>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2365-4.jpg</fanart4>
				<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/y4gHWQ1.png</banner1>
				<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2365.png</clearlogo1>
<Notes>Pokémon Emerald Version takes Trainers back to the land of Hoenn for an expanded adventure, this time against both Team Magma and Team Aqua! Pokémon Emerald also features an even more exciting storyline featuring the Legendary Rayquaza, and the chance to catch more Legendary Pokémon such as both Latios and Latias! Around the region you'll notice exciting locales, especially the Battle Frontier. The Battle Frontier is basically an amusement park for Trainers, with a variety of challenges in a number of arenas headed by the always-intimidating Frontier Brains, some of the most formidable Trainers you've ever faced.</Notes>
<banner2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/5c0bb3f2-9f8f-4307-87de-269ee5e44d5a.jpg<banner2>
<boxart11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/76544f7b-a881-4a4a-83ec-721b9bdef3c1.jpg<boxart11>
<boxart12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/613fb154-9850-4d58-9885-eab2d13153b5.jpg<boxart12>
<boxart13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/6253e499-3b1e-4e02-b959-326096991c95.jpg<boxart13>
<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/698a92dd-bde4-42b2-bf58-2ba0eaa7be63.png<clearlogo2>
<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/1b28f2db-9862-4c5e-b76e-6a2506b78267.jpg<snapshot11>
<snapshot12>http://images.launchbox-app.com/78239400-9c39-4206-938b-5890198546ed.jpg<snapshot12>
<snapshot13>http://images.launchbox-app.com/c12e9a60-9af9-4a01-b47f-e556b5d5e283.png<snapshot13>
<snapshot14>http://images.launchbox-app.com/21bf249e-7516-4ccb-8c2c-35a273b1888c.png<snapshot14>
<Publisher>Nintendo</Publisher>
</game>
