<Game>
<Name>Mega Man Zero 3 (Europe)</Name>
				<plot>In the third installment of Capcom's Mega Man Zero series, you, unsurprisingly, play as Zero. Continuing where the Mega Man Zero 2 left off, you have to find and neutralize the recently escaped "Dark Elf," before it's able to brainwash the Resistance for the purpose of conquering Neo Arcadia. In addition to the old Cyber Elf system, this game also contains a new "chip" system, where Zero can gain new abilities by finding chips and installing chip in himself. But they didn't decide to abandon the Cyber Elves in this game by giving them nothing new. No, in order to extend the life of the Cyber Elves, they added the new concept of "Cyber Space" to levels, where you enter a door to Cyber Space and are allowed to use each Cyber Elf as much as you please without them dying. However, there aren't too many "Secret Disks" (items that can contain anything from profiles of characters to Cyber Elves to new chips) in Cyber Space, so it's better to spend more time in the normal level.Cheat: Mini-gamesYou can unlock four Minigames alternatively with this accessory, given if you have these particular Battle Chips.Cheat: Change Enemies In CyberworldFirst of all, get a MegaMan Battle Network 4 Red Sun or Blue Moon. You will need two GBA/SP, and a GBA link cable. Go to Ciel's room in the place you go to after killing Omega. Press up in front of the computer. Go to Transmission. In Red Sun/Blue Moon, go to Comm. Go to trade chips, and trade any chip into Zero 3. In Red Sun/Blue Moon, you will get a secret chip. In Zero 3, all Cyberworld enemies will be changed.Cheat: Change Enemies In CyberworldOn the second last level, go into the first hyperspace portal. Next, while you are riding the platforms, you should find a door. It leads you to 2 disks and a portal.When you go into the portal, you will fight phantom from Megaman Zero 1.</plot>
				<releasedate>4/10/2004</releasedate>
				<genre>Action</genre>
				<Developer>Capcom Entertainment, Inc.</Developer>
				<nplayers>1</nplayers>
				<rating>4.0</rating>
				<ESRB>E - Everyone</ESRB>
				<VideoURL>O7aeiPJtkBU</VideoURL>
				<thegamesdb_id>2343</thegamesdb_id>
				<gamefaqs_url>http://www.gamefaqs.com/gba/920055-mega-man-zero-3</gamefaqs_url>
				<mobygames_url>http://www.mobygames.com/game/gameboy-advance/mega-man-zero-3</mobygames_url>
				<giantbomb_url>http://www.giantbomb.com/mega-man-zero-3/3030-9497/</giantbomb_url>
				
				<boxart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/front/2343-1.jpg</boxart1>
<boxback1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/boxart/original/back/2343-1.jpg</boxback1>
<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/210400-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
<media>http://www.mobygames.com/images/covers/l/189157-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-media.jpg</media>
				<snapshot1>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86744-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-title-screen.jpg</snapshot1>
				<snapshot2>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86745-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-main-menu.jpg</snapshot2>
				<snapshot3>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86746-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-prologue.jpg</snapshot3>
				<snapshot4>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86747-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-walking-in-the.jpg</snapshot4>
				<snapshot5>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86748-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-flashback.jpg</snapshot5>
				<snapshot6>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86749-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-look-at-the-sword.jpg</snapshot6>
				<snapshot7>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86750-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-anime-images-are.jpg</snapshot7>
				<snapshot8>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86751-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-chip-thing.jpg</snapshot8>
				<snapshot9>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86752-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-the-dark-elf.jpg</snapshot9>
				<snapshot10>http://www.mobygames.com/images/shots/l/86753-mega-man-zero-3-game-boy-advance-screenshot-warning-shows-up.jpg</snapshot10>
				<fanart1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2343-1.jpg</fanart1>
				<fanart2>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/fanart/original/2343-2.jpg</fanart2>
				<banner1>http://i.imgur.com/pHnBObz.png</banner1>
				<clearlogo1>http://thegamesdb.net/banners/clearlogo/2343.png</clearlogo1>
<Notes>It's the third chapter in the Mega Man Zero action adventure series for the Game Boy Advance. Featuring a new customization system, you can now equip Zero, with a combination of chips that will affect both his attributes and abilities, allowing you to adapt him to different challenges. Among his other new skills, Zero will now have weapon called the recoil rod. Now be jumps at double his normal height. These new skills will allow our hero to march into Arcadia to defeat the evil Omega single-handedly ... Or will they?</Notes>
<VideoURL2>O7aeiPJtkBU</VideoURL2>
<boxart5>http://images.launchbox-app.com/233969bf-a7d6-4b76-a238-6e5965aeeefc.png<boxart5>
<clearlogo2>http://images.launchbox-app.com/0db1bfc0-f8d7-4989-bbf5-d4ac3f584d57.png<clearlogo2>
<snapshot11>http://images.launchbox-app.com/b6d2e667-adbd-4152-bcc5-e6bad351cf7c.png<snapshot11>
<Publisher>Capcom</Publisher>
</game>
